Muncește din greu, dragul meu
candidat pentru Mesia...
Poți face orice dacă încerci.
Eu te voi susține din umbră!
Îngerii sunt ființe răbdătoare.
Eu sunt îngerul stăruinței, Uriel.
Stăruință
M-am camuflat în umbre ca să-mi sprijin candidatul pentru Mesia,
și să nu fiu descoperită de cei loiali Diavolului.
While I lie in the Messiah Candidate's shadow,
I patiently endure even my need to relieve myself,
I disappear into the shadows so others will not see me...
What's that?
Pretend you don't see her, pretend you don't see her...
Be patient...
Please strive hard at work!
Episodul 2
Te susțin din umbră
The Seven Heavenly Virtues!
O Candidate for Messiah,
you will soon be at the station...
You must be patient a little while longer!
Good luck at work today, O Candidate for Messiah.
I have warmed your change of clothes.
Just... ten more minutes until your lunch break.
Be patient!
...the hell is this? A letter on an arrow?
I have fallen in love with you,
O Candidate for Messiah.
However, I must humbly report that your exhaustion
is beginning to show upon your face.
"Humbly report"?
Why is she following me around in the first place?
I can't focus on my work.
Perhaps my support has been lacking,
as for the last few days, the Messiah Candidate's
work performance has plummeted rapidly...
This is a fierce battle!
But I no longer have any time to waste!
If I am to train him to be a wonderful Messiah,
I must offer him even more support from the shadows!
Today's a really important day for work.
How long's she gonna follow me...?
I am extremely delighted to receive your praise.
I am Uriel, the Angel who patiently endures.
In order to support the Messiah Candidate
to raise his work performance,
I must always hide myself so none discover my existence
and patiently endure through the days.
Even if I must squeeze between walls...
Hot...!
I must be patient...
If I say something, I will interrupt his dinner...
So? What's going on?
Is that the reason your performance's
done a nosedive?
N-No, she's got nothing to do with it...
I've been seen...
But the Messiah Candidate protected me...
I must endure my urge to urinate
so as to not interrupt his work day...
I must endure... must endure...
E-Endure...
Endure...
I will endure!
Don't worry about it.
But... because I didn't know
where the restroom was, you...
Well, I can't just leave you alone.
I am seriously reflecting upon my actions!
Be it drawn and quartering, or parading me
through town to the gallows,
you may do as you wish with me!
Whoa, hey...
In the end, the Messiah Candidate was fired...
Looking for a new job ain't easy.
Wait...
What're you doing?
You're home so early!
I was just going to hide myself...!
With that sheet? And why are you here anyway?
W-Well...
I was going to support your job search
from the shadows...
In any case, I hope...
...you will treat me kindly from now on!