Handler One to Undertaker:
Enemy interception forces detected at grid point 30 and 504.
Enemy forces are battalion-sized units of tank and close combat types.
All units, advance and eliminate the threat.
Although, against these odds,
none of you will make it out of this alive!
Hurry the hell up!
Go on, pigs!
Fight to the death, you damned Eighty-Six!
What's this?
Hey, stop it!
Stop it! Stay away!
Shut up! Shut the fuck up!
May 13th, Stellar Year 2148
As you can see, it's another beautiful day across all 85 Sectors of the Republic!
Why not go out with your friends
and family today?
The weather is expected to worsen tomorrow,
however you won't need an umbrella.
Now then, enjoy your weekend everyone!
Next up, an update on the war from the San Magnolia Military HQ!
A group of mechanized drones known as Legion
belonging to the former Giadian Empire invaded the 17th Combat Ward
and sustained heavy losses after engaging with our own unmanned combat units,
the Juggernauts, and were forced to withdraw.
Our forces suffered minimal losses with no human injuries or deaths!
Defending the nation with our advanced and ethical drones,
has resulted in zero Republic casualties!
The day when the righteousness of our nation smashes the evil remnants
of the wicked Empire is not far off!
All hail the Republic of San Magnolia!
Glory to the five-colored flag!
San Magnolia Military HQ
Morning, Major!
Those pigs sure were crying
their heads off yesterday.
It was a pretty crazy fight.
I bet at least fifty of them died.
Not that anyone was on board anyway.
Hey, everybody!
The doll-loving princess is glaring at us!
Why the angry look, Major Milizé?
It's just a few busted-up drones!
Listen, you—
Morning.
Morning, Annette.
You're up early. You usually sleep in.
I pulled an all-nighter working last night.
Unlike those morons.
Forget about them!
This isn't the battlefield.
We're inside the Gran Mur.
Plus the enemy will shut down in two years anyway.
If anything, you're the weirdo taking it so seriously for the Republic's sake.
I just think this country's conscience has—
Vladilena Milizé
Yeah, yeah.
I'm not awake enough
to listen to one of your speeches.
What's that Processor's problem?
He's just a part!
No kidding!
We're from the 1st Sector. Why do we have to put up with those bitching pigs from the 86th Sector?
Why do you care so much about the drones, Lena?
They're not drones.
I'll put it this way, then.
Why do you care so much about the Eighty-Six?
The battlefield calls, princess.
Initiate ID confirmation.
Major Vladilena Milizé.
Eastern Theater Forces, 9th Combat Ward.
3rd Defense Squadron
Command and Control Officer.
Para-RAID, activate.
Synchronization target: Pleiades Processors.
Synchronization complete.
Handler One to Pleiades:
Pleasure to work with you today.
Pleiades to Handler One:
Sychronization successful.
Be careful.
The enemy is entering firing range.
Proceed with caution—
As always, such kind formalities for us subhuman Eighty-Six.
How sweet, Miss human.
You're reassigning me to a different unit,
General Karlstahl?
Yes.
The truth is, the previous Handler transferred out of the unit.
As such, we need to find an immediate replacement.
If the unit isn't being withdrawn while we find a replacement,
does that mean it's defending an important base?
Yes, it's the Eastern Theater's
1st Combat Ward, 1st Defense Squadron.
Officially called Spearhead Squadron.
It's comprised of veterans
from all across the Eastern Theater.
You could consider them an elite unit.
But...
I've just been commissioned as a Major,
I don't have the experience.
And you're also the youngest person ever
to make it to the post of major.
If you try to be too humble,
you'll make unnecessary enemies, Lena.
I'm sorry, Uncle Jérôme.
I'm sure Václav would be proud
if he could see his daughter, too.
How is Margareta?
The same as ever.
She's pestering me to get married.
Sounds like her.
To be frank, we can't find anyone else who'll accept the position.
Aren't they an elite unit?
Wouldn't it be an honor for a
Republic soldier to command them?
Correct, but there are some strings attached.
The unit leader, Personal Name: Undertaker.
S
He's got a bit of a reputation.
A reputation?
S
They call him the Reaper.
He has a tendency to destroy his Handlers.
The Processor destroys the Handler?
Not the other way around?
Correct.
It's not just a ghost story?
I don't have time in my schedule
to share ghost stories with my subordinates.
Almost all Handlers assigned to Undertaker have either retired or transferred.
Some even committed suicide.
I know it's hard to believe,
but they claim to be haunted by the "voices of the dead."
The dead?
You're free to refuse, Lena.
You work too hard, anyway.
A Handler merely needs to monitor their unit,
and let the local commander take control—
I'll do it.
I'll do my utmost as the Command and Control Officer of Spearhead Squadron.
You simply need to do the bare minimum.
And you should keep your interactions with them to a minimum.
It's a commander's duty to know its personnel.
While I'm lecturing you,
let me add one more thing.
Stop putting the number of casualties in your reports.
Officially, there are no humans on the battlefield.
So there are no casualties.
That doesn't mean we can ignore them.
What we're doing is unforgivable.
Lena.
You really are just like Václav.
All right.
I appoint you, Vladilena Milizé as the
Command and Control Officer,
the Handler of the 1st Combat Ward's
1st Defense Squadron.
Have the paperwork done by the time you get there.
Best of luck to you.
I'll do my best until my final mission.
So you accepted it?
Republic of San Magnolia Military Research Wing
Sheesh...
You're such a weirdo.
It's an honor to command such an elite unit.
Plus it's worth doing.
And all that stuff about destroying Handlers are lies, right?
I bet they were slacking and wanted an easy excuse.
It's true that some committed suicide.
One of Spearhead's Handlers went crazy
and blew his head off with a shotgun.
All right, checkup's done. No problems, as usual.
Thanks for your cooperation.
But why suicide?
Naturally, we were requested to investigate.
They thought it might be a problem with the Para-RAID.
Transfers aren't a big deal,
but we can't ignore suicides.
What did you find?
Who knows.
You don't know?
The Handler was dead.
How we were supposed to investigate it?
You're the leader of the development team.
Is that really okay?
We did our jobs.
There was nothing wrong
with the RAID Device. End of story.
We told them that if they wanted to know more,
they'd have to bring us Undertaker.
But those idiots in transport said,
"This flight has no seats open for pigs!"
Then you didn't talk to Undertaker?
We just read their report.
"No idea," they said.
We told them about the dead Handler,
and all they said was, "I see."
Well, they're Eighty-Six.
It's within the realm of possibility
that using a Para-RAID could lead to insanity.
It adds a lot of extra load on the brain
to share sensory data with another person.
And even now, we're only sharing the sense of hearing.
If you tried synchronizing vision as well,
your brain wouldn't hold up.
Too much load on the brain,
and you don't come back.
Using the Para-RAID means accepting those risks.
But your father was one of the pioneers
in this field of research.
All of the core principles were developed by someone else.
In truth, there's a lot I still don't understand.
Lena, you really should join us in R&D.
The military's just a jobs program right now.
When the Legion shuts down in two years,
"former military" isn't going to mean a thing on your résumé.
Thanks.
But we are at war right now.
Those Processors are crazy!
We don't know the long term effects of Para-RAIDs.
The Eighty-Six die quickly
so the long term doesn't matter.
But I don't want that for you.
Still, it's cowardly.
Right, right.
You really are weird.
I modified the settings.
Thanks.
Oh, Lena! I made chiffon cake.
Want some?
I'll pass for today.
See you later.
I used real eggs.
And real milk.
It's so good!
How's it feel to actually eat
the real thing for once?
It's wonderful!
But part of me wonders
if this is how it really tasted.
You forget when you eat only artificial stuff.
I've got cream puffs, too.
They don't taste like cheese
when they don't have cheese in them,
or look like they're about
to spit out black smoke, right?
Are you talking about the cream puffs
I made last time?
It'll be fine this time!
I gave some to a potential marriage partner yesterday,
and he cried tears of joy.
Sounds like you got a good match for once.
He must've really loved it.
Of course!
I also gave him a card with a lipstick kiss and the words "To My Beloved."
I dropped them off at the place where he's living with his mistress.
May 20th, Stellar Year 2148
What's wrong, Pleiades?
Please respond!
What's wrong?
Handler One to Pleiades!
Enough already.
He's dead!
Pull back! Evasive maneuvers!
Damn it!
Handler One to all members of the 3rd Squadron.
Enemy forces have begun their retreat.
The 4th Squadron will take over the patrol.
Return to base.
Roger.
Pleiades and the other six who died...
I'm so sorry about them.
Always...
Always with the kind words, Handler One.
Just so you're aware,
the 3rd Squadron will be assigned a new Handler.
Thank you for everything.
I'm going to be the Command
and Control Officer for Spearhead.
That's great news.
Eager to see you out, Handler One.
My utmost sympathies.
What does that mean—
Give the Reaper my regards.
May 22nd, Stellar Year 2148
Para-RAID, activate.
Synchronization target:
Spearhead Processors.
May 12th, Stellar Year 2148
Nice, man!
Guys start cleaning already—
Sounds like they're having a good time.
The same goes for them.
Wait! Wait up!
Eggs!
Welcome back.
Huh?
Hey, lend me a hand.
Coming.
And, done!
Thanks for all the hard work man!
It's "Thank you sir!"
Members of Spearhead, it's breakfast time!
Gather round!
Right, right.
Coming, coming.
Morning! Morning!
Morning.
Let's eat!
There's more omelets.
Seconds!
Calm down.
Can't you savor your food?
Is it good, Kuro?
Very.
Hey, didn't our Handler go crazy again?
The one in the battle yesterday.
He's done for.
Didn't you hear him?
"Stay away! Hey, stop!"
Cut it out, guys.
Those White Pigs are sure irredeemable.
Doesn't matter who it is,
it's always the same in the end.
Right?
But everyone made it back yesterday, right Shin?
Yeah, that's right.
Well, if we're going to die anyway,
we'd rather have our Reaper guide us.
What now?
Here.
May 22nd, Stellar Year 2148
Fuck, that hurts...
Damn it!
Damn it all!
I don't want to die.
Shin...
Our promise...
Don't forget...
Has Kujo moved on?
Yeah.
And your Brother's voice?
Not yet.
I see.
There's none left.
You suck.
I win!
U
129 days till I end my service!!
Fuckin' glory to the Spearhead Squadron!!
U
Handler One to all Spearhead units:
Greetings. I am your new
Command and Control officer.
A woman?
I've contacted you tonight to introduce myself.
Hello, Handler One.
This is the Captain of the Spearhead Squadron.
Personal Name: Undertaker.
We've received word of the handler change.
We look forward to working with you.
As do I.
Nice to meet you, Undertaker.
No matter how hard I wish nothing ever changes
aigan shitemo konganshitemo kawaranai yamou
No matter how hard I wish nothing ever changes
A flower blooms only to be crushed
aigan shitemo konganshitemo kawaranai yamou
fuminijirareru dake no hana
A flower blooms only to be crushed
No matter how hard I wish nothing ever changes
aigan shitemo konganshitemo kawaranai yamou
fuminijirareru dake no hana
No matter how hard I wish nothing ever changes
aigan shitemo konganshitemo kawaranai yamou
A flower blooms only to be crushed
fuminijirareru dake no hana
A flower blooms only to be crushed
fuminijirareru dake no hana
No matter what happens I'll never forget your voice
anata no koe wo wasure wa shinai darou
No matter what happens I'll never forget your voice
anata no koe wo wasure wa shinai darou
Swept up and scattered by the wind
kaze ni fukarete chirijiri ni natte
Swept up and scattered by the wind
I can't see the future in your reflectionless eyes
kaze ni fukarete chirijiri ni natte
sono konkontaru suishoutai ni wa utsuranai mirai mirai
I can't see the future in your reflectionless eyes
Swept up and scattered by the wind
kaze ni fukarete chirijiri ni natte
sono konkontaru suishoutai ni wa utsuranai mirai mirai
Swept up and scattered by the wind
kaze ni fukarete chirijiri ni natte
I can't see the future in your reflectionless eyes
sono konkontaru suishoutai ni wa utsuranai mirai mirai
shou
I can't see the future in your reflectionless eyes
sono konkontaru suishoutai ni wa utsuranai mirai mirai
No matter how hard I wish nothing ever changes
aigan shitemo konganshitemo kawaranai yamou
No matter how hard I wish nothing ever changes
A flower blooms only to be crushed
aigan shitemo konganshitemo kawaranai yamou
fuminijirareru dake no hana
A flower blooms only to be crushed
No matter how hard I wish nothing ever changes
aigan shitemo konganshitemo kawaranai yamou
fuminijirareru dake no hana
No matter how hard I wish nothing ever changes
aigan shitemo konganshitemo kawaranai yamou
A flower blooms only to be crushed
fuminijirareru dake no hana
fuminijirareru dake no hana
A flower blooms only to be crushed
Bystanding, revolting, willful ignorance
boukan shiteiru zouhan shiteiru minai furishiteiru
Bystanding, revolting, willful ignorance
That's you, that's the person I see
boukan shiteiru zouhan shiteiru minai furishiteiru
sonna anata wo boku wa miteiru
That's you, that's the person I see
Bystanding, revolting, willful ignorance
boukan shiteiru zouhan shiteiru minai furishiteiru
sonna anata wo boku wa miteiru
Bystanding, revolting, willful ignorance
boukan shiteiru zouhan shiteiru minai furishiteiru
That's you, that's the person I see
sonna anata wo boku wa miteiru
That's you, that's the person I see
Don't worry, ease up why don't you
sonna anata wo boku wa miteiru
anshinshinayo bokutachi minna itsudatte
Don't worry, ease up why don't you
That's you, that's the person I see
sonna anata wo boku wa miteiru
anshinshinayo bokutachi minna itsudatte
That's you, that's the person I see
sonna anata wo boku wa miteiru
Don't worry, ease up why don't you
anshinshinayo bokutachi minna itsudatte
an
shin
Don't worry, ease up why don't you
We're all guilty in the end
anshinshinayo bokutachi minna itsudatte
yarukoto wa onaji sa
We're all guilty in the end
Don't worry, ease up why don't you
anshinshinayo bokutachi minna itsudatte
yarukoto wa onaji sa
Don't worry, ease up why don't you
anshinshinayo bokutachi minna itsudatte
We're all guilty in the end
yarukoto wa onaji sa
We're all guilty in the end
yarukoto wa onaji sa
Spearhead.