I'm sorry about what happened to Kirschblüte.
No matter how hard I wish nothing ever changes
aigan shitemo konganshitemo kawaranai yamou
No matter how hard I wish nothing ever changes
A flower blooms only to be crushed
aigan shitemo konganshitemo kawaranai yamou
fuminijirareru dake no hana
A flower blooms only to be crushed
No matter how hard I wish nothing ever changes
aigan shitemo konganshitemo kawaranai yamou
fuminijirareru dake no hana
No matter how hard I wish nothing ever changes
aigan shitemo konganshitemo kawaranai yamou
A flower blooms only to be crushed
fuminijirareru dake no hana
A flower blooms only to be crushed
fuminijirareru dake no hana
No matter what happens I'll never forget your voice
anata no koe wo wasure wa shinai darou
No matter what happens I'll never forget your voice
anata no koe wo wasure wa shinai darou
Swept up and scattered by the wind
kaze ni fukarete chirijiri ni natte
Swept up and scattered by the wind
I can't see the future in your reflectionless eyes
kaze ni fukarete chirijiri ni natte
sono konkontaru suishoutai ni wa utsuranai mirai mirai
I can't see the future in your reflectionless eyes
Swept up and scattered by the wind
kaze ni fukarete chirijiri ni natte
sono konkontaru suishoutai ni wa utsuranai mirai mirai
Swept up and scattered by the wind
kaze ni fukarete chirijiri ni natte
I can't see the future in your reflectionless eyes
sono konkontaru suishoutai ni wa utsuranai mirai mirai
shou
I can't see the future in your reflectionless eyes
sono konkontaru suishoutai ni wa utsuranai mirai mirai
No matter how hard I wish nothing ever changes
aigan shitemo konganshitemo kawaranai yamou
No matter how hard I wish nothing ever changes
A flower blooms only to be crushed
aigan shitemo konganshitemo kawaranai yamou
fuminijirareru dake no hana
A flower blooms only to be crushed
No matter how hard I wish nothing ever changes
aigan shitemo konganshitemo kawaranai yamou
fuminijirareru dake no hana
No matter how hard I wish nothing ever changes
aigan shitemo konganshitemo kawaranai yamou
A flower blooms only to be crushed
fuminijirareru dake no hana
fuminijirareru dake no hana
A flower blooms only to be crushed
Bystanding, revolting, willful ignorance
boukan shiteiru zouhan shiteiru minai furishiteiru
Bystanding, revolting, willful ignorance
That's you, that's the person I see
boukan shiteiru zouhan shiteiru minai furishiteiru
sonna anata wo boku wa miteiru
That's you, that's the person I see
Bystanding, revolting, willful ignorance
boukan shiteiru zouhan shiteiru minai furishiteiru
sonna anata wo boku wa miteiru
Bystanding, revolting, willful ignorance
boukan shiteiru zouhan shiteiru minai furishiteiru
That's you, that's the person I see
sonna anata wo boku wa miteiru
That's you, that's the person I see
Don't worry, ease up why don't you
sonna anata wo boku wa miteiru
anshinshinayo bokutachi minna itsudatte
Don't worry, ease up why don't you
That's you, that's the person I see
sonna anata wo boku wa miteiru
anshinshinayo bokutachi minna itsudatte
That's you, that's the person I see
sonna anata wo boku wa miteiru
Don't worry, ease up why don't you
anshinshinayo bokutachi minna itsudatte
an
shin
Don't worry, ease up why don't you
We're all guilty in the end
anshinshinayo bokutachi minna itsudatte
yarukoto wa onaji sa
We're all guilty in the end
Don't worry, ease up why don't you
anshinshinayo bokutachi minna itsudatte
yarukoto wa onaji sa
Don't worry, ease up why don't you
anshinshinayo bokutachi minna itsudatte
We're all guilty in the end
yarukoto wa onaji sa
We're all guilty in the end
yarukoto wa onaji sa
I present to you! The "privileged pigs"
living outside Gran Mur!
June 13th, Stellar Year 2148
You've got a bad sense of humor, Haruto.
The joke didn't land as I'd hoped huh?
This is where you laugh, you know?
You mean, this is where we wince?
By the way, where did Anju go?
I need her to cover for my dinner duty.
She's on cleaning duty today.
Of course you would know, Daiya.
It's not just her, the rest of the girls went too.
When did they start?
I think right after breakfast.
But it's lunchtime now.
Yeah, it shouldn't take that long.
So they're bathing.
And right now, the river is...
Heaven on Earth!
No! Absolutely not!
Don't be such a stick in the mud!
We might die tomorrow!
You say that all the time, Haruto!
Don't worry, we won't look at Anju.
There's no way you won't see her!
Besides, that's not the issue.
I'm not going!
No way in hell!
Yes, we may yearn for each other,
but before that, we are comrades!
Loyal comrades!
It's so cold!
It feels so good!
Kaie, what are you doing over there?
Stop sitting around and join in the fun!
You're all looking a little nice
if you know what I mean?
What are you talking about?
Depending on your perspective,
you could call this heaven.
Stop being difficult and just join in already!
Yeah! Yeah!
Is it really okay to be having fun
out here by ourselves?
You're so serious sometimes, Kaie.
It's fine.
We've already finished doing our laundry.
Besides, I'm sure Shin knew
when he gave us the go ahead.
He's quick to catch on to these types of things,
that expressionless boy, you know?
Sorry, I should've realized!
Both you and Shin don't have any duties today,
so we should've found you an
excuse to be alone together!
No!
We're not like that!
What do you like about that guy?
I can never tell what he's thinking.
I told you, it's not like that!
What about you, Kaie?
Shin? He's not bad, I guess.
He's to the point, and I do like his stoic side.
W-Wait! Kaie!
I see. I see!
If nobody else is interested,
I can go after him myself, right?
In that case, I might just give him the classic "night's visit."
K-Kaie!
I-It's not like I really care about Shin or anything,
but, I don't think that's right.
Y-You know, if you want to be dignified
or reserved like a proper lady...
You're so cute, Kurena!
Stop it!
H-How many times do I have to tell you guys?
T-This is unforgiveable!
You're staring more intently than we are.
Why did you tag along again?
To keep an eye on you two!
Multiple targets... Ready!
Fire!
Are you two insane?
Hey, wait... It's not...
Daiya...
You won't be forgotten.
Die!
You pervert!
Stay out there!
So...
What is it, Daiya?
You know, this is where you could ask me
"Are you okay?" in a cute and concerned way?
My, are you okay, Daiya?
Why don't the rest of you come out?
Theo?
So, what are you doing here?
Well, it's... You know...
Right, Haruto?
Right, Daiya?
Wait, me?
Well it's...
Ah, that!
There was something we wanted to ask you.
Couldn't you have just used your Para-RAID?
Well, it seemed like you girls were having fun and
we didn't want to interrupt. You know?
It'd be awkward if you were
talking about love, right?
Just imagine if Kurena was saying
"Oh my! Shin, my love!"
Well, she basically just said that.
I got it!
We should trick her into saying that right as Shin connects!
I can't wait to see them react!
Kurena's reaction, you mean.
Shin's a lost cause.
That Reaper of ours won't even bat an eyelid.
He's no fun at all!
I-I did not say that!
Cut it out guys!
You're so cute, Kurena!
So, what did you want to ask us?
Well...
Daiya?
Me again?
Well... um...
What's a "knight's visit?"
So you were listening!
I said I'm sorry!
We need to bring back the laundry.
Where's Daiya?
Over there!
Daiya!
Hey Daiya, won't you carry the laundry for me?
Won't you?
Did something happen?
It's nothing, it was just a rat.
A rat?!
What an awful lie.
There are rats?
There are.
Kurena...
Why does he keep talking to that
woman night after night?
It's precious time we should be spending together!
We could die tomorrow!
It's just for now.
The princess will stop calling eventually.
They're both just killing time.
But why bother being nice to a white pig?
Shin should just break her already.
Shin doesn't break them on purpose.
Besides, could you say that to Shin's face?
You don't like her,
so you want him to break her?
Could you really?
I'm sorry.
But I still hate her.
Those white pigs murdered my mom and dad.
They threw them out like garbage and used them as target practice.
All white pigs are scum.
I'll never forgive any of them.
Really, Kirschblüte?
Yeah. The stars came falling down
from the sky like rain.
There were streaks of light
across the whole sky.
It was really something to look at.
There were that many shooting stars?
Yes, too many to count.
A meteor shower?
I've seen one of those, too.
Really?
Yeah, but it was in the middle of a battlefield,
where both sides were annihilated.
And there was only one guy left.
Right, Undertaker?
Well, that's not very romantic.
To top it off, all of our Juggernauts ran out of gas.
And until Fido caught up with us,
we were stranded in a pretty awful situation.
Fido?
Our dog.
You have a dog, too?
It's a pretty unusual dog.
Instead of going woof, it goes beep.
Beep?
Nights on the battlefield
are so dark that it's scary.
And then these pale, silent lights began to fall
from the sky, one after another. Filling the sky.
I remember I said something weird then,
and it was the biggest mistake of my life.
What did you say, show-off?
I'm not telling.
If this—
If this is the last thing I see,
then maybe this isn't so bad.
Man, why did you have to tell her?
After that, Shin snorted at me!
I doubt we'll ever see something
like that again.
I wish I could've seen
that meteor shower, too.
You couldn't see it where you are?
The lights in the city never fade,
so you can't really see the stars here.
You're right, now that I think about it.
Nights here are really dark.
There aren't a lot of people here,
and we're far from everything.
Plus we have blackout orders before bed,
so the stars are always beautiful.
It's one of the good things about this life.
One of the good things?
Yes.
Kirschblüte, do you despise us?
Well...
Of course, the discrimination hurts
and makes me mad.
Life in the internment camps was hard.
And I'll always be scared when I fight.
That's why for the people who forced this on us,
and justify it by saying the Eight-Six
are livestock and not human,
I can't bring myself to like them.
But...
But I know that not all of the Alba are bad.
Just like how not all of the Eighty-Six are good.
I'm one of the rarer races among the Eighty-Six.
So a lot of things happened in the
camps and my previous units.
Of course, I wasn't the only one.
I'm sure that there are good Alba, too.
Not that I've ever met any.
But a few of my comrades have.
So I understand that.
So I won't hate you
just because you're an Alba.
I see.
I need to thank them, then.
Handler One,
I'm taking a bit of an interest in you.
Really?
Can I ask you something, then?
Yes, go ahead.
June 13th, Stellar Year 2148
Hey Lena, why do I have to do this again?
I bought you lunch, remember?
You'd better buy dinner as well
to make this worth it.
What do you need the map for, anyway?
I want to send it to them.
They're fighting without any good maps.
You're bragging about them again?
Well, they're amazing.
They've fought more battles
than any other unit
in the past two weeks,
and there have been zero casualties.
Yeah, yeah. Amazing.
But would it kill you to talk about a guy who I can actually meet?
I'm having an awful time.
Especially my latest potential marriage partner...
Theobald?
How long ago was that guy?
Humbert!
His forehead goes up to here.
And he just won't give up.
I made a huge mistake giving him
my handkerchief when we first met.
Like, it was sweat from here!
It bothers you, right?
Yes, it does.
How do they know
when the Legion are going to attack?
She's not listening at all.
It really is a mystery.
They're always ready to fight
before the enemy even shows up.
Lena, don't get involved any further.
They're Eighty-Six.
Don't worry about me.
We have a human relationship built on trust.
What?
Are you okay?
I trust you, Major Milizé.
Here!
You found it!
You owe me dinner.
Thank you!
Now I can help them again.
You can't even see it.
Para-RAID, activate.
Synchronization target: Spearhead Processor.
To all units: Thank you all for your work today.
Same to you Handler One.
Hey there.
Thanks for the constant calls.
Undertaker, about the delivery date for the supply shipment you requested the other day,
I'm sorry, but it's going to take a little while longer.
Is that a cat?
Yeah, we keep it at the barracks.
I'm the one who found it, by the way.
Right after I transferred here,
it got knocked around by an HE shell,
and it was meowing nonstop in front of our door.
Its parents and siblings got flattened,
but it was just fine.
And for whatever reason, it's taken a liking to Undertaker more than anyone else.
He doesn't play with it at all.
It rubs up against him all the time,
and he just pats it once in a while.
It probably thinks he's just a good bed.
Just look at it now.
Yeah, it doesn't move when he's reading.
It'll never get along with
Black Dog, though. He's too annoying.
That's mean! And not fair!
I demand you take that back!
Boo! Boo!
What's its name?
Blackie.
Whitey.
Two-Tone.
Kitty.
Shrimp.
Remarque.
Don't name it after the author of
whatever book you're reading now.
And what are you even reading?
You have such bad taste.
Are there more of them?
Weren't you listening?
There's only one.
It's a black cat with white paws.
That's why we call it Blackie,
Whitey, and Two-Tone.
It doesn't really have a particular name.
Everybody just calls it whatever
they feel like at the moment.
Lately, it's been coming to you if you just
look at it and say something.
I see.
But why?
Did something happen?
It's nothing, it was just a rat.
A rat?
You have a dog, too?
It's a very unusual dog.
I wish I could've seen
that meteor shower, too...
You couldn't see it where you are?
I need to thank them, then.
Handler One,
I'm taking a bit of an interest in you.
Really?
Can I ask you something, then?
Yes, go ahead.
Why do you care about us so much?
Well...
A long time ago, I was saved
by a processor on the battlefield.
He said to me,
"We are members of the Republic.
We were born and raised here."
"It's a citizen's duty to protect his country.
I'm proud to do it."
"That's why we fight."
I think we need to live up
to the example set by his words.
We ask you to fight, but we don't even bother to honor your sacrifice.
We don't even try to know you.
That goes against what he said.
It's disgraceful.
Handler One.
You're a virgin, aren't you?
Sorry, I didn't mean to say that!
I meant, "like a virgin?"
That's not any better!
I mean, you're like a young girl who thinks
the whole world is made of fields of flowers...
Like you have an untarnished, pure ideal.
So, what I wanted to say is...
You're not a bad person.
So I'm going to warn you now.
You aren't cut out for this job.
And you shouldn't get involved with us.
We're not fighting for a noble reason like yours.
So there's no need for you to talk to us.
You should transfer and have someone else
take your place before you regret it.
June 15th, Stellar Year 2148
Handler One to all units:
Enemy sighted on radar.
Enemy size is—
We're aware, Handler One.
We are preparing to engage at grid point 478.
Roger that, Undertaker.
Undertaker, Gunslinger's in position.
Laughing Fox to Undertaker:
Third Platoon's in position.
Undertaker, please move Gunslinger from her current position, 500 meters to her 2 o'clock.
You can't see it where you are,
but there's high ground there.
She can use the hill to provide overwatch,
and have a wider view.
Confirmed.
Gunslinger, can you see the point
from where you are?
Hang on.
Yeah, it's there.
I'm relocating.
Your position will be opposite of
First Platoon, the main assault force.
Your fire will disperse and destroy the enemy,
while concealing the main attack force
in the early phase of the battle.
In other words, a decoy.
You may have the voice of a little princess,
but you've got guts.
The Löwes don't have good elevation.
So they can't fire at her in that position,
and if they change positions—
Don't get me wrong.
It's not a bad idea.
Right, Gunslinger?
I'll do anything, if it helps the rest of us.
Did you find a new map?
That's helpful.
Should I send it later?
Is that okay? Sending classified
map data to us Eighty-Six.
I don't care.
What good is information if you don't use it?
So that's how it is.
Also, you're not Eighty-Six.
At least, I've never called you—
Right, right.
Here they come.
Target destroyed.
Fourth Platoon moving out.
What's that Löwe doing there?
A faint light points ahead
Leukosia, I'll hit it from the left.
su
sa
ki
Back me up.
To shadows stalled in a silent haze
si
lent
lent
ha
Roger, Kirschblüte.
Not that way! Kirschblüte!
ge
So scattered and carved
Wetlands? Here?
ni
ki
za
I can't move.
mu
Can you still smile after seeing the true world?
No. I don't want to die.
e
ru
ka
Don't
you
get
there?
It
calls!
Don't
you
get
there?
It
calls!
The sky I look up to changes in color
heart
can
hear!
E
chos!
na
ked
heart
can
hear!
E
chos!
Avidity that I sought without even realizing it
Whis
per
your
name
a
gain
per
your
name
a
gain
Then
re
start
it
right
a
way
re
start
it
right
ter,
co
lor,
ar
dor,
wan
der
my,
bit
ter,
co
lor,
ar
dor,
wan
der
Got
to
feel
feel
The freedom of the sky we saw that faithful day
Mission complete.
Good work, everyone.
I'm sorry about Kirschblüte.
If only I'd found the map sooner...
If only I'd done a better job...
Sorry? Sorry about what?
From your perspective,
the deaths of a few Eighty-Six
are things you can forget about
by the time you go home for dinner.
Sure, we don't have much to do here,
so we can play along with you when you say,
"I don't discriminate even if other people do.
I don't treat you as pigs."
But we just lost one of our comrades.
Understand that we don't have time
to deal with your hypocrisy now.
Hypocrisy?
Or what, did you think we don't care
when one of our own dies?
Yeah, maybe you're right!
After all, we're not
high-minded humans like you.
We're pigs, less than human!
N-No! I didn't—
Don't try to deny it!
You throw us out here on the battlefield
and treat us like weapons,
while you get to watch from your
warm and safe place inside the walls,
where it doesn't bother you at all!
If that's not treating us like pigs, then what is?
You've never called us the Eighty-Six?
You've just never said it.
Do you think we're out here fighting
because we want to?
You locked us out here! Forced us to fight!
You've caused the deaths of millions
over the last nine years!
And you've done nothing to stop it.
You think that if you just act nice
and talk to us every day,
that counts as treating us as human, don't you?
You've never even asked us
for our real names!
Real Name.