September 28th, Stellar Year 2148
Looks like they've gathered all of the Legion in the area.
Shin!
Shin, that voice!
Go on ahead.
Take cover in the forest,
you probably won't be spotted there.
Wait for them to pass and then move on.
Wait!
Raiden, you're in charge until then.
What about you?
I'll catch up after I defeat them.
We can't advance until they're gone.
Not that I would, anyway.
Besides...
I doubt he'll let me get away.
You could've asked me to fight alongside you...
To hell with that order.
I'll hold off the small fry.
So take care of it quickly!
What a fool.
You're one to talk.
Don't die on us.
I found you, brother.
No matter how hard I wish nothing ever changes
aigan shitemo konganshitemo kawaranai yamou
No matter how hard I wish nothing ever changes
A flower blooms only to be crushed
aigan shitemo konganshitemo kawaranai yamou
fuminijirareru dake no hana
A flower blooms only to be crushed
No matter how hard I wish nothing ever changes
aigan shitemo konganshitemo kawaranai yamou
fuminijirareru dake no hana
No matter how hard I wish nothing ever changes
aigan shitemo konganshitemo kawaranai yamou
A flower blooms only to be crushed
fuminijirareru dake no hana
A flower blooms only to be crushed
fuminijirareru dake no hana
No matter what happens I'll never forget your voice
anata no koe wo wasure wa shinai darou
No matter what happens I'll never forget your voice
anata no koe wo wasure wa shinai darou
Swept up and scattered by the wind
kaze ni fukarete chirijiri ni natte
Swept up and scattered by the wind
I can't see the future in your reflectionless eyes
kaze ni fukarete chirijiri ni natte
sono konkontaru suishoutai ni wa utsuranai mirai mirai
I can't see the future in your reflectionless eyes
Swept up and scattered by the wind
kaze ni fukarete chirijiri ni natte
sono konkontaru suishoutai ni wa utsuranai mirai mirai
Swept up and scattered by the wind
kaze ni fukarete chirijiri ni natte
I can't see the future in your reflectionless eyes
sono konkontaru suishoutai ni wa utsuranai mirai mirai
shou
I can't see the future in your reflectionless eyes
sono konkontaru suishoutai ni wa utsuranai mirai mirai
No matter how hard I wish nothing ever changes
aigan shitemo konganshitemo kawaranai yamou
No matter how hard I wish nothing ever changes
A flower blooms only to be crushed
aigan shitemo konganshitemo kawaranai yamou
fuminijirareru dake no hana
A flower blooms only to be crushed
No matter how hard I wish nothing ever changes
aigan shitemo konganshitemo kawaranai yamou
fuminijirareru dake no hana
No matter how hard I wish nothing ever changes
aigan shitemo konganshitemo kawaranai yamou
A flower blooms only to be crushed
fuminijirareru dake no hana
fuminijirareru dake no hana
A flower blooms only to be crushed
Bystanding, revolting, willful ignorance
boukan shiteiru zouhan shiteiru minai furishiteiru
Bystanding, revolting, willful ignorance
That's you, that's the person I see
boukan shiteiru zouhan shiteiru minai furishiteiru
sonna anata wo boku wa miteiru
That's you, that's the person I see
Bystanding, revolting, willful ignorance
boukan shiteiru zouhan shiteiru minai furishiteiru
sonna anata wo boku wa miteiru
Bystanding, revolting, willful ignorance
boukan shiteiru zouhan shiteiru minai furishiteiru
That's you, that's the person I see
sonna anata wo boku wa miteiru
That's you, that's the person I see
Don't worry, ease up why don't you
sonna anata wo boku wa miteiru
anshinshinayo bokutachi minna itsudatte
Don't worry, ease up why don't you
That's you, that's the person I see
sonna anata wo boku wa miteiru
anshinshinayo bokutachi minna itsudatte
That's you, that's the person I see
sonna anata wo boku wa miteiru
Don't worry, ease up why don't you
anshinshinayo bokutachi minna itsudatte
an
shin
Don't worry, ease up why don't you
We're all guilty in the end
anshinshinayo bokutachi minna itsudatte
yarukoto wa onaji sa
We're all guilty in the end
Don't worry, ease up why don't you
anshinshinayo bokutachi minna itsudatte
yarukoto wa onaji sa
Don't worry, ease up why don't you
anshinshinayo bokutachi minna itsudatte
We're all guilty in the end
yarukoto wa onaji sa
We're all guilty in the end
yarukoto wa onaji sa
Something's weird!
It's as if they're trying to separate us from Shin!
This isn't how the Legion fight.
It's that Shepherd's orders.
He wants some private family time.
No matter where I shoot, it won't penetrate.
Help me!
Help me! Help me!
He wants to kill me with his own hands.
So that's what you're after.
It's the same for me, brother.
I'm reloading! Cover me!
Again? How much ammo are we using?
I'm not counting!
Don't worry.
As long as we can thin out their numbers...
Looks like they have no intention of retreating.
Fine by me.
Let's do this!
Lieutenant Shuga,
I'm borrowing your left eye!
Here they come.
Brace for impact!
Is that you, Major Milizé?
Yes. It's me.
All personnel: Sorry, I'm late.
Are you an absolute idiot?
Sharing visual information...
I just verified the impact points.
Oh, I didn't want to distract you from the fight
so I closed my left eye.
Are you not aware that sharing visual information causes blindness in Handlers?!
Plus, those were your artillery.
There's no way you got permission!
So what about it?
Blindness will happen over time.
And it's not like they'll kill me over firing these guns.
The Republic doesn't listen to common sense.
So there's no reason for me to, either.
I should've done this a long time ago.
You're a real idiot.
I'm not doing it for you.
If the Legion break through in these numbers,
the Republic would be in danger.
I'm just fighting because I don't want to die.
I'll take care of their reinforcements.
You'll just need to handle those in front of you.
Fine, leave it to us.
This is nothing new for us.
Where's Captain Nouzen?
He's fighting his brother.
That's his real objective.
He can't hear our voices anymore.
Enemy forces are withdrawing!
Hell yeah!
We did it.
Captain Nouzen!
Captain Nouzen! Come in!
Shin?
Shin?!
Wake up, you fool!
What is that?
Damn it! We've got to stop it!
But how!
Lieutenant Kukumila, send me the most accurate estimate of the enemy's position.
You'll need to provide terminal guidance.
Just mark it with your laser designator.
Wait, you mean—
You're using artillery?!
It's too close! You'll hit Shin!
I have a plan.
I don't want to let him die, either.
Even though I held back, it's so fragile.
I may have hurt you,
but I'll apologize for that, and everything else, later.
Finally... Finally you came to me.
We can be together again.
I'll read you a book again.
But first, I'll get rid of your human body!
Little insects...
You're wasting your time!
Explosive
Projectile
You pieces of shit...
You're killing Shin too?
Shin...
I'll protect you!
You want to protect him, but...
That's right!
I have to protect him!
He's my brother! I love him!
You want to protect him,
but you're going to kill him again?
I...
They're duds?
All rounds have impacted the target.
But that won't even slow him down.
We have to do something, now!
Captain Nouzen's signal is back online!
Shin! Wake up, you fool!
Stop messing around!
Get up already!
Shin, are you okay?
Shin...
That Mom and Dad died.
The fact that I'm about to die.
It's all your fault,
Shin!
My brother hasn't forgiven me.
He still blames me.
So...
That's why you're going to put him to rest, right?
Shin!
E
nough!
We're
tough
e
nough!
E
We're
tough
e
nough!
Where
do
we
go?
Don't
need
to
know
Where
do
we
go?
Don't
need
to
know
Just
keep
flow,
can
we
go
back?
I...
Just
keep
flow,
can
we
go
back?
I'll
co
ver
you,
you
co
ver
me
I'll
co
ver
I wanted you to...
you,
you
co
ver
me
Pick
it
up!
Keep
your
head!
Pick
it
up!
Pick
it
up!
Keep
your
head!
Pick
it
up!
Your
an
swer?
Your
an
swer?
First
we
must
beat
the
Le
gion
First
we
must
beat
the
Le
gion
Then
show
the
world
we're
hu
man
Then
show
the
world
we're
hu
man
First
we
must
beat
the
Le
gion
First
we
must
beat
the
Le
gion
Show
the
world
we
like
it
rough
Show
the
world
we
like
it
rough
Farewell... Brother.
I get it now.
You don't need me to hold your hand anymore.
I'm sorry.
Brother?
Shin.
A faint light points ahead
Shin!
To shadows stalled in a silent haze
si
lent
lent
Shin...
So scattered and carved
Shin...
Can you still smile after seeing the true world?
Don't
you
get
there?
It
calls!
you
get
there?
It
calls!
The sky I look up to changes in color
heart
can
hear!
E
chos!
na
ked
heart
can
hear!
E
chos!
Avidity that I sought without even realizing it
Whis
per
your
name
a
gain
per
your
name
a
gain
Then
re
start
it
right
a
way
re
start
it
right
ter,
co
lor,
ar
dor,
wan
der
my,
bit
ter,
co
lor,
ar
dor,
wan
der
Got
to
feel
feel
The freedom of the sky we saw that faithful day
September 28th, Stellar Year 2148
Major, cut the connection.
He wouldn't want anyone hearing that.
You're right.
It's over.
I told you I never wanted to see your face again.
Yeah, I heard you, Annette.
But I never said I wouldn't.
I need to get into the artillery control system.
And the ability to synchronize vision.
You'll do it to help Spearhead, right?
Of course not.
It's not my problem.
You will.
No matter what it takes.
The boy you abandoned...
His name was Shin, right?
How do you know that name?
There weren't many Eighty-Six in the 1st Sector.
Especially ones around our age
with a much older brother.
I am very familiar with your old childhood friend.
I talk to him all the time after all.
You don't mean...
That's right. He's in my unit.
Combat commander of the Spearhead Squadron.
Personal name: Undertaker.
That's Shin.
Did he tell you this?!
Is he still alive?
Is he...
Does he still hate me?
What do you care? It's not your problem.
It's not my problem?
It's not...
But if you do care, then you'll help me.
What's your answer?
You abandoned him twice.
Are you going to repeat it for a third time?
You're the devil.
That's right, Officer Penrose.
I am, and so are you.
Shin's safe.
Thanks to you.
I'm not the one who saved him.
He's good to talk now.
Major...
I thought I heard a voice.
You were there, weren't you?
Of course I was there.
I'm Spearhead's Handler after all.
Right, right.
You sure are.
The battle is over.
Good work, Undertaker, and all of you.
Thank you, Handler One.
What the hell happened to you, though?
You suddenly turned into a bad girl.
"A bad girl?" I didn't...
I just—
I thought you were trying
to blow us up along with the Legion.
Of course not!
She's joking, obviously.
You're so serious.
But don't you think that's one of her good points?
That's right. We're grateful, you know.
You saved our lives.
You're all teasing me.
Thank you.
I was finally able to let my brother rest.
That's why you're going to put him to rest, right?
Shin!
No, it was just a coincidence
that it worked out.
I see.
I can't believe you fired rounds
with deactivated fuses to throw them off.
Pretty clever.
Half the rounds were duds, so I got the idea...
I see.
I'll do even better next time!
Glad to hear it.
I'll set my expectations low.
Now then...
Yeah.
Fido, you got the containers hooked up again?
We'll decide on a place to sleep first,
then worry about repairs.
It kinda sucks that we burned through
so much ammo on the first day.
I don't think it's a problem.
We certainly took out enough of them.
Sure did.
Let's get to work, then.
Talk to you later, Major.
Hope you can pull this off with the next group, too.
Hey, is it safe to go forward?
Those dud rounds landed around there.
So it's basically a minefield...
We might not want to move straight ahead.
Shin, can you find us another route?
This is Legion territory,
but there aren't any Legion in the area.
We can take any route we want,
but... dud rounds?
We'll tell you as we go.
Shin, you really weren't paying attention to anything else, were you?
Wait... Please wait!
Don't leave me behind!
Yeah, I like the sound of that.
We're not being chased out.
We're moving forward on our own,
as far as we can go.
What do you want for dinner?
It's our first day,
so we should do something special, right?
Yeah, but...
I don't know if I've got it in me to go hunting.
I'd rather just go to sleep.
I'm tired.
Wait!
Okay, our goal for tomorrow is to reach that building.
We've got time. Want to place a bet?
Let's see, how about who's in charge
of cooking tomorrow?
I don't mind betting,
but no complaining if Kurena or I get it.
Hey!
Fine. You guys suck at cooking,
so that's off the table.
Huh? Do you see something?
Like a building?
You're right!
Is that a cathedral?
A train station, probably.
Wouldn't it be wonderful
if it was a castle or a mansion?
Especially if we can spend the night there.
I've only seen castles out in the distance in other Combat Wards.
I've never been in one.
Let's hunt for treasure!
Yeah.
We're not in a hurry or anything.
It's beautiful.
Pure red all over.
What kind of flower is this?
Is it okay to step on these?
It feels wrong.
Just walking next to them makes the petals fall off.
They were close to falling off on their own.
All the falling petals are pretty,
but kind of sad.
Seeing a sea of flowers that are all the same color during a fight is kinda scary.
The minute we became free,
we got to see something wonderful, huh?
We're coming up to the edge of Republic controlled territory.
The outer edge of the 86th Sector.
Yeah.
We finally made it here.
We've finally arrived.
Outside the 86th Sector,
the battlefield where we used to live.
Major...
We're going on ahead, Major.
Thank you.