Colonel Milizé!
April 13th, Stellar Year 2142
Father!
If there are any survivors,
cover your ears and take cover!
Are you okay?
Search concluded.
Returning to base.
Want some?
I just thought that something
sweet would go down easier.
Or do you not like chocolate?
Good.
Father...
said we were doing horrible things
to the Eighty-Six.
So why did you protect me?
Well...
We are members of the Republic.
We were born and raised here.
It's a citizen's duty to fight to protect their country.
It's something to be proud of.
I'm not one of those losers who's all talk.
So I choose to fight.
I'll fight and protect this country to the end.
I have a brother.
He should be around your age.
I'm sure he's grown big and strong now.
You can't see him?
No, I can't go back yet.
Thank you.
I'm Shourei Nouzen. Call me "Rei."
What a strange name.
It's a rare name in this country.
You're not from the Republic?
My brother and I were born here,
but our parents were from the neighboring country.
Have you heard of the Empire of Giad?
They're the country that made the Legion.
Aren't you scared to fight?
I am.
But if I don't fight, I can't survive.
So I won't die. I can't.
I have to go back...
to my brother.
June 16th, Stellar Year 2148
What is your brother doing now?
He's dead.
He died here on the Eastern Theater,
five years ago.
I'm sorry.
No, it's fine.
Do you remember when you asked me about what I wanted to do after leaving the army?
Y-Yes.
There isn't anything I want to do.
But there's something I have to do.
I've been searching for my brother for the past five years. All this time.
You mean his dead body?
No.
No matter how hard I wish nothing ever changes
aigan shitemo konganshitemo kawaranai yamou
No matter how hard I wish nothing ever changes
A flower blooms only to be crushed
aigan shitemo konganshitemo kawaranai yamou
fuminijirareru dake no hana
A flower blooms only to be crushed
No matter how hard I wish nothing ever changes
aigan shitemo konganshitemo kawaranai yamou
fuminijirareru dake no hana
No matter how hard I wish nothing ever changes
aigan shitemo konganshitemo kawaranai yamou
A flower blooms only to be crushed
fuminijirareru dake no hana
A flower blooms only to be crushed
fuminijirareru dake no hana
No matter what happens I'll never forget your voice
anata no koe wo wasure wa shinai darou
No matter what happens I'll never forget your voice
anata no koe wo wasure wa shinai darou
Swept up and scattered by the wind
kaze ni fukarete chirijiri ni natte
Swept up and scattered by the wind
I can't see the future in your reflectionless eyes
kaze ni fukarete chirijiri ni natte
sono konkontaru suishoutai ni wa utsuranai mirai mirai
I can't see the future in your reflectionless eyes
Swept up and scattered by the wind
kaze ni fukarete chirijiri ni natte
sono konkontaru suishoutai ni wa utsuranai mirai mirai
Swept up and scattered by the wind
kaze ni fukarete chirijiri ni natte
I can't see the future in your reflectionless eyes
sono konkontaru suishoutai ni wa utsuranai mirai mirai
shou
I can't see the future in your reflectionless eyes
sono konkontaru suishoutai ni wa utsuranai mirai mirai
No matter how hard I wish nothing ever changes
aigan shitemo konganshitemo kawaranai yamou
No matter how hard I wish nothing ever changes
A flower blooms only to be crushed
aigan shitemo konganshitemo kawaranai yamou
fuminijirareru dake no hana
A flower blooms only to be crushed
No matter how hard I wish nothing ever changes
aigan shitemo konganshitemo kawaranai yamou
fuminijirareru dake no hana
No matter how hard I wish nothing ever changes
aigan shitemo konganshitemo kawaranai yamou
A flower blooms only to be crushed
fuminijirareru dake no hana
fuminijirareru dake no hana
A flower blooms only to be crushed
Bystanding, revolting, willful ignorance
boukan shiteiru zouhan shiteiru minai furishiteiru
Bystanding, revolting, willful ignorance
That's you, that's the person I see
boukan shiteiru zouhan shiteiru minai furishiteiru
sonna anata wo boku wa miteiru
That's you, that's the person I see
Bystanding, revolting, willful ignorance
boukan shiteiru zouhan shiteiru minai furishiteiru
sonna anata wo boku wa miteiru
Bystanding, revolting, willful ignorance
boukan shiteiru zouhan shiteiru minai furishiteiru
That's you, that's the person I see
sonna anata wo boku wa miteiru
That's you, that's the person I see
Don't worry, ease up why don't you
sonna anata wo boku wa miteiru
anshinshinayo bokutachi minna itsudatte
Don't worry, ease up why don't you
That's you, that's the person I see
sonna anata wo boku wa miteiru
anshinshinayo bokutachi minna itsudatte
That's you, that's the person I see
sonna anata wo boku wa miteiru
Don't worry, ease up why don't you
anshinshinayo bokutachi minna itsudatte
an
shin
Don't worry, ease up why don't you
We're all guilty in the end
anshinshinayo bokutachi minna itsudatte
yarukoto wa onaji sa
We're all guilty in the end
Don't worry, ease up why don't you
anshinshinayo bokutachi minna itsudatte
yarukoto wa onaji sa
Don't worry, ease up why don't you
anshinshinayo bokutachi minna itsudatte
We're all guilty in the end
yarukoto wa onaji sa
We're all guilty in the end
yarukoto wa onaji sa
June 24th, Stellar Year 2148
Morning, Lena.
Morning.
It's so good!
I know, right?
The cream is artificial,
but the strawberries are real.
Oh, right.
Want to go look at party dresses next week?
For the Revolution Festival.
It's that time of year?
Do you think I really need to go?
Of course.
All the good dressmakers will be
booked up if you don't act fast.
Sorry, I've been a bit busy lately.
You've been pretty distant lately Lena.
If you're looking for a dress,
why not ask a gentleman to go with you?
I heard you met another prospective partner.
Hmm, Rudolph huh?
He was cute.
You're actually complimenting him?
Does this mean you've finally—
Not a chance.
I mean, just look at him.
He's five.
No matter how attractive my family wealth is, that's a bit much...
Why did you put up all the photos
from your past prospects?
My team did it as a joke.
So I won't forget, they said.
Lena, are you sure you're not tired?
Your face is a mess.
Is it?
You're using the Para-RAID too much.
I told you that sharing sensory data puts a lot of stress on the brain.
It's just that I pulled an all-nighter
analyzing combat data.
I know I've said this before,
but there's no point in doing
any favors for the Eighty-Six.
So don't you think it's okay to attend the party?
June 30th, Stellar Year 2148
What if a battle starts during the party?
We'll be fine.
I mean, who puts on a party during wartime anyway?
Whatever happens within the walls is irrelevant to us.
We appreciate the analysis
of the enemies you provide,
but it's not something that needs
to take up all your private time.
Is what I'm doing unnecessary, Captain Nouzen?
No, your high-level analysis from a theater perspective is valuable.
Your estimates of enemy force compositions
are accurate and particularly helpful.
Thank you.
I'm glad.
But you don't need
to spend all your time on it.
If you spend too much time thinking about
the battlefield, you'll end up like me.
What kind of joke is that?
Understood.
I'll go enjoy myself then.
With the stupid party,
and the stuffy dress and high heels.
The Revolution Festival?
Do you remember anything about it?
I think I remember seeing fireworks.
In a garden with a fountain,
in front of the palace.
The palace?
Did you use to live in the 1st Sector?
I don't really remember, but I believe so.
Oh, wow!
I remember going with my brother.
I'm sorry, I shouldn't have...
It's fine.
Concerning my family, I can no longer
remember their faces nor their voices.
He was reminiscing that
you'd grown up big and strong.
I could tell he really cared about you.
Your brother really wanted to go home
and be with you again.
If only that were the case...
Captain, you're supposed
to be on patrol, aren't you?
Are you in your room?
I apologize.
Well, if you've decided it's not necessary,
I'll respect that, but...
I thought you'd be angry.
I'm not that much of a stuffed shirt—
Nobody will see us here.
It's fine.
Hey, stop!
Sorry, Major.
Major?
I-It's nothing!
Really, it's nothing!
Major, we're preparing to sortie.
But, they haven't sounded any warnings.
No, the Legion are coming.
Confirmed. We're ready to go at any time.
Third Platoon's also ready.
Roger.
Captain Nouzen, how did you know
the Legion are coming?
If you weren't on patrol,
how could you find them so fast?
Major, would you please cut your Para-RAID?
There are a lot of Black Sheep this time.
It'll be dangerous to remain synchronized.
Black Sheep?
If you're curious, I'll explain later.
Please cut the synchronization.
I can't observe the battlefield
if I cut the Para-RAID.
I will not.
I've warned you.
Undertaker, you're too far ahead!
They'll surround you!
Ma...
What's this?
This isn't static.
Mom!
Help me.
Help me!
It's so hot!
Mom! Mom!
No!
Major!
Major Milizé!
I'm cutting the link, Major!
I don't want to die.
Kaie?
That voice...
Mom... Mom... Mom...
Help me!
No!
Why?
Mom! Mom!
Help me!
No!
Stop it!
I don't want to die!
June 30th, Stellar Year 2148
Mom.
What is this? It's not static.
Mom!
Help me! Help me!
Damn, you're more annoying than usual today!
No!
I wonder if she'll be alright...
Major! Major Milizé!
No... Make it stop...
I'm cutting the link, Major!
I don't want to die.
Shit! That was Kaie!
It can't be! We torched
her along with her juggernaut!
Help me!
They took her? Damn it!
I don't want to die.
Gunslinger:
Heading 060, distance 800.
The enemy's front rank,
the third Grauwolf from the right.
Roger.
I don't want to die.
Target silenced.
Good work today.
Thanks.
Everybody really gave it their all today.
They wanted revenge, huh?
It's a nasty thing.
But you know, I figured they'd be
burned out after the mission.
Maybe they're feeling a bit lonely.
Around this time, she'd usually...
Right.
Those Handlers never synchronize
after hearing those voices.
Guess you're off the hook for those reports.
Yes, it's fine, Major.
I'm impressed.
I'm sorry for losing control today.
Not at all.
Captain...
Those voices I heard during the battle...
what were they?
Once, I almost died.
Actually, I probably did die back then.
So that's why I can hear them.
The voices of the ghosts
who've died, yet still linger.
Ghosts?
But there were only Legion out there, right?
I think they're ghosts, too.
They no longer have a reason to exist due to the collapse of their country.
The ghost army of a collapsed country.
So the reason you know
when the Legion are coming...
Yes. It's because I can hear their voices.
Whenever they come close.
I always hear them, even when I'm asleep.
Wait, you said always.
Do you hear them now?
Not just during battle, but even now?
Goodnight!
How far away can they be?
I don't know the exact distance,
but I can sense every Legion within the Republic's former borders.
Isn't it mentally taxing for you?
I've become used to it.
It's been a long time since it started.
Since when?
And did you hear Lieutenant Kaie Taniya's voice
because she became a ghost as well?
Captain?
The Republic's government assumes
the war will end in two years, right?
How did you know?
Theo heard it from his Captain,
the one we talked about earlier.
The Legion have a hard-coded lifespan.
In a little under two years, it'll run out.
Isn't that right?
Yes.
The Legion's central processing unit
is modeled after biological brains.
That design will stop
functioning after two years.
If that particular design will stop functioning,
they simply need to replace the design
with a new one before the deadline.
Using the materials which are readily
available on the battlefield.
You can't mean...
Human brains.
Within nature, our nervous systems are much
more well-developed than the rest.
The brains of the fallen Eighty-Six which
the Republic forbids the burial of.
Brains will eventually rot,
and I've confirmed that some Legion have the same voices.
So in actuality, it's probably a
copy of the brain's structure.
Then...
Kaie's probably still out there.
So I don't think it's the same as
what you'd call a soul.
It can't be considered the original person.
We can't communicate with it.
They're copies of the mind on the brink
of death; their final moments.
They're the phantoms that
take the form of the Legion.
And those are the Black Sheep?
Yes.
The haunted Black Sheep that hide among the White Sheep.
Of course, nowadays, the Black Sheep are more common now.
Major, you're going to lose this war.
What do you mean?
The Legion using the new design aren't at risk of shutting down in two years.
But what about the Eighty-Six?
The only ones left are children,
and they're already being sent to the frontlines.
We'll all be dead soon.
When that happens,
are the Alba able to fight?
The Alba that pushed all military service
and death onto everyone else?
Well...
They can't.
But there are fewer Legion now!
They've been reduced to less than half of what they were a few years ago.
You mean the observable forces.
It's true that the number of Legion
on the frontlines has decreased.
But that's only because they've
relocated their forces to the rear.
They're conserving and building up their forces?
There's no way. The legion
don't have that kind of intelligence.
They shouldn't.
But that's why you've overlooked it.
What do you mean?
The heads that the Legion obtain,
are more often than not
damaged in one way or another.
But the Black Sheep are still more intelligent than normal Legion.
Now imagine if they retrieve an undamaged brain.
Is that possible?
Previously, the Legion were only capable
of taking simple direct orders.
But the ghost commanders can think
for themselves and take command.
We call them Shepherds,
and they lead armies that are
unrivaled among the Legion.
Wait. This isn't a hypothesis?
They already exist?
Can you hear their voices?
I can.
The commanders' voices are especially clear.
Yes, there's one at the
rear of 1st Combat Ward.
But, if the Republic were to fall, that would still be a few years
after you've all been wiped out, right?
Yes. That'll be the case.
So we just need to
wipe out the Legion before then.
Let's win. I'll help alongside...
No. I'll have to try my hardest.
I'll analyze the enemy. Come up with plans.
Everything I can do.
A faint light points ahead
Captain Nouzen...
yo
wai
hi
ka
Your term of service is up this year, right?
So let's win before then, and both survive.
su
sa
ki
To shadows stalled in a silent haze
si
lent
lent
You're right.
So scattered and carved
Can we call it a night?
ji
ri
ni
It's lights-out here.
ki
za
mu
Can you still smile after seeing the true world?
Sorry for keeping you up late.
Goodnight.
e
ru
ka
Don't
you
get
there?
It
calls!
you
get
there?
It
calls!
The sky I look up to changes in color
heart
can
hear!
E
chos!
na
ked
heart
can
hear!
E
chos!
Avidity that I sought without even realizing it
Whis
per
your
name
a
gain
per
your
name
a
gain
Then
re
start
it
right
a
way
re
start
it
right
a
way
Oh
my,
bitter,
color,
ardor,
wander
my,
bitter,
color,
ardor,
wander
Got
to
feel
feel
The freedom of the sky we saw that faithful day
It's all your fault!
I'll come for you soon,
Brother.
Through to the end.