Salutare, supervizor 1.
22 mai, anul stelar 2148
Eu sunt căpitanul
escadronului Vârf de Lance,
Nume de cod: Groparul.
Am primit vestea că vom
avea un nou supervizor.
Abia așteptăm să lucrăm cu tine.
Asemenea.
Încântată de cunoștintă, Groparule.
22 mai, anul stelar 2148
Bună treabă.
La fel și voi.
Cel nou pare destul de problematic.
Noul supervizor. Ai uitat deja?
Shin! Shinei Nouzen!
Iar ai făcut-o de oaie, nemernicule!
Bătrânul Aldrecht este pe
cale să explodeze din nou.
Ai nevoie de ceva?
Nu mă lua cu asta!
Cum reușești să-ți distrugi
mașinăria de fiecare dată?
Îți tot spun că au picioare slabe,
deci nu le mai forța!
Îmi pare rău.
Am rămas fără piese de schimb!
Nu vom putea s-o reparăm
până nu vom primi un nou lot!
Fido trebuie să fi adus
deja mașinăria lui Kujo.
Ei bine, presupun că
putem folosi părți din ea.
Dar ești în regulă cu asta?
Cineva a murit în ea...
Bănuiesc că este cam târziu acum.
Nu-i așa, Groparule?
Kujo a fost norocos să lupte alături de tine.
La fel și celelalte Procesoare.
Apropo, am auzit de
schimbarea supervizorului.
Cum este?
În regulă, bănuiesc.
Ce vrea să însemne asta?
S-a sincronizat cu noi ca să ne salute
și vrea să păstrăm o comunicare strânsă,
deci ne va contacta în fiecare zi.
Destul de neobișnuit pentru
un soldat al Republicii.
Deci este o persoană decentă, nu?
Cred că îi este destul de greu bietei fete.
29 mai, anul stelar 2148
Haideți să începem!
Am prins-o!
Tot așa!
Hopa sus!
Se pare că avem ceva marfă, nu?
Vom da o petrecere în seara asta!
Ești gata de plecare, Fido?
Nu suntem răi cu tine, știi?
Să nu ne pârăști lui Shin, bine?
Ăsta este un "da" sau un "nu"?
Hei, plimbăreților, mă puteți auzi?
Ce este, Theo?
Prognoza meteo s-a schimbat.
Se anunță ploaie.
Efemeroptere.
Au trimis până și unitățile de bruiere, nu?
Asta înseamnă că nu
vom putea folosi radarul.
Când vor ajunge aici?
În aproximativ două ore.
Recepționat. Venim chiar acum.
Nu este niciun Păstor de data asta.
Probabil se vor baza
doar pe puterea de luptă.
Deci vor fi doar Oi?
Atunci, va fi o vânătoare de rațe.
Toată lumea este aici.
Atențiune!
Voi explica situația.
Unitățile inamice din apropiere s-au unit cu grupul venit din urma lor.
Cel mai probabil se aprovizionează.
Când vor termina, vor începe atacul.
Vom pregăti o ambuscadă în punctul 304.
Zona de luptă va fi Strada Principală,
unde vom elimina majoritatea unităților inamice.
Chiar și primăvara se face
frig când dispare soarele.
Se face destul de frig în cabină,
deși abia ai loc să te miști.
Ei bine, armura este subțire
precum hârtia și plină de găuri.
Și mașinăria asta e înceată ca melcul.
Și se strică ușor.
Da. Parcă am pilota un gunoi umblător.
Handler One to all units:
It appears that enemy units are approaching.
Deploy to grid point 208 and intercept them!
Undertaker to Handler One:
We've already deployed.
We'll intercept them further ahead at grid point 304.
That's fast.
You're as good as they say, Undertaker.
Here they come.
The Legion's out in full force again, huh?
Scout Type: Ameise
Well, they're mostly Ameise.
They're easy to destroy,
but those things sure are annoying.
Tip cavaler: Lup Gri
Grauwolfs? What a pain.
I guess we have to take this seriously.
Screw Grauwolfs. I hate them.
Tip tanc: Leu
The Löwe's main gun is twice as powerful as ours, if not more.
It'll knock you out in a heartbeat.
Electronic-Disruption Type: Eintagsfliege
All right, time to get to work.
Open fire.
Ne-am petrecut întreaga viață în umbre
Ca niște oameni buni a căror existență a fost ștearsă
Te văd acum, în timp ce presiunea crește,
Third platoon, lure the enemy and withdraw to the southeast.
Precum îndoielile pe care le aveam când priveam înapoi
Fifth platoon, hold your current positions.
Nu ți-am înțeles niciodată logica
When the enemy force enters the kill zone,
coordinate your fire.
Mă întrebai mereu același lucru
Când toată nebunia asta se va termina
Black Dog, roger.
Care va fi...
Snow Witch, reload while you can.
Snow Witch, roger.
Destul!
As always, thanks.
Laughing Fox, likewise.
Destul!
Watch your fire, Black Dog!
...răspunsul tău?
Unde mergem?
Nu e nevoie să știm
Doar ține ritmul
Ne putem întoarce?
Te acopăr, mă acoperi
Mai repede!
Păstrează-ți calmul
Vorbești cu mine, vorbesc cu tine
Asta va fi utopia noastră
Unde mergem?
Îl ai cu tine?
Răspunsul tău?
Mai întâi, trebuie să învingem legiunea
Iar apoi, vom arăta lumii că suntem oameni
Vom arăta lumii că nu ne dăm bătuți
All units, cease fire! Spread out!
Handler One to all units!
Incoming Long-range Skorpion fire.
Please exercise caution.
I'm sending you the probable locations of their spotters.
Three locations.
Confirm and eliminate them.
Gunslinger, heading 030.
Four rooftop units, distance 1200.
Roger. I'm on it.
Handler One, directional laser-based data
transmissions can reveal our location.
Please limit yourself to verbal
communication during operations.
I'm sorry.
The next set of observers
will be appearing soon.
Keep me informed of their location.
Understood!
There's an awful lot
of them today, Undertaker.
A turkey shoot, right?
Just enjoy yourself.
You're right, there's a lot more Löwes than expected.
It'll be problematic if they exploit our cover.
We should start by whittling down their numbers.
You make it sound easy.
I'll handle the Löwes.
Take command and deal with the rest.
Roger that. Alderecht's going give us shit again after this one.
Undertaker, what are you doing?
So this is... Undertaker?
Handler One to all units!
Incoming Long-Range Skorpion fire.
Please exercise caution.
29 mai, anul stelar 2148
I'm sending you the probable locations of their spotters.
Three locations.
Confirm and eliminate them.
Handler One, directional laser-based data
transmissions can reveal our location.
Please limit yourself to verbal
communication during operations.
I'm sorry.
The next set of observers
will be appearing soon.
Keep me informed of their location.
Understood!
anul stelar 2139, nine years ago...
War was declared on the Republic of
San Magnolia by the neighboring Empire of Giad.
They began their invasion with their
autonomous combat machines, the Legion.
However, in reality,
Giad has seemingly lost control of the Legion and was likely wiped out four years ago.
Thus the Legion, with their hard coded lifespan of 50,000 hours, or a little under six years,
will completely shut down within two years.
Therefore, you recruits will only have
two years before the war ends,
But during that time, we hope you'll do your best to fulfill your duties.
After all, the Republic's Juggernauts
are vastly superior autonomous units
compared to the Legion.
There has not been a single casualty since their introduction.
That's not true, people have died!
Today, we have a real Handler
who serves as a command and control officer for the Juggernauts.
This is Vladilena Milizé.
She wants to speak to you.
What I'm about to tell you
is the true history of the Republic.
Nine years ago, the Republic's regular army
was brought to the point of collapse
in just a little over two weeks
by the Legion's overwhelming firepower.
The Republic's government went on
to make two decisions.
The first was to withdraw of all its citizens
into 85 administrative Sectors.
The other was to pass the
Special Wartime Peace Preservation Act.
This law stripped citizenship and all rights
from anyone who did not have silver hair
and eyes like us Alba.
They would no longer be considered human,
and instead would be kept
in carefully monitored internment camps
outside the 85 Sectors.
And due to that, as you're all aware,
the now supposedly empty area
became known as the 86th Sector,
and the people who live
there became known as Eighty-Six.
There they were forced to build
the fortress Gran Mur,
the wall isolating the 86th Sector,
and to pilot the Juggernauts.
There are humans inside the Juggernauts!
But because the ones inside,
the Eighty-Six, aren't "human,"
we say they're autonomous!
And even as we speak, they're out there,
surrounded by Legion and fighting!
The news you see every morning isn't true.
People are dying!
Dozens can die in a single battle.
But they're not human, right?
They're humanoid pigs that failed to evolve.
They're human!
I fight with them every day!
You say you fight with them.
But have you ever gone to the battlefield?
I have, just once.
Even though I was on the battlefield, I didn't fight.
The only ones who risk their lives
in battle are the Eighty-Six,
the people we stripped their rights from.
You can't do this, Major!
I told you not to say anything that sounds
like you've sided with them!
Sir, what does our nation's flag stand for?
What do you...
Freedom, equality, brotherhood,
justice, and nobility.
And those apply only to humans!
The Eighty-Six look human, but they aren't!
You mustn't misinform my students!
The Eighty-Six are teenage
boys and girls, just like us!
But they don't enjoy the same entertainment
and luxuries that we do.
They can't laugh innocently
the way we do.
We can't leave them all alone!
Even though we can't see them,
if we listen carefully,
we can hear the voices
of these nameless soldiers!
As segregated as we are, we gaze upon the same stars!
And you told the new recruits that?
Yes.
Will you be able to get off the hook this time?
Don't worry.
I'll get Uncle Jérôme to back me up.
You're surprisingly sly when it comes to these things.
You're being protected, huh?
It's not too late to correct the Republic's foolish ways!
Right, right.
So, how was your meeting
with the infamous Undertaker?
We're communicating regularly.
We synchronize with the Para-RAID nightly.
Nightly?
What do you talk about?
All sorts of things.
Some of which isn't work nor mission related.
Even apart, our hearts are connected.
I told you not to get too attached.
A capable leader with solid combat skills,
who's a little reckless, but bold.
He's a very good soldier.
Undertaker isn't as scary as they made him out to be.
That's just what you think, right?
Your heart rate's elevated.
Raport postoperațiune
This, too...
And this, and this...
Jeez...
Para-RAID, activate.
Synchronization target: Spearhead Processor.
Okay, one hit on King Bear,
two on Bunny Knight.
29 mai, anul stelar 2148
Haruto gets seven points!
I missed two shots, huh?
I guess handguns really aren't my thing.
Fido set the can sideways! Kaie!
Kaie Taniya, initiating mission!
What do you think?
Grid point 208.
That's what that Handler woman said, right?
It would've been the optimal location had we not already deployed.
Next, Kurena!
Fido, don't line them up! Throw them!
Yeah. It's such a by the books answer
that it makes me hurl,
but I guess she's not just some spoiled rich kid.
Raiden, you're up!
Okay!
But how long can she keep up?
Hey, Kitty!
Here you go.
Thanks.
Anju!
I'll help you.
Thanks!
Oh, okay.
I'm handing out Anju's cake!
Yay!
Is it a good book?
Not particularly. Focusing on something helps distract me from it.
I see.
Thank you, for always doing this.
Shin, it's your turn!
At least stand up! You're no fun!
All units, may I have a word?
A whole week, a new record.
It's fine.
Handler One, good work today.
Yes, you too.
You all seemed to be having a lot of fun.
We were just killing time.
Don't worry about it.
I see.
By the way, Undertaker,
I need to scold you today.
What is it?
I've read the after action reports,
that you've filed since you've been appointed as Spearhead's Captain,
and they were all the same.
Why do you care
what happens on the front lines?
You sure like to waste your time.
It's a Handler's job to analyze the tactics and formations used by the Legion.
I understand that you didn't send them
because we don't read them.
That's our fault, so I'm not mad.
But from now on, do it properly.
I'll read them.
I'm not good at reading and writing.
Well, its not like there's a school in the camps.
I'm sorry!
Well, it's more of a "too lazy to"
than a "not good at."
Right, Undertaker?
Undertaker?
All right.
Send me one for all your missions
up to this point as well.
Will footage from the gun camera do?
No, write them.
If we can analyze them,
we can come up with countermeasures.
You're an elite unit,
so your records are especially valuable.
We can lower the attrition rate
across the whole battlefield,
including your unit. So please lend me a hand.
So young.
No, I'm about the same age
as all of you.
How long has it been
since you joined the military?
We're all in our fourth year, or so?
Undertaker's been here the longest.
It's his fifth year.
So Undertaker's almost done with his service, right?
Is there something you want to do
when you leave the army
and become a Republic citizen again?
Somewhere you want to go, or want to see?
I've never thought about it.
I see.
But you might want
to start thinking about it now.
You might come up with something.
Sunt sigură că va fi distractiv.
Poate că ai dreptate.
"Nu vreau să mor."