30 octombrie, anul stelar 2148
Nu vrea să mai miște!
Nici al meu! Voi ieși din cabină!
Ascundeți-vă în spatele
Distrugătoarelor. Încă se trage spre noi.
Kurena, ești bine?
Dacă te poți mișca,
ascunde-te în spatele mașinăriei!
La naiba! Am fost lovit!
Oare până aici ne-a fost?
Shin!
Ești sigur în legătură cu asta?
Da, nu-l putem lua cu noi în starea în care e.
Măcar atât putem face pentru el.
În plus...
nici noi nu vom mai putea înainta prea mult.
Doar al lui Shin a supraviețuit, nu?
Încă avem puștile și pistoalele, dar...
Nu prea mai avem muniție, nu?
E groaznic că ne-am pierdut acele containere.
Majoritatea muniției și combustibilului au fost distruse de flăcări.
Să nu uităm de mâncare!
Da, și mâncarea!
Eu am terminat aici.
Vom mai aveți?
Totul este gata.
Atunci, haide să pornim.
Dacă nu plecăm repede de aici,
Legiunea ne va găsi din nou.
Așa este.
Cine va pilota?
Nu-l putem lăsa doar pe Shin să piloteze, știți?
În acest caz, haideți să facem cu rândul.
Sunt de acord.
Dar de ce a trebuit să supraviețuiască cel al Groparului?
E vreo problemă cu asta?
Da, Shin și-a modificat parametrii, deci controlul e așa de sensibil încât e  înfricoșător.
În plus, a dezactivat și majoritatea limitatoarelor.
Atunci, voi fi eu prima.
Nu, o voi face eu.
Nu erai tu cel care se
plângea acum câteva clipe?
Oricum, eu am fost doborâtă prima,
deci nu sunt obosită deloc.
În regulă. Putem fi de acord că dacă dăm peste Legiune, cel care pilotează va și lupta?
De acord.
Și eu sunt!
Kurena, oprește.
E o peșteră în acele stânci la ora 10.
Du-ne acolo.
Recepționat.
Cât mai repede.
I-am evitat mulțumită lui Shin.
Totuși, erau o grămadă.
Mi se pare mie sau vedem
tot mai multe în ultimul timp?
Bănuiesc că ne apropiem de baza lor.
Așa este.
Toată lumea, priviți.
Imperial City First Elementary School
Oare e cumva o școală?
Ce? Serios?
Probabil.
Oh, that's right, You haven't been to school before have you Kurena?
I guess you can still recognize a school,
even across borders and cultures.
So this is a school...
Hey, let's camp here tonight!
Let's do it.
Can you read that, Kurena?
Not at all.
But it looks like they were having fun.
This brings back so many memories.
Did you like studying?
Not at all.
Raiden Shuga!
Huh? Is Raiden absent today?
Present!
Okay.
Theoto Rikka.
Here!
Kurena Kukumila.
Present!
Anju Emma!
Present.
Shinei Nouzen!
If we're not going to study,
these are just firewood.
I see.
Is this something special, too?
Tearing down the school, maybe?
Alright, what should we use for kindling?
Wait, aren't those textbooks?
I feel kind of guilty.
Books we can't read are useless.
That's right.
Well done!!
You still have some left?
Yeah.
This is the last one.
No more after dinner desserts!
31 octombrie, anul stelar 2148
That's the last of it.
We'll be lucky if it lasts the day.
Yeah.
I guess our fun little hike is finally coming to an end.
We're heading out!
Okay!
It's my turn this morning, right?
Yeah. Thanks.
We graduated from school in a single day, huh?
Wow, we must be really smart!
We've got bright futures ahead of us.
Hey!
We have to scale this?
Don't ask me.
Is this right?
We keep going forward, right?
Yes.
Roger.
Anju, let's switch soon.
It's still early, isn't it?
It was supposed to be my shift until lunch.
I'm bored.
You scared me!
How silly!
Yeah, I didn't think we'd have so much free time.
There's nothing to do but look at the scenery.
Shin should've grabbed a book
while we were at the school.
Yeah.
Good work.
I didn't really do too much work though.
We're all set here, Shin.
Then let's have Kurena be on watch.
No way! Take my place—
The one piloting fights.
That's what we agreed upon, right?
You knew from the start!
There's a unit that we can't avoid no matter what we do.
And if we can't avoid them, we'll have to fight.
So that's why you switched places...
That's not fair, Shin!
You can't do this!
You guys keep going.
They won't find you if you hide in the forest.
Keep moving forward and the Legion's voices disappear.
If anyone's alive out there, ask them for help.
Stop screwing with us!
That means you're going to be a decoy, right?
We were going to do this together, right?
And in the end, you're...
going off by yourself.
That's not fair!
Damn it! He cut us off!
That idiot!
Wait!
I'm going, too.
You're sure, right?
We can't let Shin go by himself, right?
You're right.
That ultra-long range cannon from before...
I'll kill you.
The men, the women, the children,
the old, the nobles, the peasants...
No matter who you are,
I'll kill anyone who threatens the princess!
Of all times...
They're after my head, huh?
Shin!
Shit! Look at me, damn it!
I'm coming!
Don't give up!
Get moving!
Shin! Shin!
Can you hear me?
Shin, answer me!
You're all fools.
You can't beat the Legion with those weapons.
I'm out!
Theo!
Damn it!
Fools...
You really are... fools.
When I'm part of the Legion...
whose name will I call out?
13 octombrie, anul stelar 2148
Fido's not here.
They took him with them.
So he wasn't a dog after all.
Major Milizé, was it?
Yes.
What brings you to a place like this?
You're under house arrest, aren't you?
Yes.
Which gives me time to visit the frontlines.
Along with the next group to be executed?
I heard the rumors, but you're really a weirdo.
Go see it.
Not that they left much behind.
Okay.
I've been seeing the kids off
on their final march for a while.
But this is the first time I've seen a Handler visit.
Lieutenant Aldrecht, are you...
An Alba. Just like you.
My wife was an Eighty-Six.
After they took my wife and daughter,
I dyed my hair and went after them.
I volunteered, to earn their rights back.
But they got sent off
to the battlefield and never returned.
After Shin arrived here, I ended up asking him
if he heard any Legion out there looking for
a shithead who couldn't protect his wife and daughter.
And what would you have done if there were?
I'd go out there and let 'em kill me.
But he said that he didn't.
There weren't any Legion calling my name.
I could live with myself after that.
My wife and daughter weren't stuck
on the battlefield even after death.
I'll see them once I go to the other side...
I'm sure they're waiting for me.
I make sure to tell them I'm an Alba before they leave on their Special Reconnaissance mission.
I tell them that they have the right to hate us.
They can even kill me if it'll make 'em feel better.
But they never do.
Not this time, either.
So I'm still here after all this time.
I've kept you too long.
Get going.
Thank you.
Yeah, we keep it at the barracks.
It's a black cat with white paws.
And for whatever reason, it's taken a liking to Undertaker more than anyone else.
He doesn't play with it at all.
It rubs up against him all the time,
and he just pats it once in a while.
It probably thinks he's just a good bed.
Just look at it now.
Yeah, it doesn't move when he's reading.
It'll never get along with
Black Dog, though. He's too annoying.
That's mean! And not fair!
I demand you take that back!
Boo! Boo!
What's its name?
Blackie.
Whitey.
Two-Tone.
Kitty.
Shrimp.
Autor: Erich Maria Remarque
Remarque.
Don't name it after the author of
whatever book you're reading now.
And what are you even reading?
If you actually went through the trouble of finding this,
you're one crazy dumb ass.
Raiden Shuga.
I wrote down everyone's names for you.
I bet you're crying your eyes out right about now
because you can't tell which of us is which.
Theoto Rikka.
Ai grijă de pisicuță.
You might as well, since you insist on being a saint.
Kurena Kukumila.
We still haven't decided on a name yet.
Give it a cute one, okay, Major?
Anju Emma.
One day, if you make it to our final destination...
would you please leave flowers?
Shinei Nouzen.
Și eu trebuie să merg înainte.
Ei au crezut în mine până la final.
Să mergem.
Ce nume ar trebui să-ți pun?
Voi lupta...
până când însuși destinul va veni să mă ia.
Voi lupta până la final.
Shin...
Îmi cer scuze.
Te-am tot strigat și
te-am făcut să vii până aici.
Haide să mergem.
Episod special
Roșul macilor cuprinde câmpul de luptă
"Roșul macilor cuprinde câmpul de luptă."