What's the difference?
June 15th, Stellar Year 2148
We were thrown out on the battlefield.
Treated as weapons.
Forced to fight.
You get to watch us from afar;
hiding behind the safety of the walls.
Ordering us around without batting a goddamn eye.
That's you right now.
If that's not treating us like pigs, then what is?
You think that being kind is the
be-all and end-all?
I'm baffled that you think you're treating us as humans.
You've never once asked us
for our real names!
Theo.
Raiden! Are you seriously
going to defend this white pig—
Theo!
Fine.
Handler One, kill the synchronization.
The battle's over. You have no
obligation to remain connected.
Laughing Fox went too far,
but that doesn't mean we're in the mood to chat with you.
I'm sorry.
I don't want to die.
I'm sorry, Kaie.
I was just like those white pigs,
and dishonored your death.
No matter how hard I wish nothing ever changes
aigan shitemo konganshitemo kawaranai yamou
No matter how hard I wish nothing ever changes
A flower blooms only to be crushed
aigan shitemo konganshitemo kawaranai yamou
fuminijirareru dake no hana
A flower blooms only to be crushed
No matter how hard I wish nothing ever changes
aigan shitemo konganshitemo kawaranai yamou
fuminijirareru dake no hana
No matter how hard I wish nothing ever changes
aigan shitemo konganshitemo kawaranai yamou
A flower blooms only to be crushed
fuminijirareru dake no hana
A flower blooms only to be crushed
fuminijirareru dake no hana
No matter what happens I'll never forget your voice
anata no koe wo wasure wa shinai darou
No matter what happens I'll never forget your voice
anata no koe wo wasure wa shinai darou
Swept up and scattered by the wind
kaze ni fukarete chirijiri ni natte
Swept up and scattered by the wind
I can't see the future in your reflectionless eyes
kaze ni fukarete chirijiri ni natte
sono konkontaru suishoutai ni wa utsuranai mirai mirai
I can't see the future in your reflectionless eyes
Swept up and scattered by the wind
kaze ni fukarete chirijiri ni natte
sono konkontaru suishoutai ni wa utsuranai mirai mirai
Swept up and scattered by the wind
kaze ni fukarete chirijiri ni natte
I can't see the future in your reflectionless eyes
sono konkontaru suishoutai ni wa utsuranai mirai mirai
shou
I can't see the future in your reflectionless eyes
sono konkontaru suishoutai ni wa utsuranai mirai mirai
No matter how hard I wish nothing ever changes
aigan shitemo konganshitemo kawaranai yamou
No matter how hard I wish nothing ever changes
A flower blooms only to be crushed
aigan shitemo konganshitemo kawaranai yamou
fuminijirareru dake no hana
A flower blooms only to be crushed
No matter how hard I wish nothing ever changes
aigan shitemo konganshitemo kawaranai yamou
fuminijirareru dake no hana
No matter how hard I wish nothing ever changes
aigan shitemo konganshitemo kawaranai yamou
A flower blooms only to be crushed
fuminijirareru dake no hana
fuminijirareru dake no hana
A flower blooms only to be crushed
Bystanding, revolting, willful ignorance
boukan shiteiru zouhan shiteiru minai furishiteiru
Bystanding, revolting, willful ignorance
That's you, that's the person I see
boukan shiteiru zouhan shiteiru minai furishiteiru
sonna anata wo boku wa miteiru
That's you, that's the person I see
Bystanding, revolting, willful ignorance
boukan shiteiru zouhan shiteiru minai furishiteiru
sonna anata wo boku wa miteiru
Bystanding, revolting, willful ignorance
boukan shiteiru zouhan shiteiru minai furishiteiru
That's you, that's the person I see
sonna anata wo boku wa miteiru
That's you, that's the person I see
Don't worry, ease up why don't you
sonna anata wo boku wa miteiru
anshinshinayo bokutachi minna itsudatte
Don't worry, ease up why don't you
That's you, that's the person I see
sonna anata wo boku wa miteiru
anshinshinayo bokutachi minna itsudatte
That's you, that's the person I see
sonna anata wo boku wa miteiru
Don't worry, ease up why don't you
anshinshinayo bokutachi minna itsudatte
an
shin
Don't worry, ease up why don't you
We're all guilty in the end
anshinshinayo bokutachi minna itsudatte
yarukoto wa onaji sa
We're all guilty in the end
Don't worry, ease up why don't you
anshinshinayo bokutachi minna itsudatte
yarukoto wa onaji sa
Don't worry, ease up why don't you
anshinshinayo bokutachi minna itsudatte
We're all guilty in the end
yarukoto wa onaji sa
We're all guilty in the end
yarukoto wa onaji sa
Go! Go! Go!
June 16th, Stellar Year 2148
You can do it!
Theo!
Get him!
Sorry...
Theo!
Next! Next!
Put your back into it!
Whitey!
C'mon, don't move Whitey!
Theo, your cat's looking like a fox. Plus it's lookin' a little scary.
And it's not even laughing!
Aren't you supposed to be the "Laughing Fox?"
Shut up.
Are you bothered by
what you said to that woman?
No way!
Well, it bothers me.
Yup.
Theo...
Don't move!
It bugged me how this one fell off.
Also how he only has one button done.
Who cares?
It fits you perfectly, though!
Whatever!
That wasn't like you yesterday.
That wasn't a good way to say it,
but you were reminded of Fox,
your first captain, right?
Guys, give it a rest.
Well, we're all jealous,
because you have someone to look up to.
What's this about?
Someone who'll always be important to you.
I've never had someone like that.
Listen up Shin.
You'd better not break it next time!
Behave yourself until we get our next shipment!
I'll try.
Hey, Theo.
Don't do anything stupid like him.
Damn you kids!
He looked like he was about
to burst a vein, as always.
I'd like to keep him from getting mad,
once in a while.
That'll never happen.
Thank you.
What would the captain
have said to that Handler?
The Fox captain?
Yeah. Would the captain have gotten mad?
Well, it doesn't matter.
She probably won't try to
synchronize Para-raids ever again.
That deluded white pig. Trying to be a saint.
The captain wouldn't have said that.
Isn't that what you think?
Kirschblüte
Do you need something, Handler One?
June 16th, Stellar Year 2148
In the end, this just shows
that you're a Republic citizen.
And you need to accept
that we live in separate worlds.
No, that's wrong.
I could never forgive myself if I did that.
In that case, what do you plan to do?
Go to the 86th Sector
and fight alongside them?
You can't do that.
What you should be doing
is spoiling yourself right now.
I made too much pudding.
Annette, I'm sorry, but I'm not in the mood.
That's not healthy.
This world is a wonderful place,
where you can sneak in a pudding snack
in the middle of the day.
It's not wonderful.
Not at all.
Why is it such a big deal
that you didn't ask for their names?
You don't need to know them.
You're never going to meet them.
Henrietta Penrose.
What?
That's your name.
I know your name. We're friends.
So what?
A name is who you are.
And I didn't even think of that.
I wasn't treating them as human.
You're overthinking this.
You and the Eighty-Six aren't even friends.
But we're all human!
If you really thought that,
you would've asked their names right away.
You know? This is a good
opportunity to take a step back.
Why are you so set against them?
Because there's nothing I can do.
We have pudding here and they don't.
We're different from them.
In every way.
So getting involved will only lead to regret.
But—
Lena, the war's already started.
There's no going back to how things were.
Just quit being a Handler
and join us in R&D.
I told you...
I can't quit being a Handler.
You should listen when
your best friend gives you advice,
Vladilena Milizé.
Let's go to the battlefield.
And see everything that's happening.
We're at war, right, Father?
That's right.
And we're doing something even worse.
Something worse?
Yes.
We have to bring this to an end.
Quickly.
Could you take us a bit closer
to the forward operating base?
Yes sir, Colonel.
What's wrong?
Uncle...
I still can't forget it.
The last place my father took me.
The battlefield of the 86th Sector.
I'm sad about what happened to him.
But I'm glad I could see it.
Glad?
Yes.
Because I got to see the 86th Sector
with my own eyes.
I was able to learn the truth
about this country.
I was able to grasp the ideals
that the Republic threw away.
So...
Václav was a kind man who wanted
to make the Republic a better place.
I'm sure he was a good husband
and a good father.
That's why he decided to teach you
the truth about this country.
As a friend, it's a pity
that the Legion stole from us
a man with such a strong sense of justice.
But there's something he didn't realize.
What was it?
Just like the rest of the Republic,
he did nothing but watch idly.
In the end, talking about equality means nothing
if you're not the one fighting.
He felt, subconsciously, that only
the Eighty-Six die on the battlefield.
That's why he was able to take
you to the battlefield.
The fact that he did something so reckless
for the sake of his ideals
proves his ignorance and stupidity.
Lena, I don't want you to end up like him.
Enough of this.
You're doing a good job.
It's also my responsibility
for giving you a tough unit to deal with.
I wanted you to feel for yourself
the reality of this nation.
But you don't need to force yourself
if it's too much for you.
No, I'll continue to act
as Spearhead's Handler.
What does the Republic flag stand for?
Freedom, equality, brotherhood,
justice, and nobility.
What are you—
Are you upholding them?
Look at the real world.
Such beautiful things are nowhere
to be found in the Republic.
You're a little too focused on attaining ideals.
For others, and yourself.
Ideals are ideals precisely
because they are unattainable.
If you're aware that those ideals are impossible to attain,
don't you think it would be a foolish and cowardly endeavor to seek them out?
Here's today's update on the war
from San Magnolia Military HQ!
We were thrown out on the battlefield.
Treated as weapons.
Forced to fight.
You get to watch us from afar;
hiding behind the safety of the walls.
That's you right now.
If that's not treating us like pigs, then what is?
Our forces suffered minimal losses with no human injuries or deaths!
Do you think we're out here fighting
because we want to?
Defending the nation with our advanced
You locked us out here! Forced us to fight!
and ethical drones, have resulted in zero Republic casualties!
You've caused the deaths of millions
over the last nine years!
The day when the righteousness
of our nation smashes
And you do nothing to stop it.
You think that if you just act nice
and talk to us every day,
the evil remnants of the
wicked Empire is not far off!
that counts as treating us
as human, don't you?
All hail the Republic of San Magnolia!
Glory to the five-colored flag!
You're not cut out for that job.
You should let someone else take your place.
Not that way! Kirschblüte!
Before you regret it.
I don't want to die.
Para-RAID, activate!
Synchronization target:
Undertaker!
War Cemetery
Do you need something, Handler One?
Undertaker, can we talk for a moment?
Go ahead.
I'm sorry...
About yesterday. And everything before.
I'm really sorry.
I'm Lena. My name is Vladilena Milizé.
I know I should have asked sooner, but...
Would you please tell me your names?
If you're bothered by what
Laughing Fox said to you,
then you can rest easy.
What he said doesn't reflect what we all think.
You're not personally
responsible for our situation.
And we understand you
don't have the power to change it.
You don't need to blame yourself
for not doing the impossible.
But it was rude not to ask your names.
There was no need to ask.
Why do you think it's required
to use call signs on the Para-RAID,
even though the Legion can't intercept it?
And why the Processors'
personnel files restricted?
So Handlers won't have to think
of Processors as human, right?
Yes.
Most Processors die within a year.
They assumed the deaths of so many
Processors would be too much to bear.
But that's cowardly! I...
And I was, too.
Honestly, I was going to run away.
But I don't want to keep running forever.
So please, tell me your names.
Your real names!
Kirschblüte, the girl who died yesterday,
was Kaie Taniya.
Wehrwolf, our vice captain, is Raiden Shuga.
Laughing Fox is Theoto Rikka.
Snow Witch, Anju Emma.
Gunslinger, Kurena Kukumila.
Black Dog is Daiya Irma...
That's all of them.
Thank you very much.
Please, call me "Lena."
I've been told your name.
What's your rank?
Major. I was just promoted, though.
I'll call you Major Milizé
from now on, then.
Is that okay?
Yes.
What are you doing?
Leaving Kaie's name behind.
Eighty-Six don't have proper graves.
So in my first unit, we all made a promise.
When someone died, we'd carve their name
into a fragment of their Juggernaut,
and the survivors would carry it.
So that the last of us to survive
would take the others to their final destination.
I was the last. I've always been the last.
So that's my job in this unit, too.
You've been doing that for five years.
How many have died?
Five hundred sixty-one.
Including Kaie.
And all of them...
I remember them.
Because I have to take them with me.
Everyone who died fighting alongside me.
Until I reach my final destination.
And that's why you're "Undertaker."
That's part of it.
I've never faced those who've died under me, I've only felt sorry.
I'm sorry. Truly.
If it's possible,
I'd like to directly apologize to everyone.
Shall I connect you then?
R-Right now?
No, I'm fine.
One moment please.
One,
two,
three,
we
made
it
through
two,
three,
we
made
it
through
Four
and
five,
five,
Light up the fleeting night's sky
with
light
dle
it
with
light
and bid farewell to the eternal dusk
Heed those doubtless words
Stand
up
and
get
a
start
up
and
get
a
start
At your own pace!
no
mu
ku
ma
It’s
de
pen
ding
on
your
heart
de
pen
ding
on
your
heart
Can
take
shi
vers
of
your
scar
take
shi
vers
of
your
scar
Draw upon the ever-expanding world
One day, must I part with those I admire
Raise
your
hands
up
to
the
sky
your
hands
sion
As I close my eyes, the Vision
sion
Guides us to the future
Trou
Trou
ble
ma
ker
How’d
you
know
’bout
my
fe
ver
you
know
’bout
No matter how young the night is
The answer lies elsewhere
Raise
your
hands
up
to
the
sky
your
hands
sion
Unraveling dimensions
sion
Opening new pages
Trou
Trou
ble
ma
ker
How’d
you
know
’bout
my
fe
ver
you
know
’bout
No matter how much I love you
I can't say it out loud
All personnel...
I'm sorry about yesterday,
and for the way I've behaved until now.
My name is Vladilena Milizé,
the Handler of your unit.
I wasn't treating you like humans.
And I didn't even realize it.
It's only natural you would reject me.
But, if you're willing to hear me out,
then please tell me your names.
I bet Shin already told you, right?
What a pain.
He did.
But you didn't tell me yourselves.
Couldn't you have kept your mouth shut?
You regretted it, right?
Maybe not what you said,
but how you said it.
The mark on my Juggernaut is a laughing fox.
But it was passed down to me.
From who?
The captain of the first unit I was attached to.
A captain so cheerful and optimistic
it was almost stupid.
He was a soldier, so he was stupidly strong.
And an Alba, like you.
He was a weirdo who said it wasn't right
to make the Eighty-Six fight alone,
and returned to the battlefield.
We hated him.
But he never left.
And in the end, he died.
He stayed behind to cover the other
Processors and was killed.
I'm not asking you
to do the same thing he did.
But as long as you're inside the walls,
we'll never be equals.
And we won't accept you as one of us.
That's all.
So he's one of the good people
Kaie was talking about.
It's not just him.
She was referring to everybody
who fought their hardest.
In this crappy world that
their fellow Alba created.
Okay, I'm done talking.
Oh, I'm Theoto Rikka.
Call me "Theo," "Rikka," or
"cute shitty pig," whatever you want.
I'm sorry for the way I acted.
Enough, get over it already.
Vice Captain Raiden Shuga.
Yes.
First, let me apologize.
Your nightly calls - we called you a wannabe saint and a hypocritical pig.
We mocked you; called you an idiot for how ignorant you were to your own pig-like hypocrisy.
I apologize for that. I'm sorry.
And now that that's been said,
As Theo said, we don't think of you
as an equal or a comrade.
You idiotically stomped on our faces
while lecturing us with platitudes.
That's a fact that'll never change.
That's how we'll always see you.
If that's okay with you,
we'll keep talking with you to kill time,
but personally, I don't recommend it.
You're not cut out to be a Handler.
You should quit.
If it will help you pass the time,
I'll keep calling.
So you're a moron, too, huh?
Oh, right, send that map.
You were too busy crying yesterday
to send it, right?
I'll send it!
Bye, Major Milizé!
This has been Daiya Irma.
Haruto. Nice to meet you.
Anju Emma, Major!
Kurena Kukumila.
I'm Lecca!
Chise.
Kino!
Thank you, everyone.
I'm sorry, Undertaker.
Yes?
You haven't told me your name.
Did you not want to give it?
No, I'd just forgotten.
I'm sorry.
It's Shinei Nouzen.
Nouzen?
Is something wrong?
Do you know someone named Shourei Nouzen?
His personal name was Dullahan,
and his mark was a headless knight.
He's my brother.
I'm with you.