Hello, Handler One.
May 22nd, Stellar Year 2148
This is the Captain of the Spearhead Squadron.
Personal Name: Undertaker.
We've received word about the Handler change.
We look forward to working with you.
As do I.
Nice to meet you, Undertaker.
No matter how hard I wish nothing ever changes
aigan shitemo konganshitemo kawaranai yamou
No matter how hard I wish nothing ever changes
A flower blooms only to be crushed
aigan shitemo konganshitemo kawaranai yamou
fuminijirareru dake no hana
A flower blooms only to be crushed
No matter how hard I wish nothing ever changes
aigan shitemo konganshitemo kawaranai yamou
fuminijirareru dake no hana
No matter how hard I wish nothing ever changes
aigan shitemo konganshitemo kawaranai yamou
A flower blooms only to be crushed
fuminijirareru dake no hana
A flower blooms only to be crushed
fuminijirareru dake no hana
No matter what happens I'll never forget your voice
anata no koe wo wasure wa shinai darou
No matter what happens I'll never forget your voice
anata no koe wo wasure wa shinai darou
Swept up and scattered by the wind
kaze ni fukarete chirijiri ni natte
Swept up and scattered by the wind
I can't see the future in your reflectionless eyes
kaze ni fukarete chirijiri ni natte
sono konkontaru suishoutai ni wa utsuranai mirai mirai
I can't see the future in your reflectionless eyes
Swept up and scattered by the wind
kaze ni fukarete chirijiri ni natte
sono konkontaru suishoutai ni wa utsuranai mirai mirai
Swept up and scattered by the wind
kaze ni fukarete chirijiri ni natte
I can't see the future in your reflectionless eyes
sono konkontaru suishoutai ni wa utsuranai mirai mirai
shou
I can't see the future in your reflectionless eyes
sono konkontaru suishoutai ni wa utsuranai mirai mirai
No matter how hard I wish nothing ever changes
aigan shitemo konganshitemo kawaranai yamou
No matter how hard I wish nothing ever changes
A flower blooms only to be crushed
aigan shitemo konganshitemo kawaranai yamou
fuminijirareru dake no hana
A flower blooms only to be crushed
No matter how hard I wish nothing ever changes
aigan shitemo konganshitemo kawaranai yamou
fuminijirareru dake no hana
No matter how hard I wish nothing ever changes
aigan shitemo konganshitemo kawaranai yamou
A flower blooms only to be crushed
fuminijirareru dake no hana
fuminijirareru dake no hana
A flower blooms only to be crushed
Bystanding, revolting, willful ignorance
boukan shiteiru zouhan shiteiru minai furishiteiru
Bystanding, revolting, willful ignorance
That's you, that's the person I see
boukan shiteiru zouhan shiteiru minai furishiteiru
sonna anata wo boku wa miteiru
That's you, that's the person I see
Bystanding, revolting, willful ignorance
boukan shiteiru zouhan shiteiru minai furishiteiru
sonna anata wo boku wa miteiru
Bystanding, revolting, willful ignorance
boukan shiteiru zouhan shiteiru minai furishiteiru
That's you, that's the person I see
sonna anata wo boku wa miteiru
That's you, that's the person I see
Don't worry, ease up why don't you
sonna anata wo boku wa miteiru
anshinshinayo bokutachi minna itsudatte
Don't worry, ease up why don't you
That's you, that's the person I see
sonna anata wo boku wa miteiru
anshinshinayo bokutachi minna itsudatte
That's you, that's the person I see
sonna anata wo boku wa miteiru
Don't worry, ease up why don't you
anshinshinayo bokutachi minna itsudatte
an
shin
Don't worry, ease up why don't you
We're all guilty in the end
anshinshinayo bokutachi minna itsudatte
yarukoto wa onaji sa
We're all guilty in the end
Don't worry, ease up why don't you
anshinshinayo bokutachi minna itsudatte
yarukoto wa onaji sa
Don't worry, ease up why don't you
anshinshinayo bokutachi minna itsudatte
We're all guilty in the end
yarukoto wa onaji sa
We're all guilty in the end
yarukoto wa onaji sa
May 22nd, Stellar Year 2148
Good work out there.
Likewise.
The new one sounds like a real doozy.
The new Handler. Did you forget already?
Shin! Shinei Nouzen!
You fucked it up again you little shit!
Old man Aldrecht's about to go off again.
You need something?
"You need something" my ass!
How the hell do you come back with a trashed unit every time?
I keep tellin' you they've got weak legs!
Stop pushin' them so hard!
Sorry.
We're basically out of spares now!
We're hosed till we get another shipment!
Fido should've brought back Kujo's unit.
Yeah, 'guess we could scavenge parts from it.
But are you seriously okay with using parts from that unit? Someone died in that...
I guess it's a bit late for that.
Ain't that right, Undertaker?
Kujo was lucky to have served alongside you.
Same goes for the other Processors.
By the way, I heard about the Handler change.
How is she?
Fine.
What do you mean fine?
She synchronized to say hello,
and wants to maintain relations,
so she'll be in contact with us every day.
Pretty rare for a Republic soldier.
So she's a decent human being?
Must be hard livin' like that. Poor thing.
May 29th, Stellar Year 2148
Ready... Go!
Got it!
Yes!
There we go!
Big haul, huh?
We're gonna have a party tonight!
Ready to go, Fido?
We're not bullying you.
You'd better rat us out to Shin, got it?
Is that a yes or a no?
To everyone in the scavenging party,
can you hear me?
What's up, Theo?
The forecast changed.
Rain's coming.
Eintagsfliege.
The signal jamming units, huh?
That means our radars are already down.
When will they get here?
About two hours from now.
Roger. Heading back.
There's no Shepard this time.
They're probably relying on simple brute force.
Just Sheep?
It'll be a turkey shoot.
We're all here.
Attention!
I'll explain the situation.
Enemy rearguard units have formed up with the units to our immediate front.
They're likely resupplying.
Once complete, they'll attack.
We'll set an ambush along their route at grid point 304.
We'll create a kill zone on Main Street,
and neutralize the bulk of the enemy forces.
Even in spring, it gets cold without the sun.
It gets pretty cold in here despite how snug the cockpit is.
Well, the armor's paper-thin
and has plenty of gaps in it.
Plus they're slow.
And break easily.
Yup. It's a piece of shit.
Handler One to all units:
It appears that enemy units are approaching.
Deploy to grid point 208 and intercept them!
Undertaker to Handler One:
We've already deployed.
We'll intercept them further ahead at grid point 304.
That's fast.
You're as good as they say, Undertaker.
Here they come.
The Legion's out in full force again, huh?
Scout Type: Ameise
Well, they're mostly Ameise.
They're easy to destroy,
but those things sure are annoying.
Dragoon Type: Grauwolf
Grauwolfs? What a pain.
I guess we have to take this seriously.
Screw Löwes. I hate them.
Tank Type: Löwe
The Löwe's main gun is twice as powerful as ours, if not more.
It'll knock you out in a heartbeat.
Electronic-Disruption Type: Eintagsfliege
All right, time to get to work.
Open fire.
Third platoon, lure the enemy and withdraw to the southeast.
Fifth platoon, hold your current positions.
When the enemy force enters the kill zone,
coordinate your fire.
Black Dog, roger.
Snow Witch, reload while you can.
Snow Witch, roger.
As always, thanks.
Laughing Fox, likewise.
Watch your fire, Black Dog!
All units, cease fire! Spread out!
Handler One to all units!
Incoming long-range Skorpion fire.
Please exercise caution.
I'm sending you the probable locations of their spotters.
Three locations.
Confirm and eliminate them.
Gunslinger, heading 030.
Four rooftop units, distance 1200.
Roger. I'm on it.
Handler One, directional laser-based data
transmissions can reveal our location.
Please limit yourself to verbal
communication during operations.
I'm sorry.
The next set of observers
will be appearing soon.
Keep me informed of their location.
Understood!
There's an awful lot
of them today, Undertaker.
A turkey shoot, right?
Just enjoy yourself.
You're right, there's a lot more Löwes than expected.
It'll be problematic if they exploit our cover.
We should start by whittling down their numbers.
You make it sound easy.
I'll handle the Löwes.
Take command and deal with the rest.
Roger that. Aldrecht's going to give us shit again after this one.
Undertaker, what are you doing?
So this is... Undertaker?
Handler One to all units!
Incoming long-range Skorpion fire.
Please exercise caution.
May 29th, Stellar Year 2148
I'm sending you the probable locations of their spotters.
Three locations.
Confirm and eliminate them.
Handler One, directional laser-based data
transmissions can reveal our location.
Please limit yourself to verbal
communication during operations.
I'm sorry.
The next set of observers
will be appearing soon.
Keep me informed of their location.
Understood!
Stellar Year 2139, nine years ago...
War was declared on the Republic of
San Magnolia by the neighboring Empire of Giad.
They began their invasion with their
autonomous combat machines, the Legion.
However, in reality,
Giad has seemingly lost control of the Legion and was likely wiped out four years ago.
Thus the Legion, with their hard coded lifespan of 50,000 hours, or a little under six years,
will completely shut down within two years.
Therefore, you recruits will only have
two years before the war ends,
But during that time, we hope you'll do your best to fulfill your duties.
After all, the Republic's Juggernauts
are vastly superior autonomous units
compared to the Legion.
There has not been a single casualty since their introduction.
That's not true, people have died!
Today, we have a real Handler
who serves as a command and control officer for the Juggernauts.
This is Vladilena Milizé.
She wants to speak to you.
What I'm about to tell you
is the true history of the Republic.
Nine years ago, the Republic's regular army
was brought to the point of collapse
in just a little over two weeks
by the Legion's overwhelming firepower.
The Republic's government went on
to make two decisions.
The first was to withdraw of all its citizens
into 85 administrative Sectors.
The other was to pass the
Special Wartime Peace Preservation Act.
This law stripped citizenship and all rights
from anyone who did not have silver hair
and eyes like us Alba.
They would no longer be considered human,
and instead would be kept
in carefully monitored internment camps
outside the 85 Sectors.
And due to that, as you're all aware,
the now supposedly empty area
became known as the 86th Sector,
and the people who live
there became known as Eighty-Six.
There they were forced to build
the fortress Gran Mur,
the wall isolating the 86th Sector,
and to pilot the Juggernauts.
There are humans inside the Juggernauts!
But because the ones inside,
the Eighty-Six, aren't "human,"
we say they're autonomous!
And even as we speak, they're out there,
surrounded by Legion and fighting!
The news you see every morning isn't true.
People are dying!
Dozens can die in a single battle.
But they're not human, right?
They're humanoid pigs that failed to evolve.
They're human!
I fight with them every day!
You say you fight with them.
But have you ever gone to the battlefield?
I have, just once.
Even though I was on the battlefield, I didn't fight.
The only ones who risk their lives
in battle are the Eighty-Six,
the people we stripped their rights from.
You can't do this, Major!
I told you not to say anything that sounds
like you've sided with them!
Sir, what does our nation's flag stand for?
What do you...
Freedom, equality, brotherhood,
justice, and nobility.
And those apply only to humans!
The Eighty-Six look human, but they aren't!
You mustn't misinform my students!
The Eighty-Six are teenage
boys and girls, just like us!
But they don't enjoy the same entertainment
and luxuries that we do.
They can't laugh innocently
the way we do.
We can't leave them all alone!
Even though we can't see them,
if we listen carefully,
we can hear the voices
of these nameless soldiers!
As segregated as we are, we gaze upon the same stars!
And you told the new recruits that?
Yes.
Will you be able to get off the hook this time?
Don't worry.
I'll get Uncle Jérôme to back me up.
You're surprisingly sly when it comes to these things.
You're being protected, huh?
It's not too late to correct the Republic's foolish ways!
Right, right.
So, how was your meeting
with the infamous Undertaker?
We're communicating regularly.
We synchronize with the Para-RAID nightly.
Nightly?
What do you talk about?
All sorts of things.
Some of which isn't work nor mission related.
Even apart, our hearts are connected.
I told you not to get too attached.
A capable leader with solid combat skills,
who's a little reckless, but bold.
He's a very good soldier.
Undertaker isn't as scary as they made him out to be.
That's just what you think, right?
Your heart rate's elevated.
After Action Report
This, too...
And this, and this...
Jeez...
Para-RAID, activate.
Synchronization target: Spearhead Processors.
A faint light points ahead
To shadows stalled in a silent haze
si
lent
lent
So scattered and carved
Can you still smile after seeing the true world?
Don't
you
get
there?
It
calls!
you
get
there?
It
calls!
The sky I look up to changes in color
heart
can
hear!
E
chos!
na
ked
heart
can
hear!
E
chos!
Avidity that I sought without even realizing it
Whis
per
your
name
a
gain
per
your
name
a
gain
Then
re
start
it
right
a
way
re
start
it
right
ter,
co
lor,
ar
dor,
wan
der
my,
bit
ter,
co
lor,
ar
dor,
wan
der
Got
to
feel
feel
The freedom of the sky we saw that faithful day
Okay, one hit on King Bear,
two on Bunny Knight.
May 29th, Stellar Year 2148
Haruto gets seven points!
I missed two shots, huh?
I guess handguns really aren't my thing.
Fido set the can sideways! Kaie!
Kaie Taniya, initiating mission!
What do you think?
Grid point 208.
That's what that Handler woman said, right?
It would've been the optimal location had we not already deployed.
Next, Kurena!
Fido, don't line them up! Throw them!
Yeah. It's such a by the books answer
that it makes me hurl,
but I guess she's not just some spoiled rich kid.
Raiden, you're up!
Okay!
But how long can she keep up?
Hey, Kitty!
Here you go.
Thanks.
Anju!
I'll help you.
Thanks!
Oh, okay.
I'm handing out Anju's cake!
Yay!
Is it a good book?
Not particularly. Focusing on something helps distract me from it.
I see.
Thank you, for always doing this.
Shin, it's your turn!
At least stand up! You're no fun!
All units, may I have a word?
A whole week, a new record.
It's fine.
Handler One, good work today.
Yes, you too.
You all seemed to be having a lot of fun.
We were just killing time.
Don't worry about it.
I see.
By the way, Undertaker,
I need to scold you today.
What is it?
I've read the after action reports,
that you've filed since you've been appointed as Spearhead's Captain,
and they were all the same.
Why do you care
what happens on the front lines?
You sure like to waste your time.
It's a Handler's job to analyze the tactics and formations used by the Legion.
I understand that you didn't send them
because we don't read them.
That's our fault, so I'm not mad.
But from now on, do it properly.
I'll read them.
I'm not good at reading and writing.
Well, its not like there's a school in the camps.
I'm sorry!
Well, it's more of a "too lazy to"
than a "not good at."
Right, Undertaker?
Undertaker?
All right.
Send me one for all your missions
up to this point as well.
Will footage from the gun camera do?
No, write them.
If we can analyze them,
we can come up with countermeasures.
You're an elite unit,
so your records are especially valuable.
We can lower the attrition rate
across the whole battlefield,
including your unit. So please lend me a hand.
So young.
No, I'm about the same age
as all of you.
How long has it been
since you joined the military?
We're all in our fourth year, or so?
Undertaker's been here the longest.
It's his fifth year.
So Undertaker's almost done with his service, right?
Is there something you want to do
when you leave the army
and become a Republic citizen again?
Somewhere you want to go, or want to see?
I've never thought about it.
I see.
But you might want
to start thinking about it now.
You might come up with something.
I'm sure it'll be fun.
You may be right.
I don't want to die.