Ciclopul către supervizorul unu:
Au ajuns deja la vechiul terminal de tranzit de mare viteză din punctul 122.
Scuze, radarele noastre erau bruiate și nu am reușit să-i detectăm până în ultimul moment.
Asta va fi o luptă grea pentru nou-veniți.
Ce plan ai?
Mergeți cu toții în punctul 062
și trimiteți o unitate ca să le ademenească.
Asta îi va aduce în fața altileriei rămase.
Deci ne vom lupta cu ei fix înaintea de bazei noastre, nu?
Dacă vor trece de noi, tot ce va rămâne sunt minele și artileria ca să-i oprească, nu?
Așa este, dar dacă vrem să supraviețuim, asta e cea mai bună variantă.
Bine, Maiestate!
Now for today's update on the war
from San Magnolia Military HQ!
The pride of our nation, the Juggernaut, has intercepted
2 decembrie, anul stelar 2148
and decimated their forces causing them to withdraw.
Defending the nation with our
advanced and ethical drones,
has resulted in zero Republic casualties!
The day when the righteousness of our nation smashes the evil remnants of the wicked Empire is not far off!
All hail the Republic of San Magnolia!
Glory to the five-colored flag!
Hei, este prințesa distrugătoare de păpuși!
Am auzit că ai reușit să învingi Legiunea și astăzi,
o victorie pătată de sângele acelor porci.
De asta e cunoscută drept Regina Pătată de Sânge sau Regina Sângeroasă!
Ai găsit care este diferența între oameni și porci?
Vai, are mereu aceeași expresie.
La ce naiba se gândește?
A fost retrogradată pentru acei porci...
Și poartă o uniformă neagră când nimeni altcineva nu o face...
Legiunea nu va mai exista în doi ani!
Vine dintr-o familie faimoasă și bogată, nu?
Dacă s-ar comporta cum trebuie, ar avea o viață foarte ușoară.
'Neața.
În legătură cu lucrul despre care mă întrebasei, vreau mai întâi să mă asigur de ceva.
Setările suplimentare ale dispozitivului RAID.
Foarte bine.
Voi ajunge acolo în două ore.
Bine, ne vedem acolo.
De câte ori trebuie să-ți spun, căpitan Milizé?
Folosirea neautorizată a artileriei, trimiterea de provizii neplanificate
și trimiterea de ordine către unități care nu sunt sub comanda ta.
Ai idee câte plângeri primesc?
Nu-mi da mai multă muncă doar de dragul acelor rezidenți ai Distructului 86.
Dacă mi-ai dat permisiunea anticipat,
nu ai fi nevoit să te confrunți cu asemenea lucruri, locotenent-colonel.
Ce vrei să spui?
Tu și ceilalți vă puteți plânge cât doriți,
dar nu o să-mi peste câtuși de puțin de ceea ce spuneți.
Nemernico!
Cunoaște-ți locul! Ești doar un căpitan!
Ești sigur că vrei asta?
Realizările tale sunt bazate pe performanțele subordonaților tăi.
Ce?
Eu am cele mai bune performanțe dintre toți supervizorii.
Dacă voi începe să distrug mai puține unități ale Legiunii și promovarea ta va fi afectată.
Nu-i așa?
Ai grijă cum vorbești, căpitane.
Scuză-mă, locotenent-colonel.
Te voi lăsa pe tine să te ocupi de provizii.
Bine.
Captain, am verificat artileria zonei de luptă a Districtului 8 din regiunea sudică.
Exact cum ne așteptam, doar douăzeci la sută mai sunt funcționale.
Nu mă surprinde.
Iar rata de uzură de pe câmpul de luptă...
Hei, priviți!
Priviți! Ninge!
Chiar a venit iarna, nu?
Ciclopul către supervizorul prim:
Mă recepționezi?
Da. Ce este?
Am dat peste o formație inamică în timp ce patrulam.
Avem nevoie de ordinele tale.
Am înțeles.
Vă rog să continuați investigația.
Ciclopule, raportează situația.
Îmi cer scuze că am întârziat.
Ai venit destul de devreme, nu?
Haide să ne vedem de discuția noastră, Lena.
Bine.
Am înțeles. Mulțumesc pentru raport.
Desigur. Voi aștepta aproximările tale în ceea ce privește puterea Legiunii, Maiestate.
Da, mă voi strădui.
Let's both work together to do our best.
Desigur.
Doar ești supervizorul nostru. Ne bazăm pe tine.
Și eu mă bazez pe voi.
Am nevoie de informațiile tale de pe câmpul de luptă, Ciclopule.
Știi, nu ar fi momentul să-mi folosești numele adevărat?
Dacă nu intenționezi să o faci, atunci de ce ne-ai mai întrebat?
Shiden Iida
Deoarece...
asta e responsabilitatea mea ca supervizor.
Mereu ești așa serioasă și formală, știi?
Crezi ce dorești.
Totuși, mulțumită ție vom reuși să trăim puțin mai mult.
Apreciez efortul, dar vom ajunge în escadronul Vârf de Lance în câteva luni.
Cel mai puternic tip pe care-l știu a fost trimis în misiunea specială de recunoaștere acum ceva timp.
Probabil e mort acum.
Decapitatul zeu al morții care-și prefera mereu lamele.
Care crezi că va avea loc primul? Misiunea noastră de recunoaștere sau atacul Legiunii?
Nu știu.
Dar treaba mea acum este să vă pregătesc pentru marele atac al Legiunii, care va veni.
M-am hotărât deja să vă ajut, dar...
în cele din urmă, nu contează.
Și o vei face indiferent?
Da.
Dar, Ciclopule, nu uita să-mi trimiți raportul patrulării.
Recepționat!
În orice caz, mi-au spus să supraviețuiesc.
Au crezut în mine și mi-au spus să lupt și să supraviețuiesc.
Teppy
To live up to the hopes of those
who are no longer with us...
Shin!
Eu doar până aici pot merge.
You can go the rest of the way yourself, right?
Ai camarazi alături de tine acum.
Chiar ai crescut.
Nu lăsa ca amintirea mea să te tragă în jos.
Mă poți uita.
De fapt...
Vreau să-ți amintești de mine, din când în când.
Trăiește liber și găsește-ți fericirea...
Și din când în când, știi?
Doar din când în când.
Ai grijă de tine.
Și găsește-ți fericirea.
Frate!
I'm aware, it'll just be a few words.
You've just woken up?
Greetings.
To start, would you please tell me your name?
Right!
You see, the generals are really cautious
and forced me to wear this hazmat suit.
But this is no way to greet someone, right?
My name is Ernst.
And yours?
Shinei Nouzen.
Welcome to the Federal Republic of Giad!
"Giad"?
Oh, I should explain.
The Empire of Giad that created the Legion was
overthrown and reformed into a Federal Republic.
Because of that, we're also fighting
the remaining Legion, though.
When we found you, you were captured
by the Legion on our western front.
Sorry, sorry.
Of course you'd be worried.
You were sleeping so we turned the windows opaque.
We're still not sure
what happened before we found you.
If you do happen to remember anything...
Sir! That's enough for now.
Sorry!
The scary lady's going to get mad at me,
so I'll be going.
But remember this.
You're the first foreign visitors we've had
since our nation's founding.
And we were too busy fighting the Legion
so we don't have any procedures in place for this.
But don't worry, we will not harm you.
I'm Ernst Zimerman,
the provisional President of the Federal Republic of Giad.
What does our analysis show?
It's safe to say they aren't agents
of San Magnolia or any other country.
And what about them being a new Legion type
or carrying a new type of Legion bioweapon?
Our initial scans and test shows no abnormalities.
And the Legion unit that captured them?
It's an older model, but is undoubtedly a Dinosauria.
And the object attached to their ears?
They stated it was a communication device.
It creates a mental link between devices
and is reminiscent of that certain family's ability.
How revolutionary.
The safest option for the Federacy
would be to eliminate them
Shin,
you were out for three whole days.
Seriously, Kurena was bawling her eyes out.
I-I was not!
Shin, I know now's not a good time,
but you'd better ready yourself once you're better.
Sorry, but we all feel the same way.
If you ever pull that shit again,
I will kick your ass.
I didn't mean to die—
You're going to make me mad.
Even if you didn't mean to die,
you knew it'd probably happen if you went out there.
I'm sure we've all been in that position at least once...
But that's why we can't forgive it!
Because we understand!
It's not fair.
Never do that again!
I was so worried!
Sorry.
But who knows what happens now...
So yeah, starting from today,
you're all citizens of the Federacy!
Huh?
We haven't seen you for a month,
and the first thing you say is "So yeah"?
Really?
You sure you want to make a bunch of strange kids
who were kicked out of their old country into citizens?
Wouldn't it be safer just to kill us?
Is that what you want?
What benefit do you get from saving us?
A society that refuses to save children
because there's no "benefit"
is a society that benefits no one.
And if humanity can't survive without
killing children because they're "strange,"
then humanity doesn't deserve to survive.
Anyway, I'll be assuming the role
of your guardian for a while.
So rest a bit and see this country for yourself.
Then you can decide what you want to do.
Baza Sankt Glykine
The war machines we recovered, the "Juggernauts..."
2 decembrie, anul stelar 2148
Capabilities aside, their combat logs are amazing.
I'd like to speak with them.
Hey, we're already involved with them.
We won't let you have them.
What?
High-mobility combat data and the personnel who generatepd that data.
They're a perfect fit to operate my prototypes.
They'd be wasted on those slow Vánagandr.
What did you say, spider woman?
What did you say, beetle?
You're all free to speak with them.
But I won't let them be operators.
If we did, we'd be no different from the Republic.
But they're all saying in their counseling sessions
that they want to go back to the battlefield.
That's because the battlefield
is all they know right now.
Actions should be met with rewards.
Since they've fought for so long,
they should be offered a chance at peace.
Especially since their homeland refused to do it.
I want the Federacy to be just, at least.
Because...
that is the ideal of mankind.
Let us save our pitiful comrades!
Let's save them!
The Eighty-Six are victims!
Victims!
Let us save our pitiful comrades!
They were all happy when you were rescued,
Let's save them!
because they've finally learned
that another country had survived.
But when they learned how you were treated,
they became overcome with the desire
to save you and your comrades.
This is my house, but from now on it's your home.
Welcome!
Hurry up!
Push that desk!
We need to hurry!
Welcome, poor souls who were banished
from your country!
The great Giad welcomes you with pity and compassion!
We don't expect any kind of recompense
from low-borns like you,
so your thanks are enough!
Hey, red-eyes!
Why are you looking away?
I thought there might be someone else here.
You already shut the door!
Are you making fun of me?
Yes.
This is the problem with low-born people
from the Republic.
Is this your daughter?
It might be rude of me to say it but
you probably need to discipline her better.
Oh, no.
She's not my daughter.
Do you really think I'm the daughter
of this lowly bureaucrat?
I'm—
Frederica Rosenfort.
Some things happened, and now she's staying here.
It's annoying to explain to everyone,
so officially speaking she's my daughter.
But regardless, you'll be living together for a while.
So I'd appreciate it if you'd think of her
as a slightly naïve little sister.
"Little sister," huh?
Oh, on paper I've also adopted you all too.
So you can call me "Dad," if you want.
I'm just joking.
What's that on your neck?
Stop that Frederica.
I've already explained their situation.
You also have wounds you'd like to keep to yourself.
I'm the cute little sister
you've been given to heal your wounds.
The family and home and happiness you lost...
The noble and compassionate
Federacy is willing to give you.
Be very nice to me!
Big brothers and sisters!
Theresa, they're being mean!
Right, right.
Frederica, everything that just happened
was your own fault.
Was not! Was not!
Eu sunt Theresa. Voi avea grijă de voi.
Welcome home, everyone.
I'm bored.
They all went to sleep so early.
Sorry, I know you're tired.
I was holding on to this.
It was in your war machine.
Is it yours?
Yes.
Thank you, Theresa.
Not at all, sir.
Kids that age eat a lot.
It's fun to cook for them.
I'm sorry.
This is likely to be difficult.
Not at all.
Serving you is my job.
Do you despise me for trying to
compensate for things like this?
That I'm using them as replacements?
No. They could never replace them.
Every person is their own,
irreplaceable individual.
But still, people try to bury the past.
In whatever way they can.
Whom are you talking to,
Empress?
Kiri...
It's too late.