Tayiri    Tayiri Castle    Irityrdia-Worshiping Nation
To think that Cuscull's wretched mages
would defeat us so soundly.
Reust    Tayiri Crown Prince
I'll marshal the troops yet again
and personally take command this time...
Prince Reust.
Could you be...
What do you want?!
Accursed Witch of the Azure Moon!
Tris    Cuscull Mage
Hey, what's with that attitude?
Show Lady Aeterna some respect!
Shush, Tris.
What?
Pamyra.
What? Hey!
Ah, wait!
Everything will end in two weeks.
I'd like for you to hold off on
marching into Cuscull until then.
What?
What's the meaning of this?!
Come down here if you want to ask me a favor!
You lowly mage!
Lowly mage, you say?
Can't you see that stance is what's
brought these events upon you?
Mages disrupt the world of the one
true god, Irityrdia, with their powers!
Have you ever swung your sword
down on an infant's skull?
What's this now?
Or burned alive a mother
clinging to her crying child?
Tayiri is the one who has tolerated these acts.
None other than your very own nation.
As successor to the throne, you've studied
history and how other nations govern.
Three hundred years
have passed since the Dark Age.
No other nation as fiercely
ethnocentric as yours has survived.
What you're doing is akin to
eating away at your own innards.
I'm sure you can understand that much.
Lady Tinasha, we must be going.
I've warned you.
Give it some good thought.
Wait, I'm not done talki—
~ The End of the Dream ~
Cuscull Castle    Nation of Mages
The Four Great Nations joining forces?
How over the top.
Even though it's meaningless.
There.
The new map of the mainland
will look like this.
I-Is it really possible to create a spell
that covers the entire mainland?
Don't worry.
We have Aeti.
No matter how large or complex
the composition of the spell,
with enough magical power,
you can construct it piece by piece.
I taught you that a long time ago.
You were an excellent student.
So open-minded.
Always quick to pick up on
what you were taught.
Far surpassing me...
What's wrong?
Did you recall something?
I just can't do it.
It's like I'm still in a dream.
This is no dream.
I know that.
There's no need for any worry.
I'll be the one to protect you, Aeti.
About His Majesty's behavior earlier...
Renart.
Do you know why all the witches
of the mainland are women?
What?
Renart    Cuscull Mage
Men's bodies, magically speaking, are unstable,
and have difficulties
holding up over a long time.
So you mean His Majesty...
He's feeling the psychological effects.
With His Majesty in this state, a spell
composition covering the entire mainland...
It's possible.
If we use my magic.
But if it comes to fruition,
the mainland is sure to change drastically.
They were the ones who called me here,
so why are we not advancing?
It's been six days since we came to Tayiri.
Is it due to the crushing defeat
they suffered in the Asdra Plains?
We have combined forces
from all Four Great Nations now,
so I'm surprised at how cautious
Prince Reust is being.
Your Majesty!
Those mass disappearance cases...
The same thing's happened in Farsas!
While we're stuck twiddling our thumbs here,
cities in all Four Great Nations
have been attacked.
Do you think she's the one behind this?
If she wasn't, that'd be
troubling in its own right.
King Oscar!
It's Cecelia.
Do you have a moment?
Pardon my intrusion.
You visit me every day.
What are you after?
Young king of Farsas,
is there something wrong
with wanting to see you?
If you continue to be so cold,
I have some ideas of my own.
Oh? Like what?
That mage woman
who accompanied you in Farsas...
She was the Witch of
the Azure Moon, was she not?
Maybe they just look very similar.
I won't let you dodge me with that excuse.
I saw her again.
Where?
I find that hard to believe.
That woman visits my brother every night.
The nerve of that traitor.
It should almost be time tonight...
Show me the way to Prince Reust's room.
Dear brother, it's me.
What business have you here?!
Was it not Tayiri that asked me
to slay the witch?
Please wait!
What are you talking about?
Playing dumb will only
put you in a worse spot.
Stay away!
Akashia's wielder!
Pamyra    Cuscull Mage
You deceived us!
Come.
Oscar.
Lady Tinasha!
Let's withdraw!
Hurry!
It won't last for long!
Quickly!
Tinasha!
Thanks to Prince Reust,
we sure did waste a lot of time.
I'm curious what it means that the date
she specified has passed.
I went around checking all the towns.
What a pain!
So, what'd you find?
That girl sure is diligent.
It looked like everyone had disappeared,
but she had just put up a defensive barrier
so they couldn't be perceived.
Everyone in town is safe, even as we speak.
I see.
She won't protect herself.
You need to act as her shield.
Sure.
That's what happened.
Gandona General
Cezar General
That's a hard story to swallow at first glance.
Indeed.
Well, well.
It seems you're at a loss.
Pleased to make your acquaintance.
I am Bardalos, chief mage of Cuscull.
What?!
Blasted clown!
What do you want?!
Come now, calm yourselves.
I thought you'd want to watch our mighty king
extend his dominion over the mainland.
If I may have the honor of
guiding all of you there.
Who would agree to that?!
Don't get too full of yourself!
I understand.
Your Majesty?!
Take me there.
Why, I'd be happy to oblige.
However, all of you will be coming along.
I see.
The very definition of an ambush.
Lanak.
Welcome...
to the ruins of Tuldarr's cathedral.
Formerly Tuldarr    Cathedral Ruins
I've asked you to join us here today...
because I have a proposal.
Currently, the mainland is rife
with cruel discrimination and conflict.
However, let's put an end to all of it.
Those who don't comply,
no matter where they may be,
will instantly receive divine punishment.
I will gain the powers
needed to carry this out.
Are you trying to become a god?
Now then, let me introduce you to my bride.
Is something wrong, Aeti?
Why are they here?
I had Bardalos bring them there.
I wanted everyone to witness the moments
until the procedure is complete.
I see.
Silence swaying in the sea of lament.
I choose the countless outstretched hands.
I need an opening.
I am he who defines.
I command the first lake
to be born, Compassion.
Place yourself at daybreak.
The five magical lakes formed
from nature's energy and magic,
along with countless human souls.
I command the second lake
to be born, Jealousy.
Place yourself at morning.
If I can connect them again
through a spell composition...
I command the third lake to be born, Denial.
Place yourself at noon.
I can watch over the entire
mainland from right here.
I command the fourth lake to be born, Longing.
Place yourself at twilight.
I can even command the weather to my will.
I command the final lake to be born, Hatred.
Place yourself at midnight.
Not too shabby, huh?
Now, let us celebrate together...
the dawn of a new age.
A-Aeti, what are you...
Come.
What is the meaning of this?!
It took so long.
I had searched for you all this time.
When I found you, I was
so happy I could have cried.
You were truly necessary.
As the one who summoned the magical lakes,
you were the only one
who knew their defined names.
The souls of the citizens you killed
four hundred years ago,
who melted into and were bound
by the magical lakes...
Now I can finally free them!
Aeti...
Yet again, you would betray me?!
Betray you?
Come, let us begin your atonement.
Incapacitate her!
I don't care if she loses her limbs!
That's the same look you had back then.
Have you finally awoken?
Shut your mouth, little girl!
Ah, I knew it!
Pamyra. Renart.
Hurry up and run away.
No way.
I refuse.
Overwriting such an immense spell
and sublimating the magical lakes...
You're the only one who could pull it off!
Protecting you is our duty.
Pamyra!
You really did betray us?
How amusing!
Lady Tinasha!
Oscar!
Ask me for help already.
What should I do?
I just need ten minutes.
Got it.
The swordsman who wields Akashia?
I've heard the legends,
but how much of it is true?
Dunno. Never interested me.
It can't be!
Lady Aeterna would never betray us!
Summon the demons!
Kill them!
Take this!
It's...
It's your fault that my sister...
So these are the centuries of
accumulated sins that Tayiri bears?!
Die! You monster—
Save your contemplation for later!
Yeah...
Inscribed pacts woven of a voiceless voice.
Hope is born in the depths of despair.
A double incantation?
And what's more, this is...
From Tuldarr's...
The flow of time is irreversible, and
the sea that holds it forms consciousness...
coronation ceremony!
Aeti...
It couldn't be...
The spirits of Tuldarr allegedly
summoned by their first ruler?
I thought that was just a myth!
Controlling multiple high-ranking
demons is impossible!
And twelve of them in all...
There's no way.
The end is nigh.
What a shame, just when I'd come
face to face with the mage killers.
Don't worry. I'm keen to end it here, too.
If you want to end it, then come at me.
Go on, burn to cinders.
I'm here.
Though distant the day it began,
ye be unchanging.
So?
What are you going to show us?
Appear before me!
Spirits tied to Tuldarr by ancient pact!
I am Tinasha As Meyer Ur Aeterna Tuldarr!
As your ruler, my declaration defines you!
Come to me!
Twelve Spirits of Tuldarr
It's been a while since we emerged.
I command you.
Annihilate my enemies.
Feel free to ignore those
without the will to fight.
If you can, don't kill them.
Aeti...
Aeterna...
Oh, so we meet again.
What do you want?
Not much.
I just have one question.
If you want to know something, ask Aeterna.
Aeti knows everything.
That's why I'm met with pity.
If she had been weaker,
none of this would have...
It's her fault that Tuldarr was destroyed.
It's because of her that I'm...
She believed in you until the very end.
When you sliced her belly open...
What did you feel?
Nothing at all.
She's nothing but a tool.
King of Farsas.
As the wielder of Akashia,
you know what must be done.
It's fine, you two.
Thanks.
When you broke Lucrezia's spell,
do you remember what I said?
Tinasha!
You've come to?
I didn't expect you to sleep for a full week.
Why am I still alive?
Whoa there.
Cutting right to the chase?
If you weren't recovering,
I'd give you a noogie.
In the end, Prince Reust decided
not to initiate force on Cuscull,
leaving it as an autonomous state for mages.
What?
Your lecturing must have gotten through to him.
You... really think so?
A lot happened.
In the past, and the present.
Even so, I'm...
I see.
Oh, that reminds me.
You're officially my fiancée now.
Why's that?!
That was the only way to bring
you back alive in that situation.
There were those who wanted you dead,
but a lot more of them
wanted to use your powers.
And what about what I think?!
Well, now that it's come to this,
work hard for the remaining half a year.
As you wish, my contract holder.
Thanks.
~ Green Vines ~