West Yarda
Oscar.
How's it look?
This is probably the one.
The princess of Yarda who's gone missing...
is in the middle of that sandstorm,
in Cados Fortress.
Thank you for allowing us
this unannounced visit.
I'm Oscar Lyeth Increatos Loz Farsas.
Gait                              Nephelli    Princess of Yarda                         Iosef
It's a pleasure to meet you.
My name is Nephelli Initia Lyn Yarda.
They really found her.
First, let me say that Farsas has no intent
of making known our intervention here.
I hope you can say the same.
I understand.
But what is the king of Farsas doing here?
They're the ones who attacked us first.
Besides...
I'm the prime candidate
to be dealing with a witch.
What?
U-Um, are you saying that woman
who's cajoled the prince...
Is a witch?
That's right.
Wh-What does a witch want with us?
Leonora is the Witch Who Cannot Be Summoned.
True to her name,
she shows up without any invitation.
You were simply unlucky.
Now then, how do we lure Leonora out?
Once she finds out I've come
into contact with Princess Nephelli,
I'm sure she'll be here in no time.
We could also get rid of this sandstorm
around the fortress, just to make sure.
Leonora's got a short temper,
so winning will be easy.
I'd say you have a short temper, too.
By the way, when I visited
the royal court of Yarda just now...
What?!
Did I hear that right just now?
Ow, ow, ow!
Look, even if we kill Leonora,
there's no guarantee it'll stop the
civil war she's been orchestrating!
We need to delay it somehow.
Be more specific.
I teleported most of the faction leaders
out to the borders of Yarda.
The mages have had their powers sealed,
and the army's out of commission
thanks to laxatives.
You're pretty ruthless yourself...
The king had fallen ill
from potions, so I cured him.
Also, I talked briefly with Prince Savas.
With my brother?!
Yes.
He seems to be regretting his actions,
so I think he'll buy us time.
That's a fair bit of meddling you've done.
All in a day's work cleaning up after a witch.
And so, we'll have Leonora meet her end here.
~ Castle of Sand ~
I see. Thanks.
Will the spirits be able
to handle the demons there?
They say they can, so I'll leave it to them.
You fought her once before, right?
How did it go back then?
I won.
What do you need me to do?
Let me see.
Can you take care of Unai?
Leonora had him absorb a demon, so he
boasts outlandish, inhuman physical strength.
Don't worry.
I'll take him down with ease.
Stop acting all on your own.
I can't forgive the one
who tried to kill you.
Stop that.
Why?
Find the right time and place for that!
Got it.
You don't get it at all!
I'd regret it if I stopped now
and died tomorrow.
Don't be so ominous!
I don't believe it!
The sandstorm... is gone.
It should be an hour at least
until Leonora gets here.
Go wake yourself up and come back.
Pamyra, if you would.
As you wish.
Unai!
I'm here.
Unai    Servant to Leonora
They stopped the sandstorm.
We're going to go kill that woman.
Get yourself ready.
As you wish.
I feel alert now.
I just can't stand being
woken up by someone else.
I should have slept by myself.
If you had, I would have woken you up.
I took the liberty of going first.
It's fine...
Lady Tinasha, your neck...
I'm so sorry.
Why are you with that man?
Are you planning to manipulate him,
like that witch did to my brother?
Oh, my apologies.
Ignore what I said.
Manipulate him?
He doesn't listen to a thing I say.
I'd say he's the one in control of me.
Princess Nephelli.
Do you want him for yourself?
If witches hadn't interfered...
she could have become the queen of Farsas.
If the Witch of Silence hadn't
placed that curse on Oscar...
If a protector by the name of
Tinasha had never shown up...
If Leonora hadn't set her sights on Yarda...
The fates of humans are strange indeed...
And witches toy with them as they like.
That's why I...
Wretched child.
You're scared of people?
You don't want to touch
or be touched by anyone?
Live life a little more freely.
Do as you like.
We have the power needed to do so.
I'd never even dreamed of it.
That anyone would desire me as a fellow human.
It's fine.
I can stand proud.
I can face her now.
It's been exactly one hour.
Well...
I'll be off.
You're late.
Sorry.
What's this?
If anything happens, pull on this.
The sensation will transfer to this one.
The sensation will transfer?
That's it?
That's more than enough.
Got it.
That'll do.
Tinasha.
Yes?
Once this fight is over...
What is it?
Why don't we get married?
Fine by me.
I accept.
Are you serious?
Of course.
Now I can't afford to lose.
Were you planning to lose before?
Okay, time for this war to begin.
There's too many of them.
It's been so long, little girl.
I've come to show myself.
Are you happy now?
Don't you worry about Unai.
My man will entertain him.
How cheeky, coming from a spirit sorcerer
stripped of her purity.
It gave me a chance to reorganize my spells.
I'm dying to test them out.
How foolish.
I'll live my life however I want!
Strike true!
I need to deliver a deadlier blow, huh?
"Inhuman" is a fitting word here.
Try as you might, it's all futile!
You're bound by your human limits.
Why don't you try me, then?!
Not bad, little girl.
This much is nothing special.
We're both witches here.
I'm well aware of that.
Much more than you are.
So why don't I show you?
You and that lukewarm life you've lived...
Here's what a real witch can do!
That which is changing and nonexistent...
Cease to fluctuate.
Destroy your form.
Reach your finite limits.
Appear before me, my eternal stone.
Oscar!
I'll teleport you...
Blood-red butterflies?
The Amber Castle...
Beautiful, isn't it?
I made it a long time ago.
You trapped all the humans inside, too?!
Oscar!
Meaning, be destroyed!
Let my intentions alter this world!
Be destroyed!
Did she do something?
Sorry, but if I don't get back soon,
my cat's going to be very angry with me.
You really have been a wretched child
these four hundred years.
This is what happens
when you grow attached to a human.
Learn your place, winged vermin!
I'll tear you into pieces.
Who did you say you'll kill?
Why, you...
I'll make you regret ever becoming a witch.
I want to kill her.
I can do it!
That's what these powers are for!
Oscar!
I'm going to set aside my hatred for you.
Why?
With all that power at your command...
I'll beat you with my mind at ease.
Come here.
Let's have some fun.
What's wrong?
Giving up already?
No.
I just happen to know.
Know what?
She'd never lose to anyone.
She seems really angry.
Also...
What's with that injury?
Sorry.
I'll treat it later.
Hmph!
It's like you're a run-of-the-mill woman.
How low you've fallen.
It looks like we see things differently.
For me, he's the reason
I can stay a decent person.
How utterly absurd!
Leonora can quickly
heal herself after most attacks.
Her magic increases
as long as this castle's here,
so a drawn-out battle is not in our favor.
That's why...
It's about time we end this fight.
How pointless!
I wouldn't call it pointless.
Craft as many spells you want,
but they're meaningless in this castle!
Die!
Unai...
You switched your places?
I'll be taking a short nap...
Is it all over now?
Yes...
It's all over.
Leonora has been slain.
You'll hold up your end of our promise, right?
I understand.
As long as your blood runs in their veins,
I won't lay a finger on Farsas.
I'd rather you leave them alone regardless.
What will you do now?
Let me see...
I'll live my life with him, then die.
The bride is that infamous witch, right?
What do you think she's like?
I bet she's dressed in all black,
wrinkly, and absolutely terrifyi—
Lady Tinasha.
Please try and smile a little.
That's a difficult order.
Missy!
Saye!
Wait, no!
So you were the witch, Lady Tinasha?
Yes, that's right.
When I grow up, I'll become a soldier!
I'll become strong enough to protect you!
I look forward to it.
Lavinia    Witch of Silence
[Lavinia. It's been a while.]
[Did you come to see him? Or kill him?]
[I'm just here to get a look
at his eccentric bride.]
I, Oscar Lyeth Increatos Loz Farsas,
take thee, Tinasha As Meyer Ur Aeterna Tuldarr,
as queen of Farsas, granting you
all rights as my lawfully wedded wife.
I hereby accept.
I pledge upon my name and blood
to take thee as my husband
and bestow upon thee all that is mine.
Your Majesty, I am your witch.
And you are my king.
As a witch, I give you my undying love.
To think that I really
did end up changing my mind...
I love you, Oscar.
~ Two Joined Memories ~