Tuldarr    Treasury
This place is a treasure trove!
Well, it is the treasury.
Let's decide what we're
going to take back to Farsas.
I'll bring any dubious items back to my tower,
so please separate those as well.
Yes!
I'll do my best.
Huh?
Where have I seen this before?
I'll bring it back to the tower for now.
~ Green Vines ~
Minnedart Fortress    Eastern Farsas, Bordering Yarda
Are things the same around the eastern border?
Edgard    Farsas General
No signs of unusual movements
from neighboring nations,
although there are minor conflicts.
Galen    Farsas General
A nearby village was attacked
by horse riders a year ago.
We sent out soldiers as fast as we could,
but most of the townsmen were killed,
so we brought the survivors here.
Horse riders...
You mean the Ito?
Yes.
Nomads who swiftly rush in
to plunder all they can.
Elze!
That's Elze, the village chief's widow.
He died protecting her,
and she hasn't laughed since.
Poor girl.
Nowadays, she spends
all her time playing with the children.
Once upon a time, when our village
was in the grasslands,
there lived a very
beautiful girl in the village.
She had countless young suitors, but she
would not take one as her husband.
I bet there were no good men there!
Shh.
One day, the village was attacked
by evil men on horseback.
They set fire to the houses, burning
the village down to try and kill its people.
But then there appeared
a swordsman clad in blue.
He chased the evil men away
and saved the girl from being abducted.
Deeply moved, she asked
to take his hand in marriage,
but he turned her down
and left without a trace.
The end.
The swordsman's so awesome!
Hey! Let's have a pretend fight over there!
Yeah!
Me too!
My apologies.
I was curious about the story you told them.
This story is actually based on a true tale
of two hundred years ago from our village.
The blue swordsman claimed to be
the son of the girl he saved.
Um...
You mean he had come from the future?
Yes, that's right.
The blue swordsman was the child of the girl
and a nomad who abducted her back then.
He said he traveled to the past
to change his mother's misfortune.
If he changed his past,
he would cease to be born.
But knowing this, he still saved his mother.
That's how the story goes.
What would you have done?
If it was me...
I wouldn't change the past.
You've outdone yourself.
I wasn't sure what we'd do when I heard
they only had one room available,
but I didn't think you'd
turn yourself into a cat.
Sharing a room is perfect,
since I can tell if you sneak out at night.
You really don't trust me, huh?
I don't know why you think I would.
Are you going to spend
all of tomorrow like this?
What's wrong?
I synced with them!
Synced?
Calm down and explain yourself.
I fell into a deep sleep and tuned
into a matching dream frequency.
What does that mean?
In this fortress, someone is broadcasting
a dream with strong emotions while asleep.
It's most likely someone with magical power,
who never learned to control it.
What kind of dream was it?
A dream of someone they hate and can't forget.
I hear our neighbor Yarda has been
turning into desert more and more lately.
Yes.
For now, there haven't been
any conspicuous movements,
but we'll continue to keep an eye out.
Please do.
We should get back.
We still need to visit all the villages.
The Ito, huh?
Stay still, Tinasha.
Be a good girl.
My name is Javi.
I'm the leader of the Ito.
There's something you have that we want.
Pretty demanding for a thief.
I have no qualms about taking all of you out.
It's clear that your threats are empty.
Say what you will, but plundering
is our clan's way of life.
The strong take for themselves.
We take pride in our way of living!
What do you want?
A woman.
A woman?
The woman I failed to kidnap a year ago.
With her as the prize...
we'll have a duel on the red rock plateau!
It's like a cage for a giant.
This land is sacred to the Ito.
It's said that a god visited
this place long ago.
A god?
Aetea? Or one of Aetea's children?
Neither.
The name has been lost.
A god from another land.
Another land?
I sense something strange with this place.
I can teleport everyone,
so why don't we do this somewhere else?
Like the castle training grounds?
That sounds interesting,
but our opponents won't oblige.
We just need to hurry up and win.
If I win this duel, I forbid you
from ever looting on Farsas land.
You can imagine what awaits you if you do.
Have you heard the details?
Th-That man killed my husband.
He must be someone you hate.
I-I...
It's been a while.
I'm here for you.
Begin!
This duel's over.
Time to keep your promise.
Elze...
So it was her dream.
Tinasha, can you reattach his arm?
No thanks.
Then at least stop his bleeding.
That should do it.
Get away from there!
What's going on?
I'll teleport them.
This isn't good.
We need to stop that thing.
Yeah.
Tinasha?
That's...
Tinasha!
Are you okay, Tinasha?
No...
No?
No, no, no!
I hate being wet as a cat!
What's wrong?
Calm down a little!
Just turn back into a human!
What exactly is this place?
I'd like to know as well.
Are you okay?
You looked like you weren't
feeling well earlier.
That was because of
outside magical interference.
Some sort of power from the earth
attacked the magic in my body.
It felt like it was digging through my insides.
I was too creeped out to form any spells.
Ito Sacred Grounds
We're directly under the Ito sacred grounds.
Is this their history carved into the walls?
"Past"...
"Magic spheres"...
"Memories of a clan"?
Oscar.
This must be the visiting god
that attacked us earlier.
"The deity from the north found the devil
fiends hiding among humans and killed them."
"All gave thanks to the deity,
but with fear in their hearts."
"They made a place for it to rest," it says.
"Devil fiend" is a pejorative term for
mages used in the early Dark Age.
At the time, mages weren't treated as humans.
This god reacted to magic
and revealed any mages,
so the Ito must have found it useful.
So they made their
sacred land its resting place?
But what could it really be,
if it reacts to magic?
It looked like mist, but is it a demon?
No, it's not.
That's not what this is.
Rity...di...?
Before it, those with magic find themselves
affected physically and mentally.
Their magic runs wild
and harms those around them.
You don't mean...
The deity worshiped by the powerful
nation to the north of the mainland:
Irityrdia, the one true god of Tayiri?
The one responsible
for the persecution of mages...
Oscar, could you wait here—
No thanks.
Of course!
I figured that was the case.
I want to teleport you back home
against your will!
Wait, are you going to be okay?
Aren't you going to react like you did earlier?
I'll put up a defensive wall.
I'm not a cat this time, either.
You don't have Akashia,
which is why I'm worried about you.
I'll borrow this, since it's right here.
Stay away.
If you reach your limit, you can turn back.
Elze.
She's been possessed by Irityrdia?
That's not good.
Hey, that's your move?
Not bad.
Are you okay?
Your face is pale.
It feels like I'm really seasick.
I don't feel anything like that.
Half of my magic was acquired after birth,
so I'm more easily affected.
Whereas your magic has been sealed away.
Sealed away?
I'd love to hear about that,
so I'll ask you later.
So?
Can we do something about
Irityrdia here without killing Elze?
It won't be easy.
It's strong against magic,
so we can't drag it out.
That said, it's impossible to destroy
what's inside without damaging her body.
Perhaps that human figure carved on
the wall was a possessed human as well.
First, we need Akashia.
It seems it has the power
to annihilate even Irityrdia.
Oscar.
Yeah.
But if I slice through Elze with Akashia,
she's good as dead.
Yes.
That said, if this being escapes from here...
I can't let you kill her.
I understand how you feel,
but it would be catastrophic to let her
outside while possessed by Irityrdia.
Just by going near her, those with magic
will end up dead or insane.
If a mage goes berserk, the people
around them will be in danger, too.
That thing is a phenomenon
that propagates innocent deaths.
Do you want to repeat the mistakes of history?
If you can't even understand that much...
we can start by killing you first.
I don't care who she kills, or how many people.
Please save her.
If you insist.
If I become a threat to the world...
would you please kill me?
Only if there was no way to change that fact.
I can keep fighting,
because that's how you are.
Let's get started.
Irityrdia.
I know I'm the one who has awakened you.
You were within an ancient seal,
but you reacted to my magic
and awoke, possessing that girl.
Face me.
O god who has killed and driven mad
so many, and left a blemish on history.
As a mage of this mainland...
I, the Witch of the Azure Moon,
will be your foe.
Don't leave me!
Come.
Tinasha! Stop!
Tinasha!
Not yet.
What do you mean, not yet?
I'll make you spit out that crystal ball.
But then it might get away.
It's here.
You've got this, right?
I swear...
You want me to slice your stomach open?
I know you can do the job
with the smallest possible wound.
You're really asking the impossible here.
Could it be that you
don't have any confidence?
Don't egg me on, idiot!
I'm just sick of you always using me.
Are you a cat?
No, I'm not.
Fine, I'll do it.
You're the one and only one for me.
I'll beat it without a sweat.
Yes, of course.
Oscar.
For so, so long, I've wanted
to give this god a good beating.
So please.
Are you okay?
There aren't any shards left inside, are there?
I'd be able to tell if there were.
I'm fine.
What about the girl?
Elze received treatment
and was left in the village ruins.
If she feels like it,
she'll come back on her own.
I suppose.
You're going to sleep in your human form?
Have you forgotten we're sharing a room?
I know that you have very strong self-control.
That'll come back to bite you someday.
I curl up into a ball when I'm a cat.
I want to stretch my limbs.
Let me sleep for just one hour.
Get some proper rest.
I'll protect you, no matter what.
What was that?!
Couldn't help myself.
J-Just when I was about to fall asleep...
~ The Things Unknown ~