A fine sight indeed...
It reminds me of old times.
Towns and people burning,
like in the Dark Age when I was born.
Lanak    King of Cuscull
A new age is about to dawn on the mainland.
First comes... the Four Great Nations, was it?
They'll be the first to go.
That does it.
So it's true.
Why now, after four hundred years?
You can rest now.
Thanks for all your hard work.
~ As the Abyss Is Born ~
People kill other people.
That's what emotions and power wreak.
And if that is the consequence, I'd rather
shut myself off from love and hatred.
I'd rather not remember.
I don't want to go mad.
Since, from the very start...
I've been engulfed
in a madness I cannot escape.
I hereby define this.
Let these words turn to poison by my will.
Sow these seeds to grow into thorns.
What's this?
Tinasha.
I'm sleepy.
You can sleep after you explain this.
I've placed another curse over it,
so they offset each other.
Huh?
To put it simply, I've broken your curse.
You've broken it?
You can clean that off now.
Please go take a bath.
Is this your blood?
I used it as a catalyst.
Why'd you wait until I was sleeping?
It's easier when you're unconscious.
Well, I'm off to bed.
What now?
Well... thanks.
Why must I attend
King Kevin's birthday celebration?!
You call it a ceremony,
but it's little more than a diplomacy ball!
If you don't go, who will?
Have fun dealing with those snakes.
You can't be serious!
Your Highness, we've received
a message from Tayiri.
It seems Prince Reust won't be able to attend,
what with the attack from Cuscull.
Instead, his sister, Princess Cecilia,
will be arriving today.
Cuscull?
An attack?
Cuscull mages burned down
a city near their border.
Tayiri's persecuted mages
for hundreds of years now.
Is it simply an act of revenge,
or something else?
Tinasha?
I'd like to ask you something.
What is it?
Oscar, are you fond of Nark?
Nark is that dragon you keep around, isn't it?
I'm currently its master,
but I wanted to transfer ownership.
It looks like Nark's taken a liking to you.
Why so suddenly?
Sure. I don't mind.
Really? Let me go ahead.
Now you're its master.
Got it.
How unexpected...
It's good to shake things up.
It's unheard of for a witch
to show herself at an event like this!
I'll keep your identity a secret.
If you call me your fiancée,
I'll blow you to bits.
I'll keep that in mind.
Your Majesty Kevin, Twentieth King of Farsas.
I extend my heartfelt congratulations
on your fifty-third birthday.
Your Highness!
Cecelia    Princess of Tayiri
Princess Cecelia.
Best wishes on this joyful occasion.
I'm terribly sorry my brother couldn't make it.
No, I hear your nation has suffered an attack.
Nothing but a bunch of
pesky gnats, I assure you.
I'd like to hear more about Cuscull,
or those gnats as you say.
My!
Discussing such complicated matters...
I'd rather not, out here in the open.
Thank you for being so kind as to come.
My contract holder
is quite persistent, you see.
It must run in his blood.
I don't know how to thank you
for lifting the curse on my son.
I was just fulfilling the contract.
Now he can marry anyone he likes.
You must have it rough.
I can only imagine.
You say that like it's none of your business.
I wish you'd rein him in somehow.
He won't listen to what I say at his age.
I'd be happy if you would just marry him.
You won't let that go?!
I'm tired.
Good thing I can't dance in this dress.
Lanak.
The embroidery on this dress took
ten dressmakers half a year to complete.
Your Highness.
If you're tired, would you like to head to bed?
What is it, Tinasha?
My apologies, but I have important business
with him, so if you would kindly leave.
How rude of you to burst in through the window!
Your Highness, who is she?
My wit...
Wit?
...filled mage.
A lowly mage who doesn't know her place...
How disgusting!
Out with you!
A lowly mage, you say?
Watch your tongue, you imbecile.
What was that?!
Leave.
Do you need to be told twice to understand?
What is it?
Oscar.
I should have died four hundred years ago.
You mustn't be infatuated with the dead.
Go and accomplish that which you must do.
Don't forget that the future of this
kingdom's people depends on you.
Tina—
Do you remember what I said
when I broke Lucrezia's spell?
I've come for you.
You've grown into a beautiful adult, Aeti.
Lanak!
You really were alive!
I know you've been searching for me.
But I couldn't act for the longest time.
It's okay.
It's more than enough that you're still alive.
I've started a nation
called Cuscull for your sake.
A fine location, and I've razed
all the surrounding cities in the way.
You will become queen there.
Who's he?
I used to have a contract with him.
The one who wields the sword Akashia?
He's a danger.
Let's leave him be.
Even with its power, it's nothing but a sword.
It's of little use if its user lacks strength.
What in the world is going on here?
I've broken your curse.
My contract with you ends tonight.
There should still be time left.
It's over.
If you're going to hurt Lanak,
you'll have to face me.
As I am now, I can kill you.
However...
That's enough.
Let's go.
Tinasha!
Lady Tinasha...
How's His Highness doing?
He's in a foul temper.
Though he may not look it.
I'm done.
You handle the rest.
Ah, yes.
Your Highness, where are you
going with that sword?
I'm off to Lucrezia's forest.
Please wait!
What if you run into danger?
I won't, so it's fine.
Let go of me.
You can save yourself the trip.
I'm right here.
I came to see if it was true.
Figures that she really did leave.
What do you mean, "figures"?
Well, I received an invite to Cuscull, too.
What?
I turned them down, of course.
I imagine the other witches did as well.
So her going along will cause
trouble across the mainland.
What relationship do Tinasha
and that Lanak fellow have?
She's been searching for him
ever since she became a witch.
Good for her, reuniting after so long.
But he didn't seem to be in his right mind.
It's like he was in a dreamlike haze.
Jealous?
I don't think that matters,
as long as she accepts him.
No way.
Do you have any right to interfere?
I won't give her up.
She's irreplaceable to me.
I'll kill that man and bring her back.
If she still insists on being with
another man, then I'll let her go.
Understood.
I'll tell you what she said to me exactly,
but only to those who are prepared
to fight her to the death.
Go on.
Before I tell this story,
let me tell you her real name.
Her real name?
Tinasha As Meyer Ur Aeterna Tuldarr.
Tuldarr?!
Isn't Tuldarr the magic empire that was
destroyed overnight four hundred years ago?
If her last name is the same as that nation...
That makes her royalty.
More precisely, she was
the future queen candidate.
Tuldarr was a monarchy, but the ruler was
decided by pure power and not lineage.
Decided by power?
What if an eccentric
happens to be the strongest?
That's why, as soon as Tinasha was born,
she was separated from her parents
to be raised in the palace.
Her powers were that extraordinary?
So one candidate is chosen each
for king and queen,
and they end up engaged to each other.
The boy was the king's only son.
In other words, Lanak.
But he was far less powerful than she was.
Everyone thought Tinasha would be
queen, and Lanak her consort?
That's right.
Even so, Lanak treated her with great kindness,
like she was his own sister five years younger.
But unbeknownst to them,
the royal court was split into two factions.
The reformists, who called for
diplomacy with foreign nations.
The traditionalists, who sought
to maintain isolation from them.
And with neither side yielding,
the king eventually fell ill.
Disputes broke out with reformists backing
Tinasha, and traditionalists backing Lanak.
You call it a dispute, but wasn't Miss Tinasha
guaranteed to accede to the throne?
Yes, which is why the traditionalists
came up with a plan.
A way to prevent Tinasha's accession
and increase Lanak's power all at once.
It happened when she was thirteen.
One night, she opened her eyes to Lanak
carrying her somewhere.
This is the cathedral...
Oh, you're awake?
You have high magical resistance,
so you wake up in no time.
Lanak.
Who are these people?
Don't you move, Aeti.
Lanak?
Lanak... why?
Stop it!
We just need to prolong
your life so you don't die.
Sacred life, linger here in this place.
Let wound remain as wound,
blood as blood, smoldering slowly.
Persist here for some time longer.
What I desire is unadulterated power!
Draw upon this flesh and blood
to appear before me, power!
I'm doing this for Tuldarr, Aeti!
With this magical power, I will surpass you!
What?!
Suppress this at once!
A-Any more and...
I reign over thee in thy whole.
Take me as thy vessel and obey my command!
After the whirlwind of
magical power disappeared,
her torn stomach had somehow repaired itself.
In exchange, she had to lie there
for three days in unbearable pain.
However, after desperately trying to
hold onto the magical power,
Tuldarr had already been
reduced to a pile of rubble.
The overflowing magic absorbed
the souls of those who had died,
scattering across the mainland
and turning into five magical lakes.
And after everything had come to pass,
Tinasha had become a witch.
She built a tower in the corner of what
had been Tuldarr territory to live in.
And ever since, she's been searching for Lanak.
I never asked her why, though.
That ends my story.
How did she feel about me?
Don't ask me obvious questions.
If she hadn't temporarily sealed away
your defensive barrier with this...
do you think Lanak would have let you go?
And she left her dragon with you, too.
The answer's right there.
This doesn't change our plans.
I'll kill that revolting man
and bring Tinasha back.
That's all there is to it.
We've received a letter from Cuscull.
"To the Four Great Nations:
Tayiri, Cezar, Gandona, and Farsas.
Kumu    Farsas Chief Mage
Granfort    Farsas General
We hereby demand your capitulation."
Nessan    Farsas Minister of the Interior
A few days ago, Tayiri led a large army
of ten thousand men into Cuscull.
However, Tayiri's forces
were practically wiped out.
Bardalos    Cuscull Chief Mage
Meanwhile, Cuscull lost less than
fifty of their mages.
That's not all.
Five large cities in Tayiri
were devastated at the same time,
with thousands losing their lives.
In the affected cities,
the buildings were left intact,
with all of their citizens vanishing.
The one responsible...
appears to be the Witch of the Azure Moon.
And while Farsas has received
a request for aid...
Oscar, they've additionally asked
for you to slay the witch.
Can you do it?
I'm the only one who can kill her.
But I won't do it.
If Tayiri is asking for aid,
we should head there.
But that's only if you're treating
Cuscull as the enemy.
She's a different story.
Hasn't she gone to Cuscull of her own will?
I don't think the truth lies
in only what we can see.
Have you been taken in by the witch?!
You damn fool!
Have you forgotten that our people's
lives rest on your shoulders?!
Dear father.
There's no need for further discussion.
I've already made up my mind.
I don't plan on losing, or forsaking anything.
Maybe it does run in the blood.
I understand.
Do as you will.
In exchange...
You take the throne as king.
It's about time I stepped down.
Y-Your Majesty!
It may be a bit early,
but that shouldn't matter.
Take this opportunity
to learn all that you can.
I swear...
Everyone loves putting me through the wringer.
I understand.
I'll gladly accede to the throne.
Always keep in mind that your actions
decide the fate of this kingdom.
As long as you wield that sword,
and I remain a witch,
someday you might really have to...
I won't forget those words.
~ The End of the Dream ~