I heard you were reckless again.
Seriously...
It wasn't that big of a deal.
You don't think being stabbed
by Akashia's a big deal?
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
And Irityrdia was successfully terminated.
That's not the issue here.
There weren't any problems.
I knew Oscar would be able to pull it off.
Aren't you trusting him a little too much?
That's not true.
So?
What are you going to do now?
What?
The contract was for one year, wasn't it?
That's right.
What?
Don't do something you'll regret.
~ The Things Unknown ~
Next month is the new year, huh?
Time sure flies.
You're telling me.
That said, even after
all of the trouble we faced,
we somehow managed to survive another year.
If His Majesty would find a queen,
we'd have no worries going into the new year.
If Miss Tinasha were willing,
that'd be the fastest way.
She'd be the most beautiful queen
in our history for sure!
But she's a witch.
I stand opposed to the idea.
Mister Norman.
Norman    Farsas Civil Servant
There are plenty of other candidates.
I can't accept a witch
as our queen, even as a joke.
Well...
She may be a witch,
but she's the queen of Tuldarr!
A queen, you say?
We're talking about a long gone nation here.
Still...
If you were listening,
that makes things easier.
As long as His Majesty obsesses over you,
this kingdom will never have a queen.
Hey, Norman...
It's fine.
However—
I hear your contract is due to expire shortly.
You'll clean up after yourself, won't you?
I could erase Oscar's memories, if you'd like.
Lady Tinasha, that's going too far.
But if Oscar found out,
he'd be extremely angry.
We'll have to go about it carefully.
As long as you're aware.
Do remember where you stand here.
Why, you!
How dare you say that!
Calm down, Pamyra.
It's fine.
Witches are a danger and a calamity.
It's a fact that we
are meant to be loathed.
You're too forgiving, Lady Tinasha.
That's not true at all.
I just think I shouldn't forget
what I really am.
Were you serious about that suggestion?
I'll do it, if that's what's necessary.
But if you do that, he'll forget all about you!
Even if he forgets,
it's fine as long as I still remember.
I'm fine as long as he lives
a normal, happy life.
That'll make me happy, too.
Lady Tinasha...
But even if I don't interfere,
that man will carry out his duties.
He's a strong person.
Much stronger than I am...
I wonder why I'm still alive.
Don't be ridiculous!
If you want to die, then live among
people and die as a human!
I don't want it any other way!
Pamyra.
Please find your own happiness.
That's my wish for you!
I'm plenty happy already.
Thank you.
Look, the sky's beautiful.
Maybe a year was too long.
Oscar.
Tinasha.
Is something wrong?
Not really.
Here, a gift for you.
What's this?
Just for your enjoyment.
The sky tonight was really pretty.
Thanks.
So? Did something happen?
Why do you ask?
You look a bit sad.
I'm doing fine.
Wh-What now?
Well, you were just about to cast something.
What spell was it?
You really are superhuman.
It's nothing.
I just wanted to test out
a psychological spell.
I don't really get it, but tell me
before you try anything.
So, is something bothering you?
Just been thinking about my life.
You can just marry me, you know.
Not happening.
How stubborn.
Just marry me and quit being a witch.
How would I quit, exactly?
You just need to go back to aging normally.
Aging, you say?
How many decades do you have left?
It's more than enough.
Share them with me.
You really have strange taste in women.
Shut up.
She means a lot to me.
Don't you badmouth her.
You really should stop doing that.
Push me away if you don't like it.
How do I put it?
I know part of it is just because
I'm used to your touch,
but you really are special to me.
Is something wrong?
No.
Oscar, you shouldn't.
Why not?
Why not, you say?
Come up with your own answer.
What is it?
Sorry for disturbing you so late.
Please check these urgently...
I'd be well justified to kill you right now.
Wh-Why's that?!
Oscar!
What's that?
The castle's barrier has been broken.
What's going on?!
Over here!
Surround each one with at least three men!
Don't leave any openings!
If you can't fight, don't come out here!
What?
What is all this?
Get lost.
Are you hurt?
No, I'm fine.
Then go inside the castle.
Don't come out until it's all over.
Miss Tinasha.
Good luck out there.
I leave His Majesty to you.
Understood.
Come out!
Senn! Karr! Mila! Nil! Kunai!
Go forth!
Recognize my will as command.
Transformer resting in the earth
and taking to the sky.
I control and summon thy water.
Know that thou art manifested by my name.
Okay.
Are you all right?
Yes.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Aderayya    Servant to Leonora
Oscar!
Oscar?
That's...
Recognize my will as command.
Transformer acting as the pivot
on which the world turns.
I deny thee.
Deny, deny.
Deny, deny...
What's going on?
Sorry to call you so late at night.
You're stopping time?
Yes.
A natural poison?
Wait, is it alkakia?
Yes.
He's a lost cause.
It's a deadly poison that no one's survived,
dating back to the Dark Age.
Don't write him off yet.
I'll figure something out.
How, exactly?
I'll make a blood serum.
For a poison that kills instantly?
How on earth will you do that?
With my body.
What?
Inside my body, there's plenty of magic
and time stands still.
I can hold out for about a full day,
even with this poison.
I'll use that time to use magic
and create antibodies.
Don't be stupid!
Even if you make the serum,
you'll die in the process!
Not that you can use magic
in such debilitating pain!
That's why I'm asking for your help.
Also, I'm used to handling pain.
I refuse.
Please.
No way!
Something's wrong with you!
You're insane!
Just find another man!
Please.
Are you saying this man's worth
risking your life for?
Yes.
You two help me out, too.
Lady Lucrezia.
This has never been done before,
so I don't know how long it'll take.
You might end up dying first.
If I'd known this would happen,
I'd have worked out a little more.
A bit more muscle wouldn't make a difference.
Just try not to lose your sanity.
It'll be a real pain
if your magic goes haywire.
I'll keep that in mind.
If I die, please finish the spell.
Got it.
Also, please erase all of his memories of me.
No can do.
If you die, I'll make him bear
the burden for the rest of his life.
Please go on.
Your Majesty!
What's this?
Please don't overexert yourself.
Huh? What happened to me?
You were sick and bedridden.
We were all worried about you.
Was it that bad?
No wonder everything's a blur.
I feel like someone's missing.
I'm sure it's all in your head.
I see.
That aside, would you like something to eat?
No, I'm going back to sleep.
Sorry.
I understand.
We'll be taking our leave,
so please call us if you need anything.
Norman.
Do you know anything from before I fell ill?
No, never mind.
Sorry for asking a weird question.
Your Majesty.
Have you decided who you'll take as queen yet?
My queen?
I believe it's about time
you thought about your heir.
Please choose someone
who meets the requirements.
Oscar.
Tinasha.
What are you doing?
After we silenced all your subjects
and tampered with your memories...
Where's Tinasha?
What on earth happened?
The alkakia you were poisoned with
has spread throughout her body.
Is she alive?
We wouldn't leave her here if she was dead.
It's a mystery as to why she's not.
The incredible pain
should have driven her insane,
but she was chanting incantations to the end.
I swear.
I wanted her to find a man
because I thought she'd settle down,
but it only made her worse.
Why is she hovering on the brink of death?
Sorry.
No woman would want someone
to see her like this.
But she got these wounds because of me, right?
You've finally come to.
Lucrezia.
If you can walk, then come here.
I'll heal those wounds for you.
Tinasha.
I would have visited you if you'd waited.
I teleported here, so it was instant.
Were you busy?
I don't mind.
Is your body okay now?
Yes.
I'm back at full health.
Then strip down for me later.
Why?
I want to make sure you're fully healed.
I am!
I swear, what's going on in that head of yours?
I should be asking how you see me.
What?
As a contract holder.
No, what else?
Also, you're important to me.
I see.
What's wrong with you?
No, well...
You should think about things a little more.
Okay?
And so, I have no idea why he laughed at me.
Miss Tinasha, you don't realize it?
Realize what?
Lady Tinasha.
As His Majesty said,
please think about it a bit more.
For example, would you have done
what you did for any other contract holder?
I think it'd depend on the circumstances.
His Majesty is special to you, right?
Probably.
Yeah, that's right.
And why is he special?
I wonder why.
I'm fond of him?
Isn't he more than a contract holder?
Someone that sexually attracts you?
Eh?
Is that what's going on?!
Don't ask me that!
Wh-Who here thinks I love Oscar?
Y...
You can't be serious!
Be a little more honest with yourself.
You've loved him for a long time now.
How?!
How, you ask...
I'm not the one to ask.
I should be asking you.
How can you not realize it?
What?
I'm in love with Oscar?
I need to kill him.
Why is that your conclusion?
Are you an idiot?!
Tinasha.
Oscar, do you have a moment?
What's this now?
I've thought about it,
and I really have no idea.
So I'm asking everyone and taking
the majority opinion as the answer.
What are you up to?
Am I in love with you?
You really have just completely broken, huh?
That's right.
You just realized it?
Come here.
Why are you crying?
I have no idea.
But...
I'm glad I met you.
That's an honor to hear.
~ Blank Slate Children ~