Your Highness!
Please spar with me, too!
Very well.
Anyone else interested?
Tinasha.
Come here.
Absolutely not.
Why did you refuse immediately?
I know there's nothing in it for me.
It will serve as training.
You can use magic if you'd like.
How powerful will this man become?
Perhaps he's the one
who can kill a witch like me.
Understood.
I'll take part.
However, I'd like you to use Akashia.
You can attack at any time.
I'll do just that, then.
Hmm...
~ A Breath of Life into Image ~
Man, they were amazing.
Both Miss Tinasha and His Highness.
So that's how you use magic for close combat.
Most mages let the swordsmen
take the front lines,
and stay in the back
firing big spells instead.
I've never seen a mage who uses a sword
to cover their offense and defense.
It looked like she was
testing His Highness to me.
Or rather, trying to teach him.
What?
After all, she was smiling.
So he really can see them.
Let's leave it at that for today.
These swords are no good anymore.
These are light wounds
considering you were using magic.
Did you go easy on me?
That's not the case.
Complicated spells
require incantations and focus.
To be honest, I wouldn't want to fight
in close quarters with you again.
I really don't want to kill you, after all.
How naive of you.
Do you want to die?
No, I still have plenty I want to do.
Like breaking that curse on you.
If you become my wife, that'd be fine as well.
I refuse!
Do you realize how much older I am?
An envoy from the tiny nation
of Cuscull, to the north, has arrived.
He wants to see the Witch of the Azure Moon.
How does he know that Tinasha is here?
I'm not too sure myself.
For now, he insists on meeting her.
I was thinking of leaving this matter to you.
How about it?
I understand.
I'll see him first.
Kagar    Envoy from Cuscull
My name is Kagar.
All I ask is for a brief audience
with the great witch herself.
Unfortunately, we don't have any witches here.
I'd like to know how you got
that idea in your head.
Surely you jest.
I won't take much of Your Highness's time.
I'm well aware that she resides in this castle.
Lady Tinasha, or should I say, Lady Aeti.
Huh?
Where's Oscar?
His Highness is out at the moment.
Is that so?
That's fine, then.
I didn't have any business with him.
Excuse me, Lady Tinasha.
I haven't introduced myself yet.
I began serving His Highness as a maid
after being introduced by General Ettard.
My name is Miralys.
I see.
But I also know the true reason
you're here at the palace.
What?
H-How do you know that?
I can tell by looking at you.
So please, pay me no mind.
Hey, I heard you had a sparring match with him.
How do you know that?
And before that, why are you here?
I'm here for some tea.
Do you have a death wish,
showing him how you fight?
He said the same thing.
That man is strong enough without your help.
I don't need the owner
of that sword getting any stronger.
If staying neutral is getting to you,
just give up or whatever already.
I suppose you're right.
I'm not sure myself
why I felt like fighting him.
I just felt it might be nice to have someone
who could kill me if anything happens.
Perhaps I've grown tired of continuing
my search for that person.
Lady Tinasha, do you have a moment?
Yes.
We have a guest who wants to see you, Aeti.
Okay.
Ah...
So it really was your name.
It's an honor to be
in your presence, Lady Aeti.
Please stop calling me by that name.
My apologies.
Would it suffice to call you
Lady Tinasha, then?
Fine by me.
So, what do you want with me?
Actually, Cuscull's founding has restored
the rights of mages persecuted in Tayiri,
and our main goal is to utilize
and develop their skills.
We beseech you to come to Cuscull and lend
your knowledge to expand even further.
What?
I'm here as this man's protector.
Nothing more, nothing less.
I only agreed to let you
meet me on his behalf.
So why should I listen to someone
who hasn't even climbed my tower,
and what's more, lend them my support?
Please...
Away with you.
Damn it!
I was sure she'd come if I used that name!
I can't go back empty-handed!
I need to at least separate
those two from each other...
Lucrezia.
Perfect timing.
Do you know of the nation of Cuscull?
Huh?
Never heard of it.
They're a collection of mages who
proclaimed independence this past year.
Hmm...
Oh, have you noticed the ripples of strange
magic emanating from the north lately?
They're subtle, sporadic fluctuations
similar to those from a magical lake.
A magical lake...
Hey! Meredina!
What's going on here?
No, this is...
You conniving woman, deceiving men's hearts!
Leave this country at once!
Meredina!
I've heard similar accusations many times.
But I have not once tried to tempt anyone.
She's the one getting worked up over nothing.
I've never desired anyone's heart.
That woman's under mind control.
Let go!
Can you undo it?
Why me?
Please.
It won't come cheap.
Let me see her.
When was the last time you cried?
I don't remember.
I'm finished treating her.
Thanks a lot.
What'd you call me out here for?
I've sent out a familiar to look into Cuscull.
So starting today, I want you to spar with me.
What?
I'll be careful not to die,
so please do your best.
Not bad for the first day, I guess.
Why are you doing this?
Let me think.
There's more than one reason,
but if I had to sum it up...
I want you to have lots
of options available to you.
Options?
No matter what happens in the future,
I don't want you to regret that your lack
of strength has closed off a path.
I want you to choose the path you want,
from as many options as possible.
That's my reasoning.
I'll see you here tomorrow, too.
Feel free to come
after your official duties.
That ends my report.
It's two against one.
Will you be okay?
This much is nothing!
I see.
In that case...
Something caught my leg.
It was a magic vine.
I believe you should be able to see them.
Huh?
You dodged it when we sparred in the palace.
Don't let your mental state
affect your fighting.
Let's call it a day for today.
You must be more exhausted than usual.
Let's rest at the top...
Eh?
Ah, hey...
Don't fall asleep here!
Where am I?
You're awake?
You're completely unguarded.
I was concentrating.
I'm sure I'd notice if there was an intruder.
Not what I mean.
Be angrier when someone touches you.
Why's the person who touched me saying that?
I'm used to it from you by now.
If it bothers you, then control yourself more.
Here you go.
It should help your fatigue, so drink up.
So sweet!
Drink it.
Good job.
Hey, do I have magical power, too?
Yes.
I had no idea.
But in your case, you can't use magic
so long as you wield Akashia.
Guess I can't become a mage, then.
Still, you should be able to see magic.
Please pay it more attention
starting tomorrow.
This is scorching hot.
Observe the flow of magic and cut through it.
Find the spot that acts as the linchpin
of the spell's composition.
You make it sound so easy...
The linchpin of the spell...
The flow of magic...
Is this it?!
Well done.
That was fast.
Maybe I should have you face humans next.
You sound like you're making bugs fight.
Huh?
Are you folks also here to challenge the tower?
Just the people I was hoping for!
Welcome to my tower.
Are you saying you're the witch?!
Indeed.
You came here with a request
for me, did you not?
Emerge victorious in a fight against him.
If you do, I'll grant your wish.
Okay!
Let's do this, everyone!
Yeah!
I'll make sure no one dies.
So fight with everything you've got.
I swear...
Begin!
Wow, incredible!
That was better than I expected.
I think we can make today our last day.
You put a lot of hard work in.
Can I win a fight against you now?
I can't say for sure.
If we knew the answer now,
it wouldn't be any fun.
It looks like it's brought back
information on Cuscull.
It appears that there are around
two hundred mages gathered in Cuscull.
Spirit sorcerers, too.
That can't be!
The average nation has anywhere
from twenty to thirty mages!
Are they planning to start a war?
I can't deny the possibility.
They aim to summon demons as well.
You mentioned a palace.
Are they a monarchy?
It appears so.
I don't know who their monarch is,
but it's not the former lord of the domain.
As a kingdom revolving around magic,
there's a good chance that they're a mage.
Can we have you continue
to investigate the matter for now?
I'm sure they're plotting something.
It's awful, Your Highness!
General Ettard...
I'd heard he was in poor health.
Miss Miralys, you entered the palace
thanks to General Ettard, if I recall.
Yes...
He treated me so kindly
for a distant relative.
It's thanks to him that I'm here now...
Both Als and I are indebted to him.
Before Als entered the palace,
Ettard gave him sword training.
And me, after I was cursed...
Your Highness.
Despair eats away at people.
Become a man of strong will.
Do that, and results will follow.
Don't you die before me.
General Ettard's belongings
will be left to his close friends.
I've informed General Als
regarding the curse on Your Highness.
I never knew that happened to you.
It's a real nuisance.
Sounds real bad,
unless Miss Tinasha marries you.
Yeah.
The direct lineage will die out.
How about it?
I said no!
I'm doing the analysis, aren't I?
What displeases you about His Highness?
Wh-Wh-What, you ask?
What was it again?
Don't ask me.
His problem is that he likes
to poke fun at people.
Maybe.
Hey...
That said, we have more than
half a year left on our contract.
I'm sure things will work out.
I sure hope so.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
Only the lid ended up cracking.
Can't you fix it?
I can't undo what has been broken.
I may be able to stop time,
but I can't turn time back.
I'm sorry.
I guess magic has its limits, too.
All living things share the same fate of death.
H-Help...
You don't know who I am, do you?
You've got some nerve showing yourself here.
Your lord killed him in front of my eyes.
Even if I could redo it all,
that sin will not wash away.
Understand?
Lord Lanak...
~ Unnamed Emotion ~