Aeti.
Did I wake you up?
What's going on?
Something good's about to happen.
I wanted you to be there to see it.
Is it important?
Yes, it is.
As important as you are.
I'm still sleepy.
You can go back to sleep.
Oscar?
Yes, it's me.
I'm sorry.
I had a bad dream.
Because you fall asleep sitting up.
Get some proper rest when you sleep.
You have a point.
That dream again...
~ Unnamed Emotion ~
Thanks.
Your Highness.
His Majesty wants to see you.
Father does?
I haven't fully investigated the matter...
Were you discussing something
with my protector?
Yes, I was seeking counsel from her.
It's about your bride.
What?
Your future queen needs to have
high magical resistance, am I wrong?
I've asked Miss Tinasha to see whether
the girl in question meets our needs.
What girl?
I think it would be barely possible for her.
Who are we talking about?
You haven't realized it?
Miralys?
Bingo.
You were aware as well?
Yes.
Her magical power is sealed away,
but in terms of capacity, hers easily
exceeds that of a court mage.
I figured she would be a potential
candidate as your bride.
It seems her family passes down
magic through their bloodline.
When one generation dies,
their descendants inherit their magic.
How come I wasn't told of this?
I thought you'd bristle at the idea.
Like you are now.
Now look here...
That's enough.
Everyone is doing what they can for your sake.
This is a good opportunity.
Don't be arrogant and try
to solve it all on your own.
Why don't you get to know Miralys better?
Miralys.
I hear your magic has been sealed away.
Who was responsible?
My mother.
And Master Kumu reinforced it as well.
I see. A twofold seal?
That aside, how come she hasn't been around?
Do you mean Lady Tinasha?
I haven't seen her in the past week or so.
Where has she been?
B-Beats me...
My apologies.
No, you don't need to apologize.
They found a potential princess?!
Yes.
Which means I'm off the hook for that now.
Besides, it's a good thing for him
to have more choices.
Especially for marriage partners.
The more the merrier, wouldn't you say?
I'd feel bad if I was the only choice he had.
Are you being serious here?
Yes.
I don't really have time for jokes.
Hey.
You may be a witch,
but more importantly, you're human.
Can I go back to my analysis?
Master Tinasha. Master Tinasha.
What is it?
A challenger has arrived.
I thought I closed off the entrance.
He used a teleport circle to make his way in.
Prince Oscar, that is.
Tinasha.
Ugh...
Is that any way to greet me?
New records set for both
smallest party and shortest time.
You've really surpassed
the limits of a normal human.
That's the least of my concerns right now.
Why have you been hiding from me?
I've been busy.
Trying to break this.
There's no need to rush it.
I want to finish it while I can.
The blessing placed on you
by the Witch of Silence...
It's truly quite elegant.
It comes together beautifully,
despite its complex, delicate composition.
Is that so?
Seeing this, I realize that love and hatred
are two sides of the same coin.
I find it... quite frightening.
Frightening?
What are you scared of?
Whenever you're free, make me dinner.
Sure thing.
Miss Tinasha!
Found you!
I've been looking all over!
I wanted to talk to you about Miralys.
Yes?
Looking through General Ettard's belongings,
we couldn't find anything tying her to him.
I see.
That got me curious, so I looked into her
background, but it turned up nothing.
Is it really okay to consider her for princess?
You too?
Huh?
Actually, when I first arrived at this castle,
I searched across the mainland for
a woman who could be Oscar's wife.
But I found no one other than the witches.
Isn't that because Miralys's grandmother
still had her power back then?
If I excluded by age, the witches
would have been the first to go.
But even so, there were no women
who had as much power as Miralys does now.
So you mean she's hiding something.
However, I don't know whether
she's after the Farsas royal family
or whether she wants to drag
me away from this place.
If I knew which it was, I could take action.
Perfect timing.
Our chance to uncover the truth.
What?
Oh, I get it.
How devious of you.
It came with perks, so I'll take it.
If she's after His Highness,
she won't do anything.
But if it's you she's after, she'll take
some sort of action against me.
I'll take my leave now.
That's...
Oscar.
Did you call for me?
Come in.
What were you up to today?
The same as always.
I did some analysis, listened
to reports from my familiars...
Is something wrong?
This is...
A sealing ornament with
the same properties as Akashia.
Only direct royal descendants can handle it.
Where'd you get this thing?!
The royal treasury.
Oscar!
I knew you could be clueless,
but I thought you were better than this.
I was going to wait patiently,
but I have my limits.
What?
I didn't bring you here to
hand you over to another man.
Since you don't understand, I'll teach you
until you feel it in your bones.
Stop it...
Let me down...
Stop...
Don't...
Tinasha?
Tinasha.
Sorry.
I just wanted to scare you a bit.
It was in poor taste.
I won't do it again.
No, I'm sorry.
No.
I'm the one apologizing here.
Why?
Why, you ask?
What?!
You already gave Als a good beating?
My bad.
Tell that to Als!
He was just trying to sound out Miralys.
He didn't suffer any major injuries.
I just sparred with him about ten times.
I'll go heal him up after this.
That said, don't hide information
about Miralys from me.
She sounds incredibly suspicious.
But its possible she's
being used by someone else,
and we had no evidence to report to you.
What's more, look at how cute she is.
I didn't want to ruin any chance
of you falling in love with her.
I swear...
This is what I mean by not understanding!
Ow, ow, ow!
Come with me.
Now's the right time.
I want to make things very clear.
I'm not keeping Tinasha around because
I don't have any other choices.
She's here because I've taken a liking to her.
So it's pointless and unwelcome to parade
any other women in front of me.
I won't choose anyone but her.
Surely you understand now.
Be there one, a hundred, or a thousand
choices, I will always choose you.
So don't complicate things
and distance yourself.
That's the truth of the matter.
Unfortunately, I have no intent
to make you my wife.
You'll be removed from your position for now,
so we can look into your background.
U-Um, Your Highness...
I...
If you will.
Yes.
The castle's barrier...
Oh no!
Tinasha!
Oscar!
Let go of me!
You're...
I would have left you alone
if you hadn't caught on.
You broke Kumu's seal by yourself?
Sorry.
Can it be healed?
I'm fine...
More importantly, stand back.
Being splashed with my blood
has weakened your defensive barrier.
Leave this to me.
Go help evacuate the others.
Good grief.
You sure do underestimate me.
Can you fight looking like that?
I'll need to fight with only my right eye.
That demonic beast...
He entrusted it to me.
You regenerated the beast using its core?
How clever of you.
What are you doing?
You shouldn't be on the front line
with that eye, either.
Why did you have me undergo all that training?
Allow me the option to
make up for my mistakes.
But the barrier...
It'll be fine.
If you really insist, then at least
secure an easy victory.
I won't tolerate any injuries.
Don't suddenly make things harder.
Get him!
Incinerate that which has form by my hand!
Let it be defined.
Why, you!
That was close!
I can't attack or defend against
that beast without incantations,
so I might not be very useful here.
And you were going to fight it alone?
What about Miralys, then?
I can kill her at any time.
However...
It'd be best to take her alive.
We need to ask her what she's after.
Magic spheres!
I know well enough that I don't stand
a chance against you head-on.
What?!
It distorted the trajectory!
Burst!
This is troublesome...
If you have a plan, I'm all ears.
There are two options.
One where the palace is half destroyed,
and one where it isn't,
but that demands a lot from you.
Which do you prefer?
The second one.
Then we'll take a standard approach.
I'll stand back like a good mage,
so you take the front.
Buy me some time.
Commence definition.
What the eye sees is but one of many.
Boundless life is squandered into tranquility.
You should know when to give up,
if you don't want your throat torn out.
Unfortunately, I've gone longer
without this barrier than with it.
I don't know what you're after,
but I'll capture you and have you tell me.
Get him!
Flames, consume him!
You used the beast as a shield?!
I was raised with bad manners.
No injuries, huh?
That's rich, considering
your stomach got torn open.
Okay, my mind is set.
Come at me.
This place will be your graveyard.
Twilight without form...
Contort space!
Sorry.
I'm prepared for any nasty looks I might get.
It's only natural that I buy her time.
I need to be able to handle enemies
like these if I want to stand by her side!
Incinerate that which has form—
Oh no, you don't.
What... is that?!
Be rid of meaning.
Make sure you let her out later.
You won't lose. Not as long as I'm with you.
Where's Miralys?
I let her escape on purpose.
Where is she headed?
Out of my way...
I finally figured out where it is!
There.
This is it!
I don't know what you're trying
to steal, but it won't be yours.
I need this, no matter what it takes!
You'd never understand!
I'll tell you now that I'm here.
In the future, you'll be reunited with
the delusion you've been searching for.
What?
So have fun suffering all by yourself...
Little Miss Queen-to-Be!
Not on my watch.
If only...
If only I had more power...
Don't do it!
Valt...
I'm sorry...
Delusion...
Lanak?
Is she dead?
No.
Her body is alive, but her soul is gone.
She disappeared of her own will.
I see.
That should do it...
Are you really fully healed?
Why the doubtful tone?
I'm all better.
Would you like to make sure?
Sorry about everything.
I should be apologizing, too.
In the end, what was that orb
she was trying to steal?
Well, you see...
Originally, it didn't belong to Farsas.
It was something my mother brought,
so I'm not certain what it's used for.
Your mother, you say?
Yeah.
What's the matter?
No, it's nothing...
So?
I never got an answer from earlier today.
Do you feel like marrying me yet?
I'll never get married.
You should just give up.
I swear...
I can wait, so it's fine.
Even if you leave yourself
with only one choice,
I'll give you countless options so you forget.
May the darkness of my past
that I seek never reach you.
May it not affect the path that you walk down.
Let go of me already.
I'm getting sleepy.
Today has tired me out as well.
Should we sleep together?
Get out!
I'll hurl you back to your room
with teleportation!
May the day I let go of
this hand come one day.
That is my wish.
~ As the Abyss Is Born ~