I'm sorry, Oscar,
for making you help me on your day off.
It's fine.
Well then...
Is this blood?
"Aeti"...
Where have I seen this before?
What's this?
Oscar!
The tower's... gone?
Bingo.
I lucked out.
Who are you?
I'm not here to hurt you.
Don't make any noise.
I came here for your help, Tinasha.
Who are you?
Your future husband.
Did you hit your head?
If I'm dreaming, I'd love to wake up.
I heard from someone in town earlier that
it's the year 236 in the Tuldarr calendar.
Yes, that's right.
That settles it.
I'm from the year 654, in Tuldarr time.
Are you saying you came here
from four hundred years in the future?
There is no magical law
that lets you go back in time.
It's impossible.
You told me the same thing once before.
So I'd like to wake up soon if I'm dreaming.
Please wake me up.
Why me?
In any case, you're my only hope.
Send me back to my original time.
I just said you can't travel in time.
Maybe you could live for four hundred
years placed magically into slumber,
but men's bodies are too unstable for that.
Is there no other way?
Nope.
Is that a problem?
It is.
I see...
I'll see if I can't find something, then.
You can stay here until then.
No one ever comes here, anyway.
Really?
It might take some time, is that okay?
Yeah, thanks.
I'm grateful, but don't let your
guard down around strangers like that.
What right do you have to say that?
Go to sleep for today.
I'll find an empty room somewhere.
What? Just stay here.
I swear...
I'm pretty small, so I won't be in your way.
Or are you into little kids?
Don't accuse people like that.
How old are you now?
Thirteen.
What?
No, it's nothing.
I'll be right here then, so get some sleep.
You're not a morning person, right?
H-How do you know that?
Bed. Now.
Okay, I get it.
Good night, Tinasha.
Good night.
You really are an odd one.
For some reason, it's really...
You have to do all this as queen candidate?
There's the possibility
I could be assassinated,
so I learned to take care
of most things myself.
It's fine, though.
I may live by myself, but I'm not alone.
The kingdom is here for me.
I need to study hard to serve
its people and protect them.
I'm doing my best
so I don't let them down in the future.
I see.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Your tea's just so good.
How much longer until your next birthday?
The next one?
About half a year left.
Half a year...
If I stayed here in this era...
If I could save her from that tragedy...
So, do you remember yet?
The magic implement that sent you to the past.
No...
I've seen it before, but where was it again?
What's with that sword of yours?
Magic doesn't work on this sword.
There's only one sword like that in the world.
Akashia of Farsas.
That's the one.
You're Farsas royalty?
Yep.
What?!
It dispersed my spell!
I remember now.
What?
I saw it in the Farsas treasury.
Except it was red...
Should we head to Farsas, then?
No, it was my mother's keepsake.
It doesn't exist in Farsas in this era.
Your mother's passed away?
When I was a kid.
I see...
Don't feel bad.
I don't remember her.
Yeah.
I'm sorry.
Oh, that's right.
The one I touched was blue.
I found it in the tower...
I think it came from the Tuldarr treasury.
I can't do that.
No one can enter the treasury
without the king's authorization.
Besides, I can't trust you with that.
That's true.
My bad.
It took you a while to warm up to me before.
What do you mean?
Don't mind me.
Hey, what's that?
What do you mean by "that"?
Inside your body.
Such complicated curses and blessings...
You can see them?
Yeah.
There was an extremely strong
blessing placed on me as a child.
To cancel it out, I had a curse placed on me.
Huh...
C-Can I get some of your blood later?
I'd love to analyze it.
I don't mind, but is it that interesting?
I like doing research.
And everything's worth trying at least once.
How about I train you to use a sword, then?
What?
What?!
It'll be useful in the future.
You ought to do it.
No matter what you say,
I won't leave you alone.
Oscar, what did you do back in Farsas?
You carry the royal sword,
so you're a direct heir to the throne, right?
Dunno. What did I do?
Can I spend the afternoon doing research?
Sure.
This dragon's really friendly.
It must know who you are.
You're the one who gave it to me to begin with.
Really?
Yeah.
Hey, what am I like in the future?
A fine lady.
Like none other.
Don't give me that.
I know that marriage stuff is a lie.
Well, I'm sure it's hard to believe.
Oh, I need to get back to my room!
I forgot Lanak's coming.
Lanak?
You know him?
He's been busy lately,
but he comes and visits often.
It looks great on you, Aeti.
I had it made just for you.
I'm glad to hear that.
Aeti.
What?
Oh, nothing.
I know I just arrived,
but I must be leaving for today.
Okay...
Lanak, wait.
What is it?
I have a favor to ask.
Tinasha.
You scared me.
That necklace...
Lanak gave it to me.
Oh, I asked Lanak
to get me into the treasury...
Don't trust that man.
Huh? Why not?
You don't know Lanak at all, do you?
He's the only family I have.
He's going to hurt you.
You don't know anything about me...
Stop making up lies!
Lanak is the only one who stayed by my side!
I don't have anyone else.
Without him...
I'd be truly alone...
Let go of me, idiot!
There's no way I'd be okay being all alone...
I wanted to see my mom and my dad!
I wanted to be a normal kid, just for one day!
But...
They said someone had to do it...
They said it'd get better when I grew up...
But the truth is, I've been
putting up with it all along...
It's okay, Tinasha.
You won't be alone in the future.
I guarantee it.
You'll come and find me for sure.
You'll find happiness.
There's no way she wouldn't be lonely, huh?
I'm sorry.
Nah.
I should have put it differently.
I know just how hard you've worked.
Lanak said he'd take me to the treasury.
I see.
Thanks.
Oscar!
How'd it go?
I really found it!
A blue orb about this big.
I couldn't take it with me,
so I did a bit of tampering instead.
At the end of the day, the warding spell
against intruders will be disabled for one hour.
So I can go in myself?
Now I can finally see you again...
Do I really end up marrying you?
It's true.
Four hundred years from now,
the year 527 in the Farsas calendar.
I'll be there waiting.
I'll make sure you find happiness,
so look forward to it.
More importantly...
Don't hang around Lanak too much.
Who made you my nosy dad?
I'm not your dad or your brother.
I'm your husband.
See you later.
Yeah.
See you.
Take care...
Huh? Aeti?
You were awake?
Lanak, what are you doing here so late?
There's no mistaking it.
Why did I come to this era?
Wasn't it because if I was by her side,
I thought I could save her from that tragedy?
But four hundred years later,
she smiles so happily.
Even if I go back now,
she'll eventually find happiness.
Four hundred years...
That's way too long!
Wait, I still...
~ Two Joined Memories ~
Lanak.
Who are these people?
Don't you move, Aeti.
Looks like I made it.
This is why I said to stay away from him.
O-Oscar...
Why are you...
Kill him!
Lanak?
It's okay.
I'll take care of it.
Put up a barrier.
Protect yourself.
My goodness...
Where did you even find this man?
You exist for my sake.
So she should sacrifice herself for you
and have her flesh and blood used
to summon magical power?
Aeti...
Poor Aeti...
I love you.
I find you beautiful.
But your magic is a nuisance.
Just looking at you annoys me.
Don't listen to him, Tinasha.
His words are laced with poison.
You can move on.
Live on with courage.
Believe me.
Lanak.
Hate or loathe me all you want.
Thanks for everything.
And...
If you insist on trying to kill me,
I'll take you on.
If I had more power, you'd be...
Begin the incantations!
Y-Your Highness...
Hurry it up!
Current which flows
and flows not in this place...
What I desire is unadulterated power.
Draw upon this flesh and blood
to appear before me, power!
Lanak!
He's going to use himself as a catalyst?
Behold, Aeterna, as I surpass you!
Let me show you the power of a king!
Wh-What's this?
Oh no!
You mustn't go any further!
Stop the summoning spell!
Quiet, little girl!
This isn't good!
Oh no! I can't stop it!
If this keeps up, Tuldarr will be destroyed!
It's over, huh?
You do it.
Bring it under control.
What?
It's impossible!
You saw what happened to Lanak!
You can do it. I know you can.
You have the power.
Really?
Yeah.
This is your kingdom.
It's fine. You still have time.
You'll protect it.
Let's triumph with ease.
I'm here for you.
Here I go.
It's okay.
It's over.
Well done.
Tinasha, I ended up lying to you.
I'm sorry.
I came here to save you.
What?
So we won't meet again.
Why not?
You just need to go back
to your own time, right?
There's nowhere for me to return anymore.
It vanished when I came here.
Vanished?
I once asked Tinasha about a legend
told of a village near Minnedart Fortress.
A swordsman who traveled
from the future to save his mother.
Why was it that he disappeared after that?
The answer is simple.
The world doesn't branch off into paths.
Should you attempt to change the past,
the moment you travel back in time,
a new history begins to take its place.
In the instant that
the magic sphere is activated,
the world that the wielder
came from is destroyed.
It's a magic implement to change
the past and overwrite history.
Now that I've fulfilled my role,
I should disappear as well in due time.
That can't be true!
I mean...
If I had known about the magic
sphere's power from the start,
I wouldn't have chosen to change the past.
It's like denying
the path she's led as a witch.
To wish for all of the suffering
she's faced to be wiped away...
is nothing more than childish arrogance.
I knew that.
But even so...
I wanted to hold your hand
when you suffered the most.
I don't regret this result.
Oscar...
No...
Become a good queen, Tinasha.
You have the power to do so.
The reality of the time
I spent with you won't disappear.
Even if you forget...
Even if I forget...
Even if we never met...
I will always love you.
Wait...
Close your eyes.
Don't leave me!
Oscar?
A witch residing in an azure tower.
A royal prince struck by a curse.
If they could turn back time,
what would they wish for?
This is a story where everything
can be rewritten.