Toamna anului 998 al Erei Sfinte
Au trecut două luni de când am ajuns în regiunea Yagumo.
Încă nu am găsit niciun indiciu despre părinții mei, dar...
Toată lumea de aici are părul negru.
Cine este acela?
Bună.
Sunt un călător și caut pe cineva.
Mi-ar plăcea foarte mult să-l pot întâlni pe primarul acestui sat.
Aveți idee cine este?
Oh, b-bună.
Ești un călător? Bunica mea
este primarul acestui sat!
Serios? Dacă nu este nicio problemă, m-ai putea conduce la ea?
Oh, sigur.
Sayo, ce tot faci?
Te voi lăsa în urmă.
Așteaptă, Ruri!
Țara promisă
Bunico!
Ai un vizitator!
Un vizitator îmbrăcat
destul de neobișnuit, văd.
Este o plăcere să vă întâlnesc.
Numele meu este Rio.
Doamnă primar, am venit aici sperând să găsesc răspunsul la câteva întrebări.
Serios? Observ că ești destul de politicos.
Ai venit dintr-o altă țară?
Da, am călătorit prin multe țări.
Înțeleg. Eu sunt Yuba.
Cu ce treburi pe aici?
Ei bine, caut pe cineva.
Am venit în acest sat deoacere
am auzit că dumneavoastră cunoașteți pe toată lumea din această zonă.
This seems like it's going to be
an involved conversation. Come in.
Pe aici.
Mulțumesc pentru primire.
Am auzit că părinții mei au trăit aici,
în regiunea Yagumo acum cincisprezece ani, dar...
Înțeleg. Care erau numele părinților tăi?
Zen și Ayame.
Zen și Ayame?
Ați mai auzit aceste nume?
Ruri, Sayo, întoarceți-vă la treabă.
Ce? De ce?
Nu ar trebui să vă băgați nasul în trecutul altor persoane.
Fine. Just when it was getting interesting.
Să mergem, Sayo.
B-Bine.
Dacă mi-ai putea da puțin mai multe detalii...
Desigur. Am auzit că amândoi s-au născut în regiunea Yagumo.
My father died before I was
old enough to know him.
I lived a peaceful, happy life
with my mother, but...
My mother died, too, when I was five.
Coming to the Yagumo region was
something my mom and I promised to do.
When you're bigger, I'll take you there.
It's a place called Yagumo.
Really? You promised, okay?
Yes, I promise.
As I traveled, I started to think that
if I could find where they lived,
I'd like to make graves for them.
The least I can do for them is hold
a proper memorial in their homeland.
There's no mistake.
Both of them are people I knew.
And you do have the look of them.
Forgive my rudeness, but how
did you know my parents?
I'm Zen's mother.
What?
Your grandmother.
My father's...
Thank you for coming here.
But the truth is, I don't
know what to tell you.
We already have graves for both of them.
What?
These are Mother and Father's graves.
That's right.
Would it be all right if I paid my respects?
Yes.
I finally made it here, Mother, Father.
Both of them had to leave this country
in secret for certain reasons.
There was no possibility that
they would come home,
so those of us who knew of
the true circumstances
made graves for the two of them here.
What was the reason?
I'm sorry, but I cannot
be the one to tell you.
But the time may come that
I am able to talk about it.
What do you think? Will you live here
in the village until that time comes?
Would that be possible?
Yes. You're my grandson, after all.
Grandchildren should
never stand on manners.
Grandchild...
All of my relatives have died. Right now,
it's only Ruri and I living together.
Ruri is Zen's older brother's
daughter. Your cousin.
She's fifteen now.
She's one year older than I am, then.
Are you that young? You seem quite mature.
I'm nothing like that.
Shall we head back?
Madame Yuba?
May I stay here a little longer?
Yes. But stop addressing me so formally.
Mistress... Yuba.
Better. Don't stay out too late.
I'll keep your lineage hidden
from the others for a while.
Excuse the intrusion!
Honestly, Rio!
What took you so long? I'm starving!
Welcome back, Rio.
Hurry up! Let's eat!
Yes.
Good morning.
Morning. You're up early, aren't you?
I'll start helping with things
around the village today.
I thought I'd get breakfast
ready before that.
I'm very happy to see
that you're so motivated.
Morning, Grandma.
Miss Ruri—
Good morning.
Morning. You...
Did you forget that Rio's here?
Oh, no! What am I doing?!
Impressive. You're quite skilled.
In that case, I'll ask you to make miso soup.
It looks like we don't
have quite enough water.
Yeah. And Sayo and Shin
are coming today, too.
Rio! Use the water over there.
We refill it every day with spirit arts.
So both of them can use spirit arts.
Hot water would be better
than plain water, right?
Shall I make some?
What?
That's amazing! Rio, you can make
hot water with spirit magic!
Even Grandma can't do that!
There's a little trick to it.
I can teach you, if you want.
Yes!
Good morning.
Morning!
Man, I'm starving...
Good morning.
Who're you?
Rio and Shin haven't met yet, have they?
This is Sayo's older brother, Shin.
This boy is Rio.
He's the son of a long-time
acquaintance of mine.
I'm called Rio. Pleased to meet you.
Yeah. Nice to meet you.
This is so good!
There's meat in this!
This miso soup is delicious, too!
Rio made everything for us.
What?
Amazing!
I'm just glad you like it.
If you want, please have more.
I want more!
Honestly, Big Brother,
show a little restraint!
Man, it's only morning and I ate so much!
Shin, take Rio to Dola's place.
Huh? Why?
I was thinking of having Rio be a hunter.
Huh? Him? A hunter?
Yes. Rio says he can hunt, too.
And Dola said he wanted help, right?
But it's grueling work, you know?
Does he have the stamina?
He's built pretty delicately.
When you want to make hot water,
He'll be fine. He's strong enough to have
traveled to many countries at his age.
you concentrate your will in
your hand like this, and...
Really? I see.
And he can use spirit arts.
Even I can use something
like the spirit arts.
He may be overwhelmingly stronger
than someone like you.
Bah.
Hey, Rio!
I'm gonna take you hunting!
Make sure you don't get in the way!
Big Brother!
Sir Rio, I'm so sorry. My brother
speaks rather sharply.
Not at all.
Would it be all right for
me to leave the rest to you?
Huh? Sure.
Hey, why is it "sir" Rio?
What?
I-I mean, he sort of feels like a noble.
Like someone too high up to be reached...
I see.
It's a lenou bird.
Good job shooting it down, Rio!
Your skills are impressive.
All right, we can't let
him beat us, right, Shin?
Huh?
I get it already!
Blast it!
All right, let's head back.
Good job, both of you.
Today we'll be able to give everyone
in the village more meat than usual.
I didn't manage to take
down a single one, though.
It was you and Rio that got
these results, Huntmaster.
What are you sulking for?
It was the three of us working
together that got these results.
Bah.
Sorry.
I'll talk to him later.
Can you come help starting tomorrow?
Yes, you can count on me.
I got pretty dirty out there.
Discharge.
What is this thing?
I thought it must be you, Rio!
I'm sorry. That must have been a shock.
I'll clean it up now.
No, it's fine, but...
Did you make this with spirit arts, too?
Yes. I wanted to take a bath.
Really?
Huh?
Miss Ruri?
You smell nice, Rio!
Sayo, you come smell, too!
What? No, I-I'm fine!
Now, now. No need to get so embarrassed!
What is that smell?
It's soap.
Soap? You mean the stuff you wash yourself
and clothes and things with? That soap?
Sir Rio, you can make soap, too?
Amazing...
What is this thing?
Big Brother! Sir Rio made it
for us! He says it's a bath!
A bath?
There goes the outsider
trying to score points.
You really are rude.
Rio, pay no attention to him.
Miss Ruri is right. Big Brother, that was mean!
Sayo, not you, too? Don't go getting
all silly over some weakling!
I'm not being silly!
Shin! Rio isn't a weakling!
In spite of his looks,
he's got a lot of muscle!
Right?
Huh?
Y-You... have you no shame?!
Bleh.
Hmph!
Sayo, we're going home.
I came here to pick... you...
Bah!
The crops turned out well again this year.
I heard that the tax examiner
will be coming soon.
Yes.
Oh, that's right. Given your skills,
I have a favor to ask you.
Yes?
After the annual tribute and our own rations,
the rice that remains is to
be sold in the royal capital.
Could I ask you to guard the transport team?
If you think I'm good enough.
That's a great help.
It's a fight!
It's Shin and those guys
from the other village!
Gon! Who do you think you are
just walking around our village?!
And you're just heading into the
bathing hut like it's nothing!
You've gotta be kidding me!
Huh?
I'm here as a guest to visit the head
of your village. That should be obvious.
Ruri... You've grown into quite
the woman since I last saw you.
And behind you is...
Don't look at my little sister
with those filthy eyes!
Oh, she's your sister, is she?
Still, she's a stunner.
You...
Shin, don't!
If you punch this guy over these
pathetic taunts, it'll cause problems.
He may be rotten, but he's the son of
the head of the neighboring village!
Gon, why are you here in our village anyway?
Let me stay at your place, won't you?
What?
I'm on my way to sell trade
goods in the royal capital.
but unfortunately, my cart broke.
It'll take time to repair.
Then we'll lend you one of our guest huts.
Hey, now. I might be your husband
one day. That's pretty cold of you.
D-Don't say weird things
like that! It's disgusting!
The head of this village
only has you for an heir.
So I'm saying I'll volunteer
to be your husband.
You can't be serious!
We villagers will never allow it!
That's right!
Huh? None of you are
Ruri's man, but you're jealous?
What a bunch of sissies.
What did you say?
Bring it on.
You piece of crap!
Shin!
In the end, this is all you've got?
Big Brother!
Stop it!
That's enough!
Old Lady Yuba. It's been a while.
First, let him go! Talk comes after that.
Big Brother!
Oh, dear.
I see.
Gon, I apologize for Shin and
the others' misunderstanding.
But your behavior was imprudent, too.
You went too far.
Tonight, we will lend you a guest
hut at the edge of the village.
But you are not allowed to
leave it. Do you understand?
Sure thing.
A newcomer?
He's effeminate. I don't like him.
Big Bro?
Oh, dear. Are you all right?
What happened?
I-It's nothing. Let's go.
Man, now my clothes are dirty.
Everyone just go back home
quietly for today, all right?
I've forbidden them from leaving the hut,
but don't let down your guard!
Hey, Gran.
Will you let Sayo stay with you for a while?
The two of us live alone, so...
I think she'd feel safer
with you and Ruri around.
Yes. That's no problem.
Sayo, that's what we'll do.
Yes, Madame.
We should go to sleep.
Yes.
Miss Ruri, Miss Sayo...
Sir Rio...
Please put this in a corner of your room.
It's a protective amulet.
A protective amulet?
It's beautiful!
Sir Rio, thank you so much!
That's our big bro for you!
Of course. I made sure to
bust up the cart really well.
We can take all day tomorrow
repairing it at our leisure.
The fun comes after that.
Madame Yuba!
It's been a long time.
Welcome! Thank you for coming all this way!
Pleased to meet you. I'm called Rio.
I'm called Saga Hayate.
I'm traveling to all the
villages as tax examiner.
I hope you'll take good
care of my aides, too.
Watching like that can't possibly be any fun.
Your movement's so pretty,
we couldn't help watching!
It's just simple training.
No, no, it's really impressive!
You've done it every day since
you came to the village, right?
Why did you start martial arts?
Well...
Even if I die, I'll protect you, Mii-chan!
It's a little embarrassing to say...
What? I want to know even
more now! Right, Sayo?
What? Yes. I'd like to know.
Well, this is a problem.
Do you mind if I dress myself?
Huh? Oh, please go ahead.
When I was little,
there was a girl I liked...
I wanted to become strong enough
that I could protect her.
Wow, really?
What is she doing now?
We're not in contact anymore.
She might be with someone she loves.
And I don't know if she even
remembers me in the first place.
I don't know where she's living, either.
But if she's alive, then you
might meet again one day.
Right, Sayo?
Y-Yes.
That's true.
Though, right now, I'm training for myself.
That bath was truly wonderful!
Thank you very much.
I'm glad to hear it.
Miss Ruri, you two should go ahead and
use the bath first. It's getting chilly.
That's true.
Let's go then, Sayo.
Yes.
Quiet. I'm not responsible for
what happens if you struggle.
Miss Ruri!
If you make a fuss, I'll punch
her right in the face.
And you, too.
Y-You...
What are you doing?
Crap.
St...op...
Stop?
Sir Rio...
Sir Rio, stop!
This is bad!
Sir Rio! Cease! If you hit
him any more, he'll die!
Is that Gon?
It seems he was trying to assault
Lady Ruri and Lady Sayo.
I'll handle this.
Lady Yuba, please see to the two of them.
Ruri, Sayo, come with me.
Am I correct in that you lot are
the ones who caused this uproar?
Y...es...
You have committed a grave crime.
I seek punishment from the kingdom.
Send a messenger!
Yes, sir!
This is the second time I've
wanted to kill someone.
As Rio, I've had this feeling
inside me all this time.
But...
without me noticing,
I've been pulled closer to Amakawa Haruto.
I turned my eyes away from my revenge.
Even though, in the end, I...
I'm the same sort of person as that man.
Tomorrow morning, a messenger
from the kingdom will arrive.
They've decided that Gon and the
others will be taken into custody.
Everyone.
I caused you such trouble yesterday.
I can't apologize enough.
You have nothing to apologize for.
Thank you for protecting Ruri and Sayo.
Yeah. It's only because you arrived
so quickly that I was safe.
Sir Rio, it was only because you wanted
to protect us that you got so angry!
If you hadn't hit him, Sir Rio, I would have.
Everyone... thank you so much.
But, please... let me apologize
just one more time.
You're so serious.
Just like a certain someone.
Who?
Well, let's have breakfast.
Sir Rio, I'm hungry!
Yeah. Let's hurry and eat!
Data viitoare
Descendența regală
"Descendența regală."
By Minazuki Futago
Rio! Haide să luăm prânzul împreună!
Bine.
Rio! Haide să facem baie împreună!
Bine...
Ce?!
Hi-hi