Charles Arbor?
Cu el se va căsători doamna profesoară Celia?
Ei bine, e genul de căsătorie făcută doar pentru avantaje.
Și prin asta vrei să spui...
În ultimul conflict,
Regatul Beltrum a suferit o înfrângere zdrobitoarea în fața Imperiului Proxia.
Mulțumită acțiunilor casei ducelui Arbor,
am reușit într-un final să începem negocierile pentru pace,
dar puterea și autoritatea familiei regale au fost pierdute.
Când facțiunea ducelui Huguenot a fost trasă la răspundere,
aceasta a fugit din capitala regală.
Casa ducelui Arbor s-a mobilizat
și ceea ce au ales pentru a obține mai multă putere
a fost casa contelui Claire.
Dna profesoară Celia... nu, casa contelui Claire își dorește acest mariaj politic?
Nu știu.
Nu cunosc asemenea detalii.
Ce vei face, Haruto?
Ceremonia de căsătorie este mâine.
Înainte să aibă loc, vreau s-o văd pe dna profesoară Celia și s-o întreb personal.
Bine.
Dar doamna profesoară e în castel.
Apărarea de acolo va fi și mai strânsă decât cea a academiei.
În acest caz, îmi voi folosi forma spirituală și voi investiga.
Un spirit în forma spirituală e o masă de energie spirituală și mana...
Ar putea exista lucruri în castel astfel încât să detecteze puterea magică neobișnuită.
Crezi că vei fi în regulă?
Pot vedea barierele puse să detecteze magia.
Înțeleg.
O-Oh, dar Aishia, tu și doamna profesoară încă nu v-ați...
Știu cum arată Celia.
În acest caz, mă bazez pe tine.
Da, contează pe mine.
Mireasa de Argint
Îmi cer scuze, Celia.
Nu am reușit să vin și să te văd deloc.
Iar acum... E deja noaptea de dinaintea nunții.
E în regulă, tată. Erai ocupat cu treburi oficiale.
Dle conte Claire...
Nu, bănuiesc ar trebui să vă spun "tată-socru" acum, nu?
Pregătirile pentru ceremonie sunt complete. Vă rog să fiți fără griji.
Am auzit că această ceremonie va fi un eveniment mare.
Da.
Doar e o nuntă între casa ducelui Arbor
și casa contelui Claire.
Vom putea să le arătăm celor din regat, dar și celor din afara lui,
că puterea Regatului Beltrum e de neclintit.
Dar...
starea lucrurilor din regat încă e haotică.
Mă aștept ca securitatea va fi de nepătruns, nu-i așa?
Desigur!
The Knights of the Royal Guard,
the Mage Corps, and others...
I-am adus în regatul nostru pe cei mai buni.
Then I do feel more at ease. However...
I suppose worrying about everything
is part of parental love.
Mersi, tată.
Instead of you worrying for us,
Father, we are worried about you!
For some time, strange rumors
have been flowing from the royal court.
That you and a portion of the nobles
have been secretly in contact with
Duke Huguenot, who fled the kingdom.
That slander is completely unfounded.
Yes, I know.
But it is true that trust
in you has been shaken.
I would never betray this kingdom.
Father, please don't worry.
My marriage to Celia is partly
to help protect your standing.
The House of Duke Arbor would never
abandon the House of Count Claire.
And I am very grateful for that.
Father, soon we'll have
you serve as commander and director
of the House of Duke Arbor.
That's all right with you, isn't it?
That sounds like a threat...
My dear Celia, I am truly sorry.
If I were better at maneuvering...
I understand. I will do everything in
my power to fulfill this responsibility.
Well, then! To the peace and
prosperity of both our houses!
And to this beautiful bride.
To the both of you.
We are in your care, Lord Charles.
Father and I will both dedicate
ourselves entirely to this.
No, it is I who am grateful to you.
I look forward to the
wedding ceremony tomorrow.
Yes.
The defenses are very strong,
just as I thought.
Perhaps it's in preparation for tomorrow.
Haruto, I've found where Celia is.
Good. Where is she?
She's outside the palace.
Start at the main gate. On the left,
a fair ways in, there's a large building.
Understood. I'll head there now.
It's been such a long time
since I've seen Father,
but we weren't able to speak
as parent and child at all.
Still, with this, Father and the
House of Claire will be all right.
All that's left...
is for me to become that man's
property for the rest of my life.
Here at the very end...
I wish I could have seen him again.
For certain, absolutely certain, understand?
Stay safe...
until you return, all right?
I think probably...
the feelings I have for Rio are...
Cine-i acolo?
Nu spune nimic.
Sunt eu, doamnă profesoară Celia.
Rio.
Ce?
Oh.
Nu ne-am văzut de mult.
R-Rio?
Da.
Chiar ești tu, Rio?
M-am întors, exact așa cum am promis.
Deși, mi-a luat patru ani ca s-o fac.
Rio!
Chiar ești tu.
D-Doamna profesoară...
Da...
Chiar ești aici și nu e un vis.
Doamna profesoară, mi-a fost dor de tine.
Da, și mie!
În tot acest timp...
Da.
Rio...
Observ că te-ai mai înălțat.
Observ că tu nu te-ai schimbat deloc, doamna profesoară.
A-Am devenit puțin mai feminină!
Așa este.
Ai fost mereu frumoasă, dar acum ai devenit și mai atractivă.
There you go, saying things
like that again!
You've grown dashing, Rio.
Puternic și elegant.
Mersi.
S-Sunt așa fericită că te-ai întors teafăr.
Stai...
Cum ai ajuns aici?
Nu te-ai strecurat, nu-i așa?
Ei bine, ba da...
O, da! Ai reușit să ajungi în regiunea Yagumo? Pe unde altundeva ai mai fost?
Vreau să-mi povestești totul!
D-Da...
O, stai.
Ai dori niște ceai? Voi aduce chiar acum.
Beam adesea ceai împreună, doar noi doi, nu?
Da, așa este.
După ce ai plecat, am ajuns să beau ceai mereu singură, știi?
Dna profesoară... Te vei căsători, nu-i așa?
Am auzit că mirele este Charles Arbor.
D-Da.
Așa este.
Știu că e nepoliticos să întreb așa dintr-odată, dar...
Și tu îți dorești această nuntă?
Îmi cer scuze că întreb asta.
Dar când am auzit că ceremonia e mâine...
Desigur, și eu am fost de acord cu acestă nuntă.
Chiar dacă persoana cu care te vei căsători e... Charles Arbor?
He's someone you have an ill-fated
connection with, isn't he?
I thought perhaps
this might have something to do with
the circumstances of your family.
No. I am of age, after all.
Nu mă pot gândi doar la cercetările mele pentru totdeauna.
Serios?
Da!
And in spite of appearances, Lord Charles
is chivalrous and kind toward women!
Dna profesoară...
În acest caz, te vei căsători tu cu mine, Rio?
Sau mă vei lua și mă vei duce undeva departe și-ți vei trai restul vieții cu mine?
Eu... ei bine...
Glumeam doar.
Ce?
Îmi cer scuze. Uită ce am spus, te rog.
Dna profesoară...
Rio, ar trebui să pleci.
Nu am terminat încă de vorbit.
Nu mai poți rămâne. Oamenii care mă supraveghează vor fi aici curând.
Mă voi trezi foarte de dimineață mâine și încă mai sunt multe pregătiri de făcut.
Mă bucur că am reușit să te văd înainte de ceremonie.
Oh...
Și nu veni mâine la ceremonie. Ar fi prea jenant.
Acum, haide, grăbește-te și fugi.
Ai grijă să nu fii prins când pleci.
Voi închide acea ușă și-ți voi oferi douăzeci de secunde ca să pleci.
Haide.
Dacă nu te grăbești să pleci, voi striga.
Haide!
Unu, doi, trei, patru, cinci, șase...
Mersi, Rio...
că te-ai întors, așa cum ai promis.
Chiar m-a bucurat.
Dar nu pot lăsa să fii prins în asta.
Adio, Rio.
Haruto?
Nu am reușit să-i aflu adevăratele sentimente.
Ce vei face acum?
Nu știu.
But I want to know a little more
about what's motivating this wedding.
Te voi ajuta.
Scuze.
De ce-ți ceri scuze?
Deoarece trebuie să mă ajuți mereu, Aishia.
Cred că ți-am mai spus. Voi fi mereu de partea ta, Haruto.
Dacă ai nevoie de mine, mă poți căuta oricând.
Mersi.
Fall in!
Sir!
Right face!
Lord Charles, l-am adus pe domnul Reiss.
Ah!
Reiss!
Allow me to offer congratulations
on this, the event of your wedding.
Thank you so much for coming!
With our relationship?
I am delighted to attend.
Yes, thank you!
When did you arrive in our royal capital?
I've just arrived.
If I'd known earlier that you'd be staying,
I'd have provided a proper welcome!
No, please don't trouble yourself.
Though we are officially at peace
with the Kingdom of Beltrum,
we two are from enemy countries.
If you are too friendly with me, I am sure
there are some who would not be amused.
I see.
So this time, I will keep my visit quiet.
I am touched by your consideration.
It's fine.
But once the ceremony is over,
please come to my home!
Tonight is your first night together.
I will visit another day.
Oh, well, I...
To take such trouble and to be
so considerate is quite, well...
I sense a spirit.
It's quite a powerful one.
Sir Reiss...
Is something wrong?
No, nothing.
I will go to the ceremony hall
early and wait there.
Allow me to send someone
to show you the way.
You there! Show Sir Reiss to the ceremony hall.
I am honored.
Sir!
Be sure to show him every courtesy.
It's disappeared.
Yes, sir.
Everything is fine.
I am a doll.
I have no feelings. I am just a doll.
Celia...
Please come out here a moment.
Yes, I'll be right out!
Oh, my...
You look m-magnificent, Celia! Truly beautiful!
Thank you very much, Lord Charles.
Very nice... Truly wonderful!
Even better than I'd imagined!
Are you nervous?
Don't worry. I am here.
Yes.
And, you see, I thought it might
help you feel more relaxed,
so I've brought my wives.
You should take this opportunity
to become friends.
Tenasina, take care of the rest, won't you?
Leave it to me.
I am his first wife, Tenasina.
There is something I would like to
make clear from the very beginning.
Y-Yes?
Normally you, the daughter of a count,
would be superior to us in social standing.
But once you have married Lord Charles,
as his seventh wife, your place
amongst us is at the very bottom.
Of course. I understand.
I will not allow any impertinent behavior.
It shall be as you say.
I am inexperienced and inept,
but I hope you will look on me kindly.
Your complexion looks terrible.
You are going to be a bride of the
House of Duke Arbor, you know.
Smile more brightly.
Y-Yes.
Well, I suppose that will do.
L-Lady Celia!
What is all this noise?
Her Highness, Princess Christina,
First Princess of the Realm is here!
Princess Christina?
Let her through right away!
Yes, my lady!
Who gave you leave to—
My deepest apologies!
But would it not shame the House of Duke Arbor
to keep Princess Christina waiting?
Princess Christina!
What an honor to see you!
I am sorry for arriving
so suddenly, with no prior notice.
Please, don't trouble yourselves for me.
Thank you so much for
coming, Princess Christina!
My!
You look beautiful, Professor!
That wedding dress suits
you wonderfully well!
Th-Thank you very much.
Princess Christina, please come
inside and rest at your leisure!
I was hoping to speak with my
former teacher, Professor Celia, in private.
Oh! P-P-Please forgive my impertinence!
W-Well then, we will take our leave.
Now, ladies, let us go!
Professor, I've come to offer congratulations
in place of my mother and father.
Thank you very much.
You truly are beautiful, Professor!
I-I accept your words of praise
with a heart full of gratitude.
I'm glad.
What?
Your complexion looks a little
better than it did earlier.
O-Oh...
Did those individuals say
something unpleasant to you?
No. I was just so nervous yesterday
that I didn't sleep well.
I think that might be the cause.
I see.
It really has been a while, hasn't it?
Princess Christina, I'm so
happy to see you again!
So am I!
It's thanks to you, Professor, that I'm
finally able to be outside like this.
For so long, I had been confined in the palace.
The scrutiny of Duke Arbor's faction
is quite stringent, isn't it?
In my case, the inadequacy of the
royal family is the cause of it.
I believe Flora feels the same.
When Duke Huguenot fled
the kingdom with Princess Flora ...
I'm sure it must have been painful.
It made me see that all faith in the
power of the royal family had been lost.
And the ill effects of that have
resulted in your wedding, Professor.
I am truly sorry for all of this!
P-Princess Christina!
This wedding is something I decided upon!
Why are you apologizing?
Because I've stolen your
smile from you, Professor.
While I attended the Academy,
I admired and looked up
to you, Professor Celia.
Back then, Professor, you seemed
so clearly happy, unlike now.
Now, you're like a bird locked in a cage.
If there were ever a chance for you to
regain the smile you had back then...
Princess Christina...
I swear I will do everything in my
power to help when the time comes.
Thank you.
And I will pray that you and
Princess Flora will one day be reunited.
It looks to be a lavish ceremony.
Yes, it will be.
We should get going—
Alfred...
You are about to gloriously take command
of the assembled forces, are you not?
After all, you are the strongest
warrior in the kingdom.
Your skills have caused some
to call you the King's Sword.
But how unfortunate for you.
I have authority over the
security for the ceremony.
You have no choice but to obey my orders.
I only ever think of how
I might fulfill my bounden duty.
Well, don't go showing off.
Primăvara anului 1000 al Erei Sfinte.
Primăvara anului 1000 al Erei Sfinte
Thus, the wedding ceremony between
Professor Celia and Charles Arbor began.
Nu pot vedea!
Uite-i că vin!
Aproape au ajuns aici!
Trec podul!
Îi văd!
Uite-i!
Uimitor!
That's a huge procession!
Oh, it's the bride!
She's all silver...
Trăiască Mireasa de Argint!
Mireasa de Argint!
Înțeleg. Mireasa de Argint, nu?
Coming from ignorant peasants,
that's not a bad appellation.
Well, it just shows how
very beautiful you are.
Th-Thank you.
When I think that very soon you
will be mine and mine alone...
I look forward to the moment
we kiss to seal our oaths.
Trăiască Casa Arbor!
Trăiască lordul Charles Arbor!
Într-o bună zi, acest regat va fi al meu.
Iar tu vei fi soția mea.
Are they here yet?
Haruto, Celia e aproape.
Așa se pare.
Haruto, ești foarte calm.
Asta se datorează ție, Aishia.
Eu doar am investigat. Nu a fost mare lucru.
Nu e adevărat. Mulțumită ție, acum știu mult mai multe.
E mireasa!
Îi văd!
E așa de frumoasă!
Trăiască mireasa!
Trăiască Mireasa de Argint!
Lord Charles! Lord Charles!
Doamna profesoară...
Haruto, voi merge acum.
Da.
Celia?
Ce? Ce?
Celia, rămâi calmă.
Cine ești?
Sunt Aishia.
Haruto... nu, Rio mi-a cerut să vorbesc cu tine astfel.
Rio?
Privește în dreapta ta.
Rio...
Rio!
De ce ești aici?
Ți-am spus să nu vii!
Rio, tu erai singura persoană care nu voiam să mă vadă astfel!
Hei! Ce s-a întâmplat, Celia?
Oh, eu...
Nu sunt sigură. Am atât de multe emoții adunate înăuntrul meu...
Înțeleg. Plângi de fericire, nu? Nu știam că-ți pasă atât de mult de mine.
Dar trebui să fim impozanți acum.
Toată lumea ne privește, știi?
Da.
Bun.
Aishia, mă poți auzi?
Unde s-a dus Rio?
Totul a fost... doar o iluzie?
Celia...
Sunt... doar o păpușă.
Oprește-te acum!
Grăbiți-vă!
Prindeți-l!
Avem un intrus!
Data viitoare
Reuniune predestinată
„Reuniune predestinată.”
Cronicile spiritelor
Exciting Bonus Manga
Rio!
By Minazuki Futago
fwhoosh
Professor
Celia!
whoom
ziiing
Hah
pop
Miau
E o pisică
Serios...
Tu chiar poți folosi magie de transformat ființe în pisici...