"Saitama City"
"City of Roses"
"Chuo Ward"
"Bonus Lv. 1:
'Most strange spell names
have unknown origins'"
Oh!
"Sparklers"
We're almost out.
And it'll be all over.
Well, I'm gonna go out with a bang!
Ha!
Hi-yah!
--Ooh! Niiice!
--Hey! That's dangerous!
This reminds me of that fireworks show
in our first year.
Oh, last year in Konosu?
Yeah! That's when you and Tama first met.
First...?
Right!
Yeah.
You and Mimimi hadn't talked much at all
by the summer of our first year.
Uh-huh. Not at first.
That's right.
Wow! You're wearing your
winter uniform already?
Yep! I know it's still a little hot today,
but this blazer is just so cute!
I might just make the
switch tomorrow, too.
--Let's switch to blazers tomorrow!
--What, already?
A girl in your class
who's kind of a loner, huh?
I'm pretty sure she wants
to be friends with everyone.
Okay, then try talking to her
a little bit every day.
Know what, Natsubayashi?
You're so cute--like a tiny little animal!
Huh? Um... what?
Poke, poke!
Wh-Where'd this come from?
This? Oh... nowhere special.
Hi, Hanabi! Good morning!
Not you again! Stop that!
Ooh, all your protests
really get me going!
What's your endgame here?
Hanabi! Good morning!
Seriously, what's your deal?
You smell divine.
Don't just go around smelling people!
Hey, Hanabi!
Let's hit the cafeteria!
I brought my lunch today.
Oh, that doesn't matter!
Let's eat together in the caf!
Um, well...
C'mon, now, hurry it up!
Okay.
All that sexual harassment
must really suck.
Mimimi doesn't know when to quit.
Hey, you big meanie!
No. She really doesn't.
Wow, super blunt!
Hello!
I'm Aoi Hinami, from first-year class 1.
You must be the Hanabi Natsubayashi
that Mimimi's been bugging.
Huh?
So Minmi's been doing this
all along to help me fit in?
Uh-huh.
Oh... oh, I see.
But keep this conversation
between us, would you?
Huh? But I haven't thanked Minmi.
I know, but that's okay.
Just let her keep up her front, okay?
Really? Sounds like it was a success.
¡Si! Thanks, Aoi!
I haven't done anything.
Oh, right!
Hey, listen, Aoi:
Did you hear about the off-season
fireworks show this weekend?
This weekend?
Oh, the Konosu Fireworks Festival?
¡Si! Nice, Aoi--you're a sharp one!
I was thinking about going myself.
Aren't they firing off some Guinness
World Record-breaking shell?
Yeah! We can go together!
Great!
And hey...
I kinda wanted to ask Hanabi to come, too.
Hanabi?
You mean the girl whose face
you've been in every day?
Uh-huh.
Um... are you sure?
I'm in a different class and all.
I mean, your advice helped me
and Hanabi become friends.
I want you two to be friends, too.
I'd love for you to meet her!
Oh, I get it. Then yes--introduce us!
A fireworks show?
Okay, you might not be a fan,
but there's this friend
I want to you to meet!
We do track-and-field together:
Aoi Hinami.
Aoi Hinami?
She's another ultra-cutie pie!
Well?
Well? Well?
All right. I'll come.
Whoa! What an easy yes!
Don't tell me you're
a sucker for cuties, too.
Well, uh...
Yeah... something like that.
"Guinness World Record"
"4-Shaku Tama"
"Konosu Station"
"Today"
"Minami Nanami: Aoi & I are on our way!"
"Minami Nanami: Almost there!"
"Today"
"Minami Nanami: Aoi & I are on our way!"
"Minami Nanami: Almost there!"
I suppose I should pretend
we've never met.
It's hard, fitting in.
There you are, Hanabi!
And this here is Aoi--
cutie pie extraordinaire!
Nice to meet you! I'm Aoi Hinami.
Let's make it a great day.
Um... I'm Hanabi Natsubayashi. Pleasure.
You're so adorably tiny!
Say, I know this is sudden,
but can I call you Hanabi?
Eh? Uh-huh, sure.
Oh, and either Hinami or Aoi works for me.
Okay. Um... Aoi?
Here!
Ooh, you're getting along great already!
Thanks.
Hmm? For what?
Wow, look at those lines.
Aren't their croquettes a thing?
That's right! But I, Minami Nanami,
have a taste for grilled squid!
How about we split up
and buy both to share?
Good idea! Let's do that!
Okay!
What about you, Hanabi? Want to try both?
Um... I'm fine with just a croquette.
Got it!
The grilled squid is calling me.
Which means it's up to you two
to pick up the croquettes!
I can go by myself. It's just croquettes.
Is three enough?
Um... I think so.
Thanks in advance!
Sure thing.
"Yummy!"
"Grilled Squid"
That Hanabi's a tough one, huh?
Right? But that's what
makes her so delicious!
Whoa there, Mimimi. Scary.
But you can tell, right?
She's a good, no-nonsense girl.
You, me, everyone--we can
be better friends with her.
How can we make that happen?
Hmm. Good question.
Do you remember what got
everyone to warm up to you?
Was there something?
Oh!
So was there?
When I started going by "Mimimi"--
that might've made it easier
to talk to me.
All like, "Mimimi!"
Then let's do that!
Huh? Do what?
A nickname!
No crowds here, huh?
Can't have you underestimating
my research skills, now.
Oh! It's starting!
What beautiful hanabi fireworks.
Oh, but this Hanabi is the cute kind.
Hey! That was dumb!
Do you like hanabi, Hanabi?
C'mon, you're doing that on purpose!
Well, I love Hanabi!
I'm a different Hanabi!
--Hanabi!
--Sorry, sorry!
Tamaya!
I haven't heard that old cheer in a while.
I think I'll do it, too.
Tamaya!
Aren't you gonna say it, Hanabi?
Well, um...
Tamaya!
Huh? Wh-What the--?
Because you're hanabi, too.
You make no sense!
Tamaya!
H-Hey, now!
Don't mess around with people's names!
Oh, Tama, you're so strict!
What's this "Tama" business?
Like a fireworks shell.
You're Hanabi, so: Tama!
A great fit, right? Little and cute!
I-It's not cute at all!
Really? I think it's cute.
Not you, too!
C'mon, now, Tama!
Are you blushing, Tama?
Sheesh...
Ooh! Tamaya!
Tamaya!
Ta... Tamaya!
Hey! Tama's shouting "Tamaya"!
I'm not a firework!
Minmi is such an idiot.
Catch you later, Tama!
Yeah, yeah. See you, Minmi, Aoi.
Bye now!
Oh, man, that was a blast!
It sure was.
You know, since you're involved,
we'd best not tell Hanabi
we gave her that nickname
for her own good.
Well, I'm using it because I like it!
Oh, Mimimi. Always trying
to help out in secret.
"Fireworks"
Pretty rich coming from you, Aoi.
It's all over.
Yeah.
Then let's head back.
Right.
Uh-huh.
Trash: collected! Fire: extinguished!
All right, let's hit it, Aoi--and Tama!
Okay!
We were just leaving, you know?
--Tamaya!
--Oh, hush!
"Saitama City"
"City of Roses"
"Chuo Ward"