"Bottom-Tier Character Tomozaki"
Meniul cu deserturi al lunii august
Înghețată cu sirop de fasole dulce
Înghețată cu sirop de lămâie
"Bonus Lv. 2:
Post-game equipment for girls
is a little different than usual"
Vă mulțumesc pentru răbdare.
Aici înghețata ta cu sirop de lămâie,
iar aici înghețata cu sirop de fasole dulce.
Relaxați-vă și savurați-le!
Era super drăguță, nu?
Da, și eu eram de aceeași părere! Super drăguță!
Poți lua pauză acum, Fuuka.
Bine.
Se pare că Nakagawa termină de pregătit o comandă,
deci o voi livra și apoi îmi voi lua pauza.
Oh, ai face asta?
Mersi mult, Kikuchi.
Totul este gata. Ai putea s-o duci?
Desigur.
Kikuchi este așa de drăguță și o persoană așa de amabilă.
Chiar este. Și nu ești deloc de nasul ei.
Da, nu ai nicio șansă.
Uau, asta a fost urât, șefule!
Bun, voi lua pauza acum.
Bine.
Bucură-te de ea!
Vara aproape s-a terminat, nu?
Fumiya Tomozaki
A trecut cât ai clipi
"It really did"
"BTW, I finished Kind Dogs Stand Alone!
Let me know when you're done--
I want to talk about it with you"
"Ichibangai"
Să vedem...
Este așa de cald. Înghețatele noastre se vor topi.
Nici măcar nu am cumpărat!
O, cred că este drept în față.
Am reușit!
Nu este acest loc...
Hei, dacă lucrează astăzi Kikuchi?
Given her personality,
she may be overly polite.
I can see that, yeah.
All riiight! Let's head on in!
C'mon, Fumiya.
R-Right.
He never did write back...
To-Tomozaki?!
And a bunch of people from our class!
What's up?
Wow, I've never heard you be that loud!
You must have been really startled.
Um... I was.
I guess Kikuchi... isn't here today?
What's up, Fumiya?
Jeez, did I startle you that much?
You don't have to be so loud.
You sure are acting weird, Tomozaki.
Why, you...
Mmm, how to choose...
Does everyone know what they're getting?
Yep. I do.
I've decided, too.
So have I--I think.
You know I've got it down!
What? Everyone but me?! Hang on a second!
Hurry up or it'll get cold.
Hey! We don't even have
any of our food yet!
Oh, right.
Oh, I get it now.
That's fine. I'll take
that half of the floor,
and you can take the other half.
Is that okay with you, boss?
Sure. You're a good worker, after all.
Thank you so much.
Her classmates are here, eh?
That Fuka's a shy one.
She sure is.
What if one of them is a boy she likes?
Wh-What, Fuka?!
That's one huge overreaction, boss.
And he bought us a matching pair.
Afterwards, we rode the Ferris wheel--
Here we go! The Ferris wheel!
Ooh! Can it be?
Did Shuji finally...?
Nothing happened, and the ride ended.
No way! Make a move, Shuji!
Right? Right?!
Still, I saw that coming.
T-Totally.
Did he not start dating right away
when he was with Shimano?
He saw his chance and wound up
going for it pretty quickly, yeah.
I thought so!
Maybe Shuji just isn't
interested in me after all.
Mmm, I think he's acting like this
because he likes you.
He really cares, so he
doesn't want to hurt you.
Y-Yeah, I get that.
R-Really?
I think you can breathe easy.
Oh, okay.
Well, all right. If you say so.
Honestly. You two are both
as naïve as each other.
You hush!
You don't even have
a special someone, Hiro!
Who, me? I sure do.
You don't even have
a special someone, Hiro!
A-A special someone?
I-I shouldn't!
This is basically eavesdropping!
Order up!
Wh-What's this?
A cheese-stuffed Hamburg steak
with cheese sauce.
Someone must really like cheese, huh?
This is probably Hinami's!
What?! You do have someone
you like, Hiro? What's she like?
Hmm, good question.
I am dying of curiosity over here!
Yeah, I'm crazy curious myself!
You can say that again.
Well, you know...
We can talk and talk
and she stays mysterious--
and before I knew it, she had me
in the palm of her hand.
Oh, come on, you big tease! Is she older?
Nope, our age.
Huh!
A girl our age, and you're
wrapped around her little finger?
I wonder what she's like?
I can't even imagine!
Th-That's right. Can't even imagine.
Right? Plus, she's such a hard worker--
Thank you for your patience!
Who had the cheese-stuffed
Hamburg steak with cheese sauce?
Me!
And when she happens to smile,
it's so innocent and charming.
Like that.
Oh, really?
Well, gee, that's fantastic!
Whoa!
Seriously?
So everyone at that table
is a classmate of yours?
Th-That's right.
That sure is a bunch of
good-looking people, though.
Y-You think so?
Oh, but maybe not that one guy.
Yeah, that guy's more burly than handsome.
That... that would be Takei.
Yummo!
Man, that was delicious!
It really was!
This was fun!
You do appreciate a good love-life chat.
We heard all kinds of
interesting tidbits today, right?
Right!
Man, I wish I had a love life!
All right, then: shall we?
Okay!
Where to next, gang?
Nice work today, Fuka.
Thank you. I'll be leaving now.
See you later!
Good job!
I know I caused a lot of problems
for everyone today.
No, not at all. You're always
a soothing presence around here.
Exactly right.
Good thing they didn't spot you!
Right!
Was it a good thing?
It's almost like there's a whole other
world out there that isn't mine.
But I chose to avoid it.
"I should be done reading it tonight,
so let's discuss our takes on it tomorrow!
And hey, weren't you at your
job around noon today?"
"Tomozaki,"
"Tomozaki,
you always manage to find me"
"And hey, weren't you at your
job around noon today?"
"Yes, I was. You could tell, huh?"