Seventy-two...
Seventy-three...
Seventy-four...
How many times was that?!
Seventy... five?
New record!
Let's go!
Four...
Five...
Six...
Please! One more!
No.
You promised we'd stop after
the next time you dropped it.
Aw! Just one more time! Please! C'mon!
It had me just bawling!
Can you even make a bad medical drama?
Go on without me, okay?
Ayano... I heard you quit
the badminton club.
No one's good enough.
It's okay.
Mom said I should quit.
There's gonna be a girl called
Kaoruko on my new team.
She's really good! I can't wait!
Octo-octo...
Your mom left?
Ayano, you're trying for Kitakomachi, too?
Yeah. I wanna go to school with you, Elena.
You're not gonna play badminton anymore?
I think there's gotta be way
more fun stuff out there!
Elena... I'll be waiting outside, okay?
You two are pretty close, huh?
But wow! Did you see that
smash Ayano-san made before?
So amazing!
I actually squeed when I saw it!
Oh... really?
When I see stuff like that, I start
to think I could fall for a girlー
Nothing ventured, nothing gained.
Sorry, Noriko.
I'm not joining the tennis club after all.
Ayano, come over here!
Wait, Elena!
Are you...
I really think you should
be playing badminton.
Ea era perfectă
Morning!
Miyako-sensei said we have to have
them in by the end of the week.
But I haven't made up my mind yeｔ—
What's wrong, Noriko?
We'd planned to go to a movie.
And he just canceled...
Huh? I thought you were
after Saionji-senpai...
Yeah? The text is from him.
That's fast! You're dating already?
I was gonna tell him I liked him today...
I failed to seal the deal.
You two want to go instead?
I've got reserved seats...
No way!
We have club today, remember?
Keep it up, Yu!
Ten seconds left!
Okay!
Ten minute break!
I think Aragaki-san's
turned over a new leaf.
At that age, the smallest thing
can throw you off your game,
but you can rocket back just as quickly.
I remember those days myself.
Thanks to you, Tachibana-kun,
we can practice for real again!
Everything's great!
No, there's one other
person I'm worried about.
Hey, Hanesaki-san.
Is it true you've been playing
badminton since elementary school?
No...
Since kindergarten, then?
I think since I was two or—
Wow, you've got great legs.
Like they were born that way!
Now the arms! Wow, big muscles!
Programul de astăzi:
Alergat: 5 minute
Extensii
Dashes
Footwork
Shadow Drills:  1 minute x 3 hits
Lovituri fundamentale
Meciuri de antrenament (libere)
Ten minute break!
Oh crud!
Fifteen times.
Ayano-chan!
Here!
Last place treats first place to a drink!
That's a Kitakomachi rule!
44, 45, 46, 47, 48, 49, 50...
She sure is great at this!
Like, on a totally different level...
Aw... sixty-one!
If she went for it,
she could keep it up forever.
Elena?
I relied on you too much, Masao-kun.
I need to change...
That's why we had to break up!
But when I was away from you,
that's when I learned...
I like having you rely on me!
Thanks for putting up with me
after I called out of nowhere.
Wasn't that a great movie?
I love it when a woman wraps
a man around her finger!
A text!
He wants to know if I want to grab dinner...
Saionji-senpai?
Yeah. It's pretty bare-bones. No emojis.
Oh, what to do?
Just go.
I planned to eat at home anyway.
I just knew we'd be
great friends, Fujisawa-san!
Manag—Fujisawa?
I was a little worried she might
not fit in there without me.
But everyone's been so welcoming,
I thought she could stand on her own.
It's been rough on me, too.
Why did Hanesaki quit badminton?
I heard you were childhood friends, so...
During the junior nationals,
she was perfect.
On a totally different level
than she's playing on now.
Leave it to me! I'll figure it out.
No, this is more than a manager can handle.
I should be going.
Hey! I found it!
After stretches, we'll do mini-matches.
Everyone find a partner!
Might I join in, perchance?
And I believe I'll play with... her!
Kaoruko-chan! W-Wait!
What a musty old gym.
Do you want to join the club or something?
Little in the way of training equipment...
Hardly an ideal environment, is it?
Excuse me, but we're practicing.
If you're going to be a nuisance, leave.
Did you call me a nuisance?!
What's come over me?
Who is this cool older man?
Serigaya Kaoruko.
She's a first-year, but she's already
been named the ace at Konan High School.
Konan?
They've got a pretty
strong team, don't they?
What's she doing here?
Come on. Get ready.
I won't move an inch until
you agree to play me.
She's really putting Ayano-chan
through her paces.
She's predicting Hanesaki's moves and
mixing up her attacks based on that.
She's been proficient in psychological
warfare since middle school.
She knows how to set her opponent up.
And on top of that,
her technique has only improved.
How truly unsightly.
I came here to observe an old rival, but...
I'm so disappointed.
Hanesaki-san...
Don't forget, you can't beat me.
Wait, Kaoruko-chan!
You can't cut across the lawn!
Hanesaki, you let her dictate
the pace of the match.
Next time, you should be more assertve—
H-Hey...
Wait, Ayano!
Ayano! What's the matter?
I'm quitting the badminton club.
Oh, come on!
I'm staying in, okay?
We should both do our best!
No, thanks.
You can stay, but I'm quitting.
< Club Submission Form >
Hanesaki-san didn't come to school today.
What about our manager?
I don't know.
Izumi, you handle practice today.
Aragaki!
Look, she has to motivate herself.
Forcing her to play won't
do anyone any good.
Don't be like that.
Aren't you the team captain?
Is this the place?
Confectionery
Founded Kaei 6
Hane-ya Sakihana-do
Founded in the sixth year of the Kaei era?
That's 1853.
One hundred and sixty years ago.
Wow. I didn't know you were so smart.
I am Ayano's grandmother, Cho.
I'm her grandfather, Masashi.
Ayano has not yet returned home.
Did she go to school today?
I may know where she's gone.
It has to do with badminton, doesn't it?
Like mother, like daughter...
both so awkward.
Excuse me.
That is Ayano's mother.
Shindo... Uchika?
Japanese National Badminton Tournament
10 Straight Wins
Celebrating ten straight wins
at the Japanese nationals
Shindo Uchika
Her mother pursued badminton
like a woman possessed.
Hanesaki's mother was... Shindo Uchika?
She won the Japanese nationals
ten times in a row?
Celebrating ten straight wins
at the Japanese nationals
Shindo Uchika
Octo-octo...
"I was heading to school,
but I couldn't bring myself to go."
"I couldn't just go home,
so I'm killing time here." Right?
That's mean.
When you know someone since childhood,
you learn a few things.
Did you know that weird girl
who came in yesterday?
In middle school, she gave me a cold.
A cold?
What is it, Kaoruko-chan?
Our big match is coming up.
But I caught a cold.
I need to play you...
...in a match...
...on even terms!
Eat it!
I reign triumphant!
I've defeated you on even terms!
You have been defeated!
Mom...
Don't go...
Uchika-san hasn't been back since.
Mom left because I lost to Kaoruko-chan.
But that's no reason to
quit badminton, is it?
You used to love it so much.
I mean, it's your life.
You can separate your mom from
the idea of badminton.
I worked hard and kept winning.
I thought that if I got good enough,
Mom would come back.
I believed that, and...
Ayano...
And I kept winning!
Game. Match won by Hanesaki.
Hanesaki Ayano
Shindo Uchika
Takes on a New Challenge
The prodigy raised by the queen
finally takes her crown
I don't have a reason to
play badminton anymore.
New record!
Aragaki-senpai, I need to ask a favor.
Octo-octo...
You need to go to school, okay?
Hanesaki...
You can quit badminton if you want to.
But ever since that match,
I've been practicing to beat you.
Please, play one last set with me.
Look... that's none of my business.
Ayano, I've been watching you play badminton
in your mother's class since we were kids.
Do you know what I was
thinking while you did?
No...
I felt... left out.
Lately, too... I've felt a little left out,
watching the Bad Club
girls fawning over you.
But... even so!
I still think you should
be playing badminton.
No need to go to the gym, I'd say.
We can do it here.
1-Love.
Wow, the wind really gets in the way, huh?
Hey!
That one was out.
Who cares?
Hey, where are you hitting it?
But you said...
Why me?
Because you're the same.
Despite all the things you've said,
you're crazy in love
with badminton, aren't you?
I know Ayano is, too.
I mean, neither of you
are all that complicated.
I always envied you.
In elementary school, in middle school...
I always thought, I don't have anything
I can devote myself to like that.
Because when you're
playing badminton, Ayano...
You look like you're having so much fun!
I love badminton!
How'd you manage that one?
I used to play in the park
like this when I was a kid.
It was so much fun.
I've never seen a playground
with a squid in it...
But that's what Fujisawa-san told Nagisa.
Over there?
Isn't that an octopus?
Hurry it up!
But Nagisa-chan, you got it
stuck in a tree last time.
Because I returned your shot!
There!
Hey, no fair!
Let us join in!
Me, too!
C'mon, let's split up into teams and play!
You still have practice!
Still?!
You didn't even bring your rackets.
I can just borrow yours!
C'mon, we came all this way!
Oh, boy...
Keep it going!
< Club Submission Form >
Anul: 1     Clasa: 4
Nume: Fujisawa Elena
Vreau să mă alătur Clubului de: Badminton.
< Club Submission Form >
Anul: 1     Clasa: 4
Nume: Hanesaki Ayano
Vreau să mă alătur Clubului de: Badminton.