Ayano, I watched you play badminton
in your mother's class when we were kids.
Do you know what I was
thinking during that time?
No.
I felt left out.
Lately, too, I've felt a little left out,
watching the Bad Club girls fawning over you.
But... even so!
I still think you should
be playing badminton.
I love badminton!
< Club Submission Form >
Year:1 Class: 4
Name: Fujisawa Elena
I hereby ask to join the badminton club.
< Club Submission Form >
Year:1 Class: 4
Name: Hanesaki Ayano
I hereby ask to join the badminton club.
Kitakomachi High School Badminton Club
Summer Training Camp Schedule
All done, Sora-chan!
Can I play with your hair?
Don't worry! I'll put it back right after!
C'mon, just a little?
Okay...
Awesome!
What to do, what to do...
Wow! It's so silky!
Wh-What are you doing?
It's all good. Just leave it to me!
How about you, Nagisa?
No... I have short hair, anyway.
We could still put a pin in it!
Here, take it!
There! All done!
You look great, Ayanon!
A-Ayanon?
Ayanon! It's short for Ayano-chan!
Cute, huh?
Sure...
Wow, it really changes her whole look!
Hayama-senpai, could you take a picture?
Sure!
Here goes!
Say cheese!
It's really nice, isn't it?
It feels like we're part of the team.
A team...
Værste.
Sorry, Tachibana-senpai!
#4 I'm Lost Right Now, Too
I was sure I'd already told you.
So you're saying another school
is here for a training camp?
Yes...
And they really want to have a
practice game against Kitakomachi.
I see.
Fredericia Girls Junior College Affiliate High School
Pure of Heart and Victorious
Girls Badminton Club
Fredericia Girls Junior College Affiliate High School
Pure of Heart and Victorious
Girls Badminton Club
FreGirls?
Wow, they're regulars at the Inter-High.
They're based in... Miyagi, I think?
What's such a strong school doing here?
One of our girls absolutely
insisted on playing Kitakomachi.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
I'm the captain of the Fredericia
Girls Badminton Club, Shiwahime.
She's so... dignified.
These are our regulars.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
A pleasure to meet you!
They're completely overwhelmed.
I'm Kitakomachi's captain, Aragaki.
It's a pleasure to meet you, too.
A pleasure to meet you!
Since our club is so small,
we'll have one singles match
and two doubles matches.
For singles, Aragaki.
For doubles, the first pair will be
Ebina and the younger Isehara,
and the other will be Izumi and Hanesaki.
Singles
Aragaki
Don't be spooked just because
they're a strong team.
Let's win!
Yes, sir!
Yes! Let's do it!
Ayanon, we're counting on you!
I've never seen Hanesaki
in a real match before.
I really want to see how good she is!
And you boys will be playing
the college students.
Doubles
Ebina
Isehara (Younger)
Izumi
Hanesaki
Singles
Aragaki
Ugh!
We've got our work cut out for us, too!
They're counting on me...
Ayano-chan, let's do our best!
Okay.
That's right.
Can someone pick up some things
from a convenience store?
Convenience store?
It's all cabbage fields around here.
Um, I...
I was hoping I could go to a
convenience store anyway.
Hold on a minute.
I'll get you the money.
Ayanon! Thank you!
S-Sure.
Hanesaki, I'll draw you up a map.
Way to the Convenience Store
Start
College
Long
Uphill
About 5 km?
Almost there!
Finish line!
Convenience Store
Great
weather
today!
You can see mountains!
Big mountain!
I...
I'm lost.
What should I do?
Are you lost?
A... A foreigner!
Did you hear me? Are you lost?
Y-Yes...
I hear you.
I'm lost, too.
I was looking for a convenience store.
I-I'm also... doing that.
Then let's search together!
Is that a map?
Y-Yes. But...
What is this? Did a little kid draw this?
Almost there!
Uphill
About 5 km?
You can see mountains!
Big mountain!
But that symbol...
W-Wait a minute!
Captain!
I couldn't find her anywhere!
I can't get through, either.
Honestly, our youngest
is such a problem child.
It's so typical of her.
Aw, I'm sure she'll be back soon!
Honestly...
The only reason we came here is because
she wanted to play Kitakomachi, right?
Yes...
Why's she so obsessed with
this school, anyway?
I knew it!
Say, this symbol is about that thing, right?
Y-Yeah...
Looks like it.
Um... if we're facing the gate,
it would be to the right.
So if we go straight this way...
Thank you.
You're in high school?
Japanese people really do look like kids.
Where did you come from?
Miyagi.
Wow...
Miyagi?
But I was born in Denmark.
I came to Miyagi as part
of an exchange program.
Oh, I see.
What made you want to come to Japan?
There's someone I really want to beat.
I can't believe I'm playing the FreGirls...
My heart is pounding like a drum.
Yeah.
But we've got Aragaki-senpai,
and Ayanon seems really good, too.
I think we might even win!
Sora-chan, did something
happen with you and Ayanon?
No.
Really? But you seem...
Yu, Sora...
She's not back yet, is she?
You mean Ayanon?
I guess she has been gone for a while.
Beat her?
I want to play her.
The reason I came to Japan,
and the reason I'm here at this camp...
It's all been so that I can fight her.
I've been waiting a long time to play her.
Just the thought of beating
her into the ground...
It fills me with excitement.
Oh, I see!
I'm here on a training
camp for my club, too!
The sight of your back is so disarming.
I just mean that it's kind of soothing.
I know someone else who's like that.
So, what about you?
Why'd you join your club?
Lately, I've started thinking
that it might be fun...
And I think I might be get
to be part of a team.
A team?
Yeah. I've been alone for
a really long time...
But I think I could have
a lot of fun with a team!
Hey, what exactly do you—
Oh, there it is!
Popilla
Thank you for coming.
That's going to be tough...
No, I think I might like
helping everyone out!
You think?
That's weird.
Hey, what club are you in?
The badminton club.
What school are you from?
It's called Kitakomachi High.
Hold on a minute.
Are you...
Hanesaki-san!
Sora-chan!
I think my club senpai... came to get...
Was there a point to your
little friendship act?
Can you get what you want that way?
Later.
Sora-chan, did you come to get me?
I'll carry half of it!
W-Wait!
Welcome back!
Great timing. The first match
is just about to begin.
Let's cheer on Aragaki-senpai together!
Come on, guys! Make some noise!
You too, Gaku.
Aragaki-san! Give it all you've got!
It's my first match with everyone.
I want to win and be part of the team.
You're finally back...
Connie.
Game! Match won by Shiraishi-Misato,
Fredericia Girls.
Sorry, I messed up the last one.
I should have covered you sooner.
Great job!
They really are good!
I was hoping we'd be able
to score a few more.
Now it's one to one.
Ayano's team will have to break the tie.
Don't sweat it!
Tagajo
Connie C
Connie C?
But Ayano can beat somebody
from FreGirls, right?
Yeah... Hanesaki's talents should
get us pretty far, but...
You were gone forever.
Was it really that far away?
You didn't get lost, did you?
I made it back in time. What's the big deal?
You had us worried!
Hina never lets up.
I wish she would, though.
Connie never takes the bait, anyway.
Let's go, Ayano-chan.
Sure.
Hanesaki! Win this one, okay?
I'm going to play this match my way.
It's not like you'd listen to me anyway.
Hey, you're catching on!
Yeah, I'm black and blue, too!
Those college students are amazing!
Oh, but you hung on pretty
good in that second game!
If only that hairpin had landed.
I guess it's too late to
salvage it now, though.
Hayama-senpai, Gaku-sen—
Well, don't get too bummed out about it.
It's just a practice match anyway.
Let's just work hard for next time, okay?
Right.
Just a little more wrist
snap in that hairpin...
Hayama-senpai! Sora-chan!
The match is starting!
Whoops!
Thank you!
Yu-chan, did you come here to let us know?
Thanks.
Okay, the third match is starting.
Let's play!
Get ready.
I'm going to show you how
meaningless your "team" is.
Ayano-chan, did something
happen between you two?
I don't think so...
You don't have to do anything.
I'll play them both. Don't interfere.
Do you not get how doubles works?!
Go for it!
Ayanon, do your best!
Get that win, Ayano!
On my right, Connie-Tagajo, Fredericia Girls.
On my left, Hanesaki-Izumi,
Kitakomachi High School.
Hanesaki to serve. Love-all. Play.
She told me not to interfere...
But I can't let a perfect
shot like that get away!
Yeah!
1-love!
It's okay!
Defense!
Sorry. I'll stop the next one.
S-Service over.
1-all.
Connie! What are you doing?
It's pointless unless
I win the match by myself.
If you're going to get in my way,
you can play by yourself.
Ayano-chan, focus.
We just need to give this all we have.
Okay.
Hey, sorry I'm late.
Good morning, Coach Watari.
Yes, good morning.
I won't interfere.
Thank you.
10-2.
This is impossible.
I can't possibly win all by myself!
Let's swap, then!
Service over. 3-10.
I'll handle the rest.
Don't get in my way again.
Do you think you could've returned that one?
Thought so... I couldn't even see it.
Great one!
Yeah! It'll get through!
So high...
What was with that wimpy return?
We're finally face to face here.
Give me a little more fun.
What's with that Connie girl?
Connie...
Connie Christiansen...
Tagajo
Connie C
A prodigy from Denmark.
She won multiple world titles
at just sixteen years old.
She's from Denmark?
What's she doing here?
The length of her limbs,
her physical prowess...
She's at the top of her age group
on an international scale.
Hanesaki might have great instincts, but...
11-10! Interval!
Ayano-chan, let's turn things around.
O-Okay...
One minute!
Like I said, your team is meaningless...
Big Sister.