Creative Sempai
„Colega mai mare e creativă.”
Home Economics Room
Cooking time is over,
so please take your remaining
treats home and eat them there.
Let's split ours!
They look so good!
Let's trade!
What am I gonna do?
I'll make you the best
cookies ever! Just you wait!
No way can I serve this
charcoal junk to Ma-kun.
Wait, isn't that the magic girl over there?
That's right! We have joint classes today.
All right! I'll get her to
teach me some things,
and remake the cookies during lunch break!
No way...
She's eating them by herself?
How do you even walk up to someone like that?
But there's nobody else I can ask for help.
Hey...
What?
How may I assist you, Miss Balloon Person?
It's a little late to try acting all dignified.
Give it all you got, guys! Win this thing!
You don't have to watch them so closely.
Honestly, I don't know what
to talk about with her.
Oh, hey, by the way...
Why are you so obsessed
with the magic club, anyway?
Well...
It was a real club when I was a first-year,
but the next year,
every single sempai graduated.
I went all-in on recruiting,
but no one would join up.
Then it got scrapped this year.
That's why I'm working hard
to revive the magic club—
You look like a total flake,
but that's some hard work, huh?
You're one to talk! You look
like the biggest flake of all!
I know! Can we eat these cookies here
while we wait for mine to bake up?
Not those!
How come?
I prepared those especially for my assistant!
They're not safe to eat!
I think I'm getting why nobody
wants to join your club.
And here are the cookies I made in class!
Eat up!
They look really good.
And, Assistant, these are for you, from me!
Don't be so suspicious!
Hey, they're just normal. Good stuff.
What? They shouldn't be.
So you did put something in them!
You don't think those are the cookies that...
These cookies contain
something like a string.
How could this happen?
Oh no!
Ma-kun, spit it out! Spit it out!
I spilled the cookies!
Th-They're not really that big!
Why are you suddenly mad?
They're not that big, huh?
Fund-Raising Sempai
„Colega mai mare vrea să strângă fonduri.”
We got our club funds!
Sweet! Almost like we're a real club!
We are a real club!
Now, let's see what's inside!
It's like a thimbleful of earwax...
You could have picked a less gross comparison.
Anyway, let's use our day off for fundraising!
Money, please!
Feeling bad vibes already!
First, let's double-check our supplies.
Cape! Hat! Magic paraphernalia!
Donation box!
And barf bags!
Barf...?
Excuse me, you there!
I'm going to do some magic for you!
There she goes...
Sempai gets stage fright.
When she does magic in front
of people, she barfs her brains out.
Stay away from me!
If magic won't work, why don't
we try street performance?
Well...
Is that really still guy there
also a street performer?
Yes, that's a kind of performer
known as a "human statue."
I'm gonna try that!
Femeie transformată în piatră
Is this how it's done?
5 minute mai târziu
This is harder than I thought.
And it's lonely having no one else around.
That girl's awesome!
She's holding totally still! Like a mannequin!
Getting a reaction feels nice!
Would you be so kind as to contribute, then?
I'm gonna get an eyeful.
I wonder if Sempai's made anything yet.
Get back here, you brats!
This chick's fast!
Just try that again, mister!
This is no time to be playing around!
Let's see... What should I make next?
A lion!
A crab!
Things are going well for
Saki-chan and her brother.
V!
Hey, nice work!
Looks like you got a lot of things
besides money, too.
Acorns?
Really little kids like to put their
own treasures into the box.
Isn't it super charming?
Lady!
Balloon lady... thanks for the balloon!
I found these. They're for you.
Like, thanks so much!
See you!
Thanks!
See you later!
Saki-san's really nice.
Street performance is a wonderful thing.
Anyway, let's blow this joint!
Coș de gunoi
She threw them away!
We made some real bank today!
I know! Let's do some splurging to celebrate!
Nice!
Did you forget why we're doing this?
Hey, that's right. Where's Sempai?
You made such an amazing statue!
H-How does 50,000 sound?
You'll give me all that?!
Don't take that guy's money!
Pool Sempai
"Pool Sempai."
See? The pool opened today!
So it did. But what did you
call me out to it for?
Fear not! 'Tis but a swimsuit!
And today's theme is the water escape!
Have you been wearing that all day?
And third-years don't have swimming class.
Since you've forced our hand...
We'll just have to join you!
You guys just want to play in the pool!
I will now describe underwater magic!
Ce e magia subacvatică?
You enter the water with hands and feet tied,
free yourself from your bonds, and then escape!
A reușit să iasă!
It never fails to get hearts racing!
Obviously, care is taken in how
the ropes are tied and such
to ensure the safety of the performer.
It's just a performance, after all!
I guess you do get people who mess up
and nearly kill themselves now and then.
In fact, there was a recent
magic show in America that—
Maybe we should call it off?
Okay, my warm-up is complete!
Time for the bondage!
Wait just a minute!
Don't be a wet blanket
just because we're at the pool!
I'm not being a wet blanket!
If you mess up this time, you'll drown!
That wouldn't even be funny!
But I pulled it off every time
in the bath at home!
Iei
If only she'd ever learn...
Don't you worry! I can do this!
I can do it!
Please, come back!
I can do it. I can...
Look, I'm just really worried
you could die this time.
Someone save me!
Familia Inugami!
Pretty sure you just jumped in on your own!
Are you okay, Saki-san?
I think I'm... dying.
Dying?!
I'll die without mouth-to-mouth from Ma-kun!
It's just an act.
Protecția pentru față!
So excited...
We can just leave her like that for a while.
You're used to this, huh?
Come on, Sempai. You'll get
sunburned if you just sit there.
I can do it. I can.
She's in full-on pout mode!
I'll just bind your wrists, then.
You can go into the water like that.
Aw, but I can get out of this in seconds!
Prove it first!
Once I do this, I'm gonna do the real thing.
Câteva secunde mai târziu
She's been down there for a while, huh?
You don't think... she still failed?!
Assistant-kun!
Sempai!
Are you okay?
I almost had them off!
Overcoming Sempai
"Overcoming Sempai."
Hey, there.
Assistant!
Choco Puffs
I just bought some at the school
store! Wanna share?
If there're no surprises inside, sure.
Okay, I'll make some tea. Just hang on!
Thank you very much.
Busy, busy!
Hey, I've been thinking...
There are times when you get it in front
of people and times you don't, right?
Get what? You mean hype?
I'm full of it!
I mean stage fright!
Should we put your stage fright to the test?
You're not necessarily afraid of doing
anything in front of people, right?
That's right! I did that street performance
at the park, remember?
Femeie transformată în piatră
And you don't always get nervous
when you're doing magic?
It always works right when
I practice on my own!
It's true!
So you only get nervous when you're
both doing magic in front of others.
Yeah... the thought that I need
to make it work gets me sweating.
Then I'll take a video of you doing a trick.
I'm looking at the camera and not you,
so you might not get stage fright.
I see! That might just work!
Okay, I'm recording.
Turn off the camera.
I might never be able
to do it in front of a crowd!
What are you, some rare animal?!
Maybe performing in front of people
is too high a bar to start with.
Let's start with a more easygoing audience.
Poof
Cicada Husk
This feels vaguely like mockery.
Cicada (Living)
Eyeball Balloon
Stain That Looks
Like a Face
Assistant
(Blindfolded)
Things that make her
get stage fright
Cicada (Living)
Eyeball
Stain
Blindfold
So the blindfold fails.
Am I doomed to never
perform in front of people?
A tragic fate for such a brilliant magician!
Either cry or brag. Don't do both.
Well, I'm going home.
You're abandoning me?!
Keep practicing in front of this.
The chin seems a little long.
Now, I'll perform the bill-cutting trick!
I'm more nervous than I thought I'd be.
But don't worry. It's just a plank of wood.
Focus, focus...
Now, in goes the precious cash!
What a travesty it would
be if I cut it in half!
Go! Go!
Look! A clean cut right through the middle!
But don't you worry!
If I open the envelope,
the 1,000 yen has...
It's... It's...
It's intact!
I did it!
That's amazing, Sempai!
I did it! I did it, Assistant!
Wait... what are you doing here?
Oh, hell.
Oh no! It's just like when we first met.
It's on my clothes!
Chinese Sempai
Mentalist Sempai
Mikan Sempai
Internet Sempai
Delivery Sempai
Join us next week for more Magical Sempai!