Magical Sempai
Growing Sempai
"Growing Sempai."
Cleaning duty held me up, so I'm late.
Big Sis, let it go for a minute!
Don't worry. I've got it.
It's so big and full already.
Should I use my mouth now?
No, don't grab it so hard!
I know.
I'll watch my nails and be gentle.
What are those siblings doing in the club room?
What are you people doing?!
Hey, Assistant!
Saki-chan and Ma-kun were showing
me how to make balloon art!
Just what I thought!
Okay, let's start with
how to blow up your balloons!
Really? Seems pretty basic...
Before you blow into it, make sure
you stretch it nice and good.
I'm gonna get right to it!
Mysterious, huh?
There's a trick to blowing
it up with your mouth.
Of course, I can do it with just my nose!
I think you lose girl points
for acting smug about that.
Everyone, got your balloons?
Okay, let's start with a doggy!
Isn't that a bit advanced?
You can make it purely with cod roe twists,
so it's good for practice.
Cod roe twists?
Twist the balloon three times to make bubbles.
Fold the bubbles back
on each other and twist again.
This is a cod roe twist.
Then repeat that two more times, and...
Ta-dah! You've got your doggy!
The trick is to twist with determination.
It's a little scary once
you're actually doing it.
How are you doing, Sempai?
Conger Eel
Snake Eel
Japanese Eel
Moray Eel
Don't make me do more than this!
You've got quite the haul.
What kind of person twists a balloon?!
My hands are exhausted...
I've done enough for today.
I personally recommend not stopping there.
When you get tired,
just stick it between your legs,
and rest!
I get it! Smart thinking!
There's nothing smart about that!
I guess you don't get nervous
if you're not doing magic?
Instead of being nervous, I'm terrified!
But you totally finished it!
Hey, I did!
I did it, Assistant!
Bummer!
My dog turned into cod roe...
Roe...
How did this happen?
Unfailing Sempai
"Unfailing Sempai."
Assistant, hold onto your butt for this one!
What now?
Sempai just discovered
a way not to fail at magic!
Sempai...
What? Curious?
At times like these, it's best to remain calm.
Our first job is to contact
the consumer center...
It's not a scam!
Watch and you'll see!
Now, wait just a single minute.
Close the curtain!
1 Minute Passes
Strangely quiet in there.
I wonder if she's pouting
because she can't get out.
I'm opening the curtain, Sempai.
She's gone! How?
Sempai?
Strange... I thought the magic
was taking off the shackles,
but was it about disappearing instead?
Then she actually succeeded?
Trick successful!
That's right... I couldn't remove
the shackles at all!
However, I never claimed I was
going to escape from the shackles!
Victory!
It's the perfect way keep
from ever failing at magic!
But it's getting hot in here, so maybe
I'll jump out and surprise him now.
Oh, well. Better go...
Huh?
No way! I'm stuck and can't move!
Competitive Sempai
"Competitive Sempai."
Yes? Who's there?
The club room is locked, so I'm going
to get in through the chem room.
Okay, but...
Oh, wait a minute.
Take this with you.
A cola? Thanks so much!
It's no ordinary cola.
It's freezing inside?
It uses the supercooling phenomenon.
Supercooling?
If a liquid is slowly and evenly
lowered to its freezing point,
and then opened, moved,
or otherwise stimulated,
it will immediately freeze over.
That's amazing!
Sorry I'm late!
Is that my assistant's voice?
He's really having fun talking to her.
I wouldn't want to interrupt.
The "my friend's friends
aren't necessarily
my friends" type
I guess I'll wait a while.
While you wait for your club president
to arrive, I'll show you one more thing!
The tablecloth pull!
Does that have to do with science, too?
Law of Inertia
The reason things don't fall when you pull
the cloth is due to the law of inertia.
An object at rest tends to stay at rest,
Friction
so if a stationary object's stationary force
exceeds the friction created
when the cloth is pulled,
Stationary Force
you can pull out just the cloth.
Let's begin the experiment!
It's heavier than I thought...
Look out!
Is my assistant more interested
in science than magic?
But he's in my club, so...
He's in my club!
But what if he's been having secret chemistry
club meetings that I just never saw?
What if he's been
having secret chemistry
club meetings that
I just never saw?
But maybe I should just watch a little longer?
Maybe I should just
watch a little longer...
Are you all right?
Um... Ah...
Is that what it's about?!
What's going on here, Sempai?
Which means more to you? Me or chemistry?
Don't make this more
complicated than it has to be!
I see everything now!
It's time for us to fight with our
honor as club leaders on the line.
You don't see anything!
I'll pull the cloth next!
Wh-Where did that come from?
I'm sorry, Madara-san.
I think she just really wants to pull the cloth.
She's so confident...
You think she'll pull it off?
I wouldn't get my hopes up.
Now, let's begin!
This is remarkable.
I admit defeat.
I'm sorry about the mess.
This is also remarkable.
Nice and cool...
It uses the heat of vaporization.
Science is so cool!
That's right! Science is very cool!
I found her threatening because
she promotes that "magic" fraud,
but she's proving herself rather harmless.
I never should have
judged a book by its cover.
It seems I still have much to learn.
How long are these people going to stay here?
Feels so good!
And they're multiplying!
You know? It feels even colder on wet clothing!
Don't blame me if you catch a cold.
Um... Are you guys leaving, ever?
Silent Sempai
"Silent Sempai."
Would you look at that!
Saki-chan and Ma-kun don't
seem to be coming today,
so maybe I'll let him sleep.
I'll try to do magic in total silence.
I'll start with this coin.
I'll make it fly, opposing all laws of gravity!
If I place the coin in my palm
and pinch it tightly,
the pressure on both sides
will make the coin fly!
Just be careful. Don't drop the coin!
Oops!
Oh, no! Did I wake him up?
Sempai... please....
He's talking in his sleep?
I wonder what he's dreaming about...
Now it's time to bring out
our two good friends!
All I need is a single handkerchief.
When I put this over my hand,
a pigeon will appear—
—over there?!
But where's the other one?
Don't come out of there!
I'm glad he didn't see that,
but without his snark, it feels a little...
I can't believe I acclimated to that.
It got a little dicey for a minute there, but
I got a pretty good club practice out of it!
Hey, Assistant. It's time to go home!
Assistant?
Maybe I'll leave him a while longer.
Okay, okay! Almost there!
Why did I feign sleep expecting
something to happen?!
Bunny Sempai
"Bunny Sempai."
Sh-Shank you for coming today!
Sempai... why are you dressed like that?
You know how when you get a mosquito bite,
and you pinch the nearby skin,
which hurts, but makes it itch less?
I... g-guess so?
So it occurred to me...
To get over my stage fright—
in other words, my embarrassment—
I just need to wear an even
more embarrassing outfit!
I worry for your future, Sempai.
Today's performance begins
with the cups and balls!
I can't look away!
What, you love the trick that much?
Like hell I do!
Stay calm. Don't get drawn
into this deviant's rhythm!
See? She's as red as a beet!
You can't get over your stage
fright just by changing your outfit!
As usual, she'll fail the minute
she's in front of an audience.
So I hold the ball tight, and...
There!
Ta-dah! What a mystery!
When I open my hand, the ball is gone!
Sorry, I didn't see it.
Of course you didn't!
It's a testament to my skill!
What's with that, "Hah, I tricked you!" look?
Move on already!
Next, watch! I've sandwiched
the ball between the cups.
Sandwiched... Must be pretty
soft in there, yeah...
Huh? The ball is quite hard, actually.
Now I'll use my magic wand!
If I stroke the side of
the cups with the wand...
W-Would you look at that?
The balls have all moved to the bottom cup!
I managed it, even though he's watching!
Incredible. Truly incredible.
W-Well? How did you enjoy the cups and balls?
I had a pretty good showing today, right?
Yes, the cups were truly amazing!
Hooray!