Observatori și colega mai mare
„Observatori și colega mai mare.”
Colegă mai mare,
avem o problemă serioasă.
Vom avea câțiva observatori.
La acest club nașpa?
Tu n-ar trebui să spui asta.
Iei! Iei!
Ce bucurie. Oare ce să fac
pentru această ocazie...
Colegă mai mare, legat de asta...
Te rog să nu faci niciun truc magic.
Respingere totală?!
Hei, ai auzit?
Este această fată ciudată în
ultimul club de la etajul doi.
Pare amuzant!
Haide să mergem după ore!
If you try your usual weirdness on them,
it could negatively impact my school life,
so please keep things chill.
Is that understood?
Bring it on!
Is she completely hopeless?
Anyway, I'll deal with them,
so you hide in there.
Crushing! My very right to exist is rejected!
It's no fair if you do all the tricks!
I won't!
I'm considered a very cool guy in my class!
Pictured: his personal self-image
This is a new, cringey side of you.
Anyway, get in there!
No, no, no!
Wait a minute.
That box is made for escape tricks.
I must remain vigilant.
Though wherever I stick her, she'll probably
worm her way back out soon enough.
Yay!
Stare...
Wh-What?
You fear a magician's powers, don't you?
This is so annoying!
This is it!
C'mon, let's go in!
Sempai, hurry! Hi—
Maybe I should do a super-difficult sequence
where my head falls off and
also starts spitting out flags!
Someone help me!
You can't show them that!
Go back to normal right now!
Ow!
Stop, Assistant! You're pulling my hair!
Excuse me...
Is this the magic clu—
Wait! I haven't done anything yet!
Wait up! Assistant, stop them!
Are you crying? Why?!
Onion Sempai
"Onion Sempai.”
What are you two doing together?
Remember our last time out in the park?
Yeah, you screwed up that quick change trick.
Learning from that tragedy, I've come up
with a brand-new quick change routine!
It was my idea, actually!
Yay!
You came up with it, Sensei?
I sure did!
I love costumes, so I brought
a whole bunch together.
Uniforms, maid outfits, nurse outfits...
I rigged it so that one pull of a string
will put my little sis in some
cute costume or other!
Anyway, a picture is worth a thousand words!
Take it away, Big Sis!
You got it!
Here goes nothing!
H-Hey, Sis! This is pretty skimpy!
Worry not!
That's fabric matched to your skin tone!
Oh, you're right! I feel so much better now.
Is it really that much better?
Now, let's do another one!
I-I'm not embarrassed!
I'm still completely covered!
My assistant knows this, and he'll
react with his usual indifference—
No, he's staring intently!
Now for the last one!
We won't know what it is
until we peel it all off!
W-W-Wait, Big Sis—
Here we go!
It's fabric! I'm still technically covered!
That makes it okay!
You bet it does!
Thank you, Sensei.
Chemistry Sempai
"Chemistry Sempai.”
This is Madara-san,
president of the chemistry club.
She let me double up in the chemistry club,
and she's a very considerate person, but...
Chemistry Room
S-So awkward...
I need to think of something to talk about.
Um... chemistry is a lot like magic, huh?
Wrong.
Bad communication!
Can I have that juice?
I drank out of it, though.
That makes it better.
Does it?!
I-It's still standing!
Mysterious, no?
But it's an entirely explicable phenomenon.
If you can get a vertical line drawn
from the juice's center of mass
to match up with the point of contact
between the can and the table,
you can stand the can on a diagonal.
Wow...
But magic obscures these
natural scientific principles
to trick people into thinking
something supernatural is happening!
Please don't associate
chemistry with that kind of fraud!
Is there anyone normal at this school?
A-And... doesn't the magic
club do... shameless things?
Chemistry Prep Room
Fun
Magic Club
My butt! It hurts, it hurts, it hurts!
Pull it out!
I hear the strangest things
from there sometimes.
A-All a misunderstanding!
If I may continue...
I will now empty out this can.
I-Is she going to drink it? That's an indirect—
She flushed it.
Fill it one-third of the way
with boiling water,
then cap it.
It's hot, so be careful.
I will now perform a magic trick.
Mumble, mumble...
Amazing! She didn't even touch it!
Technobabble
The slow reduction of temperature
results in vapor condensation,
leading to a reduction in volume
and concordant crumpling.
Wow... I bet Sempai would
find that really impressive.
B-But that's not all chemistry has to offer!
Let me show you something
even more impressive!
She's a little like Sempai, really.
I'm back!
It's huge!
What is this thing?!
It's known as a vacuum cannon.
It uses the principle that striking
it reduces the volume of the box,
which causes it to expel
donut-shaped blasts of air.
To better track the air currents involved,
I've incorporated a mist made from dry ice.
Want to try hitting it?
You bet I do!
Madara-san, you don't even like magic,
but you let the magic club use the prep room.
You're a very kind person.
I suppose I am.
Really, there's no stopping someone like
her when she gets an idea into her head.
But the real truth is, I'm just a pushover.
Okay, firing away!
W-Wait a minu—
The magic club... truly is a shameless place.
That's not true!
I'm sorry! I'm so sorry!
Unexpected Sempai
"Unexpected Sempai.”
Today, I'll spring out of this box,
startle my assistant, and then
perform a few tricks!
It's the perfect way to interest him!
He's here!
She left her stuff on the chairs again.
Huh? I can't get out!
Is Sempai not coming today?
This isn't good... I can't get out.
And if he realizes I'm in here,
my whole plan will go down the drain!
I know!
Colega mai mare
Asistentuleeeee!!!!!!!!!!!
Aruncă o privire pe hol!!
Citit
Ce?
I'll use my smartphone
to get him out of the room!
Then I'll escape!
Now, get that smartphone...
Oh, whoopsie.
Huh? Where's my smartphone...
Oh no, my spider threads!
My cards, too!
It sure is peaceful around here
without Sempai, though!
Sempai's annoying and stupid
and crappy at magic,
and obnoxious about recruitment,
and she calls this a club,
even though it's not...
Proastă
Ener-
vantă
Varză
la magie
Neplă-
cută
Of course, I could never say
something so mean to her face.
But I can give her credit for one thing.
What is it?
One thing I'm too embarrassed
to say in front of Sempai...
"You sure are cute.”
He thinks I'm cute?!
Those glassy, staring eyes...
Wh-Wh-Where did this come from?!
That silky hair...
That plush texture...
Does he mean... I look soft to the touch?
That completely vacuous expression...
Is that a compliment?!
This sure must be love!
Iub
ire
Does Assistant really l-l...
Does he really feel that way about me?
I know I'm cute, but I never know
what to do at times like these!
Guess she's not coming. Think I'll go.
What should I do?!
B-But he was talking to himself,
and if he knew I was listening,
he'd probably be humiliated!
But, but, but... would it be more
dishonest to pretend I never heard?
In that case...
Ta-dah! I was inside the box the whole time!
And I'm very sorry for eavesdropping!
Um, so anyway, it's normal
to like someone like me,
and it's common for respect
to turn into affection!
I won't blame you for liking me that way,
but I'm afraid the club
is my main priority now!
I mean, I'm certainly flattered, but—
Huh?
Inviting Sempai
"Inviting Sempai.”
It's the weekend.
I was invited to Sempai's house.
Hey, Assistant!
Over here!
I'm on the second floor, so come on up!
Th-Thank you.
Even if she's magic-obsessed,
it's still a girl's room...
Come on in!
It'll be an exciting experience!
Right this way!
O adevărată dezordine...
This isn't exciting at all.
I called him here for one reason alone.
I overheard his confession
of affection for me.
Yes, he's done nothing wrong.
So I need to treat him with appropriate care.
First, make him feel genuinely welcome.
Would you like some cookies I baked yesterday?
There's nothing weird in them, is there?
Oh no!
What if offering handmade snacks
just makes his feelings more intense?!
I'll take one, the—
Oh, the "All Cookies Disappear Trick"!
She started eating them herself. Terrifying.
Um, so... there's a reason
I called you here today.
Because you lo... lo...
Low?
Loved...
A cane?!
Th-That's right!
This is my "appearing cane,"
a cane that appears out of nowhere!
That's not what I meant to say!
Oh, did you want to practice
a new trick with me today?
Yes! That, too!
Now, let's practice the
disappearing handkerchief trick!
Shove it tight into your hand, like this...
These are my panties!
Wait, you don't mean...
I wonder where you buy stuff like this.
Model cu porumbei
My stage undies!
Give those back!
Hey! You're stretching them!
I already showed him my panties!
This can't get any more humiliating!
Listen! The reason I called you here
is because you said you loved me!
So I wanted to give you a proper response...
When did I say that?
Huh? But just the other day...
I got it all wrong!
Unknowing Sempai
Gal-Pan Sempai
Plotting Sempai
Suspicious Sempai
Join us next week for more Magical Sempai!