Chinese Sempai
"Chinese Sempai."
Tomorrow, we'll learn about Chinese magic!
So she said, but what even is Chinese magic?
Nihao!
Xie-xie!
I'm spinning even more than usual today!
Nihao, Sempai!
What's this Chinese magic we'll be—
Hey there, Assistant!
Today's topic will be the
Chinese magic called bian lian!
Bian lian involves swapping out
masks faster than the eye can see!
The mechanism is said to be
a Chinese national secret!
Is that even true?
So we're going to work together
to figure out how they do it!
Yeah!
Teoria lui Masashi și Saki
I theorize that they wear
multiple thin layers,
swiftly peel them off,
and hide them in the sleeves.
Oh, totally! I was gonna
say the very same thing!
Let's try it!
We need something thin,
so I prepared some plastic wrap.
We'll cut some face-size
sheets and then layer them up,
then fix them to Masashi-kun's face, and...
There! The meat is packed and ready to go!
What's that you just said?
Sorry, couldn't help it!
Ma-kun, tell her off already!
Did you guys forget the air holes?!
Teoria asistentului
Maybe there's another person behind them.
That person swaps the masks really quickly.
There's an idea! Maybe that's
why their clothes look so big!
Okay, coming in behind!
Her chest is all up on my back.
Hey, maybe you should be in front—
What did you say?
The dumber one should be in front.
You're scarier than the mask!
Teoria colegii mai mari
I think we've almost gotten
to the heart of this.
You think this little league
garbage is a national secret?!
Lastly, I bet they rig up the masks somehow.
Like, they're designed to split in the middle.
Now, since the dumber one should be in front...
I'll sock you one.
I can't see anything through her hair!
I can't even tell where the mask is!
I think that's it!
Now grab tight and tear it apart!
Here we go!
Purge!
Well? Did it break cleanly?
Instant 180...
Colega mai mare e mentalistă
"Mentalist Sempai."
Long day, so curry me away...
Did you stop for lunch in the cafeteria?
I haven't had a bite.
Cancelarie
I got chewed out for
practicing magic in class.
You dummy.
Personal space!
I have just now read your mind.
Um?
You were feeling sorry for me
because I missed lunch, right?
I was hoping you would
get out of my face, actually.
A "mentalist" is a performer
who uses psychological techniques
to guess what someone's thinking
from their facial expressions,
but makes it appear to be
supernatural phenomenon!
Another day, another phony-sounding subject.
For instance, the eyes!
Watching their eyes is the easiest
way to read a person's emotions!
If they're looking to the upper-right,
there's a good chance they're
imagining something audio-visual.
If they're looking to the lower-left, there's a
good chance they're touching something,
noticing a change in temperature,
or otherwise using their senses.
Now, Assistant! I shall read your body
language to determine what you're thinking!
My eyes aren't making it clear
that I don't give a damn?
Fine, all right.
But only for a little while.
You just dropped something onto the desk!
Yes, and?
"Dropping something on a desk. This symbolizes
open hostility towards another!"
Um, I don't think the desk is
needed in that particular example.
You probably shouldn't
take this stuff too literally.
Your gaze is shifty!
This indicates that someone is lacking
in confidence, introverted,
and difficult to break out of their shell!
My, how accurate!
Are those fighting words?
You are henceforth an open book to me!
Mentalists are awesome!
It's not that hard to read someone's
thoughts from their behavior.
For instance, you're currently
delighted by your own coolness, right?
That's right!
Because you just said so!
And now you're thinking,
"How did he know?" Right?
N-No! I wasn't trying to show you up!
I just wanted to show you
a mentalist's amazing powers—
Now you're lying so you look less bad.
So embarrassing! Stop guessing!
Now my accuracy is making
you want to escape the situation.
She's gone quiet.
F-Fine! Try to read me now!
You're thinking that putting on a poker face
will make it impossible for me to read you.
I guess that's the sign that I'm hungry, huh?
That much was obvious.
Mikan Sempai
"Mikan Sempai."
Look! Look! It's hand power!
What's with the pile of mikans?
A farmer who lives near
me gave me some, so I'm sharing!
But there's no way I'll get through all these.
I thought boys had big appetites!
Within limits!
Today, I'll do a trick named after the mikan!
I knew this was leading to magic somehow.
I have here a paper pot
with a hole right above it!
If we plant our magical mikan
seeds here, all of a sudden...
You see a sprout (me)!
[Me = "Sprout" or "Eye"]
I bet kids would love this one.
And after the sprout comes...
Leaves (ha)!
This might be less appropriate for kids.
And then, the flower (hana) blooms!
[Hana = "Flower" or "Nose"]
Hey, that's a really good act.
I see we got some nectar, too.
I'm not even making a dent in these things.
I guess I got too many.
My eyes! My eyes!
She probably wouldn't
survive a day on her own.
Colega mai mare și internetul
"Internet Sempai."
Extracurricular activities?
Yes!
Now that the magic club is official,
we can visit nursery schools
and old folks' homes!
So exciting!
Are we even getting requests for that junk?
I was thinking we'd work on that today!
We'll create a magic club site
and show them what we do!
Have we done a single thing
we'd want to make public?
I think someone's jealous of Sempai's
impending international fame!
Your words make no sense.
I've actually made one already!
Let's see...
Bun-venit
Fun Magic Club
★ Club Activities
★ Member Profiles
★ Today's Club
Unu!
No freaking way!
Doi!
Trei!
I wanted to make sure it was memorable!
V!
If by "memorable," you mean
"mentally scarring," maybe.
Trei!
What is this creature with
legs growing from its head?
That's you!
I'm suddenly terrified.
What, it's no good?
If you want people to come,
you gotta put those assets on display!
I'll make you up something on my smartphone!
We gotta have photos of what we do, right?
Wow, it looks professional!
Good thing Saki-san is digitally literate.
Sempai@MagicClub
Following
I do magic! ☺
DM me for meet-ups!
Sempai@MagicClub
I'm hungry!
School uniform
That should do it!
The hell it will!
Wow! Wow! I've got cat ears!
Look at that quasi-idol crap!
What if some creepy old man pays
our moron sempai to make sexy videos
And my eyes are so big and shiny!
Hey, what trick is this?
or demands indecent things from her?!
I'm getting all these messages!
You creep me out sometimes, Assistant-kun.
What to do? What to do?
Remakes It
Now, allow me to reveal the site
I stayed up all night making!
Magic Club
Tanenashi High School Magic Club Home Page
Visits OK!!
Announcements
Today's latest video
You made it worse!
Popular
Club Members
Hey, wanna cosplay for the next one?
It says we'll get more views
if we show our faces!
Yeah, and the sexier the better!
I'll make it myself.
Just Did It Himself
Delivery Sempai
"Delivery Sempai."
Școala de Asistente Tanenashi
Miraculously, the web advertising bore fruit,
and we got invited to perform
at a nursery school.
That's that!
That was Saki-chan's balloon art!
Okay, okay! Play rock-paper-scissors
for who gets it!
She's really got them warmed up.
Sempai?
I know, right?!
Okay, magic lady! You're on!
Spectacol de magie
R-Right...
I hope she can handle this.
Calm down.
I prepared some tricks that kids should love.
Now I just have to make it work.
W-Well, I'm gonna do some magic!
First, watch this cane!
Look, a flower!
She broke it.
I pulled it too hard!
Th-They like it.
I might just make this work today!
It's not so much that you're on fire
as your audience has low standards, I think.
Hush! It's funny, so let's watch.
Okay, let's keep it going!
Now, look at this picture!
What does it look like?
A horsey!
That's right!
I see. Her pictures are very relatable.
Was that supposed to be a horse?
Desenează fără referințe
I bet she drew it without using a reference.
But what's this?
There's actually another
animal hidden in this picture!
A cow?
A rhino?
Oh, a reversible picture!
Reversible?
Bere
It's a kind of optical illusion.
You flip it over to make a different picture.
Bătrân
Card tricks might be a little
much for the kids, after all.
Sempai... I guess she really
thought this through.
I'm worried about the picture, though.
What happens when we turn it upside-down?
You know what it is, right?
It just looks like an obscene mascot costume!
What is it?
I don't get it.
Oh, is it too hard?
Then let me give you a hint!
It starts with C-O-C...
You're kidding me!
Sorry, time's up!
The answer is...
Cockatiel!
Prove it!
Okay, here's the last one!
Candy!
I'm going to wave my little magic cane
over the candy and make it disappear!
Three...
Two...
One!
Wait, it was the cane that disappeared!
Too easy!
The "disappearing candy" was a
misdirection for the disappearing cane!
I hung the cane on my
ear after the last swing!
Where's the cane?
That's so weird.
And while they're focused on the cane...
What? Now the candy disappeared!
Are you amazed, children?
There's nothing a magician can't do!
I did it! My first success!
She hid it in her clothing!
Find it!
Don't do that! Hands off!
That's not how it was supposed to go.
I think that's been her greatest success.
Biased Sempai
Make-Up Exam Sempai
Ice Cream Sempai
Swimsuit Sempai
Join us next week for more Magical Sempai!