Magical Sempai
Beach Sempai
"Beach Sempai."
The beach!
And now...
Sempai's new swimsuit!
What do you think?
And it's got my magic
tools safely tucked away,
so no problems here!
There's nothing but problems here!
Now, let's go frolic our brains out!
Wait for me!
I'm exhausted.
How long are those two going to frolic?
Take that!
That totally spooked me!
I-It swept my swimsuit away!
M-Magic Girl!
Could you maybe, like... help me?
To make a swimsuit disappear in an instant...
Truly, this is the magic that nature wields.
It got you, too?!
Saki-san is calling us.
She probably wants us to join them.
Not that I'm going.
We're gonna be stuck
in the water! What do we do?
Remain calm, Saki-chan.
We'll solve this problem with magic!
Here's what we'll use!
Sand?
But no ordinary sand!
This is magical sand!
By evenly applying a water-repellent spray,
it hardens into a clay-like
consistency when it hits water!
I get it! We'll smear it on our breasts
and let it harden in the water!
That's awesome! You know a
couple things after all, Magic Girl!
I underestimated you.
I can't accept that
compliment. I wonder why...
A-Anyway...
Let's make it to land!
I forgot! It turns back to normal sand
when you take it out of the water!
I take back my compliment.
Time for street performance to do its stuff!
Let's hide behind human balloons!
B-Balloons?!
Less bitching, more blowing!
Blow! Blow!
We were kinda lacking in air,
but we made it work!
To think I'd be saved by my nemesis, balloons.
Hey! Everyone!
They came back in strange outfits.
Our swimsuits got swept away, see!
It totally sucked, you guys!
Crab Sempai
"Crab Sempai."
What?
Isn't that...
You came, Grandma?
I found something. Come and see!
There's a crab underneath this rock!
Hang on. I'm going to catch it!
It is you, Madara-san.
No!
I mean...
Um, this crab!
It's called a river swimming crab,
and it can be found across a wide
range from Hokkaido to Okinawa!
They're edible, too!
You eat them?
Wh-What are you doing here?
The magic club came to hang out.
This is quite a coincidence.
This sure is a remote place though, huh?
Crap reception, no wi-fi...
And I'm almost out of gigabits...
My grandmother lives here.
B-But the country has its positives, too!
There's a beach!
And lots of green,
which makes the air very clean!
You don't have to make it right.
But there are also things
you can only do in the country.
Lie down over there.
Like this?
I'll do it, too.
I-Is that what she was talking about doing?!
Because nobody else is around?!
What are you looking at?
Don't look at me. Look at that.
You see the sun going down?
Y-Yes, I do.
It's very beautiful.
It's over...
Stand up right now!
Why?!
Just do it!
Look at the ocean again!
It's still up!
That's so weird... It's like
I've gone back in time.
Right?
Because the Earth is a sphere,
the higher up you go, the further
you can see around the curve.
Just by standing up, you can see
a set sun just before it sets again.
If Sempai saw it, I bet she'd
have a fit, saying it was magic.
Though science is more than some parlor trick.
It'll get cold soon.
We should probably get going.
I bet you're getting cold, too.
Forget everything that happened today!
Madara-san!
Watermelon Sempai
"Watermelon Sempai."
The club is going to split a watermelon,
so I invited Madara-san along.
Assistant-kun, you're late.
Where have you been?
Things got complicated.
Madara-san?
I... I find girls like her... intimidating.
Your girlfriend?
I c-can't stand frivolous women
who promote baseless hypotheses!
Sorry, just a joke.
First Watermelon Splitter
Ma-kun
Lookin' good, Ma-kun!
That's right!
More to the right!
Yes, that's the way! Keep walking!
Well done, my sweet.
Say, the sand's a lot harder than I thought.
Not sure I can get outta here...
Hey, Ma-kun?
Who shall be next?
Second Watermelon Splitter
Madara-san
Sorry about the sudden invitation.
It's fine. I didn't have anything else to do.
And I have a secret weapon.
A secret weapon?
Behold.
She spun around so much,
but she doesn't seem dizzy!
Madara-style
watermelon-splitting secrets.
One, understand the tilt of your body.
Two, train your three semicircular canals.
Three, memorize the terrain.
Just because it's a game is no
reason not to take it seriously.
She's surprisingly into this!
I have a natural advantage, of course.
I don't get carsick, either.
Hey, wait! Stop! Stop!
Natural Disadvantage:
Lousy Sense of Direction
Hey, chill out!
You had a good thing going there!
I'll bury your face, too.
Third Watermelon Splitter
Sempai
Did I tie it right?
Okay!
Behold the power of Sempai!
See? I'm walking with such confidence!
Shakier than a newborn fawn...
Look out, Sempai! A broken shell!
Where? Where?
I told you, don't step left—
Assistant-kun!
What? What?
What's going on?!
I found it! Here's the watermelon!
W-Wait, I'm not—
Well? Impressed by Sempai's
space-reading skills?
Annihilation
Fireworks Sempai
"Fireworks Sempai."
Well, now that the sun's down,
let's finish up with some fireworks!
Nice!
Of course!
Speaking of fireworks,
I have some tricks that use fire...
I've got this and this and this...
Sempai, playing with fire is dangerous,
so let's leave the tricks out of it.
Okay.
I don't trust you one bit!
Is this a rope escape trick?
Hey, Assistant?
Sempai and fire are a dangerous combination,
so let's get things ready without her.
She's burned the club room down before.
Why are you even still in this club?
Speaking of burning, I have
an exciting money trick I can do!
We'll start with the lighter
Saki-chan brought for the fireworks.
No way! When'd you get that?
Why can't you be that sneaky
when you're doing magic?!
Now, it's time for a disappearing money trick!
Someone lend me a 1,000 yen bill!
Fine! I'll pay up myself!
I got the lighter from Saki-chan,
so you know it's just an ordinary lighter!
This trick lives or dies by misdirection!
While everyone's distracted by the fire,
I'll swiftly swap the bill
in my hand with a fake!
The darkness makes this easier!
Now, behold!
It's all burned away!
But because my money is so powerful,
it moved just in the nick of time!
1,000 Yen
For Practice
Wh-What?
Well? We're having fun now, right?
You don't look like you're having fun.
Okay, let's recover with
one more burning paper trick!
It's called flash paper!
Flash paper is a magic item
that burns in an instant when lit!
It burns so quickly, your hand
never even gets hot!
Like the lighter,
it's invaluable for misdirection!
But therein lies the secret!
This time I'll stun them with
a sudden flower conjuring!
Remain calm, Sempai.
Your hand feels overheated from your nerves,
but it's just your imagination.
It's not your imagination!
The flower in your hand is on fire!
That's hot!
Magic Girl, don't throw it that—
Amazing...
It's like a festival.
Water!
It's finally out.
All our fireworks, up in smoke...
I failed...
I just wanted to deepen
my friendships with everyone.
She's still smoldering, though.
Sempai, we can set off fireworks another time.
Nothing left to do, so I guess
we ought to head home.
Fair enough.
I h-have some fireworks, though.
Grandma told me to bring them.
They're last year's, so they might
have gotten a little moist, though.
Madara-san...
They're working like normal!
Normal is nice.
And I just like having everyone here together.
Hey...
I feel like the two of us
got closer, don't you?
Well... sure.
It's hot! It hit my foot!
It's hot! It's so hot!
No, not a bit, in fact.
Four Balls Sempai
Ventriloquism Sempai
Tailing Sempai
Join us next week for more Magical Sempai!