Unknown Sempai
"Unknown Sempai."
Acum, colega mai mare știe cât de mult îmi place chestia asta.
Totuși, nu am nicio idee cum a ajuns la ideea că îmi plăcea de ea.
I admire her cup size, at the very least.
Deci îți plac sânii mari, nu?
Păi, la fel ca tuturor.
Cu cât sunt mai mari, cu atât mai bine, nu?
C-Cine naiba ești?!
Hi, there! It's so great to meet you!
Îmi poți spune Saki, bine?
I'm feeling a vibe!
Serios, cine ești?
Her ribbon color suggests
she's a third-year student,
but there's no way Sempai has any friends.
So? Are you the one in charge here?
Well... are you trying to join the club?
Nope!
Invazie
I came to hijack the magic club!
Please don't hijack me!
I want to leave.
Why do we need some stinkin' gyaru?!
What are you even good for?!
Let's see...
I can do this!
A flower made of balloons?
So cute!
That's balloon art,
a kind of street performance.
Pretty cool, yeah?
I c-can do that, too!
I have doubts.
B-Balloons scare me!
So you transferred here last month,
and you've been searching for a club?
Yep!
I heard the magic club was totally
shutting down 'cause no one would join it.
I thought magic tricks and street performance
would make a way cool combination!
Of course, the club president
would have to be Ma-kun!
Ma-kun?
Ma-kun's my little bro!
He's super hot and precious and smart,
and he just looks perfect every day!
He'll be way famous some day, you just know it!
Are un
complex
pentru
fratele ei
She's into her brother.
But I'd remember if a jerk like
that transferred to our school.
Cartea celor șase coduri
Pardon me.
Ma-kun!
I was told I would find my big sister here.
Gyaru-Pan Sempai
"Gyaru-Pan Sempai."
Big Sis, were you moving
things along without me?
I'm totally sorry, Ma-kun!
To summarize last episode's events...
There's a gyaru and a fat dude among us.
Um, I don't actually have to be the president.
I'm happy to be a normal member.
All right! Let's make a great
street performance club together!
That sounds nice.
It means your club will be
officially recognized.
I'm happy to have more club members,
but becoming the street performance club
isn't exactly the way I wanted
to keep the magic club alive.
Let's split the difference
and be the street magic club!
Don't just upgrade yourself!
Someone who likes magic will
totally get street performance!
Go on, Ma-kun. Show her what we got!
Me?
All right. I'm going to make a doggie.
Ma-kun's so talented!
Ma-kun's so hot!
Especially how he twists those balloons
with these cream puff arms of his!
I don't get it.
Come on, people! Here's where you clap!
Ah... right.
Sempai, why are you clapping, too?
Bam
And you! Don't go acting all bashful!
Okay! I won't let my bro get all the spotlight!
I call this... the human balloon!
It's impressive, but a little unsettling.
And now, I let all the air out!
Street performance is awesome!
Now I'll pop the balloon
and escape all cool-like!
Huh? My skirt's missing!
It got caught up when I put the balloon on!
What'll I do?!
Big Sis! Just call it off!
Ma-kun...
I greatly appreciate your concern,
but I cannot let your show
end in disaster due to my error!
A m-miraculous escape! Now, clap!
Forgive us for this
embarrassing performance.
Everyone messes up now and then!
Don't apologize, Ma-kun!
Measuring Sempai
"Measuring Sempai."
Well? Your interest in street
performance is growing, right?
Something will start growing
if you don't put on your skirt.
Assistant! We can't let them beat us!
Don't be so competitive!
Wait... you just really want to show
them magic tricks, don't you?
Yes!
Damn your pure soul!
N-Now, the magic club will
conduct a magic show!
We hope you enjoy it.
To start off... watch, as a
cane appears from nowhere!
Behind her?!
Murder...
Sorry about that!
The next one will work fine.
I call this "The Disappearing Coin!"
When I shake my hand three times,
the coin will disappear!
Three,
two...
Hey, wait!
What are you showing my Ma-kun?!
Unhand me.
You showed him the same thing!
Okay, let's pick back up from
the coin's disappearance!
I'm pretty sure that's cheating.
Look at where the coin has moved to!
What the...
Don't dig so deep!
Perhaps it went into his pants!
Stop!
My assistant is too tired to continue,
so we'll call an end to it here!
Do you guys do this every day?
Well?
Have I sparked your interest in magic?
I don't think anyone's feeling a spark!
So, let's take a vote!
Who wants to be the street performance club?
Me, me, me!
No fair!
Assistant is on my side! Don't manhandle him!
What was that?!
Hello, there! I wanna be the advisor!
Sensei!
Big Sis!
I came here like you said, Sensei! But she
won't let this be the street performance club!
I knew my sister was behind this!
Is this a fight I see?
I know just how to settle it!
All right!
I win!
Huh? We need to judge
on shape, not just weight!
How could you agree to this?!
Suspicious Sempai
"Suspicious Sempai."
Three... Two... One...
You're getting sleepy! Very sleepy!
Are you asleep?
You're asking me?
That's weird.
For Dummies!
How to Hypnotize People
I did it just like the book says.
Where did I mess up?
I can't believe you bought
that obviously phony book.
The problem is, I got the order wrong!
Controlul mușchilor
Controlul celor cinci simțuri
Controlul timpului și amintirilor
I need to bring you slowly into
a trance by putting your muscles,
then your senses, then your sense
of time and memory to sleep.
But I guess I did your senses first!
It says you can make someone
your puppet if you do it right,
so I was really looking forward to that.
If that's your plan, there's no
way I'm letting you do it!
It all starts with control of muscles.
First, clasp your hands together
with just your index fingers extended.
Then gaze in between
your fingers, and you'll find...
They come together!
Wow, they really did it!
Would you look at that?
Please do that quietly.
It says here that characteristics
of people difficult to hypnotize are:
deeply suspicious, easily distracted,
lacking in imagination, and insensitive!
Enervat!
So the dumber you are, the easier it is?
I get it!
You're not cut out for hypnotism,
so you should try it on me!
Do I have to?
Get to it!
For Dummies!
How to Hypnotize People
Okay, how about this one? I transfer
your sense of touch to a plastic bottle.
That sounds so fun!
This is so fishy.
I'm going to transfer your sense of touch,
from head to toe, to this plastic bottle.
It's moving now.
From the tip of your head down to your body.
From your body, slowly, down to your toes...
Now all of your senses
are transferred to this bottle.
Well? Feel any different?
I'm not really sure...
Well, then, if I may...
S-Stop tickling my feet!
That's your feet?!
Then, what if I tickle here?
Please... not there.
What did I just touch?!
Chemistry Prep Room
Fun
Magic Club
Sempai, wake up! Sempai!
I am awake.
Oh, jeez...
I got carried away and overdid it.
For Dummies!
How to Hypnotize People
She's the one who asked
to be hypnotized, right?
Maybe I'll have a little fun to get her
back for all she's put me through...
"Always speak in a way that
plants the suggestion of initiative
in the hypnotized person's mind."
You just arrived at a hot spring
to wash away the exhaustion of the day.
You want to get into that hot water at once.
You should leave your
clothing in the changing room.
Three, two, one...
Okay!
Hypnotism freaking rocks!
Um... I need to get changed,
so could you wait over there?
R-Right...
She remembers that much, at least?
She's fallen for it so hard,
my guilt at deceiving her is
outstripping my uncertainty.
I'd better call it off.
Aceste tehnici sunt puternice! Nu abuzați de ele!
How to undo hypnosis...
"Even if someone is hypnotized, you can't make
them do things they really don't want to do."
Which means... Sempai doesn't mind
the idea of going to a hot spring with me?
All ready!
No, she's probably just too stupid
to be thinking anything at all.
Time for a bath!
But it's rotten of me to
take advantage of that!
Sempai, I'm sorry!
There's not really a hot spring here!
Too late?!
Huh? Wh-What am I...
Not good!
You're naked... b-because you're a cat.
You're covered in fur and you
have a tail and cat ears.
Meow!
I can't get her out of her trance!
How suggestible can a person be?!
Wait a minute.
Maybe I could use the hypnosis
to cure her of her stage fright!
This is partly an apology, but if
I can make Sempai good at magic...
You're a professional magician.
You can do magic tricks without flubbing them.
You've just gone up on stage,
where you'll perform amazing magic tricks.
Three,
two,
one.
Hello! Welcome to the world of magic!
She's not nervous!
If this keeps up, she might just do it right!
What's the matter?
So many people have come to see me...
I never said it was a sold-out crowd!
Următoarea zi
As you can see, the bill is back to normal...
1.000 yeni
pentru antrenament
Ah, it's cut in half!
You suck.
I guess that didn't cure it.
Creative Sempai
Fund-Raising Sempai
Pool Sempai
Transferring Sempai
Data viitoare în Colega mai
mare din Clubul de Magie!