Biased Sempai
"Biased Sempai."
Today, I'm going to use these envelopes
to guess your deepest secrets!
It's called the mind-reading trick!
I don't have any secrets.
The people who say that are always
hiding the most lurid things of all!
That's what makes it fun!
Stop biasing it!
Even if I had secrets, I wouldn't tell you!
Write a secret down, put it in the
envelope, and bring it to me.
The key to this trick is how
I've marked each envelope!
They'll let me know immediately
who wrote each one!
Here you are.
Okay, don't panic!
I'm sure the envelope I gave him
had a hole in the bottom right.
Or was it bottom left?
I totally forgot!
I'll just have to open them and make
my guesses during the unveiling!
Then the secret written in this envelope...
"I miss the connection we used to have."
Assistant... I'm sorry!
I'll go back to bossing you
around all the time!
What are you talking about?!
Well, you said you miss our connection...
You're feeling neglected since
Saki-chan and her brother came, right?
Like hell I'd write something like that!
That should have been clear within seconds!
Then who did write it?
Saki-san, clearly! About Masashi!
Huh? But...
Saki-chan wrote, "My growing
chest is becoming a bother..."
I went up another size?
I see!
No way would I ever write that!
Oh, that was mine.
Return my boner!
But if the secrets are too obvious,
it stops being fun!
They weren't obvious to you!
Try to write things you'd never admit to!
It's not fair that we're
taking the brunt of all this.
You need to participate this time.
Tha-thump
Okay, opening now...
Tha-thump Tha-thump
Tha-thump Tha-thump Tha-thump
Tha-thump
Dear Ma-kun... It's hard to say this,
so I wrote you a letter.
How do you feel about me, Ma-kun?
Now that we're in the same high school,
I'd like it if we could spend lunch together.
This wasn't the kind of "things
you'd never admit to" she meant!
Tha-thump
"Sister, please stop stealing
my recently-used items of clothing."
Tha-thump Tha-thump
Tha-thump Tha-thump Tha-thump
Tha-thump
And you should take this
one up with her directly.
Tha-thump
Tha-thump Tha-thump
I guess this one's from Sempai.
Tha-thump Tha-thump Tha-thump
What did she write?
Nothing...
Sempai, what are you...
I thought about it, but I have nothing to hide
and nothing weighing on my conscience.
Just the worry of having no worries, you know?
That's your reaction?!
Make-Up Exam Sempai
"Make-Up Exam Sempai."
Okay, I'll call in the proctor.
Make-Up Exam
Focus on quiet self-study until then.
Fine...
Weird... Magic Girl seems smart
when she's not doing magic stuff.
Let's get this junk over with, huh?
Hey, hey...
Want to try a simple magic trick with numbers?
So that's how she distracts herself.
It's a game where you alternate saying
numbers from one through thirty.
You can say up to three numbers at once,
and whoever says "thirty" is the loser.
But...
I'll make it so you say thirty every time!
There's a trick to it, of course!
I just have to stop myself at twenty-one!
By arranging the numbers
carefully from the start,
I can catch her in my trap!
Thirty again!
Ha-ha-ha-ha
Let's start, then.
One, two...
Twelve, thirteen, fourteen.
Fifteen, sixteen, seventeen.
Eighteen, nineteen.
There! Now I just have to take
twenty and twenty-one to win!
Twenty...
It's from my assistant.
Let's see.
He says, "How long until
the exam is finished?"
And I reply, "About twenty minutes."
Now, let's continue!
Twenty-one, twenty-two!
Huh?
Twenty-three, twenty-four, twenty-five...
Hey, I might win this thing.
Twenty-six...
Twenty-seven, twenty-eight, twenty-nine...
Thirty!
One more time!
If you insist.
I can't lose on a trick I proposed!
Whoever focuses on powers of four plus one—
that is, five, nine, thirteen, seventeen,
twenty-one, and twenty-five—is the winner!
I'm actually smart, you hear me?!
Okay, one.
Two.
Three, four...
Five?
I can win just by watching
the look on her face.
Nineteen, twenty, twenty-one!
T-Twenty-two...
Why isn't this working out?
If she stops at twenty-five, I'll lose.
Please, stop at twenty-four!
Twenty-three...
Oh, twenty-four. I'll stop at twenty-four.
Are you sure?!
I finally got it!
My predictive magic worked!
Twenty-five!
It's from Sempai.
Colega mai mare
Wah, don't think I'll make it
today...
You run the magic club
Looks like they'll be late.
Want to stop by the arcade?
Sounds good!
Colega mai mare și înghețata
"Ice Cream Sempai."
So hot... I want to go home.
That's what you say, but you still come
to club on every day of summer vacation!
You little scamp!
You're the one who called me here.
We can't do club stuff in heat like this.
Look at the both of them.
They're actually melting!
I thought this might happen,
so I prepared something special!
Suc
Ice Cream Bars
Who wants ice cream?!
Me!
Help yourselves!
I see you're wondering why the box
sounded full when I shook it!
Behold!
I put some change inside this box
strapped to my arm to make noise!
This is the summer magic trick,
the Disappearing Ice Cream!
Oh, no!
She even ticked off Masashi.
I can't believe I had to buy ice
cream for the whole club.
You completely deserved it.
But I won't be discouraged!
I will now make this spoon disappear!
Your persistence is almost admirable.
Watch closely!
Three, two, one!
I'll have to eat it with my fingers.
Why don't you just get a new one?
What's wrong, Saki-san?
Ice cream headache?
Can't we ditch this dumb stuff
and do something summery?!
D-Dumb stuff?
Do something? Like what?
Like go to the beach!
The beach?
The white beaches, blue skies,
and the blue ocean!
Deepening friendship!
Fleeting summer memories!
I wanna go! I wanna go! I want
to get my fill of summer!
That's not the face of someone
thinking about friendship!
Rustle rustle rustle
Friendship... and fleeting summer memories?
I don't think Sempai's into the idea—
M-Me?
If you all want, I don't
mind making a few plans.
Not that I care either way.
You're looking super enthusiastic!
So... we're going, then?
Yay!
Colega mai mare și costumul de baie
"Swimsuit Sempai."
Tomorrow, at last, is beach day!
Is everybody ready?
I know I've got my ducks in a row!
Got my wallet, my snacks,
my hat, my cards, my cane,
Behemoth-kun, my pigeons...
Leave the living things here!
And finally, my swimsuit!
Ta-dah!
Costum
de baie
școlar
Hang on. You're gonna wear that outside?
This white one is super cute,
but the frills are also appealing!
And I love the flower pattern!
This one's a real bargain!
Do we really need to be here?
Do you have any recommendations, Assistant?
Y-You want my opinion?
S-So if there's one I like, you'll put it on?
That's the only way to know if it's good!
I'll say!
So if I hand her a skimpy one,
she'll actually wear it?
No, wait...
You want me in this porny stuff, huh?
Creep!
Speculație personală
She'd make me feel so awkward,
I'd have to ditch the trip!
She's mentioned something about magicians
who can make audience members
choose what they want them to choose!
How does that work again?!
If magic fails you,
psychology may prove useful.
Let me help you use
psychological negotiating tactics
to put Sempai in a sexy swimsuit.
I don't think that's necessary.
See? This one looks pretty modest,
but it's got string ties in the back.
You fool!
I won't let you be satisfied
with a compromise swimsuit!
What, you want to see her, too?!
Door • in • the • Face
"Door in the face."
Could you buy me some snacks?
No way!
Then just fetch me a beer from the fridge?
Well, okay, I guess.
You intentionally make a big
request for them to refuse...
Then they'll agree to the more
minor request you actually wanted!
That sounds like fraud.
Do you want her in a sexy swimsuit or not?
I do!
But wait, this doesn't add up.
It's pretty much all string
I'd have to offer her something
super-sexy from the start,
when the whole point is not to gross her out.
Yeah, I thought so!
Low Ball Technique
"Low ball technique."
Hey, can I borrow some change?
Dried Squid
Okay...
Actually, I forgot my wallet.
Can you just buy the whole thing?
Okay...
Just as a pitcher shifts gradually from
easy-to-hit low balls to harder-to-hit ones,
you get them to agree to something minor,
then add on more problematic
conditions they have to agree to!
That's totally fraud!
But sexy suit time!
I want it!
How about this one, Sempai?
Okay, I'll try it on!
Now, hand this to her,
claiming you meant it for Saki-san.
You are pure trash.
I do want to see her in that thing,
but she's gonna be so
pissed off if I hand it to her!
I'm hella pissed off! Grr!
Speculație personală
Thou shalt not blow an awesome opportunity!
What about the psychology?!
I-It wasn't me!
Masashi just grabbed it and—
It's dreadfully embarrassing, but if this
is what Ma-kun wants me to wear...
It's a mistake! Take it off! Now!
An acceptable end result.
Th-This is what you wanted?
Straining!
I'm not sure about this...
Like hell!
You put it on backwards, stupid!
That assistant of mine!
Picking such an odd swimsuit...
Hey, a changing room is just like a magic set!
I just had a brilliant idea!
Okay, now...
I'll move my shoes to the neighboring stall,
and close the curtain.
Then I'll call to my assistant,
and when he opens the curtain,
he'll be shocked to see nobody there!
I call it the "Instant Disappearance Trick!"
Ma'am?
These belong in front of this stall.
Was someone playing a prank?
Assistant! There's a swimsuit
I want you to see!
Open the curtain!
Okay!
Why aren't you wearing it?!
Th-That w-wasn't—
Close the curtain!
Beach Sempai
Crab Sempai
Watermelon Sempai
Fireworks Sempai
Join us next week for more Magical Sempai!