Magical Sempai
Four Balls Sempai
"Four Balls Sempai."
You never get tired of playing
with yourself, do you?
Why won't it work out?
Could I see them?
At last, you show interest...
It's been so long.
I'll teach you anything you want to know.
Don't make it sound like
you ever taught me anything!
The name of this trick is "The Four Balls."
You stick one ball in between
each of your fingers,
which leaves you with four.
You can increase or de... de...
decrease the number of balls!
There are just as many as before.
To make the ball in the right hand disappear,
you use a technique called palming,
where you pinch it in your palm
to make it look like it disappeared.
But my hands are slick with sweat,
so it's not working right.
Even though I practiced so much...
On the way to school,
when I'm eating, even in the bath...
If you can do it in the bath,
why is sweat a problem?
I wonder if my hands
are just too small to do it...
Can't you just get some smaller ones
that fit your hands better?
I thought the bigger ones looked cooler!
Self-defeating vanity.
I envy your big hands, Assistant.
See? They're so much bigger.
There's nothing better for doing
magic than big hands.
Well... it would look strange
if yours were this big.
I think they're fine... just the way they are.
Y-Y-You think?
Sorry for touching!
G-Gross!
The sweat! The sweat!
But he was just complimenting them.
Ventriloquism Sempai
"Ventriloquism Sempai."
When I arrived in the club room...
I found Saki-san dead on the ground.
What a twist!
I'm not dead.
Oh, you're not dead.
I'm done for.
My Ma-kun meter's all petered out.
What kind of stupid scale is that?
That's right. You're not with
Masashi today, are you?
It's because...
This morning, I was rummaging through
Ma-kun's trash like usual, when...
Smells like Ma-kun!
And now he hasn't talked to me all day!
It's entirely your fault.
I refuse to comfort you.
Wait! I know what to do at times like this.
What is it?
You' aweshome, 'ig Shish! You're sho hrehhy!
You can't flatter me with the truth!
So you do ventriloquism
with that Masashi puppet?
It's just a hobby, is all.
You open your mouth a tiny bit,
then without moving your lips...
I' 'ashashi.
It must be hard to talk.
Bs and Ps are hard to say.
So are Ms.
Because you use your lips for those.
If you can say "pushy," it means
you're on the right track.
'Ushy. 'Ushy.
See? Hard, right?
Puhhy.
Oh, I think I can do it. Puh—
I get it already! You can stop saying it!
Well, now you try it, Assistant!
Use what I taught you,
and you'll have it in no time!
All right, Masashi, introduce yourself.
Nasashi here.
Ny havori'e dri'k ish curry.
Ma-kun would never say that.
That's the issue? Scary...
I just feel so lonely without Ma-kun around!
The puppet can't fill the gap in my heart!
You seemed to enjoy it, though.
Whatever.
I'll just have to mess around with
you today, Assistant-kun.
What? Wait a minute.
This is very abrupt, Saki-san!
H-Hang on...
Saki-san?!
Just kidding!
I'll give you this Magic Doll
as thanks for cheering me up.
It's a present from me to you!
I really don't want it.
Well, gotta get to the part-time job!
You're just going to leave it here?
Bye-bye!
White, eh?
Tailing Sempai
"Tailing Sempai."
Now, behold!
It's leaking out! It's totally leaking!
Hey, hey...
Does Sempai have a boyfriend?
Don't tell me... you're planning
on that, are you?
Don't do it, seriously.
It's not that. I saw her yesterday.
She was walking around with a strange man.
No way.
After Club
Now, let's begin tailing her!
I wonder who the man is.
I'm sure he just accosted her
for a survey or something.
She entered a family restaurant!
Behavioral psychology
suggests it's suspicious
for a teenage female to enter
a family restaurant alone.
You're so smart, Ma-kun!
Did you use that mental stuff?!
Are you talking about being a mentalist?
Look! Two plates of cake and two glasses!
And she's sitting in the back,
wary of eyes upon her!
She's clearly waiting for someone!
She drank one down.
She's practicing the coin trick.
Can I go now?
She ended up eating both
slices of cake by herself, too.
I think you were off base.
She's watching her smartphone.
She took off!
She probably needs to hit the bathroom.
No, she's meeting someone.
When one puts their face that
close to their smartphone,
it's proof that they're engaging
in intimate messaging.
Are you enjoying this?
She's running right for the convenience store!
She must be going for...
The bathroom!
Thank you for
always keeping
the bathroom clean
She's been in there a while.
But if I'm in the toilet, I'll be
fixing my hair and my make-up.
Of course! That explains
why she's been in there so long!
I think it's time to let it go.
She's back!
She looks cleaned out, is all!
We tailed her for half the day,
and not only did she not meet anyone,
all she did was eat and poop.
I'm telling you, there's no
way Sempai has a boy—
Sorry! Were you waiting long?
I got a little sidetracked,
so I'm running late.
It's okay. I didn't wait long at all.
Let's go, then.
This is getting fun!
Okay!
You okay?
Assistant-kun, do you like
Magic Girl that much?
Maybe I'll console you.
I'm about as big as she is.
No way!
It's not like I'm trying to be her boyfriend.
It's like when you take care of a stray cat,
and you find out it was a housecat all along!
It's that kind of thing!
Sounds possessive.
The way he refuses to take any responsibility
just makes the boyfriend act creepier.
But there's nothing wrong with
Magic Girl having a boyfriend, right?
The question is whether or not he's dangerous.
Time for the mentalist to resurface.
More of this?
Higashi Tanenashi Station
First, let's judge his appearance.
He's wearing street clothes on a weeknight.
In other words, he's likely
not an office worker.
Unemployed or a student, then?
No, that ring on his left hand
means he's likely not a student.
His shoes are expensive,
and his clothing is dark.
He's watching his surroundings carefully.
It's very likely that the man is married.
And a professional assassin!
So cool! You're such a genius!
Are you all right in the head?
His only visible possession
is the key to a minivan.
Minivan...
I saw that in one of your secret
adult videos, Ma-kun!
Vehicle to Rendezvous or something!
That guy might be involved with adult videos!
That's a gross hobby.
It's not like that! It's just that
it starred my favorite actress—
Friendly Fire
They're going into a department store!
Look, Mimura-san!
They sell Okinawa stuff here, it says!
So his name is Mimura, eh? Well done!
Ryukyu Gifts
Okinawan Chinsukou
Look! Chincocksu!
She read it wrong!
Has the adult video shoot started already?
Would this be the introduction or something?
Look! Look!
This bitter gourd is so big!
Stop it!
Now that it's on my mind,
I can't stop thinking about it!
The bumps are so cool...
I-I-It's gotta be a cooking show!
Th-Th-They scouted out a
pretty high school girl,
and th-th-they're having her
introduce local cuisine!
It's a totally family-friendly show!
Assistant-kun is breaking down.
Given the flow of the date so far...
I thought Mimura was a man
cheating on his wife with Sempai,
but it's clear he's a professional
killer-slash-adult video performer
who lures out teenage girls
with dubious proposals
then uses regional produce
to f*** them in his minivan.
That seems ridiculously improbable!
They're in a lingerie store!
What are you thinking, size-wise?
Assistant-kun, get a grip!
Not sure...
About average, I think?
Average, my ass!
Go for the cow tits!
Calm down, Assistant-kun!
Thanks for everything.
They're back outside!
It'll be cold in short sleeves at night.
Let's move to the car.
Look at that nice, fat...
Yeah, do it!
It's too bitter raw! Please cook it!
How do you feel now, pig?!
Magic Mirror Van, move out!
Underage kids aren't allowed out past ten!
Assistant?
Mimura-san is my big sister's husband.
Her birthday is next week,
so I went with him to buy a present.
I just didn't know what to get by myself.
What a nice man.
Sorry about the misunderstanding.
It's late. Should I give you a ride home?
S-Sorry.
We live nearby, so we'll be okay.
Just a really nice guy...
You were tailing me because you
thought Mimura-san was my boyfriend?
I'm very sorry.
There's no way.
The fact that she laughed it off...
is somehow more scary.
Growing Sempai
Unfailing Sempai
Persistent Sempai
Silent Sempai
Bunny Sempai
Join us next week for more Magical Sempai!