Ce naiba înseamnă asta?
Funcționați, senzori proști!
Fir-ar, de parcă acele surori nu erau niște belele imense,
acum și tu îmi stai în drum?
Hei.
Sunt meditatorul fetelor
Nakano de la etajul 30.
Numele meu este Uesugi.
Ușa de aici
este defectă.
Hei.
Ce faci aici de unul singur?
Miku.
Nu ai auzit de uși cu închidere automată?
Le găsești peste tot acum.
Poți introduce numărul apartamentului nostru cu această tastură.
Și ne va suna.
D-Desigur că știam asta.
Am dat-o în bară din start.
Nu-i un început prea bun.
Dar...
Ce tot faci?
Ce?
O-Oh.
Ne vei medita, nu?
The Quintessential Quintuplets
Deci, a trebuit să vii.
Bun-venit, Uesugi-san!
Hei.
Ei bine...
Ar trebui să fie pe undeva pe aici.
Cel alb, nu-i așa?
Scuze.
De ce încă ești în pat la amiază?
Asta este a ta, Ichika?
A-Atât de matură.
Avem aceeași față.
Probabil și tu ai arăta bine în ea.
Ar trebui să arunci lenjeria
pe care o ai din gimnaziu.
U-Uesugi-san este aici!
Șșș!
Deci...
Cum ți se pare, Uesugi-san?
Crezi că aș...
Nu-mi pasă. Doar îmbracă-te.
Nu-mi pasă de părerea ta, oricum!
Pariez că nu știi nimic despre modă!
Bun, suntem gata.
Să începem să învățăm.
Eu cred că doar voi privi.
Învață-ne istoria Japoniei
cum ne-ai spus că o vei face.
Eu voi învăța de una singură aici, deci nu mă băgați în seamă.
Încă sunt multe probleme,
dar comparativ cu ce era la început, acesta este un progres imens.
Hei! Așteaptă!
Și ele sunt oameni.
Fii drăguț cu ele și poți
ajunge la o înțelegere.
Bun, haideți să începem.
Încă ești aici?
Încă nu ai renunțat la meditat, nu?
Sper să nu adormi cum ai făcut-o ultima oară.
Asta s-a întâmplat
deoarece mi-ai pus somnifere.
O, fir-ar. Trebuie să fiu drăguț.
Trebuie să fiu drăguț.
Ce spui?
Ai vrea să ni te alături, Nino?
Doar peste cadavrul meu.
Presupun că trebuie să mă mulțumesc doar cu patru deocamdată.
În regulă. Să începem fără ea astăzi.
Bine.
O, da, Yotsuba,
cunoștința mea din echipa de baschet caută
o persoană care să joace cu ei un meci.
Ești destul de atletică.
De ce nu mergi tu chiar acum?
C-Chiar acum?
E bine...
Dar...
Aparent, au doar cinci membri,
iar unul dintre ei are o fractură.
Nu vor putea să joacă
dacă nu găsesc pe cineva.
Îmi pare rău pentru ei.
Nu vei merge, nu-i așa?
Cu siguranță s-au antrenat din greu.
Săraca echipă.
Yotsuba?
Îmi pare rău, Uesugi-san.
Nu pot abandona oamenii
care au nevoie de ajutor!
Cred că glumești.
Acea fată nu știe cum să refuze.
Nu spuneai că ai treabă la ora două, Ichika?
Fir-ar, uitasem!
Și tu, Itsuki.
Ar trebui să mergi într-un loc mai liniștit, cum ar fi librăria sau ceva asemănător.
Asta este o idee bună.
În regulă! Adunați-vă, toată lumea!
Să începem sesiunea de învățat.
Înfruntă realitatea, Futaro.
Toată lumea a plecat deja.
Acea Nino, iar îmi stă în drum...
Ce încearcă să facă?
Ce?
Încă ești aici, Miku?
Îmi ești datoare cu o băutură de
când ai băut-o din greșeală pe a mea.
Ți-am cumpărat-o deja.
Bun, haide să începem cu învățatul.
În regulă, haide să ne apucăm.
Suc Matcha?
Matcha
Soda
Hei, Miku!
De unde începem?
Atunci, de ce nu începem
cu perioada Kamakura?
De când sunteți așa de apropiați?
Deci, îți plac băieții
plictisitori și simpli, nu?
Asta a fost cam urât! Retrage ce ai spus!
Ești prea fixată pe înfățișare, Nino.
Nici asta nu a fost prea drăguț!
Ce?
Ce este în neregulă cu
a vrea băieți arătoși?
Vrei să-mi spui că doar
frumusețea interioară contează?
Și dacă asta fac, ce?
Înțeleg.
Deoarece nu-ți pasă de înfățișare, poți ieși îmbrăcată așa nearanjat.
Iar aceste unghii ascuțite
ar trebui să fie la modă?
Nu înțelegi, nu?
Nici nu vreau s-o fac.
H-Haideți, fetelor.
Sunteți surori. Încercați să vă înțelegeți.
Chiar trebuie să ne contrazicem asupra
frumuseții interioare și exterioare acum?
Presupun că ai dreptate.
Nu ne mai deranja.
Cum adică vă deranjez?!
Guuurgle
Bine, atunci. De ce nu ne întrecem în
"frumusețe interioară", după cum afirmi?
Haide să avem un concurs de gătit
ca să vedem care este mai casnică.
D-De ce?
Dacă câștig eu, nu se va învăța astăzi.
N-Nu vei accepta, nu-i așa?
Voi încheia asta repede.
Doar stai jos și așteaptă, Futaro.
Tu stai jos!
De ce nimic nu merge așa cum vreau eu?
Și gata!
A dutch baby with seasonal veggies and ham.
Omurice
O-Omletă cu orez.
Acum, tu o să decizi care fel este mai bun.
De fapt, m-am răzgândit. O voi mânca eu.
You made it, so you might
as well have him eat it.
Mersi.
Okay, yeah.
Ambele sunt destul de bune.
Vorbesc serios.
Not a Gourmet
Too Poor
Ambele sunt bune.
Ce?!
Nu se poate.
Ce naiba?
Prea plictisitor.
Doamne, acea fată...
It's gotten so late.
We fell right into Nino's trap.
I'll have to try again another time.
Sorry.
But now it's all clear.
I don't know why,
but Nino especially hates me.
I don't feel like I'll ever get to be
on good terms with her.
You're wrong...
I think.
Huh?
Miku?
If you face her in good faith,
she'll come around.
In good faith?
What am I supposed to do?
Don't ask me.
It's your job to figure that out.
Face her in good faith...
Good faith...
Shoot.
Uh...
What?
Sorry, I forgot my flash cards.
I'm taking a shower.
Feel free to come in and grab them.
Wait, Miku, you're okay with that?
P-Pardon me.
M-Miku?!
You're already out of the shower?!
Come to think of it,
she's not one to care about these things.
I'll just grab my cards and leave.
Who's there?
Miku?
I thought you were going to take a bath.
It's free now.
Nino!
My contacts are on the usual shelf.
Could you get them for me?
Her eyesight is so bad that she can't see me?
Sh-Shit...
What should I do, then?
Good faith? If she finds out I'm here,
there'll be no faith left!
No Faith
What do I do?
What?
Are you still mad about me
messing with you at lunch?
Sh-Shit!
C-Contacts...
Where are they?
Here?
I just got carried away.
I feel bad about it, okay?
Damn it, where are they?
What are you doing?
That's not where they are.
They're on the shelf above.
Huh?
I though they were on this shelf.
I can't face her now!
I can't take any more!
Run for it!
So you are mad.
It's his fault.
It's all his fault.
He keeps coming into our home
just because Dad ordered it.
This home is for us five.
There's no place for him here.
Is she...
That's it!
From now on, he's banned from our place!
Look out!
Above you!
At that point, I still didn't know...
Wh-Who's there?
Thank you.
You were great as always today, Ichika-chan.
See you next time.
Sure.
I didn't know how hard it would be to
face these five idiots one at a time.
Thanks so much.
You're so good, Nakano-san.
We're lucky to have you.
Let's kill it next time, too.
Hey, I want to ask you something...
Would you be up for officially
joining the basketball team?
And I'd be taught a lesson, too.
It's because of what she said.
So you have a thing for
dull-looking guys, huh?
It's not even true.
That I'm a complete idiot, too.
I-Intruder!
N-No!
I just came to take something.
Take what?
Nudes of me?
You pervert!
Molester!
Voyeur!
That's not what I meant!
You're the worst.
Order in the court.
Your Honor, please have a look at this.
The defendant, a tutor,
lost control of his urges in front
of a young high school girl.
Defendant Uesugi...
This is you in this photo, is it not?
I-It's a false charge.
Absent due
to basketball
team duties
Your Honor...
Yes, Plaintiff Nino-kun.
This guy pretended to leave the apartment
and waited for me to exit the shower.
H-Hey!
That's a fabrication!
For his heinous crimes, I request that he
be barred permanently from entering here.
Th-That's too much!
I can't say I approve of your actions.
Ichika...
I just came to get something.
Y-Your Honor?
Objection.
Futaro may look like a criminal,
but he's innocent.
What do you mean, I look like a criminal?
I let him in over the intercom.
There's a recording, too.
This was an unforeseen accident.
Miku!
You're still taking his side?
This guy said it himself!
That he's here to take something!
Take
To take sneak shots!
You mean he forgot something,
and he came to get it.
Get
Your Honor, Miku is defending him
due to her feelings for him.
N-No.
I knew you would believe in me, Miku.
Don't come any closer.
Huh?!
Are you acting like that
because you're wary of him?
I'm not.
You're imagining things.
Just so you know, he saw me naked.
It's not like there's much to see.
Maybe not for you, but there is for me.
Our bodies are about the same.
N-Now's not the time to be arguing.
Shut up, Itsuki.
Also, delete that photo already.
Your Honor!
There, there.
Even if Miku were right, would you
really end up in this position?
Ichika!
I knew you would understand.
This guy threw himself
onto me out of nowhere.
No, I was...
Futaro, is that true?
Y-Yeah, but that was...
You're guilty.
Commit seppuku.
M-Miku-san?!
Shoot, I need to fight back.
I'm going to lose my tutoring job.
But can I get them to believe me?
The shelves...
Some books fell off the the shelves,
and he shielded Nino from them?
If you look carefully,
you could see it that way.
Is that not it?
Th-That's exactly it!
Thanks, Itsuki.
I haven't done anything for you to thank me.
I'm just proposing a possible explanation.
True.
Yeah, there's no way Futaro-kun
would have the balls.
H-Hey!
Why are you talking like
it's been resolved now?
Quit talking out of your ass!
Stop it, Nino.
How dare you?
Come on, don't get so heated.
We sisters used to get
along so well, remember?
That said, this happened
because I was being careless.
Sorry.
We used to?
I...
Hey, Nino?
She just left.
Shouldn't we get her?
Let her be.
I can finally go home and study.
Hey! Dinner's ready!
Uesugi Raiha
Hello
Inbox
Get this, we're having
your favorite: curry udon!
Are they really okay with things as they are?
Guess I shouldn't meddle too much
in another family's issues.
God, you're so useless.
What?
She didn't bring her key,
but she can't bring herself
to ask the three girls inside?
What are you looking at?
I don't want to see your face anymore.
I see.
Well, sorry.
She'd probably lash out if I helped her.
Go ahead and wait by yourself.
What are you doing?
There's a problem I just couldn't solve.
I don't feel like going
home until I solve it.
I see.
All you ever care about is studying.
So stupid.
Studying is stupid? That's a paradox.
Wait, I guess you could say
I'm studying because I'm stupid.
Shut up.
Everyone's so stupid. I hate them all.
Everyone? Including your sisters?
You're lying.
I'm not.
They've got to be crazy to let
a creepy guy like you inside.
Our home...
"This home is for us five.
There's no place for him here."
That's what you said.
Just shut up already.
It can't be just because you hate me.
You hate your sisters?
Are you sure it's not the opposite?
You love your four sisters, don't you?
That's why you don't like
an outsider like me.
What?
You're so incredibly wrong.
You think you understand me.
That could never happen.
Creep.
What? What's wrong with that?
I just...
Nino, I know how you feel.
I have a sister.
Yeah.
I didn't do anything wrong, did I?
This is so stupid. Why should I
have to beat myself up over this?
I've made up my mind.
I'm not going to accept you.
Even if that makes the other girls hate me.
Nino, how long are you going to sit here?
Hurry up and get back inside.
Miku?
You're here too, Futaro?
Perfect.
About tomorrow...
Let's head back, Miku.
But I still need to talk to him.
Forget it.
It looks like it's going to get even harder.
This is why I hate meddling too much.
#03   A Mountain of Problems
Next Time on The Quintessential Quintuplets
#04 A Day Off
Jocul cu întrebări al surorilor!
Nino's in charge of the chores.
We're taking turns cooking
from now on, though.
Okay!
De câtă apă avem nevoie?
Pune din ochi!
Ești concediată!
Five cups of rice each.
Am comandat pizza!
Ești concediată!
Sunt...
Concediată!