Well, this sucks.
Yeah.
We're locked inside.
Okay, I'm going to break down
the door so we can get out.
Get back.
Wait.
Isn't that a burglar sensor?
It might bring the security guards here
if we break down the door.
All the better if they find us.
Wait, no! Don't!
You'll ruin the school camp.
Besides, if Miku found out about this...
Fine.
Try to see if you can disarm it.
If only I were two meters tall.
Say what?
Hurry up and get on my shoulders.
Stay calm.
I can't trip this sensor
in my heart, either.
Don't you dare say I'm heavy.
Are you all right?
Yeah.
Here I go.
Wh-What's wrong?
This sensation...
It's giving me a weird case of deja vu.
Hey! No enjoying my thighs!
Also, you're too heavy for me to lift.
You went and said it after all!
The Quintessential Quintuplets
We need a key to disarm the sensor.
After some investigation...
Looks like we'll have to wait for help.
Hey, Sensei...
What are you doing?
I'm trying to start a fire, obviously.
It'll ruin our last day here
if we catch a cold.
Futaro-kun's smart,
but he's kind of a dummy.
Since there's nothing to do,
let's talk about something fun.
I'm trying to focus. Later.
Ichika still isn't back?
Yeah.
She left saying she needed
to do campfire group stuff.
Miku! Itsuki!
Have either of you seen Uesugi-san?
He vanished in the middle of
helping the campfire group.
He's not in the dining hall,
and he isn't in the room.
He's wandered off to waste time again!
Are you sure I can take him?
I guess Big Sis will have to take care
of poor, lonely Futaro.
I'm going to go look for them.
Miku?!
Yotsuba, what's that key for?
And that's the whole story. Anyway...
The other day, Itsuki-chan was like...
And Nino was so screwed.
What do you think she said
when she saw that croquette?
Not a single response.
You're going to make Big Sis cry again.
He's avoiding asking why I cried.
I wonder if he's just not interested.
Really, why did I cry, anyway?
I might quit school.
Huh?
You finally took notice.
Hold on, you're quitting?
I'd technically be taking a break.
I wouldn't mind.
Cut.
That was good, Ichika-chan.
So, you know how I've been
shooting for a movie, right?
I'm starting to get more gigs now, too.
Other actors playing student roles skip school
knowing they'll have to retake the year,
or move to more flexible schools.
You know how hopeless I am
when it comes to school.
I don't think I'd miss high school.
Besides, Miku might be
better off if I'm gone.
Good for you.
You found something you want to do.
But wait, what happens
to my pay if you're gone?!
Am I losing twenty percent?!
I'm surprised, though.
You fail at life!
I thought that's how pissed you'd be.
Is that how you see me?
Why do you study, Futaro-kun?
I envy you for having options.
Though you're 99 percent likely to fail.
There you go again.
But it'll be a good experience.
And if it works out, great.
Everything is worth a shot.
Futaro.
Ichika.
Are those two really...
It'll be fine.
Miku...
No need to worry with Ichika.
Fine by me.
I mean the campfire dance.
We can call off the dancing together thing.
Oh...
But in return...
Let's dance right now.
It'll be our very own campfire tonight.
Well, no one's looking, I guess.
Yay.
So you were embarrassed.
Obviously.
I never knew you had such a cute side.
Sensor readings normal.
It'll be all right.
It's bad enough that there's a rumor
about a legend going around.
People will make certain
assumptions about us.
Legend?
You didn't know?
Yotsuba told me there's a legend that
people who dance at the campfire
will be together for life.
Does...
Does Miku know about that?
Yeah, she was there.
I-I never intended to...
Ichika?
The campfire was important to Miku.
And yet, I...
Futaro-kun...
Ichika!
Close one.
You know...
You're pretty clumsy.
Let go!
Hey, stop squirming!
Impact detected.
Please unlock within thirty seconds.
If the alarm is not disarmed,
security personnel will
be dispatched immediately.
Shoot, we need to get out
before someone comes here.
Yeah.
What the hell?!
Sprinklers?!
Gotta put out the fire.
Deal with the sensor first.
D-Deal with it how?
We need the key.
The key?
What do we do?
The key is right here.
Ichika...
What were you two doing here?
It's the last day.
I had to explain the incident
with Ichika to the teachers.
We got in huge trouble.
Itsuki and Miku didn't fully believe us.
I hope we have another chance to explain.
How did our fun school camp end up like this?
Okay, Miku-chan, we'll be in the dining hall.
Yeah.
I'll be right there.
If we really are all equal,
what am I supposed to do?
Man, I'm sorry.
I can't believe I had to get sick now.
Just my luck.
Accident or not,
it was the result of your carelessness.
Stay in bed for the day
and reflect on what you did.
Oh, you don't need to stay with me.
Go skiing.
But...
I'll meet up with you once I feel better.
Or are you having a hard time
facing Futaro-kun?
You've been wary around him
ever since our stay at the inn.
So that was you.
It's only been three months.
That day, when I asked him for help
with schoolwork at the cafeteria,
I didn't have the faintest idea...
that things would come to this.
Does Futaro-kun seem like
such a bad person to you?
Th-That's not what I mean.
I still feel drowsy. Back to sleep.
Uesugi-san!
Y-Yotsuba!
You aren't getting away just
because it's an optional activity.
We're going skiing!
Let's ski down all the slopes!
I'm cold. Let me sleep.
I can't ski, anyway.
Sleeping is a waste of time.
If you really can't ski,
I'll hold your hands and guide you.
All right, let's practice!
By the way, where's the idiot quartet?
Ichika's sick, and Itsuki's
taking care of her.
I guess that's not surprising
after what happened.
Huh?
You should have checked
before you locked the door.
What are you talking about?
Nothing.
Nino's already skiing.
There she is.
Who is that?
Miku.
Miku?
You're really hard to tell apart
from just your faces.
That was a spectacular fall.
Are you all right, Miku?
Yeah. I'm fine.
All right! I'm always the one
being taught stuff,
but today, I'm gonna
teach you two everything!
Wow, you look so awkward.
Hello.
Man, it's cold, huh?
Seriously, who are you?
It's me. Ichika.
Oh, you.
Ichika!
Are you really all right?
Yeah, I'm not all better yet, but...
Oh yeah, what about Itsuki?
Wasn't she taking care of you?
Itsuki-chan's skiing on her own because
she doesn't feel like she can face you.
Ichika!
These guys refuse to learn
anything I teach them!
That's how I always feel about you!
Let's make it fun, then.
We'll play tag.
Yotsuba's the best, so she's it.
Okay.
What about Nino and Itsuki?
I'm catching them as soon
as I find them, obviously.
One, two, three, four...
Hey!
Damn it, I only just learned to go forward.
Wait, this might be a chance
to explain myself to Miku.
Miku, want to...
Wait, hey!
Hold up, Miku!
When did she get so good?
This is bad.
There's something I want to make sure about.
Ichika.
You haven't told anyone
about last night, right?
I might quit school.
How could I?
So that means...
Ichika...
How do you stop?
What?
Uesugi-kun!
Yotsuba...
When you teach something,
you have to cover everything.
Uh, are you all right?
Are you alive?
I-I'm fine.
Don't mind me.
I attracted attention.
I don't know if it's because I never
got Raiha's good luck charm back,
but I've been having crap
luck since yesterday.
This bandage...
Is that you, Kintaro-kun?
It is, isn't it?
Huh?
No, I'm not.
What kind of weird name is that?
Yeah, right.
I only ever gave this to you.
Shit.
Now what?
Why are you running away?
Should I tell her now?
That I was lying to her during
the test of courage last night?
Hey, wait!
How do I deal with this amicably?
Shoot! Yotsuba!
Found you, Uesugi-san!
Kintaro-kun!
Uesugi-san!
I'm getting dizzy.
Kintaro-kun!
Uesugi-san!
Huh?
Yotsuba.
Found you, Nino.
Did you see a blond guy go your way?
And have you seen Uesugi-san?
Weird.
Where did he go?
Miku.
That was close. She almost caught you.
Is this an igloo?
You didn't make this, did you?
No, it was already here.
Ah.
It's pretty warm inside.
F-Futaro...
It's cramped in here. Don't move too much.
O-Oh, sorry.
I'll get out, then.
Don't leave, either.
I don't know anymore.
Miku?
I-I mean, Yotsuba might still be out there.
That's true.
Let me stay here for a while longer.
Okay.
Where does she get that
endless stamina, anyway?
It's hard to believe
she's really one of you quintuplets.
She would have caught me if this
igloo hadn't been here, too.
Whatever happened to skiing, anyway?
Why am I doing this?
Well, then...
How are we going to escape?
Let's see...
I know.
Let's get Yotsuba to have a handicap.
A handicap?
We could make her carry things
so we can be equally fast.
That'll make it more fun, I guess.
Yeah. Okay.
But I don't really like that.
The five of you started off with
the same physical abilities, didn't you?
You're quintuplets.
That means Yotsuba earned
her athleticism for herself.
That's true.
I know this is just a game, but...
I don't want to disregard that effort.
Anyone who does it wants
that person all to themselves.
Are you sure I can take him?
No need to worry with Ichika.
What were you two doing here?
We're equals.
You should be his partner.
Being equals is fine,
but you can't ignore the work she put in.
Let's be fair, not equal.
H-Hey...
Ow...
What are you doing?
"Let's be fair."
What the hell am I saying, anyway?
The heat's making me crazy.
I'm going to get some fresh air.
Uesugi-san!
I'm gonna find you, no matter what.
Where did he go?
Kintaro-kun...
Miku
Yes, Miku? What's up?
Ichika, hey...
#11  Legend of Fate Day 3
There's something I want
to talk to you about.
#12 Legend of Fate Day 2000
Next Time on The Quintessential Quintuplets
Futaro-kun.
Get up, Uesugi!
Futaro.
Uesugi-san!
Wake up, Uesugi-kun.
I see.
I never met the quintuplets.
It was all a dream.
There's no way that's true.