A venit momentul.
Ce a fost asta?
Au reușit să se trezească.
De ce nu se aliniază?
Pădurea este în pericol!
Mireasa magicianului străvechi
Băiatul din Vest și cavalerul Furtunii Albastre
O voi face eu, Argint.
Serios, mă descurc și singură.
Voi fi în regulă.
Ce tot faceți?
Oh, Elias.
Bună dimineața.
Mătase, stai, stai.
Voi merge la facultate curând, nu-i așa?
Deci încerc să mă pregătesc.
Curând?
Adică în septembrie?
Mai sunt încă două luni până atunci.
Se pare că am nevoie de
o uniformă înainte de toate.
Măsurile mele...
Doar las-o pe Argint să se ocupe.
Știu, dar...
Vreau să mă obișnuiesc cu această mână.
I was hoping to be more self-sufficient.
Las-o în seama unui profesionist. E mai rapid așa.
Bine.
Mersi, Mătase.
Ce vei face cu aia?
Trebuie doar să trimit această scrisoare facultății, iar ei îmi vor trimite uniforma.
Are you upset that you don't get to make it?
S-Sorry, Silky.
Those are the rules, apparently.
Have you grown?
You were about this tall
when you just got here.
Was I?
Oh, you're right.
I don't really feel taller.
But...
I've gotten just a little closer to you.
You're right.
It's a bit like a sailor uniform.
Sort of like the uniform
I was wearing in Japan.
I never thought I'd be
wearing a uniform again.
Come to think of it, I haven't
asked you about school.
I don't have that many
good memories to share.
I'm still a little scared,
but I'm excited to wear this uniform.
Just a second.
Thanks.
Chise, your body's cold.
You don't feel well, do you?
It seemed like you didn't get any sleep
because of that thunder last night.
Ah.
That was definitely
a vicious storm last night.
Maybe I have a cold.
Get some rest.
You won't get better staying awake.
Okay.
Last night's severe storm has
stopped over central England.
This, and this, and...
The weather is predicted to
remain unstable for some time.
This.
Everyone should check to see if anything in their house got covered in dust.
There.
Because we just had a storm...
Oh! That, too.
Okay,
that's everything.
Are you telling me your
job is more important than mine?
Would you stop shouting?
I'm exhausted from going back and
forth to the hospital in London.
Yeah, well, so am I.
Damn it, this wouldn't be a problem
if we lived in London proper...
Gabriel would have gotten
worse if we'd stayed there.
I know that!
I told you not to shout!
You're shouting louder!
Fantastic, so we're even, then!
Fine.
Man, it's rough.
It's way more rural here than I thought.
No, no.
It's really just the middle of nowhere.
I was hoping the scenery would at least
be a bit more mystical, y'know?
Old forests, stone circles where giants
would have shown up, stuff like that.
There's none of it.
Seriously, nothing mystical at all.
I mean, I don't know this place,
so I guess I can explore a bit.
Yeah.
I'm hiding from Mom and Dad.
They're so annoying. I can't deal with them.
Oh, yeah, I guess.
The only thing that's better than London
is the treehouse in the backyard.
Yeah.
There's a treehouse here.
Come check it out, Oscar.
This weekend, maybe?
There are some historic sites nearby, too.
We might find something weird.
Like faeries, or haunted
cemeteries, or something.
Oh, okay.
Nah, that's fair.
Your mom and dad are busy.
Yeah...
But you've gotta come
over sometime, yeah?
At least once during the summer break.
Okay.
Later.
I'll call you.
Bye-bye.
Some journey this is...
You always do this when
you don't get your way.
That's because you never listen to me.
You're always just thinking about yourself.
They're still at it.
I'm thinking about this rationally!
Smoke?
Huh?
Maybe I'm seeing things.
Wait, that's where lightning
struck last night.
No running!
Mom!
You were watching?
Are you going out?
Yeah, just going for a walk.
Where's your medication?
I've got it.
Keep it around your neck.
I'm fine.
It's for your own good.
I'm not a kid anymore.
If you aren't a kid, you
ought to understand.
I said, I'm fine!
What's her problem?
She drags me out to the countryside,
gets into fights, and blames
it all on my sickness.
Oh man, that's a record!
Focus! Focus!
Seriously? Damn!
Damn!
You've got this!
Go for world record!
It was around here, wasn't it?
It's part of a stone circle!
It's chipped.
It'll be pretty with a little polish.
Crap, it's getting late.
To think the Wild Hunt would
have wandered so far...
I see.
You've been separated from your master.
Still cold, huh?
Yeah, a little.
Maybe you should rest a little longer.
I think I've slept too much.
Silver?
Stay put.
I'll go.
How unusual.
What's your business?
I merely brought a stray.
What is this about?
This is per its request.
I need to get back to the forest.
Is something wrong with the forest?
The Wild Hunt woke up and trampled it.
Wild Hunt?
Um...
Is something wrong?
You don't have to come out, Chise.
She isn't dressed appropriately
for the mid-summer.
I've had chills since this morning.
That, too, is the influence of
the wandering Wild Hunt.
They've lost their way, and
are wandering this land.
They're behaving differently than they should.
Their steps are erratic.
They wandered into the forest
without forming ranks,
and trampled it.
This one seems to have been
separated from its master.
What does that mean?
Look.
The same thing is happening
all over the forest.
If this returns, it may bring
order back to the Wild Hunt.
I'll leave you to deal with it.
I have my hands full taking
care of the forest.
Ask it to learn more.
Well, then.
Come in.
Elias, what is the Wild Hunt?
I'll explain inside.
Silky, tea and something
with plenty of calories.
There's a horse in the house.
They are a band of knights
that arrives with a storm
near the summer solstice every twenty
or thirty seasons, to hunt horses.
They leave death in their wake.
Death?
Old branches and weeds are culled,
allowing for new branches
and buds to emerge.
Although it's not clear if that
is the Wild Hunt's original purpose.
And this one was separated from that band?
That seems to be the case.
Now, what should we do?
How are we supposed to ask it anything?
Is there something you
want to talk to us about?
Sorry, I don't understand.
"I want to go home."
He said he wants to go home.
You can understand, Ruth?
Kind of.
Back when I was alive, I would talk
to the horses on the farm sometimes.
You're amazing, Ruth.
Were you a sheep dog or something?
Ruth, please.
Okay.
Talk.
"We were in a slumber.
We waited together with our
friends inside a single boulder.
When the time would come, we would
run together to the promised land.
Now was to be that time.
Lightning split us apart, and I
was separated from my friends.
I am their leader.
I must return.
A knight and a horse
together make up a leader.
That knight... My knight...
is nowhere to be found.
Help me find my knight.
Or else my friends will become night
thieves, with no mind but to destroy the lands.
Once I am reunited with my
knight, I will repay you."
You've gotten lost all by yourself, huh?
Lightning, eh?
Now we also know why you've been ill.
So we need to find his knight, first.
Chise, your body isn't stable yet.
Promise me you'll be careful.
Yes.
This isn't good.
I'm already getting chills again.
Let's start tomorrow.
You ought to lie down immediately.
Okay.
I don't think he can wait.
Sorry, we'll leave in the morning.
Okay.
A well-polished stone bears power.
That's what this book says, too.
I might even be able to summon some spirits.
There.
Ow...
Was that my imagination?
Wh-When did you get here?!
Who are you?
What are you doing here so late at night?
I'm lost.
I have to go back.
Y-You're lost?
Should I call the police?
Huh?
What's going on?
Is it busted?
Crap, it's Mom.
Gabriel!
Are you all right? I heard a loud noise.
Yeah, I'm fine.
Thank goodness.
Um...
What's wrong with you?
What are you doing up so late, anyway?
You've been polishing
rocks again, haven't you?
That's enough!
It's late!
We might not notice if
something happens to you.
Doar eu îl pot vedea?
Are you listening?!
D-Da!
There's another storm coming, too.
You know you tend to have your attacks
when the weather's not good.
Am înțeles, mamă.
Asta e tot?
I'll go back as soon as
I'm done cleaning up.
You can go back inside.
I'll wait until you're back in your room.
I can't leave my equipment here.
I have to clean it up.
Five minutes.
Got it.
Go wait at the door, Mom.
I have an early morning, too.
Hurry up.
I got it.
You...
You're...
You're a spirit, aren't you?!
I-I don't know.
Mom couldn't see you, though.
What kind of spirit?
The earth?
The wind?
Or an ancient god?
Oh man, I can't believe I get
to meet a real spirit.
I wonder if it's because
I polished that rock.
I-I don't know.
I don't remember anything.
Do you have amnesia?
But I have to get back.
I have to get back...
Hey, should I help you?
But in exchange, can you be my friend?
Friend?
What, you don't wanna?!
Uh, that's not it...
It's settled, then.
I have to find out what kind
of spirit you are, first.
I think it's around here somewhere...
That...
What's that rock?
Oh, this?
I picked it up today.
I'm still in the middle of polishing it.
Wanna try touching it?
Okay.
Did you remember something?
No.
Oh.
Huh? Did something just...
Are you all right?
Hey, are you all right?
I'm okay.
I'll be right there.
Are you really okay?
Yeah.
It happens all the time.
I cough when I exercise or get excited.
It's always "don't do this,
don't do that"...
Even when I'm hanging out with friends,
it's "don't run," "don't get dirty"...
But I'm the only one who can see you.
Mom wouldn't get angry at
something she can't see.
Cred că vom fi buni prieteni.
Do you always have that on you?
Just like me.
I keep this on my neck, too.
Gabriel!
Mai ai?
Fir-ar, trebuie să plec.
Poți dormi aici.
Haide să-ți căutăm casa mâine.
Îmi promit că ți-o voi găsi.
Ne vedem mâine!