Hei, lucrurile care ne-ai învățat chiar ne-au ajutat să ne mărim notele!
Cât de tare!
Kano...
Ți-am spus să-i vorbești mai cu respect domnului profesor!
Ești o elevă model, dar în realitate, eu sunt mai deșteaptă ca tine!
Ai doar cu 5 puncte mai mult ca mine...
De fapt, 6 puncte!
N-Nu m-am simțit bine de data asta.
Domnule profesor, nu uitați de recompensa mea!
Ce?
Mi-ar plăcea să merg într-un parc duminica viitoare.
The beach or otherwise. Whatever it is!
Atunci, eu ar trebui să fiu prima deoarece eu am luat mai mult la testul anterior!
Nu-i așa, domnule profesor?
Hei, hei, domnule profesor...
The garden opens early for those who book a room in the hotel!
Kano, we agreed that we
wouldn't resort to such things!
Ce vrei să spui?
Nu am nicio idee despre ce vorbești.
Kano!
Mereu faci așa!
We said no deviation!
Why not try to convince him, sis?
E-Este prea jenant!
Plictisitoareo.
Domnule profesor, cu care veți merge?
Ș-Știți, m-am descurcat mult mai bine la testul anterior...
Dar...
Amândouă?
Our underwear?
"Do you want us to show it to you?"
Hey, what are you talking about?
Are you waiting for a reward?
And why our underwear?
Teacher, why...
You really are despicable!
Hey, you...
Is this the condition that will
make you take us to the park?
Conditions? Really? You're disgusting!
You make me feel unsafe!
You disappoint me.
And to actually think I thought
you were a decent person!
To think I trusted you...
Why underwear?
Do you really want to see them?
I can't believe you were looking at us and thinking about this!
Hey, why are you laughing?
Don't tell me that ridicule excites you...
Your presence is unpleasant!
I never thought you were that disgusting!
Stop talking. Seriously!
Just being by your side makes me sick!
Take back everything you said.
You should apologize.
I want you to apologize, as
we have lost all respect for you.
In fact, leave, and do not return here.
You're right.
Let me show it to him, so
he can leave from here quickly.
What are you doing, sis?
Right, thanks to him I increased my points. So don't worry, Kano.
I'm pretty sure he wanted to see my pants, anyway.
What are you talking about?
He wants to see my mine!
Here it is!
That's what you wanted to see, right, pervert?
Mr. Pervert, here's the pants that you like!
You are worse than scum!!