Welcome back!
You are always on my mind...
You lost lamb!
How have things been since then?
Do you purify your heart
completely from obscenity?
Oh this?
I always listen to people's
admittances on this tribune.
If you feel you need to admit...
I'm always ready if you don't mind me.
Pentru Maria
This is a message, right?
Huh? Did you write your true feelings?
This could be an admission of remorse!
It is a very beautiful initiative!
Well, I'm going to read it.
"My Lord,
from the bottom of my heart, I feel great remorse...
I now, am in love...
Please believe me."
Oh, my God!
Our one and only God in the heavens...
Another lost lamb has been saved once again.
I definitely received your feelings.
Huh?
Do you want me to continue reading?
Do I read it vertically, or horizontally?
Okay.
Vertical reading, right?
Your panties... show it to me
Your panties... show it to me.
I want to see them.
This means that you are...
You did not come to confess remorse, but for the sake of my pa—
You came to see my inner shorts again.
So, what?
So, what...?
What are you trying to do?
You want to see them that much?
This is last time...
Right?
You want me to believe that?
The other day...
Some people admitted to drinking
alcohol, even though it's forbidden...
And they made a similar statement.
Even the one in my apartment...
He always says I dumped
him at the wrong time that day.
Everyone...
It's alright.
I'll trust you once again.
This is really...
The last time.
Okay, here...
Until you are satisfied!
Keep this image your eyes.
Why that look?
Disgusting.
Really...
You didn't intend for this to be the last time right?
Ești un gunoi!