YOSHIMURA
MAGAZIN DE FASHION
I've finished changing.
I'm done, too.
Me, too.
Okay, come on out.
What do you think?
You look really cute!
Does this work?
I don't really know, either.
You both look good in your outfits!
Right, Satou?
I think they're good?
Huh? Cat-ears? Horns?
You think there's some event going on?
Unfortunately, their heads
are the biggest problem here.
For now, let's just make sure
they don't stand out too much.
Hey, look!
I think something like this will look good, too!
All four of us could wear
different colors of it?
So cute!
Hime se distrează.
Now, what we need to think about is...
what we're going to do from here.
So you say,
but there was nothing at
the location of the door of light.
It's probably going to be difficult.
I suppose he was known as the Great Sage
because he could wield magic that powerful.
We could wait for someone
to come for us from our world,
or we can try and uncover
another means to return ourselves.
Either way, we currently have no leads.
It's looking hopeless.
And we need to fix that.
Aren't you worried about your nation?
Would you like to order something?
Huh?!
Needakitta's destination is chosen
by the Merchant Guild.
I'm not worried about my nation.
Oh, Romca...
still has my brother and the Elder, so...
I've been in this world for
the past ten years anyway.
How can you all be so carefree?
I haven't given up yet.
But now that it's come to this,
we have to consider the worst-case scenario.
Speaking of which,
I'm surprised you can eat
so much while complaining.
But the food here is good!
I'm a sucker for sweets!
Do we have enough money?
Don't worry. Leave it to me.
Huh?
Still, I'm so frustrated.
Even if I know there's nothing
we can do about it,
I still want to keep searching for a way home.
But how are we supposed to do that?
If there's a spot dense with magic,
then it should be easy
to connect it to our world.
We'll start by looking for such places!
Even though I got myself super motivated...
we couldn't find any leads.
You know, there are only humans in this land,
not any of the other races.
Okay!
Let's start by bringing more
cat-people to this land!
Time to make babies!
Stop it!
I'll do my best to conquer this
ultimate form of outdoors, too.
So you should keep giving it
your all, too, Saphir-sama!
Now that I think about it, Krystal,
what happened to that talk about advancing
your relationship with the Ring King
once you came back here?
W-Well, that's up to Satou...
You promised, right?!
Grk!
Okay, good night.
Good night.
It's a bit cramped with four people.
So I'm the one sleeping here.
Will those three be all right by themselves?
They're right next door. They'll be fine.
Hey...
Yes?!
About the money for today's clothes and food...
Oh, that.
In my room...
there was a letter left by Grandpa.
If you're reading this,
then things didn't work out.
I'm sorry I couldn't be by your side.
But I'm glad you're safe, Himeno.
You don't need to worry about a thing.
I've left you a home and money.
I laid all the groundwork
for you to be able to live here.
I want you to forget about Arnulus,
and live a normal life.
Grandpa...
was planning for if this happened.
So... he said I don't need to
worry about a thing.
I thought you had moved abroad.
Well, we ran into a bit of trouble.
What were you doing all summer break?
Just some things.
I thought I'd never have to go to school again.
Several days passed after that.
Nefritis began commuting to the library
to learn more about this world.
Granart apparently made friends
in the neighborhood.
Saphir has constantly been lost in thought.
Satou.
You've been sneaking out here every night, huh?
I don't mind being back,
but are the princesses okay
with things being like this?
Do you remember what Grandpa said at the end?
He wanted you to free the princesses
from the rings' fate.
We all have to find our own
happiness in this world.
Including you, Satou.
Forget about the other world,
and find happiness with me here.
Please?
Find happiness?
Satou.
Hime.
What?!
The shrine?!
Something's coming from the shrine?
A woman?!
I've waited a long time.
We meet at last,
Ring King.
Oh, am I interrupting?
I'll leave.
Huh?!
Hold on a minute! Did you just say "Ring King"?
You wouldn't happen to be...?
I'm the one protecting the Ring of Earth,
Amber Idanokan.
The Ring Princess... was in this world?!
It started in the distant past.
Once the war with the Abyss King was over,
there were only a handful
of dwarves who survived.
Eventually the dwarves would die out and
the Land of Earth, Idanokan, would perish.
The dwarves accepted their pending ruin,
so in order to protect and pass on the ring,
they created a vessel that would
withstand the test of time—
Amber.
Created?
I'm a manufactured object.
A replica of the dwarf princess.
I was transported to this world
along with the ring.
In order to prevent anyone
from stealing the ring.
In order to deliver it to the Ring King.
I've waited for centuries and centuries.
And now...
the Ring King is here.
Now,
let us be bound,
and then we'll defeat the Abyss King,
and bring peace to Arnulus.
No!
Arnulus is already done for.
The Abyss King has returned,
and we fled here!
We've lost. So...!
Satou definitely isn't going back!
Hime...
I see.
So my destiny will go unfulfilled.
Tell me if you have a change of heart.
I'm accustomed to waiting
for that which never comes.
Hey, Satou.
Will you be coming home early tomorrow?
I'm absolutely bored day after day.
I didn't do any of my summer homework,
so I'll be stuck with
make-up classes for a while.
You're our husband, so we need you to
spend more time with us!
R-Right!
Even Nefritis has been feeling bored, too.
What about the library?
Well, you see...
After going there every day,
they started recognizing me,
and that made it hard to go there anymore...
Saphir's been cooped up in
the house this whole time too.
Aren't you bored?
Hmm?
Not particularly...
By the way, Ring King.
It looked like you were out late
with Krystal last night.
What were you two doing?
Speaking of that, actually...
We were just going to
the convenience store for a bit!
Right, Satou?!
Y-Yeah.
Hime,
are you sure we should
keep quiet about Amber?
What can we do if we go back?
Can you really defeat the Abyss King
if we collect all five rings?
Can you really defeat
something like that, Satou?
We need to find happiness in this world now.
Sorry I was late leaving!
It's fine.
Whoa, let's hurry!
Amber? What are you doing?
I'm doing what I should be doing.
Huh?
It's my duty to watch over the Ring King.
And it's my destiny
for the Ring King to find me.
Yesterday, I heard the voice
of someone searching for me.
I thought you had finally come.
But...
You weren't searching for me.
You were searching for the happiness
the Maiden of the Ring of Light spoke of.
Come on, come on over, they're cheap!
They even have carrots.
Apples.
Amber?
The apples here are exquisite.
The people working this shop
are the family that have protected
the mountain shrine for generations.
Their offerings were always exquisite apples.
Wow. I never knew that.
Exquisite Apples
178 de yeni/bucată
Apples, huh?
Huh?
I can return you to Arnulus.
I was granted the power to do that.
Once we forge the contract of the rings,
I will regain my power,
and I can open a door to Arnulus.
It's finally over!
Where's the Maiden of the Ring of Light?
She finished her homework early and went home.
Said she had the housework.
Ring King, did you intend to return
to Arnulus as soon as possible?
That was my intention.
But after seeing the look on Hime's face...
She might be right that we
won't be able to do anything,
even now that we've gathered all the rings.
Don't worry.
The power of the rings is absolute.
You'll definitely be capable
of sealing the Abyss King.
That's what I've been taught.
Just like the legends claim, huh?
I won't force you.
The Ring King is the reason I was created,
so I'll watch over you until you die.
"'Til death do us part," huh?
I want to know the reason I was created.
I want to learn the value
of the time I spent waiting.
That's heavy.
I'm not heavy.
I was created to weigh
approximately the same as a person.
Huh?
That was a joke.
The Ring Princesses are all the same.
We live our lives for the Ring King
and dedicate ourselves to the world.
That's the reason we were born.
And that duty is never a light one.
Their reason for living?
Așa... este.
Would you give me your ring?
Have you changed your mind?
No, I found my answer.
I'll do what I need to do.
I see.
I'm happy.
You won't ask me why?
Your will is my will.
I need no reason.
I see.
Hime?
I'm sorry for startling you.
I was remembering Grandpa again.
But I'm okay.
The tears are just coming
on their own right now.
I'm sure... I'll get used to it eventually.
That ring...
It's the Ring of Earth.
Now I've gathered all five rings.
You accepted the ring from Amber? Why?
We're returning to Arnulus.
No! You can't!
We're all here right now because
we couldn't collect all five rings.
If we have all the rings, then we have to go.
I know that!
But we were finally able to be together again!
If I were to lose you
in that dangerous world...
Is that all the duty of the ring
meant to you, Hime?
You were my childhood friend
for ten whole years.
Those ten years were everything
I ever knew about you, Hime.
Yet the duty of the ring was so important
to you that you threw away that decade, right?
Your Grandpa asked me to free you
from the duty of the rings,
but that doesn't mean running away
from it or forgetting about it.
It means truly ending things for good.
Let's face this together, Hime.
This time, I'll be with you.
This duty is no longer yours to bear alone.
Your grandpa said it, too.
The power of the rings
is the power of our bonds.
I love you more than anyone else
in both worlds, Hime.
We'll be all right.
We won't lose.
What is this? You sound like a fool.
But I'm relieved.
I can't see you losing when you're like that.
Hime...
Then...
I should respond to your love, as well, Satou.
Hey, Satou?
Shall we fulfill our promise now?
Huh? You mean...?
Don't make me say it.
This is like a dream.
Doing this in your room.
Hime...
I feel like I'm stealing a lead.
Makes me feel kind of guilty about the others.
I told you you're the only one for me, right?
Yeah.
I finished preparing the teleportation spell.
Now we can return to Arnulus—
Ah.
Worst timing possible?
Mhmm. Mhmm!
But I can only use
the teleportation spell once.
What do we do?
We're coming! We'll use it right away!
You good with that, Hime?!
Y-Yeah!
What's the matter, Satou?!
It's not—! No, it is what you think, but...!
It seems the time has arrived.
You noticed?
You shouldn't underestimate
the insight of cat people.
Granart, um, I'm sorry.
No, I understand
what you were thinking, Krystal.
We have absolutely no idea
what's happening in our world right now.
So I figured I would respect Satou's wishes.
Though I was hoping it would go this way.
Hold on a minute.
I don't understand what's going on.
We don't really have time
to go into detail right now...
Ce? Deci acea fată este...
Amber Idanokan,
prințesa Inelului Pământului?
Putem merge acasă?!
Da.
Ne putem întoare în Arnulus.
Înțeleg.
Înțeleg!
Putem merge acasă.
Bun! Totul e pregătit!
Să mergem!
Ce? Unde mergem?
Nu te mișca.