Acesta e palatul din Idanokan?
Were we able to make it back?
It's so dark, I can hardly see.
Amber?
There are no monsters nearby.
There's nothing living, either.
Are you feeling sad?
Be careful.
I smell blood.
Huh?
I'm blinded!
Is this better?
Yeah.
This armor... belongs to imperial soldiers.
They must have fought the monsters here.
They couldn't even bury their dead?
Just how intense was the fighting?
It's possible this world is already...
What's wrong?
Go!
The Imperial Army!
There are some still engaged in combat?!
Satou, over there!
Satou?
Yeah.
I know.
The Abyss King.
If you go down through here, you'll come out
on the flank of the monster horde.
You'll be able to catch
the Abyss King by surprise.
Yeah.
Satou.
Don't worry.
We have all the rings.
I have everyone's power.
This is sooner than we expected,
but this is what we returned home for.
Please, Ring King.
I'm betting everything on you.
I'm sure you'll be fine, Satou-sama.
Yeah.
We're counting on you, Ring King.
Satou.
I'll be waiting, okay?
All right.
I'll be going.
You're here,
Inheritor of the Rings?
You've done well to make it this far.
Boy, new King,
I'll unite your power.
Wow...
This time, hold nothing back.
He did it!
No.
No way...
How?!
The Rings are the manifestation
of the world's order.
The Abyss is supposed to perish,
and the world is supposed to be saved...
Does this mean... I'm not good enough?!
Satou!
Inheritor of the Rings.
So, you are another ignorant puppet?
Oh, no!
No, this can't be!
What about our duty?!
What happened to the legends?!
I'm going!
We can't afford to lose Satou here!
Don't worry.
I won't let him die.
So, it really is possible to be unable
to move a single finger...
Return to the Abyss.
Women of the Rings...
Everyone? Why are you here?
You think we'd just abandon you?!
Granart!
Damn it! Let me go!
Tsk! There are too many.
Satou!
Satou-sama!
Everyone...
I'm sorry.
Satou!
Hime!
Good morning, Satou.
Hime...
Good morning.
Do you promise to love and to cherish
one another, in sickness and in health?
I do.
Grandpa?
You're awake, Satou-kun?
Oh... I guess I died?
What are you saying?
We haven't died yet.
What's this?
Alabaster-dono saved us.
That's the Great Sage for you.
What are you saying?
I'm not that great.
Creating an opening and getting
you all away from the Abyss King
was the best I could manage.
We really do need the
Ring King's power, after all.
Oh, yeah! If you're safe,
then that means Marse-san is...!
Prince Marse is safe, too, yes.
It's all thanks to this one.
You're...
It's been a while, Ring King.
I'm from Wind's royal family of Romca,
Smaragdi Romca.
Thanks to Smaragdi,
we managed to escape from
the Abyss Monsters that surrounded us.
I've been watching over
Alabaster-sama for a while.
However, once he was faced with danger...
I couldn't sit still.
Because of that,
I was able to aid Alabaster-sama.
Alabaster-sama gave my life
such wonderful meaning.
To me, he truly is my one...
The monsters have withdrawn.
I believe the Abyss King
has suffered a serious wound, too.
I guess I at least had some effect.
What are you saying?
It was wonderfully effective.
We couldn't even get
a single arrow to pierce him.
You've done well, Satou-kun.
Great Sage, what is the overall situation like?
Shortly after you left,
the Abyss King's forces
commenced their invasion,
and the Imperial Army halted their advance
at the Great Mountain Wall.
I assisted, but...
there was little we could do
other than run away.
And Maasa?!
What happened to Maasa?!
Each nation is fighting in different locations.
Maasa is safe.
Prince Marse is there, as well.
Though the number of monsters
just keeps going up, not down.
The situation is steadily worsening.
I'm really glad we didn't give up hope.
I'm glad you all made it back!
Alabaster-sama, it's almost dawn.
The Ring King has returned.
All the princesses are together, too.
The morning sun is full of hope.
The Ring King has returned!
All five princesses are with him!
I was told I couldn't go outside
because there's lots of monsters.
But it'll be okay now that
you're back, right, Ring King?
Yeah, leave it to me.
I'll save this world!
Now, we need to talk about what's to come.
Before that, I'd like to hear your excuse.
I thought we were supposed
to be able to defeat the Abyss King
once the Rings were collected?
STARE...
Grandpa, be honest with me.
Was my power not enough?
I have one idea as to why you
weren't able to defeat the Abyss King.
There was not one mention of
the Black Rings that the Abyss King wore.
Black Rings?
They looked just like this, only black.
That's not in my records.
The dwarves didn't know about that, either.
Still, even in multiple sources,
it's certain that the Ring King
sealed away the Abyss King.
However, we don't know how much
power was required to do so.
Then what are you saying we should do?
There's only one thing we can do.
We have to draw out even more of
the Rings' power before our next battle!
Which means Satou-kun needs to strengthen his
bonds with the Ring Princesses even further.
Even stronger bonds... Does that mean...?
Baby making!
Well, that's one option.
It is?!
Satou-kun!
Marse-san!
What are you doing here?!
I received word that you
had returned, and came at once.
I wanted to see you as soon as possible.
Now, moving on to the main topic.
It's said that the Ring Princesses stood
alongside the Ring King in battle long ago.
In order to draw out the Rings' power,
both the will to fight alongside him
and the strength to carry out
that will may be required.
Strength, huh?
Saphir, Amber, and I may be fine there...
But we're not very helpful.
So, on that note,
we'll have everyone acquire the strength
that befits a wife of the Ring King!
That's right, this training...
is wife training!
This will be your room, Ring King.
The Princesses are already waiting for you.
Satou, once again, you made up your mind
to fight to save this world for our sakes.
So I believe we should
steel our resolve, as well.
Ring King, replenish your energy
as much as you need.
Now, choose the woman you'd like!
Of course, you're welcome
to choose all of us at once!
Huh?
What's the matter?
Isn't a harem every man's dream?!
Look at what you're doing.
You're troubling the Ring King.
This is the problem with beastmen
who can't read the mood.
What?!
SNAP
What did you say?!
That's big talk from the shorty
who fell behind her little sister!
Huh?! Saphira has nothing to do with this!
What? Did I hit the mark?
You're raising your voice so much.
I am not!
Bridal training, huh?
You sound happy.
Huh? Not particularly.
You've been working
so hard for us this whole time,
so it's my turn to work hard, too.
Is that...?
Yeah.
In my real family, I had a father,
a mother, and a little sister.
My little sister remained in this world,
so I haven't seen her in ten years now.
My parents are here.
Father, Mother, I'm home.
It happened when I was little.
So I only vaguely remember
what they looked like,
but they both risked their lives to protect me.
This man...
is my husband.
Thank you, Satou.
I was able to return here, thanks to you.
Krystal.
Grandpa?! How long have you been there?!
Since, "Father, Mother, I'm home."
That's basically the whole time!
I don't think it's anything
to be embarrassed about.
I think it was a lovely story.
By the way, about your magic training.
Yeah, I'll do my best!
I'm counting on you!
No, it won't be me.
I've summoned a teacher
more appropriate for you, Krystal.
I wanted to let you know,
since they should be arriving soon.
What?!
Hmm, so you're...
You're not too bad.
I'm Morion Ravri Nokanatika.
Mă bucur să te văd,
surioară.
Și...
Cumnate.
Cumnat?
Morion Ravri Nokanatika?
Tu ești sora mai mică a lui Hime?!