Uau, asta chiar se simte ca o aventură!
Sau, cel puțin, asta am crezut la început,
dar cât de departe este?!
Umblăm prin acești
munți de trei zile deja!
Oh, aproape am ajuns.
Vorbești serios?
Dar nu te relaxa prea mult.
Dacă aluneci, vei sfârși ca el.
Uau! Ce oase mari!
Mărețule Înțelept, ai idee ce sunt?
Ei bine, par a fi monștri
din era Regelui Abisului.
Doar s-a dus o mare bătălie aici,
pe Marele Zid Muntos, Kaogamika.
Existau monștrii așa
de mari? Incredibil.
Cum are femeia asta
atât de multă energie?
Apreciez că ai mers în recunoaștere.
Deci? Cum se arată drumul?
Nicio urmă de oameni sau monștri.
Păi, chiar dacă am fi atacați de un monstru,
l-am putea doborî cu
forma de dragon a lui Saphir.
Sincer, e destul de epuizantă.
Picioarele mele sunt mereu terminate după ce am folosit atât de multă putere magică.
Voi înțelegeți, nu-i așa?
S-Serios?
Pare dificil să folosești magie.
Vrei să-mi spui că fetele astea...
Ea are mușchi în loc de creier!
Ea e o mare incompetentă!
Și ea e doar o prințesă anti-socială?!
Cred că vreau să merg acasă acum.
Gata, gata.
Am găsit un loc puțin mai în
față unde ne putem odihni.
Cred că ne vom opri acolo pentru astăzi.
Haideți, țineți pasul, copilași de oraș!
Ne vom putea odihni curând!
Bine.
Hei, bunicul lui Hime,
tu ești Marele Înțelept, nu-i așa?
Speram să-mi spui
dacă chiar are vreun
rost să adunăm inelele?
Ce e cu întrebarea asta?
Oamenii Imperiului
plănuiesc să lupte cu Regele Abisului fără a se baza pe puterea inelelor, nu?
Am auzit și că au reușit să înfrângă majoritatea monștrilor care au atacat Maasa.
Doar că...
nu mă așteptam să fie așa.
„Eroul care va salva lumea.”
„Legendarul Rege al Inelelor care îl va învinge pe Regele Abisului.”
Asta au spus oamenii despre mine,
dar nu pare să existe persoane care așteaptă asta cu adevărat din partea mea.
Ei bine, lumea e un loc vast...
Fiecare persoană își trăiește viața în funcție de propriile idei.
Nu se vor agăța cu toții de aceeași speranța.
E normal ca unii să creadă că,
dacă putem învinge monștrii
cu puterea oamenilor,
atunci l-am putea învinge
și pe Regele Abisului la fel.
Înțeleg.
Lumea are mult mai puțin încredere în aceste inele decât mă așteptam.
Dar am învățat multe lucruri
în viața mea de pribeag.
Am auzit și multe legende fragmentate, dar înfiorătoare, despre Regele Abisului.
Am văzut și cicatricile adânci rămase încă din era miturilor.
Puterea Regelui Abisului e de neimaginat.
We've already seen him controlling monsters
and his knights with terrifying power
that we can't begin to comprehend
with our understanding of magic.
Yet even that power only amounts to
the scant portion leaking out from his seal.
I find it very hard to imagine he can be
dealt with using the power of mankind alone.
Every record in this world
leads me to that same conclusion.
Well, if the Abyss King's resurrection
goes according to legend,
then the resurrection of the
Ring King is destined, as well.
You've already gathered
four of the rings, Satou-kun,
so maybe the last one
will surprise us and come to us.
Hmm...
Now, it's time for the shift change,
so get some sleep already.
Yeah.
Some Great Sage I am.
I'm useless.
POVESTEA INELELOR DE CĂSĂTORIE
Totul a început când mâinile noastre s-au atins
Destinul ne-a fost hotârât încă de la naștere
Privirea ta, din acea zi, care mi-a străpuns inima
Pasiunea și sentimentele mele transced orice cuvinte
Ochii tăi plini cu determinare
Și credința ta care se agață de adevăr,
Chiar și atunci când singurătatea te cuprinde,
Strălucirea lor continuă să dăinuie
Vreau să apăr orice viitor ai alege
Nu te voi lăsa să mergi de unul singur
Îmi încrunt privirea ca să pot înfrunta vânturile puternice
Voi lumina chiar și abisul întunecat
Promițând să merg oriunde ne vor duce drumurile noastre împletite
Logodnă, jur pe ochii tăi
This is the Land of Earth, Idanokan.
The lost capital of the dwarves.
It's awfully devastated.
They drove off countless attacks
from the Abyss King,
but their final battle is said
to have been especially fierce.
And then the dwarves all vanished,
without rebuilding their ruined city.
Seems like there really is no one here.
It's too quiet, and I don't like it.
Really? I love it.
It's so wonderful that no one is here.
I want to live here.
Ce?
If only it were warmer.
I'll wait here.
You all can search for the Ring of Earth.
What, are you already
worn out, Princess Saphir?
I'm not a fan of wandering about aimlessly.
This city is right next to
the domain of the Abyss.
You never know what may happen.
Then you can just stay and guard me.
It's quite an honor.
Live up to it.
My goodness, you're hopeless.
I'll carry you, then.
Come on, climb on.
Ce?
I don't need that!
I can walk on my own!
There's no need to refrain, you bashful girl.
I'm not refraining from anything!
That so, that so?
What's the matter?
It felt like someone was there.
Maybe it's just the quiet of the ruins
making you feel that way?
I guess...
This room... is still relatively nice.
That looks like a throne.
This was probably the palace.
This is...!
Grandpa!
Th-There's a corpse!
Calm down, Satou-kun.
That's not the remains of a dwarf.
It's a Sorcerer's Unit.
A relic mentioned in myths.
Sorcerer's Unit?
Some kind of robot?
Worry not.
It can't function without magic power.
It's just a puppet.
Dwarven civilization was centered
around sorcerous machines,
devices that ran on magic power.
I've heard that they dug
into the earth, refined metals,
and devoted everything
to honing their mastery of smithing.
So these are the proof that they lived,
the crystallization of their technology.
In the battles of myth, the dwarves
used their sorcerous machines as weapons.
The sorcerous vehicles of Needakitta are
some of their few relics still in operation.
I did hear that our ancestors received those
from the earth people long, long ago.
I have no idea how those things work!
So, even though they left
all kinds of things behind,
no one knows what happened
to the dwarves themselves?
I suppose that just shows
how chaotic that era was.
Looks like there aren't any clues about
the ring, even after coming all this way.
I guess that only leaves the underground roads.
Underground?
We're going even further in?
Vanished...
We vanished...
All of the earth people...
Hey! Grandpa, what's going on here?!
There were still ones
that could move left here?!
That's impossible!
No, wait—
A knight of the Abyss King?!
I can't believe he can control
machines, as well!
I guess anything goes for him!
Why...
We fought together...
So why were we the only ones who disappeared?
Why were we the only ones...
who had to perish?!
What is it saying?
Wind, Fire, Water, Light...
Perish with us.
Join our lord...
Join us in the same place...
Be swallowed by the Abyss...
Oh, no!
It trapped Satou-kun behind that wall!
What?
Do not interfere, outsider.
You have no ties to this world.
You should have no reason to fight.
No, I do.
You're right that I'm not a part of this world.
However,
there are people living
peaceful lives in this world.
People who Hime loves.
Is that worth risking your life over?
Yeah.
I want to protect Hime's world.
I have to protect it!
Satou!
Thank you, Hime!
You fool...
You're just being used by this world!
Do you think the dwarves hate us?
Who knows?
Those were words tainted with
the darkness of the Abyss King.
The time is ripe.
The time of rebirth...
The time of the ancient king's resurrection!
What?
The black ring disappeared?
The black rings...
are disappearing?
So, it's finally started?
What is happening?!
Look out! They're coming!
Abyssal monsters?!
It's too dangerous to fight without
understanding what's happening.
Let's retreat outside for now!
There are so many!
Where are they all springing up from?!
They must have been summoned by someone.
There are too many of them!
In that case...
Sensei! Please do it!
Huh? Me?!
Do that thing and become a dragon.
No, I can't...
I can't use great power like that in
this land with so little water magic.
For real?!
Satou-kun!
We fight back!
Satou! Behind you!
Allow me to at least back you up.
Thanks.
Hey, Grandpa, what's going on?
There's no end to them.
We can't defeat them all? No other choice...
Run! This way!
We'll buy some distance while we can!
Hmph!
Are you okay?
I'm fine. This is nothing.
I just need a little rest.
This is bad.
He's exerted himself too much.
At this rate...
I didn't want... to believe it.
I thought we still had time.
No, I hoped that was true.
I was wrong.
What is this...?
The Abyss King... has been fully resurrected!
That mass of monsters...
You can't harness the true power
of the Ring King without all five rings.
You won't stand a chance
of winning if you fight.
Would we gather the five rings first,
or would the Abyss King return first?
It was a gamble we lost.
Both me and this world.
Satou-kun?!
Anyway...
we need to run for now,
and search for the Ring of Earth.
There's still a chance it's not too late!
He won't let us escape that easily now.
No, there's nowhere to run to in this world.
The Abyss King will find us for certain.
No way! Then what are we supposed to do?
Worry not.
I won't let us go down so easily!
Grandpa, what are you doing?
I'm opening the gate!
We can't let the Rings fall into
the Abyss King's hands, no matter what!
Grandpa!
Stay back!
Please, leave this to me.
Once the gate closes, even the Abyss
King won't be able to follow you.
Though, to do that, I'll have to stay
behind and close the gate quickly.
If we leave it open,
our whole plan will be ruined.
Satou-kun, you were my hope.
I'm sorry things have turned out this way,
but please free the Princesses
from the Rings' fate.
Please take care of Himeno.
No!
Grandpa!
Are you sure about staying here, Marse-dono?
I've made my decision to fight
for this world until the end.
Sorry for making you join me in this.
No, fighting alongside
the Great Sage is an honor.
Nu am reușit să-ți spun de ce vreau să fiu cu tine,
dar nu am putut găsi niciun motiv pentru care să plec
Cuvintele deșarte, pe care le-am înghițit atunci în sec,
încă le port cu mine, neputând să ți le spun
Chiar și așa, lacrimile pe care le-am vărsat
vor fi uitate, într-o bună zi, nu-i așa?
Crezând că știu totul, și, de fapt, neștiind nimic
în sufletul meu
Plină mereu de răni,
mă întreb dacă mai știu cum să zâmbesc
Oare cum ar trebui să-ți spun
că vreau să-ți fiu mereu alături?
Tremurând cu fiecare pas pe care-l fac,
lumina devine din ce în ce mai mare
Chiar dacă nu suntem unul lângă celălalt, nu uita,
Lacrimile noastre mereu se vor potrivi
Oh, yeah.
That's right.
It has to be even harder on the others.
Grandpa...
Have we really come home?
Th-This is too tight.
Figures it wouldn't fit.
What is this thing called?
It's a brassiere.
Want to try wearing one?
Can I?
It's a bit tight...
It really is strange.
It makes me feel a little tense and determined!
What's the point of wearing
something so flashy under clothing?
Underwear isn't actually meant to be shown off.
But you're always
showing off yours, aren't you?
Letting a little peak show is actually fine.
Don't go asking her such a crude question.
Oh, right! She's seducing our man!
Ce?!
Hime?
Ce?
Un sutien?
Hey, hurry up and produce one that fits me.
I don't have any!
Haina asta are un miros ciudat.
Aia e a bunicului!
Krystal! Ce înseamnă „livrare gratuită”?!
Satou...
'N-Neața.