What...
What is this...?
Live, live on, with all your might
Follow the light to the future
Betrayed and left behind in this lonely world
Fearing a tomorrow I've lost sight of
I search for the place I belong
My heart screams out, "I want to be needed"
I want to puzzle out these entwined identities, but can I trust them?
Live, live on, with all your might
Follow the light to the future
Even if you lose everything
Stay connected to hope
I don't know why I'm here
But that's all right with me right now
I have to overcome and press on
So I can smile with you again
A Good Warrior Isn't Always A Good Boss
That's just the problem!
My father always assumes everyone is on his level!
Yeah, I totally get that,
and why this has got you so angry, Julietta.
Let's calm down a bit and have some tea.
It's from Raudadola.
My apologies.
So to summarize what
you've heard from General Edvard...
"Oh, no, the soldiers I put through
a hellish training regimen..."
"...were defeated by a mere arch chimera!"
What a pathetic lot! Weaklings, all of you!
The responsibility for this failure lies
in the man who trained them: myself alone!
And the only way to atone for it is by taking my own life!
Talk about a Grade-A moron.
Not like dying would...
Lord Leo?
Oh, sorry.
It's not like dying would make his troops any stronger,
nor would it solve the problem.
Yes, and thankfully, my father has abandoned
the notion of suicide for now...
Arch chimeras are among the strongest chimeras.
The men we hired after
the last battle are mere foot soldiers.
They had little hope of defeating it with
their lack of experience and training.
Right.
I don't know if this is just Edvard,
but is there a reason he made his newbies fight that?
My father expects everyone to be just as strong as he is.
Oh...
You understand, yes?
When my father sees his new soldiers
are unable to defeat an arch chimera,
he thinks his soldiers simply aren't trying hard enough.
Not trying hard enough...
That's an obnoxious phrase.
And most of the time, it's being
said by the skilled or powerful.
They say they have their position
by virtue of their own efforts,
but that's hardly ever the case.
A powerful fighter might've been born
with a more muscular frame.
An intelligent planner might've been put
through a good school from an early age.
They discount all the external factors
that played a part in their success.
Why doesn't my father understand?
His strength is a boon, yes,
but sadly, it's hard for people to realize
how unique and gifted they are.
Because it came naturally to them,
they expect it to come naturally to everyone else.
That's how they delude themselves.
You're right.
It's easy for guys like him to assume
everyone's on his level.
The issue we're seeing here is that good warriors do
not always make good teachers.
When people want to train others
to be strong like them, what do they do?
They ask themselves what they did to get where they are,
then have their trainees do just that.
If it's too tough for them, a good trainer will make
it easier or change things up,
but the skilled and powerful can't do that.
They think the reason their trainees fail is
because they're not trying hard enough.
You're fired!
And Edvard's a real hard worker.
That might be part of why he assumes it's effort.
Yes, and after he fought you, Lord Leo...
Ah, forgive me, should I call you Lord Onyx?
It's fine, no one's here. Go on.
After he fought you, Lord Leo,
he cursed his lack of training...
...and redoubled his daily efforts.
This probably sounds obvious,
but you really respect him, don't you?
I do.
I've always wanted to be just like him,
ever since I was little.
Sadly...
His stoic, stubborn nature is working against him now,
and his hellish training is making his troops pass out
from exhaustion right on the spot.
I'm surprised they're not just running away screaming.
His soldiers are just as serious about the cause as he is...
So they push themselves to
their limits just to follow his orders.
Lord Leo, what should I do?
Leave it to me.
I'll handle it.
Lord Leo!
He's a living weapon created
to defeat demons? Is that true?
I can't say, but that's what he told me.
At the very least, I know he lied when
he said he joined us to destroy humanity.
Then why did he join us?
If he wanted to destroy the demon army,
then he needn't take such a roundabout method...
He told me he's going to help us,
though I don't know why.
It's simple!
He sees we're in trouble and wants to help!
I don't think that's why...
He wants to help 'cause he's a good person! I can tell!
Talk about naïve.
What?! But he is!
I will admit, he HAS helped every single one of us here.
And of course, if he does anything suspicious,
we'll report him to Queen Echidna.
For now, shall we put our trust in him
and keep a close eye on his actions?
I like that!
I suppose.
I said I'd handle it... But how?
Talking it out with him won't have much of an effect.
There's got to be a more direct method...
You know, there was that thing in Lily's report...
It's big, it's white, and it's super strong!
That's it!
Lord Onyx, are you here?
The Demon Queen is summoning you.
H... He quit?!
Is that true, Your Highness?
Yes, General Edvard told me himself.
He declared he was no longer fit
to lead troops as a general.
So, then, he's left the army?
Actually, no.
He's apparently returned to being a common foot soldier
to train with his underlings.
Come, my superiors! Let us hunt and defeat
powerful beasts to train ourselves!
Forward!
That hasn't solved anything!
That's only made the problem WORSE!
I told him to rethink his decision,
but he refuses to back down on this...
What do you think of this? Have you any--
Oh, no, my apologies!
I mustn't rely on you so, it's unbecoming of me!
I will find a solution myself!
Forgive me, Your Highness,
but might I make a proposal?
Would you allow me to handle this situation
involving General Edvard?
I-I couldn't...
I will see this resolved.
Very well. I leave it in your hands.
At once! I have some preparations to make,
so I will take my leave.
One more thing, Onyx.
When this situation is resolved,
there's something I must discuss with you.
Of course, Your Highness.
Here it is, Leo!
This is what Leo was telling me about...
Yes. An artifact from the Machine Age,
far more powerful than an S-rank chimera.
A machine golem!
A machine golem...
And this is one from the late end of
the Machine Age, codename Phantom Nine.
They were built specifically
to combat high-ranking demons.
And we're going to make use of it...
I've gathered you here not for a training exercise,
but to make an announcement.
As of today,
I am stepping down from my position
as General and rejoining as a foot soldier.
Julietta will be assuming the role of General henceforth.
Oh, Edvard, my sweet, summer child!
This harsh world of ours would
never let you quit that easily.
I'll teach you that lesson here and now.
What is that?
Intruding upon our encampment
and brandishing your weapons at us?
What are you standing around for?!
Launch a counterattack!
I am still your general for today! Obey my orders!
Yes, sir!
Don't get too close, now.
You guys shouldn't be fighting this thing.
What're you doing?! Retreating from the enemy?
And you call yourselves soldiers?!
I-I'm sorry, sir, but our weapons can't do anything!
If you can't strike it, then draw its attention, or confuse it!
If you've time to complain, you've time to fight!
What's wrong? It stopped.
Oh no, did all that time underground
break its components?
If it doesn't work, then my plans'll be for nothing!
Crap, is that...
Reflection Ray!
Th-that was close!
What kind of firepower is this thing packing?!
It melted its own armor...
The damn thing's safety restrictions are all out of whack!
But I'm a Hero, and I'm going
to make sure no one gets hurt!
What IS that?
We must retreat! It's too powerful!
We can't defeat that! We'll be DEAD!
It's way more powerful than I expected.
What do I do?
I brought this out for Edvard to fight,
but should I take care of it instead?
The big doll wants to play, does it?
I'll smash it to pieces!
Stop, you moron! Get down!
What in the...
That's an ancient laser weapon!
It'll sear right through your dragon scales!
Lord Leo?!
Listen up, Edvard! I'm going to help you!
Follow my orders if you want to live!
When its eyes glow, three seconds later,
it'll shoot off a laser beam!
Focus your defensive spells on your scales and deflect it!
What?! That's a lot to take in all at--
What did I just tell you?!
It just deployed its left vibroblade!
Whatever you do, don't take a direct hit from that thing!
The blade itself is weak,
so hit it from the side to destroy it!
Vibro-what?! I don't understand!
How do you not understand?!
It's in a machine golem's basic kit!
I have never faced such a foe!
This may be common knowledge to you,
Lord Leo, but not to me!
The sword will kill you, so hit it from the side!
Understood!
Good!
"Common knowledge to you, but not to me!"
That's what I wanted to hear!
Now!
Father, let me join you!
Julietta!
Don't get in the way! Leave this to Lord Leo and I,
lest you do yourself harm!
Listen to me, Father!
Don't be stubborn, girl! This is my fight!
Fall back before you get hurt!
Its weak point is the right side of its torso!
What?!
According to our documents, that's where its, uh...
Wi... Wires? Are connected to the main g-generator?
Strike it there!
Do it, Edvard!
Julietta's right, the right torso is where it's vulnerable!
Cut it down!
Father! Are you all right?!
I am. I couldn't have done it without your help.
Julietta, Lord Leo, you have my deepest thanks.
Well done. He's done a good job so far!
All that's left is to tie things up...
Wait, did it just...
It moved!
I knew it! It called for backup!
Dammit, one was tough enough, but now three?!
It's no use. I'm going to have to fight them.
My plan was going so well, too.
But I've got no choice. I'm going to have to...
Fret not.
Shutina, prepare a defensive barrier
to protect the miners.
Yes, Your Highness!
Mernes, evacuate the civilians.
Got it!
Lily, make sure there aren't any
other machine golems active in the area.
I'm on it!
Why are they here?
I see. Onyx had a plan.
Yep! I told you he was good!
Your Highness, where are you going?
He said he'd handle it,
but when the unexpected occurs,
even the best and brightest need help.
And Edvard is one of my dear underlings.
He's helped me time and time again.
If I didn't help him in his hour of need...
What Demon Queen would I be?!
Your Highness...
You see this, yes, Onyx?
We will handle things here.
You finish things off where you are!
Echidna...
Right, I'm on it!
Stand down, you dolls of wood and metal.
Do you know who I am?
I stand above all demonkind as their supreme ruler:
Demon Queen Echidna!
Now, burn in the pits of purgatory!
Inferno!
Thank you again, Lord Leo.
Wow, I didn't know the Dragon General
was such a joke in combat!
Lord Leo?
Really, how does a Great General NOT
know about laser weapons or vibroblades?
Everyone knows about those! Literally everyone!
Literally everyone?! You can't be serious!
Nope, I'm serious! It's the basics of the basics!
You must not be working hard enough!
How can you call yourself the Dragon General
when you can't take out a machine golem?
Isn't that the exact thing you told your troops
before?
How?! How can an entire battalion
be bested by one chimera?!
It's impossible, sir! We've never fought one before!
Insolent fool!
When I was your age, I trained by fighting
deathmatches with these creatures daily!
Stop making excuses for your lack of effort!
But sir...
The backs of their legs are weak!
Slice the heels to immobilize, then smash the head!
Everyone knows that!
None of you are trying hard enough!
You're better off quitting, that's for sure!
Go back home and pick up fishing, why don'tcha!
Lord Leo?
I would request that you stop insulting my father.
Julietta...
You musn't assume that your knowledge
is common knowledge for everyone.
You have years of experience and familiarity,
but we have never fought a machine golem.
Oh, c'mon. You think you can laze around just
'cause you've never fought one before?
You're just making excuses for your lack of effort!
I am not! Anyone would have trouble
with a task they've never done before!
How would you know how to handle
a foe you've never encountered?!
You mustn't assume others can do what you can.
You should train someone starting from the basics,
then slowly work your way up.
Is that not important when
you're preparing someone for battle?
I see. Onyx had a plan.
G-General, sir, forgive us, but...
Oh, men... I'm so terribly sorry!
I should not have said you weren't trying hard enough!
Truly, the one who needed to put
in more effort was me and me alone!
I deeply apologize!
Don't hang your head like that, sir.
You're far more inspiring with your head held high.
He's right! We all joined the army because
we admired your strength, sir!
So, sir... Please, don't quit on us!
We'll work even harder, so please, keep training us!
I'm touched...
Very well! I have a long way to go,
but I hope you'll stand by me!
Yes, sir!
A good warrior isn't always a good boss.
But when they've learned how to teach others,
a good warrior can be a truly great boss.
I couldn't have done this without the others.
My, you can still move after that attack?
Then how about this!
Explode!
And a Fireball!
And a Plasma Cannon!
And a Hellfire!
And a Meteor Swarm!
Queen Echidna, that's enough, that's enough!
She needs to blow off steam. Let her be.
Y'know, you've changed lately, Mernes!
Shush.
Our hearts are always so frail and fragile
But we still face forward and continue down our long road
If we don't know something now, we can go learn about it
We might not know what's at the end of our long, continuing journey
Don't try to do everything yourself, lean on us sometimes
Sharing your weaknesses is strength in itself
There's still a long way to go,
so make sure you won't regret anything
Dash on! The reason's simple
Let loose! Make your dreams reality
The future you're heading towards is one you shape yourself
It's okay to be scared of change, you can go little by little
I want to protect the things I cherish
(I'm so glad we found each other)
So I hope you hear how thankful I am for you
Next Time:
Tokyo, 2060 A.D.