Ikite ikite ikitsukuse
Hikari o mirai e
Uragirareta kodoku na sekai ni torinokosare
Miushinatta ashita o osorete ima mo
Ibasho o sagasu
Hitsuyou to saretai kokoro no sakebi
Karamiau IDENTITY tashikametainda shinjite iikana
Ikite ikite ikitsukuse
Hikari o mirai e
Tatoe subete ushinattemo
Kibou o tsunaide
Boku ga koko ni iru imi
Ima wa wakaranakute mo ii
Kimi to waraiaeru you ni
Jibun de tachikitte susumudake
It's me, Shutina.
Come in.
Today's meeting will proceed as planned.
I see.
Queen Echidna is expected to promote you
to a leadership role alongside us.
It's finally happening.
I've one matter to discuss before the meeting.
Mernes told us about you.
Did you really lie about your reasons for joining us?
I'll discuss that today, as well as my reasons.
Trust me. I won't betray you.
All right.
Do not reveal your identity until I say so.
If we don't tread carefully with the reveal,
Queen Echidna may not forgive the subterfuge.
We don't want that.
I'll signal you when the time is right. Understood?
Understood.
What's that?
Oh, I felt like enjoying a book.
"Eibrad, the Joiner of Hands"!
Queen Echidna often read that tome.
Leo.
Do you think we will be able to possess
the Philosopher's Stone?
It won't be easy, but we'll make it work.
With my help.
When the preparations are complete,
I will send a messenger.
Got it.
Until then.
Sheesh... This doesn't look like him at all.
Whoa, hold it, why're you puttin' it like that?!
Don't make us out to be the bad guys, here!
We didn't come here to attack humanity!
I can't speak for the others,
but us imps wanted to be professional about it.
You guys might not know,
but the Demon World's full of conflict and war,
and we are sick of it.
Why did you come, then?
The Demon King's experiments accidentally
opened a Great Spirit Portal.
That's the hole that connects your world to ours.
The way was open, so we decided to come take a look.
Heard it was nicer than the Demon World, anyway.
Immigration, then?
Basically. Plus, we were curious.
Curious?
It ain't easy getting to the Human World
from the Demon World.
You need lots of catalysts and a lot of mana.
Get those together and you can hold
a portal open long enough.
Very few of us had ever seen the human world
with the naked eye before all this.
Wouldn't you wanna see it for yourself?
Good, they're not gonna try to kill me
while they're listening to me talk!
Who cares what I talk about as long as
I can keep them occupied!
What happened next?
This world was pretty damn interesting.
But the best part was all the peace!
Which was ended by your arrival.
Hey, I wanted to get along with you guys, remember?
I'm through with the Demon World
and its endless fighting!
The leaders of the Demon World
do not resolve disputes?
Belial's a shit king! He resolves everything with violence!
Belial?
He's the ruler of the Demon World.
His Majesty, King Belial.
That name is present in human records as well.
One of our royals or nobles probably popped over
to your world back in the day.
That's probably the reason
Belial's name is in your books.
I see.
Shit, they sound totally bored!
I gotta keep this conversation going!
And their sword's so loud! It's scary as shit!
I'm not boring you, am I?
No, your explanation was very informative. Thank you.
Dammit! I have no idea what they're thinking!
I gotta do something, or I'm dead meat!
Please stand.
H-hold on! I'm not done talking!
Let's walk.
W-walk where?!
Why did Belial open the Great Spirit Portal?
Huh? Oh.
We weren't even thinking about invasion at first.
All the Demon World's wars are fought over
the limited resources it has to offer.
Then Belial opened a portal to
an uninhabited island in the human world,
and we started talking about moving over.
Yet the portal was opened in the center of Tokyo.
Yeah, that surprised me, too!
And thanks to those instinct-driven types
like ogres and ghouls attacking humans,
we had a war on our hands almost immediately.
That's why we freaked out and tried to leave!
Huh?!
Whoa, what?! Why's it closing up?!
It sucks.
The only beings capable of closing up the Great Spirit
Portal were high-tier demons or King Belial himself.
Their plan from the start was
to leave us to die in the human world.
Is there a possibility that Belial and these high-tier
demons will try to colonize our world?
Oh, totally. Don't take this personally,
but you humans are way weaker than us.
There were probably some spies
who crossed over with us
and snuck back to the Demon World before the portal
closed up.
I bet they're telling Belial all
about you guys right about now.
"Now's the time to assemble your forces
and take the human world for your own!"
I mean, you've gotta know how much
more power we've got over you guys.
Engaging a single devil requires
a minimum of a three-man cell.
Man, it feels weird bein' called a devil...
Devils are the ruling class of the Demon World.
Never mind.
They're way more powerful than the rest of us,
and boy do they use it to their advantage.
High-tier demons look down on us lower-tier demons
like we're the gum on their shoe.
You get why we were so eager to get over here, yeah?
I cannot empathize, but I can understand.
Thanks, man.
You are a man, right?
I have no gender, but I was designed
to appear masculine.
You were DESIGNED...?
Welp, guess all I can do now
is just wait till someone kills me.
"Oh, go to the Human World!
The sun's warm and bright, and it's lush and green!"
Yeah, right! Everywhere I go it's one giant grey
tombstone after another!
Those high-tier devils can kiss my ass!
They should be the ones getting killed!
I'm done! Just finish me off already!
Thank you for the valuable information.
You're not gonna kill me?!
You provided me with valuable information,
and I am escorting you to
the Containment Squadron rendezvous point.
Yes?
Nothing. Just thinking about how different
you are from the other humans.
Come to think of it, he was acting weird from the start...
A monster that's neither human nor demon...
What the hell is he?
You appear to be a rather understanding devil.
I will see to it that command finds you
a residence in the Shinjuku Protection Ward.
I'd rather get back to the Demon World if I can.
We have nearly reached
the Containment Squadron rendezvous point.
Oh. All right.
Better than getting killed, I guess...
Sheesh, the silence is way more nerve-wracking!
It's fine, just stay quiet. You're going to live.
Don't mess that up by saying something!
Am I sure about that, though?
Who knows if this monster will decide to kill me
instead?!
Ugh, this silence is killing me!
I gotta take my mind off all that!
Oh, right! Your name! What's your name?
You have a name, don't you?
You are the first devil to ask me for my name.
Did he just smile?
Most everyone born into this world are given a name.
And names are a treasure that each person possesses.
That's what my father taught me.
Your father sounds wise.
Telling someone else your name
is leaving proof that you were born.
As long as someone remembers your name,
you'll never be truly dead!
There'll always be proof that you were alive!
That's how important sharing your name is!
That logic does not compute.
Sure, fine. No idea why I even started
talking about this anyways.
Seems like I got him to feel
some sort of connection with me.
And he seems happy that I asked for his name.
If that gets him to smile,
then he's not as different than I thought.
What is it?
Nothing, nothing.
Just saying that sharing your name's important. Sorry
for the tangent.
I'm Eibrad. Proud member of the Imps of the Dark Valley.
Thank you.
I am an Anti-Devil Self-Development Bioweapon,
Demonhart Series Number 05, DH-05 Leo.
You may call me Leo.
Out of nowhere, devils appeared in Tokyo.
Twelve bioweapons were made to defeat them.
Unstoppable weapons designed to imitate
and eradicate devilkind, the Demonhart Series.
I was one of them.
We possessed power that surpassed
our invaders and unyielding fealty.
We are humanity's fortress, blade, and shield.
So the ONLY thing you were made
to do was protect humanity?
Yes. Our sole purpose is to fight
devilkind and protect humanity.
That's kinda sad.
Is it? I feel no exhaustion from my duties,
and even if I did, protecting humanity is far too important.
That's not what I meant.
What a strange creature.
He is a small devil, an "imp".
Imps are intelligent, and many can speak
and understand human language.
After hearing reports that an imp was preaching
coexistence in the Roppongi area,
I headed straight to the scene and took it into custody.
As reports suggested, he was friendly,
and I obtained plenty of useful information from him.
But amongst that information, he made some
statements that were incomprehensible.
A question, Imp.
Eibrad! I just gave you my name!
Eibrad, what did you mean by 'that's kinda sad'?
Just what I said.
It makes my heart hurt when I think
about all the problems you're gonna face.
I do not understand your statement.
Look, Leo, your only reason for existing
is protecting humanity, right?
Correct.
Right, so listen.
What're you gonna do when the war's over? Captain some
royal guard or some shit?
No. I may not ally myself with
any one political entity or nation.
I will remain on standby until another threat
to humanity's existence presents itself.
Yeah, I figured you'd say as much.
Wanna sit and talk?
I suppose. There is time.
Your job's to protect humanity, huh?
That only means it lasts for the war between us and you.
Once the war's over, you won't have
a job anymore. Isn't that right?
That's correct. If there is no enemy,
then the DH Series has no duties.
And won't that just suck?
You risk your life to win peace for the world,
then end up with no job or place to belong.
I believe peace to be a desirable outcome.
Not for you it ain't! Think about it!
Think about the reason you exist!
The reason I exist?
When you were born, you already had
a reason for existing, clearly defined.
But that reason's gonna be stripped away from you, and
you'll have to live on anyway.
That's just...
Horrible and cruel, if you ask me.
Is that a threat?
Like hell it's a threat! I'm worried about your well-being!
A devil is worried about my well-being?
Yeah! So what?!
Nothing. Please continue.
Look, all I'm saying is when the world's finally at peace,
for you, it'll be horrible.
You'll wonder if the world needs you anymore.
That doubt'll slowly open a hole in your heart.
And you said your kind doesn't die of old age, right?
Correct, we do not.
Death can be a blessing.
Whether or not someone lives a good or bad life,
they all return to the earth in the end.
But not you.
Even after I am no longer needed to protect humanity
and lose my purpose, I will live on forever.
I will be whisked away from those wonderful times
when I knew my identity.
I will be forced to move on,
confused and aimless, forever.
That is what you mean to say, yes?
Yeah.
If another war breaks out,
will I not have my purpose back again?
Yeah, probably. With you living forever,
you'll end up saving the world forever.
Getting back your purpose,
then losing it again, over and over.
You're never gonna be able to rest peacefully.
That's why I said it's really sad.
My circumstances could be as he described.
I will grow, but on the day I earn my humanity...
On the day that the war between human
and devilkind is ended...
I would be born to save the world,
yet there would be no place for me there.
yet yearn for another cataclysm to come forth.
There would be a day where I questioned my way of life.
If I did not die in this war before then.
You needn't worry.
Devilkind--no, demonkind's war
against humanity is intensifying.
What?
Unfortunately, I am the weakest of the DH Series
weapons.
The other DH units will likely defeat the demon army,
but if they do not, the probability of my death
in battle before I earn my humanity is high.
You're the weakest?! At your power level?!
I am. That is why I have been building experience
by fighting far from the front lines.
The humans sure have outdone
themselves with you guys, sheesh...
So you're telling me you don't need to worry
about the future 'cause you're just gonna die?
Yes, so you needn't worry.
I do not think I will suffer as you imagine.
Well, alright then. Sure.
Here's to hopin'.
I'll be prayin' they kill you before you get too invincible.
Thank you.
You have to know I was bein' sarcastic!
Shibuya Station
They're here.
The Containment Squadron.
So I'm not makin' it home after all.
Fine, I'll do it! I'll see my bones
buried in the human world!
I'll live my whole damn life here!
Your whole life?
Yeah.
I'll find a way for demons and
humans to live in harmony.
I'll keep asking everyone to put
down their arms and get along!
Very well.
If we are unable to send you back to the Demon World,
we may need to consider coexistence ourselves.
You remember my name now, all right?!
When I bridge the gap between our peoples,
you better put up a statue of me and you!
My work here is done.
Hey, Leo!
Hey, you listenin' to me?!
Don't work yourself to death!
If it hurts too much, get yourself the hell elsewhere!
If life gets tough, then do what you wanna do!
I don't know shit about bioweapons,
but you should live your life the way you want!
I will.
One more thing!
Don't get too caught up in this
'born to protect humanity' shit!
If humanity stops needing you, that's your chance!
Find something else to live for and enjoy your life!
I will.
Leo! I'll remember your name!
Don't you forget mine!
You got that?!
He had so much to say,
yet I did not understand his words until the end.
I kept them in my memory.
If, on the small chance that life became too painful to live,
I would do as I wished.
I would forget about protecting humanity
and get myself the hell elsewhere.
Very well, Eibrad.
It was June 2060.
Tokyo,
2060 A.D.
A cold rain fell on the streets of Tokyo.
I understand now, Eibrad, my wise friend.
I'll use my life the way I want to.
Now is the time.
I trust them.
I'll reveal everything to them today.
That my name isn't Onyx, but Leo.
And I'll tell them the real reason I joined them.
Next Time:
I Want
to Quit
Heroing