It's YOU who will die here!
Hero binding spell:
Anti-Leo!
No! He's going to dodge it!
I've failed us all!
I've protected no one, accomplished nothing...
This is where I meet my end!
(Thank you.)
Live, live on, with all your might
Follow the light to the future
Betrayed and left behind in this lonely world
Fearing a tomorrow I've lost sight of
Ibasho o sagasu
I search for the place I belong
My heart screams out, "I want to be needed"
I want to puzzle out these entwined identities, but can I trust them?
Live, live on, with all your might
Follow the light to the future
Even if you lose everything
Stay connected to hope
I don't know why I'm here
But that's all right with me right now
I have to overcome and press on
So I can smile with you again
What Makes a Hero
Protect humanity from evil.
Protect humanity from evil...
Save the world.
I was to obey that order from the moment I was born.
It was fine at first.
Just as Master Eibrad had said,
the current world fulfilled my purpose.
The people wanted what I had to offer.
I fought alongside allies,
defeated powerful foes,
and brought peace to the world.
I was pure and innocent then, celebrating that peace
from the bottom of my heart.
Yet...
The peace stretched on and on,
and the world found itself without need for a hero...
I no longer had a reason to exist.
So there IS more for me to fight!
Regional conflicts...
Guess humans and demons couldn't
coexist peacefully after all.
Wars between nations...
Sheesh, you guys need to learn your lesson already.
Then, an invasion from the Demon World.
I felt the world was telling me
that I only deserved to live in it...
...when I was fighting.
I can fight again. I can be a hero again!
I can save humanity again!
A hundred years passed, then two hundred.
Before I knew it, five hundred. A thousand.
Then more, as time flowed endlessly on.
I traveled the world, searching for battle,
fighting endlessly on...
DH-05, Leo, was built around hyper skill development.
With every enemy I fought,
I would gain new techniques,
and eventually, I stopped encountering even matches.
I had become what the scientists who
made me had wanted me to become:
An unstoppable, unkillable, immortal bioweapon.
Then, once again, a long peace took hold.
Get your fresh-baked bread!
Hello, there!
This, please!
Goodness, only one?
Yup, it's okay!
We'll share it!
Is that right? What good kids you are.
Here.
Are you sure?!
Yay!
Here you go.
Thank you!
Come by again soon!
I hope this peaceful world lasts forever.
Hey, why aren't you smiling? You're supposed to smile.
Smile and say "Me too".
Eventually, I realized there was a part of me
that wanted the world to be in danger.
I wanted every person,
every lifeform on this planet, to need me.
To be in the same hopeless peril
it was when I was made.
I want to save the world. Please, let me save it!
If I can't save the world, I'll lose myself!
Bring more danger to humanity!
Bring more chaos to the world!
Every day, more desire for destruction.
Every day, more errors in my consciousness.
I could just do it myself. Plunge the world into peril.
It's so obvious. Why didn't I think of it before?
The DH series had a feature that prevented
the unit from bringing harm to humanity:
Thought Masking. It prevented
the unit from thinking harmful thoughts.
But developing a sense of self, growing an ego,
had disabled its functionality for me.
And I knew how to do it. How to craft
the perfect crisis for my world.
Though I couldn't recreate the Akashic Engine,
I made the Heroes the same as they were,
three thousand years ago,
when they'd first saved humanity.
It's been too long, everyone. This is 05-Leo.
It really has. Look how much I've changed.
You have a mission. Please give me a world to save.
Kill all of humanity,
so I can protect them.
For I...
'Cause I...
I still don't want to die.
I still want to live.
I still want to be a hero!
Demons! Demons are attacking!
What?!
Inform the King at once!
Tell me what's happening.
A huge portal opened up in the Seshat Mountains,
and demons started pouring through!
Don't worry, I'll handle them.
What was I doing?
Well, damn...
I was going to destroy humanity for
my own selfish satisfaction.
I was no hero. Not anymore.
Only a demon would do this.
I'm the REAL Demon King here.
Protect humanity from evil.
That evil is HERE. I'M that evil!
The only surviving unit of the Demonhart Series, 05-Leo,
was the greatest evil threatening the world.
Protect humanity from evil.
I'd destroy the world for my own selfish cause,
toy with human lives to fulfill my own desires.
No Demon King could be more evil than I was.
Protect humanity from evil.
I know, I know. I've got a plan.
It's not like I haven't learned anything
these last three thousand years!
Soon, I was setting off on a mission
to destroy the Demon Army.
I was the hero who would save the world.
I promise, I will defeat the Demon Queen and her army.
I had to quit heroing.
I had to defeat evil.
But I couldn't just be defeated.
I needed to leave the Akashic Engine, the
Philosopher's Stone, to someone worthy.
They had to be strong enough to defeat me,
to defend humanity in my stead.
What are you doing?!
You heard my orders!
Yes, this is an invasion,
but we must avoid killing whenever possible!
Any territory we occupy must be ruled peacefully!
Is that understood?!
Your Queen commands you!
No pillaging, no destruction, no arson!
And do NOT slaughter innocent civilians!
Remember, we did not come here to wage war!
Is an invasion not war?
Yet that was the kind of Queen she was.
Fine, I'll talk, I'll talk!
Queen Echidna's just... kinda weird!
She invaded the human world 'cause she wants to make
the Demon World a better place.
There's never been a Demon King like her!
I've never met a woman as deserving of praise as her.
She forbids us from doing unjust harm
to humans in the course of our invasion,
and she even stands on the front lines
to lead us into battle!
She hands out praise to everyone,
even us low-level imps!
Queen Echidna's a kind ruler!
Never would've guessed it'd be the Demon Queen.
But this Echidna could have been
the successor I'd been looking for.
Hell, she might be able to do more
than just take my heart.
She could become the bridge between the human and
demon realms.
I should give her an interview.
But first, I should save the world.
That was the day I began my final journey.
I vow with all my honor as a warrior: you shall not pass!
Then I vow with all my honor as a hero that I will!
It was a journey to stop heroing.
I will kill you.
Sure! Do it, if you can!
A journey to kill the Hero Leo.
Don't hurt Echidna!
Do you have a screw loose?! You've got
to be stupid to be asking me that right now!
I'd find out what Echidna and
her Four Generals were all about.
I will see Queen Echidna's dreams realized. I will see
peace come to the Demon World!
And I will happily die for her cause!
Damn, you practically sound like the hero, here!
I'd see if they were trustworthy.
So YOU are the Hero Leo.
Queen Echidna, I'm here to see what you've got for me!
I'd work for her, learn her thoughts and feelings,
and determine if she was the right person
to whom to entrust my heart.
And then, I would die.
The Demon King must be defeated.
That's just how the world works.
After three thousands years of life,
the bug-riddled bioweapon...
It's YOU who will die here!
...chose this absurd theatrical display
as his method of suicide.
Hero binding spell:
Anti-Leo!
No...
Thank you.
That smile... Was this what Leo wanted all along?
Every bone in my body is straining against it.
It's ravaging me from the inside out!
Unsurprising. I'm binding three
thousand years of power all by myself.
This is my only chance!
I can only keep his power bound for six more seconds...
It's been a long while since
I've been in this much danger.
My body feels heavy.
I can't even lift a finger.
The regeneration I'd learned from Virgo,
the auto-counter I'd learned from Aquarius,
the self-enhancements from Taurus and Cancer,
the speed from Gemini...
Every last special ability of mine, blocked from use.
I'm the same weak 05-Leo I was at the start.
Time feels like it's moving in slow motion.
Like my life's gonna flash before my eyes.
I'm finally going to die.
She's in a lot of pain...
But I can see in her eyes that she knows
she'll succeed, that her comrades will succeed.
What are you trying to say to me with those eyes?!
I had a premonition.
Queen Echidna, the Hero Leo is quickly fighting his
way through our soldiers!
When I heard that name, and realized it
was in the name of the spell, I had a feeling.
But the King who had devised the spell,
Astarot, did so hundreds of years ago.
No human he fought back then could
be alive today, or so I thought.
But when Leo told me he was
born during the Mechanical Age,
that premonition became all but absolute.
This hero has lived for three thousand years.
The hero who fought Astarot was the same hero
that fought every other Demon King.
The names they called him may have been different,
but it was only him.
He had no friends, no place to return to, no place to die.
He would continue to live a lonely existence,
protecting humanity all on his lonesome.
That is the fate of the Hero Leo.
What's that look for?
You're fine. You've got this.
No one can do everything alone.
That's why being able to trust others...
is the one trait trait you need,
the most important thing to have as a hero.
I couldn't do that. I failed as a hero.
I could never trust anyone.
How did it feel to fight through those eons?
Why didn't he show weakness to anyone?
Why didn't he open his heart to anyone?
I thought I had to be the one to protect the world.
That no one would accept me
if I decided to stop being the hero.
You're so foolishly obsessed with your mission
that you follow it to your death!
Do unto others as you would have them do unto you.
Is that how the saying goes?
Wow. That's kinda funny.
How could anyone find that funny?!
I acted all high-and-mighty when I gave you advice...
You helped my Generals to the best of your ability...
But in the end, all I wanted...
All I ever wanted...
But you must have wanted someone to save YOU!
...was for someone to accept me for who I was.
For someone to say they didn't care
if I wasn't the hero, to come with them.
For someone to tell me...
that they'd save me.
He would let himself get this hurt,
all for the sake of protecting humanity.
But who was protecting the hero?!
When he was suffering in the dark abyss,
who offered him their hand?!
But it's okay. I'm glad I picked Echidna.
I'm glad I picked them to be my last companions.
I know that even if I die, they'll be able to bring
the human and demon worlds together.
You're such a fool!
Queen Echidna will not tolerate such foolishness!
I, WE, will offer you our hand!
I will put an end to this, here and now!
They're good people.
I had fun working with them.
I wish I could've worked with them longer.
Dammit. I don't want to die.
Leo, if you wish to die a hero's death,
then I will grant it to you!
Here and now, I will end your life!
Great Generals, I leave the rest to you!
Lord Leo!
You idiot!
Leo!
Leo...!
Yeah. Bye, now.
I leave the rest to you.
Next Time:
I'm Quitting
Heroing