Ikite ikite ikitsukuse
Hikari o mirai e
Uragirareta kodoku na sekai ni torinokosare
Miushinatta ashita o osorete ima mo
Ibasho o sagasu
Hitsuyou to saretai kokoro no sakebi
Karamiau IDENTITY tashikametainda shinjite iikana
Ikite ikite ikitsukuse
Hikari o mirai e
Tatoe subete ushinattemo
Kibou o tsunaide
Boku ga koko ni iru imi
Ima wa wakaranakute mo ii
Kimi to waraiaeru you ni
Jibun de tachikitte susumudake
I'm Quitting Heroing
Guess I lost.
Feels nice.
Leo...
Did you enjoy that farce?
Pretending to be the evil Demon King?
Yeah, it was pretty fun.
I've always wanted to be the villain.
I'm glad I got to do it with you.
You went easy on us.
Did I, now?
Don't play dumb! You let my spell hit you!
Should I have dodged it?
You guys were losing pretty bad.
You wanted to lose, from the very start.
You came here hoping we would defeat you.
I guess.
Can't say it all went according to plan,
but you did disable me before I killed everyone.
Your little game nearly took the lives
of all five of us, you bloody fool!
From the start? When would that be?
How far back does that go?
I asked you before why you joined us.
If humanity had betrayed you,
or you wanted to put an end to the world,
or if you'd come seeking a place to die.
What a foolish answer this is.
Now, this belongs to you.
The Philosopher's Stone.
I used an emergency override
to cut me off from the Stone's energy.
You've only got 300 seconds, so don't dilly-dally.
I can only do this once.
So we just pull it out?
Yep. It's in pretty tight,
but it's just like popping a cap off a bottle.
No! Don't! Please don't kill Leo!
Stop it, Echidna! Don't kill him, please!
Come, Lily, don't make a fuss. Queen Echidna is unwell.
No! Leo, don't die!
Look at that smile.
Till the very end, he's protecting humanity.
He was never going to kill anyone or destroy our worlds.
He knew he could sacrifice his life to bring
peace to both and willingly made that choice.
It pains me to admit it, but he truly is a hero,
through and through.
270 seconds left.
Do you have any regrets?
Someone's picking up my work,
and the Demon Army's running more efficiently.
Everything's good. I've got no regrets.
All right.
No!
Leo!
Stop this tantrum!
No, no, no!
Lily!
The Demon World needs the Philosopher's Stone.
Actually, there's one last thing I have to say.
Sorry for all the trouble.
240 seconds, now.
Goodbye, Great Generals. Goodbye, Echidna.
I'm glad I got to know you all.
Hey...
I've changed my mind. It's too much effort.
What?!
You want me to make peace with the human world?
You fool! Have you forgotten who I am?
I am the Demon Queen, the great Echidna!
I am the ruler of the Demon World, its queen!
Do you know how busy I am?
I've no time for this errand of yours!
What?!
Now listen, hero... No, now you're merely Leo.
Listen, Leo, and rejoice, for I have decided
to officially employ you in my ranks!
Seeing as you possess the Stone and
are the only being to have lived 3000 years,
I appoint you as ambassador between
the Demon and Human worlds!
Are you crazy?! You're running out of time!
I don't care!
I'd expect nothing less of you, My Queen.
H-hey, Edvard! Talk some sense into her!
No, screw that, tear the Stone out of me, now!
Lord Leo, surely you jest!
I'm afraid I agree with Queen Echidna.
You'd best give up.
You only have 200 seconds!
There are still so many things I'd like to learn from
you, Lord Leo!
Your death would be a great disservice! To me, at least!
How is he this stupid?! It makes no sense!
Can you think of any other better to unite
our worlds than a man who's lived 3000 years?
I mean...
And my darling Julietta has taken quite a liking to you!
What father would I be if I made her cry?
I beseech you, reconsider your decision!
Do you not have a brain inside that thick skull of yours?!
You're the one without a brain!
Why?! Why did you think of this by yourself
so you can end it by yourself?!
Why didn't you ask your friends for help?!
You didn't ask me for help at all!
Why? Who could I have--
Me!
Talk to me!
You taught me that when you're in trouble,
you should ask your friends for help!
You taught me that when
you can't do it by yourself to find, uh,
I-I get it, Lily! One of my shortcomings
is my inability to trust people!
Find the right person for the job!
But this isn't the time for this! You have 160 seconds!
So why are you doing this?! Look at me and tell me!
I'm stupid, so I don't know why you want to die...
But I'll always hear you out,
so please don't die on me, you big dummy!
Mernes! He'll be able to calmly analyze the situation!
You've only got 140 seconds left. I trust you, Mernes.
You won't let your emotions get the better of you.
OW!
Are you stupid?
Ow!
That hurts! Hey! Stop it!
I didn't need to be a good listener.
I just needed to fight you.
Your words, your attitude, your eyes,
everything is screaming that you want to live.
This whole time, too.
Then live, you idiot!
If you want to live, then live!
You told me to make choices you won't regret.
But here you are, dying full of regrets.
You only have 110 seconds!
Moron! Idiot! Imbecile!
No, no, no, no!
Sh-Shutina! Help!
Help with what?
Leo, have you caught on to
the contradiction in your words?
Wh-what contradiction?
Tell me, for what reason are you dying?
What? I don't have time to--
Tell me!
To protect humanity. That's the order they built into us!
And none of the Demonhart Series can disobey it!
Another order, Thought Masking, erases
any rebellious thoughts before they develop!
You only have 95 seconds!
But in your case...
Yes! I developed, I grew a strong ego, a self!
That self turned off my Thought Masking!
But I can't keep my identity if I don't protect humanity!
If something doesn't change, I'm going to
put humanity in danger just so I can save them!
I see, I see.
That's just how it is!
No matter how strong my ego or sense of free will,
they're not strong enough to...
That's right.
By that logic, your strong ego should allow you
to disable your order to protect, yes?
What? No, it couldn't...
Try it.
But--
Try it, now!
Fine!
Disable the order?
Protect humanity from evil. Protect humanity from evil.
Disable THIS?
Is she stupid?! I've been following this order
for 3000 years! I can't just turn it off!
Protect humanity from evil. Protect humanity from evil.
How am I even supposed to do that?
Just "try it"? Help me out, here!
Protect humanity from evil. Protect humanity from evil.
It can't be done! I don't know how!
Okay, okay, fine!
Protect humanity from evil. Protect humanity from evil.
I get it, but could you shut up for a sec?
Just stop, please stop, just STOP.
Just...
Protect hum-
Wait.
Really?
I disabled it?
I HAVE TO protect the world.
I HAVE TO be a hero.
There was no way to escape those compulsions.
Did...
Did I just CONVINCE myself that I HAD to?
Leo, there are 30 seconds left.
If you truly want to die, then I will kill you.
It's your life. Use it as you see fit.
I don't know shit about bioweapons,
but you should live your life the way you want!
But if you want to live, then do not waste
your life trapped by someone else's orders.
Don't get too caught up in
this 'born to protect humanity' shit!
Humanity has exiled you.
Is this not the perfect opportunity?
Work under me, and leave 'heroing'
behind for a new way of life.
If humanity stops needing you, that's your chance!
Find something else to live for, and enjoy your life!
Quit heroing and join me!
Your three thousand years of endless solitude end now.
Leo!
No taking anything out of storage without permission!
Be a Strong Warrior. Be a Good Boss
Boy, you guys really let your guards down.
Foolish indeed.
Sharing wine with the Hero Leo,
then falling asleep in his presence...
Had you told me of this before, I would have laughed.
I don't see the problem. We're allies now.
Not allies. You are my subordinate.
I admit, you had the lot of us hoodwinked this entire time.
You even gave our Generals a false motive
behind your actions at the start.
Everything I said happened was the truth,
but I never harbored any ill will towards humanity.
From the day of your interview, it wasn't you
who was being tested, but the Demon Army.
Leo, do you have any regrets?
What do you mean?
Don't dodge the question.
That was your one chance to die.
You may not get another for centuries.
Do you regret giving up potentially
your only chance to be freed of your burdens?
Good question.
I want to help you.
Wh-where did this come from?
Back when we drank together.
When I heard your story, I knew I wanted to help you.
I wish to bring order to my world of chaos.
To rid the land of conflict.
I want to make your wish come true.
I want to help you find a way
for humanity and demonkind to coexist.
That's why I'm here. I don't regret a thing.
Have you forgotten that I am a villainous conqueror,
one who invades other worlds
and wreaks havoc for her own gain?
Do you truly believe working beneath
such a villain would be virtuous?
None of that's true. You're a kind queen
who cares deeply for her people.
That kindness drove you to invade
the human world for the sake of your homeland.
That kindness led you to empathize
with the people you were conquering.
That's how I beat you.
You love your people.
Conquest doesn't suit you.
Even now, you're asking me
these things out of kindness.
You want me to know this
is my last chance to reconsider.
But that kindness of yours has saved my life.
Let me help you, Echidna.
I'll do everything in my power to ensure
you never have to play the villain again.
To ensure you can be the kind queen
you truly are, for all your people.
This I swear.
Can I trust you?
Of course you can.
In three thousand years, I've never, ever made a girl cry.
Leo...
You're all right...
I guess that's not true. But I'll uphold that promise.
I was going to give you one last chance,
but it appears I've been misguided.
I hadn't expected you to repay me
with such a purposeful new lease on life...
But I do like it.
So you accept my answer, then?
I do.
I'm looking forward to working with you, former hero Leo.
It is an honor, Queen Echidna.
That was the story of how I came
to join the Demon Queen's army.
Father! Is General Edvard here?
I am so terribly sorry, Your Highness!
I deeply apologize for interrupting
your romantic moment with Lord Leo!
This was NOT a romantic moment, you fool!
Forget that! What did you come here for? Tell me!
Right! The wyverns are dissatisfied with
their treatment and have begun to riot!
Again?
All right, you lot! Wake up!
My deepest apologies, Your Highness!
We are awake, my Queen.
Edvard, go deal with them before
they cause any damage!
At once.
Scuse me, is General Lily here?
What's up?
Largo is complaining that the elixirs that
were due yesterday haven't been delivered.
I totally forgot!
General Shutina!
One of the tomes in the fourth library has run
amok and is summoning a stream of chimeras!
That accursed tome again! I'm going to burn it
to a crisp, once and for all! Come with me!
Mernie, I was looking for you!
We can't open the dining hall without you!
I told you I was quitting.
I know, I know, but let's talk later! Come, now!
Queen Echidna, what should we
do about the Great Spirit Portal?
Queen Echidna, we've received a message
from the viceroy in the Demon World!
Queen Echidna!
Now, Leo, I believe you said you would
do everything in your power to help me.
Is that right?
Yeah, that's what I said.
As you can see, we have mountains of work to do.
Before we take on the large-scale issue
of uniting the human and demon realms,
we'll need to tackle the problems we're currently facing.
I intend to make full use of your talents, so do be ready.
Don't need to tell me twice.
I'll take care of it, so you sit back and have some tea.
That was the story of how I came
to join the Demon Queen's army.
How the Hero Leo, a biological weapon
created three thousand years ago,
broke free of his ancient commands
to move forward on his own.
How he made a great many friends.
Friends he could trust.
How I finally, after all that time, was able to quit heroing.
Okay. Where to start?
I'm Quitting Heroing
Bokura no kokoro wa itsudatte moroi
Our hearts are always so frail and fragile
Sore demo mae o muite nagai michi o susumu
But we still face forward and continue down our long road
Shiranakatta koto wa kore kara shireba ii
If we don't know something now, we can go learn about it
Tsuzukeru koto no saki ni aru mono ima wa mada wakaranai kedo
We might not know what's at the end of our long, continuing journey
Hitori de kakaekomi suginaide tama ni wa senaka o azuketemiyou
Don't try to do everything yourself, lean on us sometimes
Yowasa ni yorisoeru no mo tsuyosanara
Sharing your weaknesses is strength in itself
Madamada saki wa nagai kui no nai you ni
There's still a long way to go,
so make sure you won't regret anything
Hashiridase riyuu wa tanjun
Dash on! The reason's simple
Tokihanate risou no yume o
Let loose! Make your dreams reality
Fumidashita saki no mirai wa jibun shidai de dou ni demo naru
The future you're heading towards is one you shape yourself
Kawaru koto ga kowakunattemo sukoshizutsu de iinda
It's okay to be scared of change, you can go little by little
Taisetsu na mono o mamoru tame ni
I want to protect the things I cherish
Megurimegutte tsunagatta
(I'm so glad we found each other)
Kimi ni arigatou todoiteimasu you ni
So I hope you hear how thankful I am for you