The hee-row?
Yes, he protects the human world.
The hero is powerful beyond words...
Just to speak of him sends chills down my spine!
He defeated Chaos Lord Belial,
the mighty Sorcerer Lord Astarot,
and countless other brave warriors of eld!
Young lady, should you become our Queen,
do not engage the hero in combat.
Fighting him would lead to your destruction!
Oh, please! That's so dumb!
I don't know why you're so afraid of this heerow.
He's just a human!
If I ever saw him, I'd give him a beat-down!
Not like I'm ever gonna choose to be Queen, though!
You told me you want to save
the Demon World, right, Echidna?
You said you'd endure blood, sweat, and tears...
to obtain the stone and bring peace to fruition.
Blood, sweat, and tears.
The time to prove your mettle is now!
If you want the Stone, if you want to save the world,
then stop me, here and now,
brave heroes!
Ikite ikite ikitsukuse
Hikari o mirai e
Uragirareta kodoku na sekai ni torinokosare
Miushinatta ashita o osorete ima mo
Ibasho o sagasu
Hitsuyou to saretai kokoro no sakebi
Karamiau IDENTITY tashikametainda shinjite iikana
Ikite ikite ikitsukuse
Hikari o mirai e
Tatoe subete ushinattemo
Kibou o tsunaide
Boku ga koko ni iru imi
Ima wa wakaranakute mo ii
Kimi to waraiaeru you ni
Jibun de tachikitte susumudake
I'll Save the World, Even If That Means Destroying It
Leo, you fool...
What do you mean by that?
Are you mad?! Have you lost your mind?!
Queen Echidna!
Nope, my mind's all here.
My job is to keep this world safe.
That's the reason I was made.
The only reason I live for!
A single swing is that powerful?!
If I can't save the world, I'll lose my whole identity.
If humanity doesn't need me,
then I'll make them need me!
I'll save the world, even if I have to destroy it first!
You would decide to switch ends and means!
Why would you destroy
the very thing you want to protect?!
All that would await you is a devastated land!
Devastation! Hell, I'll take it.
I've protected this world long enough.
Who cares if I destroy it?!
Leo...?
Emptying everything out and starting
from scratch sounds pretty damn good!
Lord Leo, enough of this foolishness!
Calm yourself! This isn't like you!
He's right! Why do we have to fight?!
Have you been paying attention, you moron Generals?!
Obsidian Cage!
A binding spell? Really?
If you want my heart, then you're going to have to kill me!
Don't be ridiculous!
If your heart really is the Philosopher's Stone,
then why not continue to help us,
as you've been doing this whole time?!
You said you wouldn't betray us!
Or was that all a lie?
Were we never friends at all?!
If you don't kill me, then you'll all die.
Edvard!
Edvard...
Leo, you really mean to kill us...?
I'm sick of it all!
My hyper-reactive skill improvement,
my existence as an immortal guardian
for humanity, all of it!
I'm not even allowed to die to end it all!
I just keep protecting, guarding, defending,
and even when they finally say
they don't need me, it doesn't end!
Leo, you bastard...
Who should I hate, huh?
The humans who made me?
Or the demons who forced their hand?
What...?
All of you, that's who.
So I'll destroy both the human AND the demon worlds...
and quit all this heroing bullshit once and for all.
No... I knew he was holding back when we fought before,
but is this his true strength?
What now? I can't fight him in this state...
And my mana core hasn't yet fully
recovered from our last battle!
Is this the time to use that spell?
It would still be a gamble.
And I have no idea if it will work...
Please stop, Leo!
Lily?!
Please, don't do this!
This isn't like you, Leo!
Do you remember when we were on Largo,
and you listened when I had problems?
You told me tons of really good advice, too!
Yep, I did. I remember.
It's my turn to return the favor!
So tell me all your problems! I'll hear you out!
So please, stop! Let's not fight!
All right.
Leo...
My problems? ALL my problems?
You want to hear what my problems are, Lily?
Yeah, I do! I'll hear you out, no matter what!
Right now, my biggest problem...
Yeah?
My biggest problem...
...is that the heroes I expected so much
from are so goddamn weak!
Lily!
I get it now.
You're no hero... Not anymore.
No real hero would ruthlessly attack
a harmless, unarmed opponent!
Fill my hands with the piercing rays of the gods!
Destroy mine enemy!
Gae Assail!
So you finally got serious.
Not even high-level spells can hurt him?!
Come, heroes!
If you want your world to survive,
then stop me with every last fiber of your being!
Very well!
I am grateful to you, Lord Leo!
You taught this ignorant oaf to understand
the weaknesses in those around him!
You were a fine teacher!
Never have I known a man such as you!
You had my utmost respect, from the bottom of my heart!
You were a true ally and a friend!
And now you realize you were wrong?
That I was a villain?
No, I still feel that way!
But even if you are my friend...
No, BECAUSE you are my friend...
He's unleashed his dragon blood?!
He's getting serious, too!
If you have strayed from the path,
it is my duty to cut you down!
Impossible!
Cocytus Ptolomea.
It's not...
Inferno Gehenna.
He's casting spells with opposing elements
at the same time?!
Edvard!
And now your precious dragon scales are all but useless.
Destroyed by a rapid change in temperature.
Know how that works? Probably not, huh.
Begone, Dragon General.
Two down.
This villain...!
Leo...
Do not discount the Demon Queen's strength!
Behemoth Tail!
Earthen Grave!
Good work! Now burn to your death!
Inferno!
No!
Impossible...
After being hit with that many attacks,
he's suffered almost no damage?!
Wait... His special ability is
'hyper-reactive skill improvement', right?
He copies the abilities of others and
endlessly improves upon them...
Does that apply to defense, too?
If he grows stronger with every foe he faces,
with every attack that hits him...
No. This doesn't fare well for us!
If this battle continues...!
I thought you'd be next, boy!
I must be out of practice. Thought that was a sure kill.
That was a perfect strike. He's just a monster.
Good point. And a real pain...
Keep at it!
So what is it, huh?
Do you wanna die, or do you wanna be killed?
Both!
I want to fight the world and get killed by someone,
anyone, out there.
Otherwise, I'm gonna destroy the whole world myself!
Liar.
You didn't need to join the army to do that.
You could've just started your endless fight.
Instead, you came over here and
got all passionate about helping people,
teaching them how to work more efficiently and crap!
You were thinking ahead.
Thinking about the people who would survive.
You wouldn't care about that
if you really wanted to destroy the world!
Shut up, Mernes.
You don't hate the world.
You don't want to kill the humans, either.
I know what you're really after!
Mernes...
A below-freezing auto-counter?! How powerful is he?!
That makes three.
What I'm really after, huh?!
I told you what I'm really after!
I want to save the world, even if I have to destroy it!
You're finally ready to fight me, huh, Lily?
I don't wanna fight. I don't wanna!
I don't wanna have to do this.
But Leo...
You don't look like you're having any fun!
You're smiling, but you're not happy at all!
So I'll help... I'll stop you!
Because I love you, Leo... I love you a whole lot!
So I'll help you by stopping you!
Lily...
Fine, then. Do it.
Right then, I realized the truth once more.
Leo was neither human nor demon.
He was a monster, created by ancient humans.
We can't win like this.
He'll kill us, then humanity,
then the Demon World, then the future...
I've no time left to falter.
Shutina, I'm using it. Buy me 42 seconds of time.
Honestly, my Queen? 42 seconds against Leo?
I have no one else to turn to. If you cannot,
that's the end of everything.
Oh, I'll do it, of course. Why wouldn't I?
It's just one more impossible demand
you've foisted upon me, like every other!
I'm sorry. If we make it back alive,
I'll treat you to the finest wine.
This may be my one and only chance.
But if I'm correct about Leo's true objective,
then I might be able to win. I might be able to kill him.
A spell?
Yes. Now that I am abdicating
my throne to you, I must pass it on.
What, just because I'm your daughter?
Please, that doesn't mean--
No, never mind. Forget I said anything.
Cease your prattling, former Demon King Cychreus.
I need not your assistance, nor any secret royal magic.
I don't want to have to pass it down,
either, but I don't have a choice.
This spell has been passed down from
Demon King to Demon King for centuries.
Centuries?
You know of the Hero, yes?
Of course. The Hero that defeated
so many of our brethren long ago.
Astarot devised a spell to assist in battle against him,
one designed solely for defeating the Hero.
Solely for defeating him?
The spell is highly limited in its uses
and is extremly costly to cast.
I know not of any Demon King who has yet to use it.
To be completely honest, the spell itself
is no more than a gamble.
Then I may never use it.
I needn't rely on such a gamble, nor fear him.
The full extent of my power will be enough.
I thought you'd say that. Maybe you'll be all right, then.
Of course I will.
Neph salem arcranus elgil hel...
Leo!
I've known for too long that you are a terrible liar!
You could've killed Edvard,
but you just sent him flying!
You interrupted Mernes before
he could finish his sentence!
You even hesitated when Lily offered to help!
You don't want to destroy the world.
The only thing you hate,
the only thing you want to destroy,
is yourself!
You're afraid of your future.
A future where you want to save the world,
but can't, where your life has no meaning.
You're afraid that you might actually destroy
the world in an attempt to save it!
I'm right, aren't I?!
So you've forced yourself to play the villain,
all in a bid to get us to defeat you
while you're still sane and in control.
After ensuring your Philosopher's Stone
and your work is passed on
and knowing that humans and demons
will ally with one another when you're gone!
You fool!
Six chains, twelve swords to avenge the world!
I'm almost there! Don't die on me, Shutina!
Don't you dare die!
Is that the best you could do
after three thousand years of life?
Leo,
you're...
Enough already. Die.
It's YOU who will die here!
Listen well.
This spell will use all of your mana to disable
the Hero's abilities for a brief moment.
We call it...
Hero binding spell:
Anti-Leo!
Next Time:
What Makes
a Hero