De ce povestesc dintr-odată despre asta?
Se presupunea că doar simulez un interviu cu Mernes ca să-l ajut cu abilitățile sale în ale comunicării...
Episodul 6: Eroul își spune povestea de viață
Deci...
Da?
Ai spus că vrei să distrugi umanitatea.
Dar asta nu e adevărat, nu?
Mă gândeam că Shutina mă va întreba asta.
Sunt surprins să văd că vine de la tine.
Mi-ai spus să mă pun în locul lor și să încerc să-mi dau seama ce urmează să mă întrebe.
Așa că asta am făcut.
Și așa mi-am dat seama.
Nu ai nevoie de noi. Ai putea distruge umanitatea de unul singur.
Bună treabă! Dacă poți empatiza atât de bine, atunci ești deja un maestru în ale comunicării...
Bun, dă-mi voie să-ți pregătesc diploma! Oare unde am pus-o?
Oh, poftim, zece tichete de masă la Restaurantul Șobolanului! Felicitări!
Nu încerca să schimbi subiectul.
De ce nu ai distrus-o încă?
Și eu mă întreb același lucru! Oare de ce nu am făcut-o?
Nu te face că nu știi!
Hei, ai grijă!
Nu te deranjează?
Ai făcut tot posibilul ca să-i protejezi, iar ei doar s-au descotorosit de tine.
Ți-ai riscat viața luptând împotriva noastră.
Nu le-ai dorit niciodată moartea?
Eu da.
Mi-ai investigat trecutul, nu-i așa?
Da, puțin. Știu că ești
jumătate om, jumătate demon.
Oamenilor le era frică de tine,
așa că părinții tăi te-au vândut ca sclav,
iar după ce ai avut mai mulți stăpâni, ai ajuns în Breasla Asasinilor.
Așa este.
The guild thought I'd be expendable,
that I'd die taking out my first and only target.
But for better or for worse...
am fost un asasin destul de bun încât să supraviețuiesc.
Cu toții...
meritați să muriți!
That's why I was more than supportive
of the Demon Army's invasion.
I so desperately wanted them
to finish off humanity once and for all.
Your Highness!
I've startling news! The castle gates have opened for us!
What?!
Very well. Do not let this chance escape us!
All troops, move in!
I raced ahead of their forces and
secretly gave them my assistance.
However...
Fear not! We have not come to slaughter you!
Our objective lies in the Capital, in Renailles!
We will rebuild the town as we use it
as our new base of operations.
We've also captured your corrupt mayor.
There was so much food in his castle!
Let's share it together!
Okay, line up! Don't worry, there's enough for everyone!
Why didn't we kill them? It was a waste of precious time.
Despite my doubts, I made contact with Echidna,
and joined the army under false pretenses.
Shouldn't we leave this town and proceed forward?
Tomorrow, yes.
Tonight, though, the populace is providing us
with a grand welcome.
You've liberated us and restored peace.
We can't thank you enough.
Think nothing of it.
It was a necessary part of our own plans.
This is good! You should try this!
Does anyone want refills on juice?
This is crazy! We're in the middle of an invasion,
hosting a grand feast?!
I understand your frustration, but this, too,
is part of Queen Echidna's strategy.
Non-stop fighting will lead to burned-out troops.
This creates the opportunity
for them to refresh themselves
and for her to speak one-on-one with
her subordinates, reigniting their motivation.
Their motivation?
You've been working hard.
I-I'm honored that you've noticed!
This is ridiculous.
Our Queen is a strange one, isn't she?
Before I joined up, I thought the Army was
an evil force hell-bent on destroying humanity.
Yeah, so did I...
That's why when they asked me to join, I said no!
There are horrible humans, true,
but that don't mean they all deserve to burn.
But then I saw that this is who they really are.
That's why I changed my mind.
Besides, no man or woman who
loves good ale can be a villain!
Indeed!
Mernes, why did you join the Demon Army?
I couldn't tell them I'd joined with
the hopes of slaughtering humanity.
No reason.
Mernes, I'm glad to have you among us.
I'll be needing your help again tomorrow!
Once we have the Philosopher's Stone,
and the Demon World has become a paradise,
I invite you to join us there.
I expect you'd like living somewhere peaceful and quiet.
I'm going to bed.
Oh? Leaving already?
Aww, I wanted to hang out with you though!
Whatever.
If I need to, I'll take out Echidna and
lead the Demon Army myself to destroy humanity.
After that, I became one of the Great Generals,
and half-heartedly helped lead its brilliant forces
through its successful campaign.
Well, successful until SOMEONE came along.
You mean me?
Remember what I said that day?
I've lost. Kill me.
If you don't, then someday, I'll exterminate humanity.
Sheesh. You're acting like you've never seen
anything cool in your whole life.
Go out and see the world a little, man.
What?
I've done that, and I'm bored of it.
This world sucks. Nothing in it is 'cool'.
That's because you've only seen it as an assassin.
The world looks different when you're seeing it
on your own terms, not just for work.
As if it's that easy...
Not like I'd know that, though.
What?
In any case, here's my advice for you right now:
Go seek out something in the world you've never seen.
If you still want to die after that, I'll kill you.
Oh, and if you do something evil, I'll kill you too.
See ya!
You spouted off all those high-and-mighty words,
so why'd you decide to quit?
To destroy humanity? I know that's a lie.
I don't care what happens to humanity.
But you don't seem to have, the, uh...
The hatred for mankind?
Yeah. You've got something else going on.
Else, you wouldn't have said all that stuff to me.
So why?
They betrayed you. Normally people
get angry when they're betrayed.
You get sad, you hate them, you truly start to hate them...
Whoa...
Man, I'm learning way too many new things
about these guys now that I've joined them.
The prim and proper Shutina is a klutz
who barely keeps herself afloat.
The brainless wild child is a diligent, good kid.
And now we've got Mernes.
The uncaring, unfeeling assassin
struggles with teenage angst.
The reason he kept quiet after hearing my reasons for
joining wasn't that he didn't like me.
He heard how I'd been exiled by humanity
and felt for me from the bottom of his heart.
Hey, man, don't cry. Now I feel like it's my fault.
Shut up!
I'll listen, so just tell me!
All right.
Yeah, getting told "we don't need you" and
"kill the hero" made me feel pretty shitty.
Huh?
Especially since I've been defending
humanity for a long, long time.
How long...?
What...
Let me tell you what the world was like when I was born.
It was a long, long time ago...
What am I telling him this for?
At the height of industrial civilization,
before magic came into common use.
The land was shaped a bit differently than it is now,
and where the Capital now stands,
there stood the city of Tokyo...
We launched rockets into the sea of stars,
encircled the earth with swarms of man-made satellites,
and an invisible, high-speed communication
network connected the planet.
There were tensions, but mostly peace,
and unlike our diverse world,
mine was made up of only humans.
Then, one day...
A hole opened up in the middle of Tokyo.
From it came imps, dwarves, orcs,
goblins, succubi and incubi...
All manner of demons we're well-acquainted with now.
Back then, we just called them "demons".
Just like Echidna, they were sick of the dark,
horrific Demon World,
and came to the human world
seeking its warmth and light.
Many tried to peacefully exist alongside humanity,
but others opted for violence.
What was humanity going to do?
Fight back, of course.
What had started on an eastern island nation
spread around the world,
and it wasn't long until there was a full-out world
war on demon kind.
And sadly,
Humans back then were as weak as they are now.
It took dozens of humans just to get rid of one demon.
We need stronger weapons!
Yes, an unstoppable weapon that can
protect humanity from this demonic threat!
Now is the time for humanity to join as one!
To kill a demon, we must create a demon ourselves.
The project is nearly complete.
We've used the demon's own power
to forge twelve powerful weapons,
living beings with limitless potential
to evolve, grow, and protect humanity.
The Demonhart Series!
As of now,
only one Demonhart survives.
And that's me.
You're a living weapon?
Wh-what the hell does that mean?
From the moment I was born, I was a hero.
I knew no other way of life.
My orders were planted at inception:
Protect humanity. Save the world.
All heroes grow old and die,
but I was made to be extremely durable and long-lived.
The other DH Series models fell in battle, one by one,
leaving me as the only surviving hero.
Actually, I'll put it this way.
I'd missed my chance to die.
Even after the industrial world fell, and magic
replaced machinery, I went on living.
It happened so long ago, I can barely remember it.
Whenever war erupted, I was there to fight.
I'd grown too strong to die in battle.
Protect humanity. Save the world.
Those were my orders,
but were they the right things to do?
Was I just keeping humanity dependent on me?
No one could answer those questions.
Even so...
Not like I'd know that, though.
I just couldn't abandon my duty to protect the world.
When the world pushed me aside just recently,
sure, I was a little sad to hear it.
But I wasn't upset about it. In fact...
I was happy.
But why?!
Yeah, I WAS happy.
Yeah, that's right.
Those warm words of "we don't need you"
and "let's kill him"...
...were the most meaningful words I'd ever heard.
It finally gave me a chance to quit heroing.
I don't have to protect humanity.
The next time humanity needs protection,
I can just do whatever I want.
I can be myself. Go see the parts of the world
I want to see, on my own terms.
So I'm spending my 'second' life doing
what I always wanted: joining the demons.
Hold on.
I'm glad Echidna didn't just get up and
go back to the demon world.
You know her father, Demon King Cychreus?
I don't understand a single thing you've said.
He wasted NO time going home.
Didn't even get a chance to talk!
I said, hold on!
Why did I tell him all that?
You know how the saying goes,
a good communicator is a good listener!
It's simple.
Once people know you're a good listener,
I just wanted someone to hear my story.
they'll start coming to you, asking to vent or to get some advice.
Don't hold it in. Talk it out, yeah?
I assumed some good listener out there
would ask me about it someday.
Who knew it'd end up being you.
You're not making sense.
Potrivit legendei, invazia Lordului Demon Cychreus a fost acum o mie de ani!
Da. Și potrivit legendei,
un „misterios înțelept” a salvat lumea.
Eu am fost acela.
Ce? Atunci, câți ani ai?
Nu, mai bine spus...
Ce ești tu, mai exact?
Just an ex-hero they built to be
a bit tougher than the rest.
Cât despre câți ani am... Nu am idee.
Sincer să fiu, m-am oprit din numărat când am trecut de o mie.
O mie?
Man, though, you live this long, you meet a lot of people.
You meet one person you want to protect with your life,
then another you want to see dead.
So believe me when I say this.
You guys are a good lot.
Echidna and the Great Guardians
are all big goofballs, but they're good people.
Good enough to make me want
to work my butt off for you.
Goofballs?
Deci nu vă faceți griji. Voi face rost de Piatra Filosofală pentru voi.
Mă voi asigura că vă veți găsi fericirea.
Vai...
I still don't get it. And you're not going
to explain any further, are you?
I'll get around to it.
I mean, I hadn't planned on telling you all this, either.
Atunci, de ce mi-ai spus?
Because you looked serious, I guess.
I'd felt this since that moment at the lake.
He's not the best talker, but he's got the
one thing that makes you a good communicator:
Turn me into a master communicator.
O motivație puternică.
That genuine desire is the most
important part of communicating well.
You might be blunt and awkward,
but I could tell you really wanted to hear me out.
That's why I couldn't stop myself
from telling you everything.
You just need to be genuine and thoughtful,
just like you are now.
You'll do great in your interviews. I know
you'll be able to get the applicants to open up.
Don't touch me.
I'm done, and I'm tired. I'm going to pass out here.
Hey, hold on, you've got your own room!
And we've got another long day in the cafeteria
tomorrow!
Noapte bună.
Hei, Mernes! Don't pass out on me!
Okay, fine.
You never change, though, do you?
He might be able to mediate.
Oh, tată...
Data viitoare
Un războinic bun nu înseamnă și un șef bun