05, engage the enemy.
Roger. Prioritizing preservation of civilian life.
I was their supposed savior, and yet...
I was met not with cheers, but with eyes filled
with fear and gandiose expectations.
But I don't care.
I'll protect humanity.
That's the whole reason I exist.
I'll protect the world.
That's all humanity wants from me.
That's all I live for.
A nightmare...
Ikite ikite ikitsukuse
Hikari o mirai e
Uragirareta kodoku na sekai ni torinokosare
Miushinatta ashita o osorete ima mo
Ibasho o sagasu
Hitsuyou to saretai kokoro no sakebi
Karamiau IDENTITY tashikametainda shinjite iikana
Ikite ikite ikitsukuse
Hikari o mirai e
Tatoe subete ushinattemo
Kibou o tsunaide
Boku ga koko ni iru imi
Ima wa wakaranakute mo ii
Kimi to waraiaeru you ni
Jibun de tachikitte susumudake
The Drinking Party From Hell
Talk about a nightmare.
I just know the rest of today's
gonna turn out crappy now...
It comes straight from Queen Echidna:
"Black Knight Onyx is to report to me at once."
What? Crap, did she catch on to me?!
What will you do?
Lily got real close to revealing
my true identity before, but I dealt with her.
You haven't gone to introduce yourself to her yet.
Perhaps she's angry about that.
Oh yeah, I haven't done that yet...
But, well...
I've told her our work has been proceeding
smoothly thanks to Lord Onyx...
That's probably why she wants to see me, you moron!
Moron!? Wh-what ELSE was I supposed to tell her?!
And Echidna didn't just stumble
into the title of Demon Queen.
Armed with her beloved Tilving, she can hold
her own against Edvard in single combat,
and she's as good as a spellcaster as Shutina.
It's scary how powerful she is.
No matter the tricks I employ,
she might still be able to see through my disguise.
In any case, you should hurry to her.
And if she realizes who you are,
call me without hesitation.
Nah, I'll be fine. I'll figure it out on my own.
Just pretend you had no idea.
Right, then, what excuse do I give Echidna?
Tis I, Black Knight Onyx.
I have come to answer your summons.
Enter.
Okay, what do you have in store for me,
Demon Queen Echidna?!
Thank you.
So you're the wonderful Onyx!
I've heard all about your marvelous deeds from Shutina!
I'm so sorry to call you here on short notice.
Well... It doesn't sound like she's figured out who I am.
Please, take a seat.
Wait, hold on. You can't be serious. Please.
There are only two seats at this table!
Come, no need for formalities today!
Let's enjoy a fine meal and good liquor together!
Whenever I have a nightmare,
I know the next day's bound to be hell.
Are you drinking, Lord Onyx?
That I am.
I must say, this liquor is incredible.
Not to mention the food.
Excellent!
This looks like your typical after-hours drink
with a strait-laced worker and his chill boss.
Of course, it's anything but.
I want to get out of here as quickly as humanly possible,
and I'm terrified she'll find out
who I am in the midst of all this.
So, Onyx.
Y-yes?
Are you going to wear that helm for much longer?
Would you please take it off?
No, I must insist. It would be rude to show
my bare face before you, Your Highness...
Please, I told you to dispense with formalities.
And I'd like to be able to talk to you face-to-face!
Huh?!
Oh, uh...
Now, then, let's see that boorish face of yours!
Oh, no!
There!
Wait a moment...
I didn't have time to change my face that much!
I-is there something wrong?
I like that stalwart expression!
I sense great strength behind your soft visage!
Tis a shame to hide it away behind a helm!
That was close! Thank goodness she's so drunk...
Come, now, don't hold back.
Stuff yourself until you burst, by all means!
I'm drinking alone with my boss,
and if she finds out who I am, I'm dead.
How am I supposed to enjoy my drink like this?!
Delicious food and liquor!
This moment is paradise on Earth!
I need to get out of this 'paradise' ASAP.
But I have to be smart and smooth about it!
Your Highness, your glass is empty.
Allow me to pour you a new drink.
Oh, thank you! How considerate.
If you'd allow me...
Let me give you a couple tips about how
to make business parties a little easier.
Tip #1: The moment your boss' glass is empty, fill it up.
Please, have some more.
I shall!
You can take a break from the conversation
while filling their cup,
and they'll think you're perceptive and cosiderate.
Here, have another!
I shall!
But that's not the only thing I'm after.
Right now, my goal is simple: get her dead drunk!
That's all I'm focused on!
My, you're thirsty! Come, have another!
I shall!
C'mon, drink! Drink 'til you're sloshed!
Then you can put an end to this horrible event!
Are you quite well, Your Highness?
Perhaps you've had a bit too much to drink?
It may be best if we--
Yes, right you are...
Now that we're warmed up,
let's go straight for the bottle!
Come, drink up, Onyx!
Don't be shy! Chug, chug, chug!
Though this strategy won't work against
heavyweights, so keep THAT in mind.
It's been so long since I've been able
to enjoy a relaxing spot of tea.
I have Leo to thank for this, too...
I wonder how his meeting is going?
I hope it's all going well.
Perhaps I should go check on them...
No, what if I say something and only make things worse?
And why am I getting all worked up over that hero?!
You're worried 'bout Leo?
Here's my report!
L-Lily?! Y-you didn't hear anything, all right?!
You misheard me! That's right,
I didn't say anything like that at all!
Huh? Say what?
I couldn't kill her with alcohol, but I'm not giving up.
I've got another trick up my sleeve...
Unfortunately, it'll take some time to execute.
I just need to segue into it...
I must say, this food is scrumptious.
Especially the sausage you're now eating,
Your Highness. It's simply to die for.
You've an eye for quality, then?
There's something in this sausage
that makes it truly fantastic.
Tip #2 for making drinking parties less of a headache:
People are fond of those who show
an active interest in them and their tastes.
And when you're eating and drinking together,
you have all the fodder you need.
This sausage is made with spices from Largo.
The minced pepper inside gives it
such a pleasant color, too.
Largo, you say?
We've been hurting for resources so much lately,
I rarely had time to enjoy such extravagant meals.
But thanks to Lily's efforts, things are slowly improving.
I always knew she could handle the task.
Look at that innocent smile.
She looks like a normal girl when she smiles like that.
Of course, I have to give credit to the chefs
who prepared the food so expertly.
You should know that those sausages
were made by yours truly.
The cooks down at the Demon Rat Davern,
the castle dining hall, made absolute slop,
so I shared some key recipes and
trained them on how to make them.
Which leads to Tip #3: if there's food,
learn as much as you can about it beforehand!
And the food topic can lead to any manner
of conversation. It's an excellent segue.
After what Shutina told me, I was curious
about the kind of man you were...
But not only are you great at your job,
you're also a culinary expert!
You're quite the man, Lord Onyx!
Hardly, Your Highness. My talents
and knowledge are all quite modest.
There's just one thing I have to ask.
You seem to always wear that helm of yours.
I know we touched on this before,
but could you explain why?
Yes, you see...
I knew it! Time for Tip #4!
The only time a powerless newbie
can sell themselves to the boss
is when the boss asks them questions!
Your answer can drastically change the flow
of the outing, or your workload the next day!
You see, I've been cursed by the goddess Tiana.
The time I'm allowed to show my face
to others is gravely limited.
As such, I must spend most
of my time encased in armor.
Goodness... And you've been without your helm
this whole time. Will you be all right?
To be frank, I may be cutting it close.
But I'm glad to take that risk if it means
a chance to spend time with Your Highness.
Oh, stop. You're quite the talker, aren't you!
And this is how you get out of a drinking excursion early.
Mention you have a clear-cut time limit,
and you can escape any horrific situation!
Now Echidna knows I'm working with limited time here...
What a great day today has been!
A toast to the friendship between
Black Knight Onyx and Demon Queen Echidna!
Let us drink and talk the night away!
Down that bottle, now!
Drink the night away? Goodness, I'd be delighted...
Absolutely not!
So you want Leo to have to go away?!
Huh?!
Well?! Do you?!
W-well no, but...
General Shutina! Are you there?
Dianette? You sound distressed. Is everything all right?
I have an extremely urgent message for you!
It's been a few hours since
this drinking party from hell began,
and while she hasn't figured out who I am yet,
I still want to get the hell out of here...
Lord Onyx, I'm deeply grateful for all you've done.
Not only did you lessen Shutina's workload
mere moments after you arrived,
but you've also been keeping a watchful eye on Lily.
Your efforts have been of great help to us all.
I arranged this feast to thank you for your hard work.
Echidna...
You're too kind, Your Highness.
Human or demon, we gladly welcome all
who have skills to donate to our cause.
I'm so very glad we have you among
our ranks in the Demon Army!
I see, then...
What of that hero, Leo?
I heard he wanted to join. Would you welcome him, to?
The hero?!
He's the one exception! I don't want him here!
That twisted man, that social reject!
He's the last person I'd want in my army!
If we were foolish enough to let him join,
he'd destroy us from the inside out!
He's right here. Literally right in front of you.
And he's already made things
WAY better for your organization.
I don't care if he does a thousand,
or ten thousand hands' worth of work!
If it wasn't for that blasted hero,
I would've had the Philosopher's Stone by now!
So THAT was what she was after.
It's all because of him! All his fault!
Damn it! Damn it all!
Let's leave her to stew and talk
about this Philosopher's Stone.
The Philosopher's Stone is a treasure
held in the holy city of Renailles.
It's said that the first saint-king
dug it up over 3,000 years ago,
then used its power to found the Capital proper.
Rumors say the Philosopher's Stone turned
the wastelands around the city to green fields,
protected the city's people from plague,
and could even make someone immortal.
Most of these rumors are bogus, of course.
How do I know? Because I've used it before.
The Stone in the Capital isn't the one I used, though.
But the Philosopher's Stone wouldn't
give someone super powers or anything.
It's not a magic power-up or cure-all.
If you looked up "the worst" in the dictionary,
his name would be there in the definition!
And he'd be in the definition for MORON, too!
Wait, she's STILL going?
How much trash does she have to talk about me?!
Do you know how close we were?!
We were so deep into Renailles that
we could see the Stone's sacred hall,
and if we'd gotten the Stone,
we could've accomplished all we came for!
I see...
So the reason you haven't retreated,
despite losing so many men,
is because you're not after conquest,
but the Philosopher's Stone.
That's right!
I was far too aggressive with that war.
I didn't have to fight all of humanity
just to obtain the Philosopher's Stone.
Why not deceive them, or steal it?
Or work with them.
There's a children's tale about human
and demonkind joining forces, isn't there?
"Eibrad, the Joiner of Hands", I believe?
Yes, it's an old human story.
I heard it myself from a succubus storyteller.
It tells of an oddball imp who travels to the human world
and builds a city where humans
and demons live in harmony.
That's right.
But it pales in comparison to our reality.
Human and demon are destined
to be at odds with one another.
The story is just that: a story.
Which only makes me even
more curious about your goals.
What do you plan to do with the Philosopher's Stone?
Ever since her defeat, I've been dying to know...
After being beaten into submission,
losing most of her army and territory,
why hasn't she returned to the Demon World?
If she was after something silly
like immortality or riches,
she would've lost motivation and left long ago.
So why does she still persist? Why is she still here
in this castle, rebuilding her army?
Come.
Wow... What an incredible view.
And it's the most beautiful in this light.
Have you ever been to the Demon World?
I have not.
The Demon World, our home, is a grand, vast wasteland.
It has no sun, no vegetation. The air is heavy,
and the water is muddy and impure.
Demon clans fight one another over
the little resources that remain,
staining the wasteland with blood.
A demonic world indeed.
I am sick of it.
Huh?
I wish to bring order to my world of chaos.
To rid the land of conflict.
To bathe it in the warm sunlight, to cleanse
the waters to sparkle in that light.
I wish for fish to swim in those waters, and
for grasslands and forests to sway in the wind.
That is why I sought the help of Shutina
and other skilled comrades:
To come to the human world and retrieve
the Philosopher's Stone to reforge the land.
I had no idea...
This whole time, she's been fighting humanity
to better the lives of her people...
Surprised to hear these wishes coming
from the Demon Queen's lips?
No.
It's all right. I'm accustomed to this reaction.
I have no quarrel with the humans,
but the Philosopher's Stone will be ours.
If they willingly offered it up, then,
you'd accept it without shedding blood?
Of course, but even if we explained
our good-natured intentions, they wouldn't.
The holy Capital is the center of the human realm.
Stealing the very thing that holds that
city together would hurt their livelihoods.
But that's a sacrifice I'm willing to make.
Those who cooperate with us, like the dragonfolk
and the humans from Lily's home,
will all be given sanctuary in the Demon World,
but I care not what happens to the other humans.
I don't! Not in the slightest!
Still, Your Majesty, you've forbidden
needless killing, have you not?
Yes, this is an invasion, but we must
avoid killing whenever possible!
I hear that policy is why the war ended
with mercifully low casualties on both sides.
And look where that got us: defeat. I curse my naivete.
I simply could not fully become the villain.
Humans may be our enemy,
but they have homes they want to protect, too.
And friends, and family... Considering that,
I simply couldn't do it.
To be honest about the Hero Leo...
I don't bear him any ill will.
Might I ask why?
He is a hero. He exists to protect humanity.
I shouldn't fault him for doing just that:
fighting an invader attacking humanity.
He may have put a stop to my plans,
but he was not wrong to do so.
The fault lay with us, the aggressors in this war.
I see her differently now.
She's kind. A loving Queen who cares for her people.
Yet she became an evil conquerer
to provide for her beloved subjects.
She must have wondered
if she was doing the right thing.
She must have been assailed by anxiety,
unspeakable despair, and ever-present worry.
And then someone brought
about the greatest despair of all.
Me, the Hero Leo.
What about you, Onyx?
Huh?
Why did you join us?
Did humanity betray you?
Do you wish to put an end to this world?
Or have you simply come seeking a place to die?
I wish to hear your motivation.
I...
This is why I hate going out drinking with colleagues.
We were shooting the shit, then suddenly
got into a serious topic where I have to be honest.
It'd be easy to lie,
but she's just opened her heart to me.
If I deceived her further, she'd be even
more upset when I revealed who I was...
No, that wasn't it.
I just don't want to lie to her anymore.
Not as part of any strategy, but because
I genuinely want to support her.
Especially now that I know
she just wants to save her home.
Ah, yes.
Right, I suppose I should tell you.
I'll tell her who I am.
I'll apologize for the deception,
then tell her how much I want to help.
Your Highness, I...
Yes?
No, Echidna, I...
Your Highness!
Your Highness, I finally found you....
What's wrong, Generals?
It's real bad! We got a problem!
H-here...
I'm going on a journey.
Please don't come looking for me.
Shadowless General Mernes.
I have failed to properly train my troops
and will be taking my life to make amends.
Dragon General Edvard.
WHAT?!
Bokura no kokoro wa itsudatte moroi
Sore demo mae o muite nagai michi o susumu
Shiranakatta koto wa kore kara shireba ii
Tsuzukeru koto no saki ni aru mono ima wa mada wakaranai kedo
Hitori de kakaekomi suginaide tama ni wa senaka o azuketemiyou
Yowasa ni yorisoeru no mo tsuyosanara
Madamada saki wa nagai kui no nai you ni
Hashiridase riyuu wa tanjun
Tokihanate risou no yume o
Fumidashita saki no mirai wa jibun shidai de dou ni demo naru
Kawaru koto ga kowakunattemo sukoshizutsu de iinda
Taisetsu na mono o mamoru tame ni
Megurimegutte tsunagatta
Kimi ni arigatou todoiteimasu you ni
Next Time:
If You Want
to Quit
Talk It Out First