Generali!
Are you all right?
Regină Echidna!
Suntem în pericol! Vrăjile mele nu funcționează și am tot avut parte de întâmplări ciudate!
Și eu am avut parte de întâmplări ciudate.
I cannot find anyone in this inn.
Not the innkeep nor her staff.
It's as if they never existed to begin with.
N-no...
I know it's difficult to believe, but it's likely a ghost.
Where are the other three Generals?
Nu te-ai întâlnit cu ei?!
Nu.
Stai, trei?
Lily?! Hei, Lily! Unde ești?!
D-did the ghost take Lily!?
This is growing dire.
Shutina! Leo! We must find our colleagues at once!
Yes, ma'am!
Remember, the Work Trip is First and Foremost a Learning Opportunity (Part 2)
Acest loc chiar e pustiu.
We've definitely searched the whole inn now.
You're right. The only place left would be...
Aici. Sper că toată lumea este bine.
Dacă mi-aș putea folosi vrăjile, aș spulbera toate fantomele din acest loc cu o singură mișcare...
That spell might blow away everything else, too!
Nu pare să fie nimeni aici...
Așa este.
This keeps me safe, this keeps me safe...
Good on you for wearing it.
Queen Echidna!
Are these the only sizes they had for these?
I dunno if it's too tight,
but my head kinda hurts wearing it.
They're one size fits all.
Then why does my head hurt?
I couldn't say.
Besides, the others were wearing it,
and they got spirited away.
But you two are safe! I'm glad you kept them with you.
Echidna, are you...
No, the ghost has me!
Shutina!
H-help!
Echidna?
Now...
There's only one left!
Echidna?
Screw you, 'ghost'! Where'd you take my allies?!
Dammit, get back here!
Show me who you are, you bastard!
What?
Ta-dah.
Hooray, you've been pranked.
Ai fost păcălit!
We totally got him!
REALLY?
Hey, can I swim in here? Is that okay?
No swimming in the bath!
I would've never guessed it was all set up by our Queen!
I knew you were hiding something.
An award-winning performance, if I do say so myself.
T'was my grand plan to prank you with a haunting tale!
Haunting Prank
Or t'was the innkeeps, as she put
that interesting option on the check-in list.
I couldn't have done it without Mernes' help.
There was only so much I could do on my own.
Is that why you FORCED me to help?
Oh yeah, how'd you guys get caught?
I got caught by a trap.
Mernes grabbed me.
When I turned a corner, I fell into a pitfall trap.
I took a nap!
So that's why you're sober.
Yup!
You all had such wonderful reactions.
It was super fun! I really thought
there was a ghost haunting us!
I was quite scared, especially since I couldn't cast magic!
How'd you do that, by the way?
Was it the headbands?
Correct!
They didn't ward off spirits, but they are a type of artifact.
They interfere with waves in the brain
and prevent magic from being cast.
Though they don't appear to work
on individuals who are intoxicated.
Are there any side effects to worry about?
Of course not!
I am your Demon Queen. I wouldn't harm
my underlings for the sake of a prank.
Huh. All right.
I apologize if you were frightened.
I AM a Demon Queen, after all.
This went a little too far for a harmless prank, though.
Really? The man who nearly killed
all of us doesn't want us to 'go too far'?
Besides, this experience will futher strengthen
our team's bonds. Doing that is part of my job.
That's right! You're so cool, Echidna!
I guess I got to see Leo make some good faces.
I don't see any problem with having
a bit of fun like this every now and then!
Cheer up, Leo. The innkeep
has gifted us some fireworks.
Let us enjoy them after our bath.
Ooh, fireworks! I can't wait!
Yay!
So pretty!
Wow!
Mernes, do you have a sparkler?
It's tradition to do a sparkler at the end.
Is this a sparkler? It's my first time,
so I don't know what any of them are called.
Wait, this is your first time? You'll like this one.
Thanks.
Hot, hot!
Ooh, wow!
Why would you think I'd like this?
Huh? It's not to your liking?
Well, Leo?
You haven't traveled for pleasure in quite a while, yes?
It's nice to spend some time with your friends, too.
Yeah.
Gotta end with these!
I really think you'll like these.
It's not bad.