Dimineața începe devreme
la Castelul Reginei Demon.
Ce zi frumoasă.
Perfectă pentru o zi plină de muncă.
Ca angajat temporar trebuie
să arăt de ce sunt în stare,
să mă apuc de treabă înaintea celorlalți...
și să arăt cât sunt de motivat!
Hei, trezirea.
Încă cinci minute...
Soarele a răsărit deja. E rândul tău acum!
Știu că ești obosită, dar ai treabă de făcut!
Am venit ca să te ajut, deci sus cu tine!
Nu vreau să mă ridic...
Vreau doar să lenevesc în pat.
Asta nu e prea bine.
Schimbarea Vocii: Regina Echidna.
Perfect.
Generalule-vrăjitor!
Raportează starea noilor aplicanți!
Sper că nu intenționezi
să-ți faci regina să aștepte!
Îmi parte foarte rău, Înălțimea Voastră!
Avem mai mulți aplicanți decât anticipasem și nu am reușit să-i intervievăm pe toți!
Dar nu va mai dura mult, vă promit!
Deci sesiunea a fost
prelungită, nu? Asta nu e bine.
Oh, no! I'll step in to ensure
they won't be delayed any further!
I'll have the list of interview candidates
by tomorrow--no, by the end of today!
You realize this is why you're not sleeping enough, right?
No, it's all because I've been lacking in my duties!
Știi...
nu poți face totul pe cont propriu.
Da, doamnă!
You should be delegating tasks to people
who work for you, people you trust.
Da, doamnă!
That's part of being a good boss.
Aveți dreptate cu tot ce...
'Neața, Shutina.
Știu că e cam devreme,
dar ai treabă pentru mine?
Suntem atacați cumva?!
Sărăcuța Shutina...
Probabil are un coșmar.
A fost destul de stresată
în ultima perioadă...
Trăiește, trăiește, continuă să trăiești
și să urmezi lumina spre viitor
Renunț să mai fiu erou!
Trădat și abandonat în această lume singuratică,
Temându-mă de ziua de mâine, pe care am scăpat-o din vedere,
Continui să caut locul unde aparțin
Inima mea strigă: „Vreau ca alții să aibă nevoie de mine”
Vreau să deslușesc aceste personalități întortocheate,
dar oare chiar mă pot încrede în ele?
Trăiește, trăiește, continuă să trăiești
și să urmezi lumina spre viitor
Chiar dacă vei pierde totul,
păstrează-ți măcar speranța vie în suflet
Chiar dacă nu știu de ce sunt aici,
sunt în regulă cu asta
Deoarece trebuie să depășesc orice obstacol îmi va ieși în cale,
ca să pot zâmbi alături de tine din nou
Episodul 2: Dă tot ce poți ca să-ți faci viața mai ușoară
Nu-mi vine să cred. Ești incredibil...
I can NOT believe you! Totally unbelievable!
Hei, ce tot mormăi acolo?
De ce te-ai activat așa?
Din cauza ta, evident!
Every! Infinitesimal! Speck!
Of your existence!
The Demon Army was suffering
from a dire lack of personnel.
After my highly-destructive assault on their army,
most of the top brass had returned to
the Demon World to recover from their injuries.
The work they'd left behind had to be handled
by those who remained: the Four Generals.
And nobody knew how to do that work--
no one, save for Shutina.
It's the sort of thing that plagues big companies:
work veterans can handle easily,
but those veterans don't have time to write
a manual or train other people to do those tasks.
Then you have Queen Echidna, who wants
to refortify her army as soon as possible.
And someone just can't help
but overwork themselves to do it.
Even if it means overworking herself to death.
That explains why her Icicle Lance barely packs a punch.
I came here to help with your workload, y'know.
You could be a little nicer to me.
Are you insane?!
Why in the world would I be nice to a man
who barges into my room while I'm sleeping?!
I mean, you're a succubus, aren't you?
Don't say that!
This is your current task list?
Yes, with the highest-priority tasks at the top.
Evaluate applications, reorganize sorcerer corps,
regular maintenance on Queen Echidna's
retainer homunculi, operating cost reduction...
There's like, fifty tasks on here.
Why don't you delegate some of them?
To whom?! I don't have any colleagues or subordinates!
All right, all right.
The last task on this list is...
Replenishing the mana reactors.
What're you looking at?
Let me think here.
A number of castle facilities and instruments
tapped into mana from the reactors.
Only the person who created them
can replenish them with mana.
So any reactors that Shutina created could
only be replenished by Shutina herself.
If anyone with a different mana wavelength tried
to help, the reactor would be destroyed.
But that's where I come in.
What's that smirk for?
From today on, I'm gonna handle
replenishing your mana reactors.
Thank you, that's wonderful.
That task is quite the headache to handle.
You're not going to ask how I'll do it?
You're going to mimic my wavelength
with Harmonize, right? It's common sense.
It's only common sense to sorcerers
as powerful as we are.
So, how many reactors are yours?
Just four.
Not many, considering there are over
a hundred throughout the castle.
They only have to be replenished once every few days.
Got it.
Give me thirty minutes and two hours.
Thirty minutes and two hours and I'll have it done.
I could get it done in less than an hour.
Don't be like that.
I'll promise you this, and stake my honor as a Hero on it.
Promise me what?
I promise to never, ever disappoint you.
In two and a half hours, you'll be all like,
"Oh yay, my workload is gonna be sooo light!
You're amazing, Leo! I love you so much!"
Then you'll jump up and give me a huge kiss!
Fine, go get it done.
That's all you have to say?
It's been fourteen seconds.
All right, I'm going...
Metamorphose!
Wait, I gotta think up a name. Something super cool.
Thirty seconds now.
Oh, one favor, actually!
Could you give me the title "Assistant to the Generals"?
That'll get people to trust me.
Very well.
Thanks.
How's the name Godhart sound to you?
Get a move on already!
...and that's why I've come to you all.
If you notice Shutina acting off at all,
let me know immediately.
Understood.
I wish I could be of help to her...
You shouldn't. Shutina would stress out more if you did.
You're right. Thank you, everyone.
Of course.
I'll help!
Yeah! I got this!
I can do this!
I've returned, milady.
Why are you talking like that?
Milady.
I figured I'd change up my speaking
style to blend in better.
It's only been thirty minutes.
Have a little faith. I took care of it.
I suppose I should give you another task, then...
No, not yet. I'm kinda tired.
What?
It's been a while since I've adjusted
my mana wavelength.
Mirage Eye?
I want to watch you work while I take a little break.
I won't get in your way. I'll sit here quietly.
I've got another task for you when
you're done resting, all right?
Leo, you must be rested by now. I need you to--
Not yet. I need to rest just a little longer.
It's been a while since I've used Metamorphose.
This stuff's pretty bland.
I should see about improving the food around here, too...
It's been an hour! Surely you're more than rested!
No, I need a little more. My mana's still recovering.
You lazy bastard!
Get up this instant!
How are you this heavy?!
Most sorcerers don't realize you can
use Gravity Root to do this!
You've got enough mana to waste on silly spells,
but you still need to 'recover'?!
Decisions, decisions... Do I go with
Lord Godhart or Lord Bloodsword?
Wait, I could go with something totally different:
Black Knight Onyx.
What do you think of that, Shutina?
What's up?
I understand full well now, Hero Leo.
You're a worthless, lazy leech of time and resources!
Whoa, whoa, calm down!
I'm calm.
And after calmly and coolly thinking this over,
I've come to the calm conclusion that
you will not be of use to our army in the slightest!
Dio Neel Zod, spiral of radiant light...
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Fill my hands with your piercing rays of the gods!
Stop! You're going to destroy all your paperwork!
Gae Assail!
Yes!
I'm going to join the Demon Queen's legion.
I have to, for good reason.
And if I want to join, I'll need to show results
and get the Generals on my side.
This, right here, is step one!
Dianette, yes? Good work.
By the look of you, all must have gone well.
Yes, Lord Godhart.
Please, call me Black Knight Onyx.
From now on-- no, FORSOOTH? Henceforth?
Anyway, Black Knight Onyx, understood?
Y-yes, Lord Onyx...
Right then, proceed with your report
on the reactor maintenance.
Yes, milord.
The talisman you granted me
worked without incident, Lord Onyx.
It appears to be durable enough to--
Wait, wait, hold on!
What talisman? What are you talking about?
Le-- Lord Onyx, was it not you
who replenished the reactors?
Oh, uh...
Please, let her finish her report, Sorcerer General.
Go on, then.
Y-yes, milady.
The talisman appears to be
durable enough for continued use,
so with your permission, I would like us to continue
replenishing the reactors in your stead.
Would that be allowed, General Shutina?
But those are reactors that I created.
You'll be able to replenish them?
I'll take it from here.
First, let me explain what exactly I was doing
in those thirty minutes I was gone.
I went to the castle workshop and procured
an amethyst from the goblin goldsmith.
I filled the amethyst with mana tuned to your wavelength.
Amethysts are sturdy stones.
They'll stay attuned to a wavelength indefinitely.
Anyone who holds it on their person
will be attuned to your wavelength as well.
So I created a talisman with the stone,
which only took fifteen minutes.
I left the workshop, then lost five minutes
to an unexpected distraction.
Hey, it's Leo!
Then I took five minutes to find Dianette here.
With my last five minutes, I showed her how
to use the talisman to replenish the reactors.
He told me as long as I'm wearing this talisman,
I can replenish all of your reactors.
After that, I said:
Find a few other people with the
appropriate ability and split the job up.
Yes, milord.
I found three other sorcerers of similar capacity.
We passed the talisman around to refill the reactors.
Excellent.
I trust, then, that all four of you
understand the procedure?
The Sorcerer General is a busy woman.
Form a team of four and assume responsibility
for replenishing her reactors henceforth.
I'll have enough talismans for all of
you within the next three days.
Yes, milord!
You took a bit longer than I'd like for this task,
but it IS your first time.
I expect you to perform it more quickly come tomorrow.
Of course, milord!
That will be all.
Wait, uh, I...
As you can see, the mana reactors
have been replenished.
It is our duty to lessen the burden on your shoulders.
Dianette, here, was worried for your health as well.
She was?
Oh, m-my apologies, but yes.
I know you've been grappling with a mountain
of tasks in recent days, General Shutina.
M-might I be of some assistance, General Shutina?
I'm fine. You focus on your own tasks.
I had neither the courage nor ability to press the matter...
But thanks to Lord Onyx, we'll be able
to assist with the mana reactors!
If there's anything else we can help with,
please don't hesitate to ask!
I-I see. Very well.
I will be sure to reach out to you if there
are tasks you can help with, Dianette.
Yes, milady!
Good work. You are dismissed.
Thank you, milady!
T'would seem you finally understand
my true labors, Sorcerer General.
All you need to do now is let them handle it
and hear their reports.
You'll only have to help out if something goes wrong.
I told you, I only needed two and a half hours,
and now your workload is permanently decreased.
Work isn't something that should be done alone.
Especially not in a large organization where
there are plenty of people who can help.
Instead of having one extremely-skilled
person work extremely hard,
it's best to delegate many
small tasks out to less skilled people.
That's how you should get most of the work done.
In an ideal world, of course.
Why didn't you explain that earlier?
You could have told me you asked Dianette to help.
Because you worry too much.
If I'd told you, you would've rushed off
to "go check on her".
Most of the people in the army are people you
interviewed, people you trust to perform well.
So trust in your judgment,
and in the people working beneath you!
Run the organization so it could still function
if you dropped dead tomorrow.
That's a lot of talk for someone
who insisted on working alone.
I've got a lot of life experience under my belt.
Wait! Wait just a second!
You make a big show of 'teaching'
and 'delegating' to a subordinate,
and while they were hard at work,
you did nothing but loaf about in my office!
You slacker! What's your excuse for that?
You wound me.
I was loafing, yes,
but I was also working.
What?
Here.
I learned a lot about from watching you
and your cleavage work.
I spotted some inefficiencies here and there.
I took the liberty of rearranging
your priorities. Take a look.
Let me see.
Wait, did you say CLEAVAGE?
See those seven tasks I circled in red?
You can delegate those.
But can they handle it?
Teach them HOW to handle it.
That's your job as their boss.
Is this a map of the Largo Sea?
The fish from that area are fantastic.
We could make some scrumptious meals
if we got some delivered,
but considering how dangerous
the shipping route would be...
Leo.
Yes, Sorcerer General Shutina?
I apologize.
I've gravely misjudged you.
C'mon, now.
I just did my job is all.
That only makes it worse.
Despite how harshly I acted
towards you during the interview,
you still pressed on and did an excellent job.
I couldn't well call myself one of the Four Generals
if I didn't thank you for that.
Don't mention it.
If you go down, the whole army goes down with you.
And then I REALLY won't have a place to go anymore.
I was just looking out for myself.
No need to thank me for that.
And here I was giving you a heartfelt apology!
How is anyone supposed to like you?!
Why do you think I was traveling alone for so long?
All right,
better start on my next task.
Call me if you need me.
Before you go...
I'm looking forward to working with you, Leo.
Oh, I forgot!
What is it?
Remember what I said after you gave me this task?
I promised I wouldn't disappoint you,
then I said something after that.
Huh?
In two and a half hours, you'll be all like,
"Oh yay, my workload is gonna be sooo light!
You're amazing, Leo! I love you so much!"
Then you'll jump up and give me a huge kiss!
Fine, go get it done.
I'll take one on the lips, or on the cheek.
We could even climb into the bed and-
Get the hell out of here!
That hurt WAY more than this morning!
Ce este?
Tu mi-ai spus să te chem
dacă am nevoie de tine, nu?
Nu credeam că o vei face așa de curând.
Vezi tu...
Lily va merge mâine în Largo
ca să se ocupe de logistică.
Mâncarea și echipamentul
din castel sunt pe terminate,
deci trebuie să fim siguri că
vom primi următorul transport.
Da, e o problemă serioasă.
Iar asta nu e singura problemă.
Ăsta e planul misiunii pe
care l-am primit de la Lily...
Toată lumea se va distra și va zâmbi!
Pe bune?
Data viitoare
Cu puțină gândire poți spori eficiența