05, interceptează inamicul.
Recepționat. Voi prioritiza salvarea civililor.
Se presupunea că sunt salvatorul lor, și totuși...
nu am fost întâmpinat cu urale, ci cu niște ochi plini de frică și așteptări imense.
Dar nu-mi pasă.
Voi proteja umanitatea.
Doar pentru asta exist.
Voi proteja lumea.
Doar asta se vrea de la mine.
Doar pentru asta trăiesc.
Un coșmar...
Episodul 4: Petrecerea cu băută din iad
Și ce mai coșmar.
Iar acum știu că toată ziua va fi una nasoală...
E venită direct de la regina Echidna: „Cavalerul Onixului Negru trebuie să-mi raporteze imediat.”
Ce? Și-a dat cumva seama cine sunt?!
Ce vei face acum?
Și Lily a fost cât pe ce să-mi dezvălui adevărata identitate, dar am reușit s-o opresc.
Încă nu ai fost să i te prezinți. Poate că e supărată din cauza asta.
O, așa e. Nu am făcut asta încă...
Dar, vezi tu...
I-am spus că treburile noastre merg bine datorită ajutorului lui Onyx...
Cel mai probabil de asta vrea să mă vadă, proasto!
Proastă?! C-Ce altceva ar fi trebuit să-i spun?!
Iar Echidna nu a primit din întâmplare titlul de Regină Demon.
Înarmată cu mult iubita ei sabie, Tilving, poate lupta de la egal la egal cu Edvard
și e la fel de bună la vrăji precum Shutina. E înfricoșător de puternică.
Indiferent ce trucuri aș folosi, ar putea să vadă dincolo de deghizarea mea.
În acest caz, ar trebui să te grăbești la ea.
Și dacă-și dă seama cine ești, cheamă-mă fără ezitare.
Voi fi în regulă. Mă voi descurca pe cont propriu.
Doar să te prefaci că nu ai știut nimic.
Și acum, ce scuză îi voi oferi lui Echidna?
Aici Cavalerul Negru, Onyx.
Am venit la chemarea Înălțimii Voastre.
Intră.
Bun, ia să vedem ce mi-ai pregătit, Regină Demon, Echidna?!
Vă mulțumesc.
Deci tu ești incredibilul Onyx!
Am auzit totul despre faptele tale extraordinare de la Shutina!
Îmi cer scuze că te-am chemat aici atât de din scurt.
Ei bine... Se pare că nu și-a dat seama cine sunt.
Ia un loc, te rog.
Ce? Nu se poate... Cred că-ți bați joc de mine. Cineva să mă scape!
Sunt doar două locuri la acea masă!
Haide să lăsăm formalitățile pentru astăzi
și să ne bucurăm împreună de o masă bogată și o băutură bună!
De fiecare dată când am coșmaruri, știu că ziua următoare va fi una oribilă.
Bei și tu, lord Onyx?
Da, da.
Trebuie să spun, acest lichior e incredibil.
Să nu mai vorbesc de mâncare.
Excelent!
This looks like your typical after-hours drink
with a strait-laced worker and his chill boss.
Of course, it's anything but.
I want to get out of here as quickly as humanly possible,
and I'm terrified she'll find out
who I am in the midst of all this.
Deci, Onyx...
D-Da?
Are you going to wear that helm for much longer?
Would you please take it off?
No, I must insist. It would be rude to show
my bare face before you, Your Highness...
Please, I told you to dispense with formalities.
Și mi-ar plăcea să-ți văd fața în timp ce discutăm!
Ce?!
Oh, ei bine...
Și acum, să vedem ce față barbară se ascunde în spatele acelei măști!
Oh, nu!
Și uite-o!
Stai o secundă...
Nu am avut timp încât să-mi schimb fața prea mult!
E-E ceva în neregulă?
Îmi place expresia ta devotată!
Simt o putere imensă ce se ascunde în spatele chipului tău blând!
E mare păcat să-l ascunzi în spatele unei măști!
A fost cât pe ce! Ce noroc pe mine că s-a îmbătat...
Haide, nu te abține.
Stuff yourself until you burst, by all means!
Beau singur cu șefa mea și dacă va afla cine sunt, s-a zis cu mine.
Cum ar trebui să savurez alcoolul în această situație?!
Mâncarea și băutura sunt divine! Aceasta este raiul pe pământ!
Trebuie să scap cât mai repede cu putință din acest rai.
Dar trebuie să acționez inteligent și calm.
Înălțimea Voastră, paharul vi s-a golit.
Permiteți-mi să vi-l umplu.
Oh, mersi! Cât de atent din partea ta.
Dacă-mi permiteți...
Let me give you a couple tips about how
to make business parties a little easier.
Tip #1: The moment your boss' glass is empty, fill it up.
Please, have some more.
I shall!
You can take a break from the conversation
while filling their cup,
and they'll think you're perceptive and cosiderate.
Here, have another!
I shall!
But that's not the only thing I'm after.
Right now, my goal is simple: get her dead drunk!
That's all I'm focused on!
My, you're thirsty! Come, have another!
I shall!
C'mon, drink! Drink 'til you're sloshed!
Then you can put an end to this horrible event!
Vă simțiți bine, Înălțimea Voastră?
Poate ați băut un pic cam mult?
Cred că ar fi mai bine să...
Da, ai dreptate...
Acum că ne-am încălzit,
să bem direct din sticlă!
Haide, bea, Onyx!
Nu fi timid! Dă-o pe gât!
Though this strategy won't work against
heavyweights, so keep THAT in mind.
It's been so long since I've been able
to enjoy a relaxing spot of tea.
Trebuie să-i mulțumesc și lui Leo pentru asta...
Mă întreb cum merge întâlnirea sa.
Sper că totul e în regulă.
Poate ar trebui să merg și să-i verific...
Mai bine nu, dacă spun ceva greșit și înrăutățesc lucrurile?
And why am I getting all worked up over that hero?!
Îți faci griji pentru Leo?
Uite raportul meu!
L-Lily?! N-Nu ai auzit nimic, nu-i așa?!
Cred că ți s-a părut! Da, nu am spus absolut nimic!
Poftim? Ce tot spui acolo?
Nu am putut s-o dobor cu alcoolul,
dar nu voi renunța acum.
Mai am un as în mânecă...
Din nefericire, va dura
ceva ca să-și facă efectul.
I just need to segue into it..
I must say, this food is scrumptious.
Especially the sausage you're now eating,
Your Highness. It's simply to die for.
You've an eye for quality, then?
There's something in this sausage
that makes it truly fantastic.
Tip #2 for making drinking parties less of a headache:
People are fond of those who show
an active interest in them and their tastes.
And when you're eating and drinking together,
you have all the fodder you need.
This sausage is made with spices from Largo.
The minced pepper inside gives it
such a pleasant color, too.
Largo, you say?
We've been hurting for resources so much lately,
I rarely had time to enjoy such extravagant meals.
But thanks to Lily's efforts, things are slowly improving.
I always knew she could handle the task.
Look at that innocent smile.
She looks like a normal girl when she smiles like that.
Of course, I have to give credit to the chefs
who prepared the food so expertly.
You should know that those sausages
were made by yours truly.
The cooks down at the Demon Rat Davern,
the castle dining hall, made absolute slop,
so I shared some key recipes and
trained them on how to make them.
Which leads to Tip #3: if there's food,
learn as much as you can about it beforehand!
And the food topic can lead to any manner
of conversation. It's an excellent segue.
After what Shutina told me, I was curious
about the kind of man you were...
But not only are you great at your job,
you're also a culinary expert!
You're quite the man, Lord Onyx!
Hardly, Your Highness. My talents
and knowledge are all quite modest.
There's just one thing I have to ask.
You seem to always wear that helm of yours.
I know we touched on this before,
but could you explain why?
Yes, you see...
I knew it! Time for Tip #4!
The only time a powerless newbie
can sell themselves to the boss
is when the boss asks them questions!
Your answer can drastically change the flow
of the outing, or your workload the next day!
You see, I've been cursed by the goddess Tiana.
The time I'm allowed to show my face
to others is gravely limited.
As such, I must spend most
of my time encased in armor.
Goodness... And you've been without your helm
this whole time. Will you be all right?
To be frank, I may be cutting it close.
But I'm glad to take that risk if it means
a chance to spend time with Your Highness.
Oh, stop. You're quite the talker, aren't you!
And this is how you get out of a drinking excursion early.
Mention you have a clear-cut time limit,
and you can escape any horrific situation!
Now Echidna knows I'm working with limited time here...
What a great day today has been!
A toast to the friendship between
Black Knight Onyx and Demon Queen Echidna!
Let us drink and talk the night away!
Down that bottle, now!
Drink the night away? Goodness, I'd be delighted...
Absolutely not!
So you want Leo to have to go away?!
Huh?!
Well?! Do you?!
W-well no, but...
General Shutina! Are you there?
Dianette? You sound distressed. Is everything all right?
I have an extremely urgent message for you!
It's been a few hours since
this drinking party from hell began,
and while she hasn't figured out who I am yet,
I still want to get the hell out of here...
Lord Onyx, I'm deeply grateful for all you've done.
Not only did you lessen Shutina's workload
mere moments after you arrived,
but you've also been keeping a watchful eye on Lily.
Your efforts have been of great help to us all.
I arranged this feast to thank you for your hard work.
Echidna...
Sunteți mult prea amabilă,
Înălțimea Voastră.
Human or demon, we gladly welcome all
who have skills to donate to our cause.
I'm so very glad we have you among
our ranks in the Demon Army!
I see, then...
What of that hero, Leo?
I heard he wanted to join. Would you welcome him, to?
The hero?!
He's the one exception! I don't want him here!
That twisted man, that social reject!
He's the last person I'd want in my army!
If we were foolish enough to let him join,
he'd destroy us from the inside out!
He's right here. Literally right in front of you.
And he's already made things
WAY better for your organization.
I don't care if he does a thousand,
or ten thousand hands' worth of work!
If it wasn't for that blasted hero,
I would've had the Philosopher's Stone by now!
So THAT was what she was after.
It's all because of him! All his fault!
Damn it! Damn it all!
Let's leave her to stew and talk
about this Philosopher's Stone.
The Philosopher's Stone is a treasure
held in the holy city of Renailles.
It's said that the first saint-king
dug it up over 3,000 years ago,
then used its power to found the Capital proper.
Rumors say the Philosopher's Stone turned
the wastelands around the city to green fields,
protected the city's people from plague,
and could even make someone immortal.
Most of these rumors are bogus, of course.
How do I know? Because I've used it before.
The Stone in the Capital isn't the one I used, though.
But the Philosopher's Stone wouldn't
give someone super powers or anything.
It's not a magic power-up or cure-all.
If you looked up "the worst" in the dictionary,
his name would be there in the definition!
And he'd be in the definition for MORON, too!
Wait, she's STILL going?
How much trash does she have to talk about me?!
Do you know how close we were?!
We were so deep into Renailles that
we could see the Stone's sacred hall,
and if we'd gotten the Stone,
we could've accomplished all we came for!
I see...
So the reason you haven't retreated,
despite losing so many men,
is because you're not after conquest,
but the Philosopher's Stone.
That's right!
I was far too aggressive with that war.
I didn't have to fight all of humanity
just to obtain the Philosopher's Stone.
Why not deceive them, or steal it?
Or work with them.
There's a children's tale about human
and demonkind joining forces, isn't there?
"Eibrad, the Joiner of Hands", I believe?
Yes, it's an old human story.
I heard it myself from a succubus storyteller.
It tells of an oddball imp who travels to the human world
and builds a city where humans
and demons live in harmony.
That's right.
But it pales in comparison to our reality.
Human and demon are destined
to be at odds with one another.
The story is just that: a story.
Which only makes me even
more curious about your goals.
What do you plan to do with the Philosopher's Stone?
Ever since her defeat, I've been dying to know...
After being beaten into submission,
losing most of her army and territory,
why hasn't she returned to the Demon World?
If she was after something silly
like immortality or riches,
she would've lost motivation and left long ago.
So why does she still persist? Why is she still here
in this castle, rebuilding her army?
Come.
Wow... What an incredible view.
And it's the most beautiful in this light.
Have you ever been to the Demon World?
I have not.
The Demon World, our home, is a grand, vast wasteland.
It has no sun, no vegetation. The air is heavy,
and the water is muddy and impure.
Demon clans fight one another over
the little resources that remain,
staining the wasteland with blood.
A demonic world indeed.
I am sick of it.
Huh?
I wish to bring order to my world of chaos.
To rid the land of conflict.
To bathe it in the warm sunlight, to cleanse
the waters to sparkle in that light.
I wish for fish to swim in those waters, and
for grasslands and forests to sway in the wind.
That is why I sought the help of Shutina
and other skilled comrades:
To come to the human world and retrieve
the Philosopher's Stone to reforge the land.
I had no idea...
This whole time, she's been fighting humanity
to better the lives of her people...
Surprised to hear these wishes coming
from the Demon Queen's lips?
No.
It's all right. I'm accustomed to this reaction.
I have no quarrel with the humans,
but the Philosopher's Stone will be ours.
If they willingly offered it up, then,
you'd accept it without shedding blood?
Of course, but even if we explained
our good-natured intentions, they wouldn't.
The holy Capital is the center of the human realm.
Stealing the very thing that holds that
city together would hurt their livelihoods.
But that's a sacrifice I'm willing to make.
Those who cooperate with us, like the dragonfolk
and the humans from Lily's home,
will all be given sanctuary in the Demon World,
but I care not what happens to the other humans.
I don't! Not in the slightest!
Still, Your Majesty, you've forbidden
needless killing, have you not?
Yes, this is an invasion, but we must
avoid killing whenever possible!
I hear that policy is why the war ended
with mercifully low casualties on both sides.
And look where that got us: defeat. I curse my naivete.
I simply could not fully become the villain.
Humans may be our enemy,
but they have homes they want to protect, too.
And friends, and family... Considering that,
I simply couldn't do it.
To be honest about the Hero Leo...
I don't bear him any ill will.
Might I ask why?
He is a hero. He exists to protect humanity.
I shouldn't fault him for doing just that:
fighting an invader attacking humanity.
He may have put a stop to my plans,
but he was not wrong to do so.
The fault lay with us, the aggressors in this war.
I see her differently now.
She's kind. A loving Queen who cares for her people.
Yet she became an evil conquerer
to provide for her beloved subjects.
She must have wondered
if she was doing the right thing.
She must have been assailed by anxiety,
unspeakable despair, and ever-present worry.
And then someone brought
about the greatest despair of all.
Me, the Hero Leo.
What about you, Onyx?
Huh?
Why did you join us?
Did humanity betray you?
Do you wish to put an end to this world?
Or have you simply come seeking a place to die?
I wish to hear your motivation.
I...
This is why I hate going out drinking with colleagues.
We were shooting the shit, then suddenly
got into a serious topic where I have to be honest.
It'd be easy to lie,
but she's just opened her heart to me.
If I deceived her further, she'd be even
more upset when I revealed who I was...
No, that wasn't it.
I just don't want to lie to her anymore.
Not as part of any strategy, but because
I genuinely want to support her.
Especially now that I know
she just wants to save her home.
Ah, yes.
Right, I suppose I should tell you.
Îi voi spune cine sunt.
Îmi voi cere scuze că m-am dat altcineva și îi voi spune cât de mult vreau să ajut.
Înălțimea Voastră, eu...
Ce este?
Nu, Echidna, eu...
Your Highness!
Your Highness, I finally found you....
What's wrong, Generals?
It's real bad! We got a problem!
P-Poftim...
I'm going on a journey.
Please don't come looking for me.
Shadowless General Mernes.
I have failed to properly train my troops
and will be taking my life to make amends.
Generalul-dragon Edvard.
Ce?!
Data viitoare
Dacă vrei să renunți, vorbește, mai întâi