Remember, the Work Trip is First and Foremost a Learning Opportunity (Part 1)
Ura! Vacanță, vacanță!
Lily, nu suntem aici ca să ne distrăm.
Asta e o oportunitate de învățare pentru noi toți.
Oh, te rog. Nu vom învăța nimic în timp ce ne distrăm.
Ești angajatul nostru de o lună. De unde știi că se va întâmpla una ca asta?
Am fost în multe călătorii de „oportunitate de învățare prin muncă”
și toate au sfârșit prin a deveni vacanțe.
Nu va fi cu nimic diferit nici de această dată.
De asta te-am angajat, Leo. Experiența ta este neprețuită.
Dar oare mai poți afirma acest lucru după ce vezi asta?
E o dărăpănătură!
Doamne.
Îmi place acest loc! Are un caracter aparte!
Mernes, tu ai ales acest loc, nu-i așa?
Da. Are patru pereți, un acoperiș și e pustiu. E locul perfect.
Așa alegi tu locul unde te cazezi?
Nu văd nimic în neregulă cu asta.
Dacă oamenii ar afla că liderii Armatei Demonilor s-au adunat aici, s-ar panica.
E important să rămânem discreți pe toată durata călătoriei.
Asta are sens. Nimeni nu va știi cine suntem la acest han pustiu.
În plus, i-am spus lui Shutina să ne facă rezervarea sub nume false.
Ți-am spus, nu-i așa?
Bun-venit, mari lideri ai Armatei Demonilor!
Și s-a zis și cu acoperirea noastră!
Îmi pare foarte rău!
Doamne!
Oh, haide, e în reuglă!
Mulțumim că ne-ați primit!
Ne bucurăm să vă avem drept oaspeți.
Avem un izvor termal în aer liber pe care vi-l recomandăm cu căldură să-l încercați.
O baie în aer liber! Asta sună grozav.
Nu avem izvoare termale la castel.
Cred că mi-ar prinde bine o baie caldă lângă o bere rece.
Hei, ce este un „izvor termal”? Este asemănător cu o baie?
Da, dar mult mai mare.
Pot înota în el?
Nu.
De ce nu?! Vreau să înot!
Haideți să ne concentrăm.
Suntem aici pentru muncă, nu-i așa?
Poate un reprezentant al grupului să semneze aici?
Desigur.
Perfect. Mulțumesc.
Nicio problemă.
Excuse me.
Am să vă informez că s-ar putea să întâlniți niște vizitatori nedoriți pe timpul șederii voastre.
Poftim? Ce vreți să spuneți?
Fantome.
Ce?!
F-Fantome?!
Sunt sigură că zvonurile sunt doar rezultatul unei neînțelegeri,
dar există celalaltă posibilitate, deci vă rog să țineți minte.
Oh, nu! Oare vom fi în regulă? Putem lupta cu fantomele?!
N-Nu știu...
Fantomele nu sunt reale. E doar o superstiție.
D-Da! Și în cazul în care vom da peste una, o voi distruge cu vrăjile mele!
Nu-ți face griji, Lily!
Oh, bine! Mă simt mult mai bine acum!
Ar fi fost bine dacă era doar o superstiție...
Delicios! Mâncarea e așa de bună.
The food and amenities are wonderful, too.
Ai făcut o treabă bună găsind acest loc, Mernes.
Mersi.
We still haven't done anything work-related, though.
Isn't this a learning opportunity?
We spent an hour discussing work!
That is more than enough for today.
Oh, haideți! Asta e 100% o vacanță!
Cease your prattling! We are Army leaders on
a journey, not a vacation. My goodness.
Regină Echidna?
I am going for a walk, and to purchase some snacks.
Ar trebui să vă însoțesc?
Da, dacă vei da peste o fantomă?
Nu se va întâmpla una ca asta.
Oh, da, am uitat să vă dau ceva.
Deținătoarea hanului ne-a dat aceste amulete protectoare. Luați fiecare câte una.
Amulete?
Astea.
Cred că glumești!
She says they are ghost-dispelling charms that
have been passed down here for generations.
Amulete care alungă fantomele... Ești sigură de asta?
I am. We wouldn't want to be attacked by spirits, after all.
Asigurați-vă că le aveți la voi mereu.
Bine!
Am înțeles.
Priviți, am patru urechi!
Așa se pare.
These things dispel ghosts? Come on. I'm gonna pass.
Ah, I see, you're going to pass, are you?
Then I suppose we should have
another private drinking party, you and I!
Seeing as we seemingly need to strengthen our--
I'll wear them with pride, Your Highness!
Haideți, puneți-le pe cap!
E ordinul reginei noastre!
Și noi trebuie să le purtăm?
They will look flattering on the women, but can you say
the same for us men?
Orders from the boss!
Keep your head down and obey, Edvard.
This is harassment.
Cu toții arătați grozav!
On that note...
With these, I will be fine to move about on my own.
Do not remove the charms, now, yes?
Okay!
Yes, ma'am.
Echidna's been gone a while.
Pass.
You think she blacked out somewhere?
Surely you jest. Echidna's tolerance
for liquor is that of a bottomless pit.
Why're there three of you, Leo?
Meanwhile, this one's punch-drunk on catnip juice.
Catnip does have that affect on canines.
Pass.
I'm gonna go check on her.
Don't ditch 'cause you're losing!
I'm not. I just won.
Will you be all right on your own?
There are no ghosts here.
Shutina... Are you afraid of ghosts?
O-of course not! I'm just being careful in
the one in a million chance there's danger!
Uh-huh. I'll be back.
I'm getting pretty tired of playing Tycoon,
so let's take a break.
How about another drink then, Leo?
You still have it in you, yes?
You've been doing nothing BUT drinking this whole time.
Well, of course! This is a special occasion,
why not share it with good friends and drink?
Tonight, we shall drink until we are sated!
Don't drink too much, now.
What's wrong?
Nothing, just... That.
Leo?
Did it move?
O-of course not! You must be seeing things!
Who's there? Echidna? Mernes?
I'm going to take a look.
Queen Echidna and Mernes have both been absent for a
while.
I must assure their safety.
No, you can't! Acting without permission
will destroy the chain of command!
It's tough to figure out what to do
when your boss isn't around.
Hello! Anyone here?
I know not your intentions,
but you should not play pranks on--
Edvard! Huh?
Hey! Stop messing around and open up!
That's right! You're not the type to joke around...
Th-the light!
There's no such thing as ghosts!
I'm sure there's a logical expl...
What was that?!
Ow! What is this?! What is going on?
Ugh! Where is it coming from?!
Shutina, over here!
What's that? Is THAT... a ghost?
Whoa.
That's a rotary phone.
An artifact from the Mechanical Age.
Humans used these before I was born.
What's it doing here?
Allow me to silence it.
Enis la fide sol...
O wind, bring forth utter quiet!
Silence!
Huh?
Yo.
S-silence!
Silence!
O wind, bring forth utter quiet!
Utter quiet!
Now YOU need to be quiet!
Leo, my spell isn't working! What do we do now?!
Fine, I'll try. Silence.
Huh?
Leo! Do something, please!
Can both of you shut up?!
You try, Lily!
It's a ghost!
Look, Lily, listen close. Ghosts aren't real.
They're just superstition.
No, we have plenty of proof.
This was the work of a spirit.
C'mon!
When I was young, we read
a tome about ghosts and spirits.
Ghosts are the strongest human monster.
You can't see them and magic doesn't
work on them. They're invincible.
Ghosts may exist even in the Demon World!
We might be in trouble, Echidna!
What if one of these things attacks us?!
Not to worry! If spells don't work,
then we shall punch it to death!
But how do we punch something we can't see?
It's all right, Shutina.
Ghosts are formidable enemies,
but I will protect you from them!
Echidna...
You see?! We'll be all right.
A ghost may be among us,
but Queen Echidna will keep us safe!
Help us, Echidna!
Why'd you make things more complicated,
you bumbling idiot succubus!
Excuse me?!
Yeah, I said it! You're an adult,
it's your job to calm Lily down!
Generals!
Are you all right?
Queen Echidna!
We're in danger! My spells aren't working,
and strange things keep happening!
I've encountered strange happenings as well.
I cannot find anyone in this inn.
Not the innkeep nor her staff.
It's as if they never existed to begin with.
N-no...
I know it's dififcult to believe, but it's likely a ghost.
Where are the other three Generals?
You didn't run into them?!
No.
That's weird. Mernes and Edvard
went out looking for you.
Wait, three?
Lily?! Hey, Lily! Where'd you go?!
D-did the ghost take Lily!?
This is growing dire.
Shutina! Leo! We must find our colleagues at once!
Yes, ma'am!
Va urma