Sold Out
Completion.
Farewell.
Hello!
Report.
I won.
I'd like you to book my next opponent now.
You're quite greedy, Hanna-chan.
But what is this all about?
Unexpected.
A minor accident occurred.
You can't see the depths of the darkness.
If you step into it, you'll just be swallowed up.
WIXOSS  Darkness  Truth
The Darkness of WIXOSS
Was it Mayu?
Mayu...
Adevăr / Sfârșit și început
The truth about the Selector battles?
Confusion. The more research I do,
the more shady rumors and
urban legends I encounter.
But as I followed what little light there was,
I discovered a certain name.
A name?
Morikawa!
Shirai-kun.
Morikawa...
I'm in a hurry.
Are you going to see Satomi?
And if I am?
Don't go!
Stay away from that guy.
Let me go.
Morikawa...
Here.
Oh, Shirai Shouhei-kun?
Huh?
June 17
This is dated yesterday...
I forgot it.
Put it away.
Okay.
Do you have some kind of special
relationship with Shirai-kun?
Of course not.
Hello.
You're a Selector, right?
Have you ever heard of the bookmaker?
That's a bad idea.
You...
What?
It's nothing.
Go.
What are you thinking?
You're just being used.
Do you understand that?
I don't need your help!
I see.
You know, and you're still doing it.
Why?
It's not your problem.
What you said was right.
Aren't you the one tying yourself down?
I decided to stop tying myself
down, and to live freely.
Really?
It doesn't look like it.
Want to try me?
Very well.
Open.
She only needs one more win?
Piruluk, grow.
And summon Shouryuu, then turn end.
Meru, grow.
Summon Muffin and Meishiro.
Full attack.
Meru, attack!
Guard.
Turn end.
You won't use your coin, Chi-chan?
It's better not to have a plan.
Her ability lets her know what I'm going to do.
Piruluk, grow.
Turn end.
She's not attacking?
Or using her coin.
What is she thinking?
Meru, grow.
Place SIGNI and do a full attack.
She's not even defending?
Morikawa Chinatsu-san.
I'll tell you about this twisted world,
and what the Selector battles are.
What the LRIGs are.
Mayu?
Uncertain.
I don't know if that's her real name.
But her emotions are what created
the Selector battles.
The girls who met LRIGs became Selectors
and battled to make their wishes come true.
Several of them won and received the
right to have their wishes granted.
They became "Eternal Girls."
Many girls dreamed of their wishes coming true
and were turned into LRIGs.
I am one of them.
I wanted to save my friend.
I kept battling to have my wish granted.
I won and won and...
I became an Eternal Girl.
I became an LRIG.
But I was fine with that.
As long as my friend was okay,
as long as she'd open her eyes again...
I didn't care what happened to me.
But...
Rest in peace, okay?
I swore revenge.
I had to fight.
I had to turn a Selector into an Eternal Girl
and return to my world.
If I fought someone, I crushed
them without mercy.
If my Selector lost, I would abandon them
and move on to the next.
To me, Selectors were just tools.
Useless.
Many Selector wishes,
and many Selectors,
perished at my hands.
Inexplicable.
The reason is unknown,
but those Selector battles suddenly
stopped without warning.
Stopped?
Of course, they didn't completely end.
After some time, a new Selector battle began.
And many, including us, were caught up in it.
Narumi-san's sister was one of them, right?
Point of interest.
The rules and system of
the new Selector battles differ
from the old ones in several ways.
The time limit of ninety days.
The fact that Selector memories become
coins they bet in battles.
You're right.
But the reason is unknown.
So in the end, the true nature
of the darkness is a mystery?
That's right.
But I have no intention of stopping.
Hanna-chan...
The battles ended, and my daily life resumed.
But the lost feelings of all those
girls would never return.
Instead of disappearing, their feelings
took on a will of their own,
and a new game began.
There is no exit in the Selector Battles.
Only an unending chain of hatred and pain.
The man named Satomi knows this.
He enjoys controlling the hearts of others.
Are you going to be his slave?
I know you really—
Shut up.
It doesn't matter how the game started.
It doesn't matter what anyone else thinks.
I'm fighting the battles for myself!
Remove all SIGNI.
Turn end.
What are you thinking?
It's your turn.
Meru, attack!
Why?
Why did you deliberately lose?
I still have something I need to do.
I can't leave the battles now.
What's your reason for fighting?
Hello?
It's me, Satomi!
Thanks for the contract.
So, I have a battle for you.
I'll send you a text with the time and place.
Oh, I'm sure you know this,
but you can't refuse.
Shou-chan, are you sure?
I'm going to bring back Morikawa.
Incoming Call
Answer      End
Call Ended
Now to send that to Shirai-kun...
Oh?
You're already done?
I was interrupted.
Interrupted?
Well, it happens!
I want to ask you something.
What?
Do you know about the first Selector battles?
Oh...
The rumor that the despair of
girls who lost their dreams
causes the battles to continue?
It's such an appealing story, isn't it?
Despair creates despair,
and soon, despair is everywhere.
And it all squelches together
into one ugly mess,
and swallows up this garbage town!
The trash gets kicked down, and then
climbs back out of the dump.
And only the truly strong can survive.
You want to be strong, don't you, Chinatsu-chan?
I'll become strong!
Stronger than anyone, right?
One more...
Coin bet!
Escape.
A-Attack!
It's our turn, Shou-chan!
Donor, grow!
Attack with Karaten and Nurari!
Just what are the Selector battles?
Did you know about the last
Selector battles, Riru?
All I know is that I fight battles
with the Selectors.
I see.
What are you thinking of?
If I fight and take back all my memories...
Is that really the end of everything?
Chi-chan?
What?
You're not going to ask anything?
I'm not going to stop being a Selector.
That's not an answer.
Don't worry.
We're together. Always.
I'll end with an attack.
Guard.
Advice.
With those cards in your hand,
you could take the attack
and build your Ener.
Oh, right!
Satomi Kou
It's time
I have a battle ready for you!
Parting.
I'm sorry it's so sudden, Suzuko-san,
but my battle class is over.
Huh?
I got a message that a battle is ready for me.
I'm about to win one final battle,
and end my time as a Selector.
I guarantee that your skill is
every bit as strong as mine now.
Goodbye.
Hanna-chan!
Um...
Can I go with you?
I want to see your last battle.
I fought a battle yesterday.
I won, but I felt awful.
There's something wrong with these battles!
I don't want you to—
Give it up!
You're in my way.
What, two of you?
Which am I fighting?
Um...
Me.
She's a friend.
Hanna-chan...
I don't care which of you it is.
Open!
Hanna-chan...
Morikawa Chinatsu
Chinatsu-chan, is something wrong?
I'm not feeling well.
Roger that. Take care.
Morikawa Chinatsu
That's a little strange.
Think she's uncertain?
She's spent too much time around
your poisonous aura.
That's bad.
I need her to grow up just a bit more.
Why not have that cute boy help?
Carnival,
you really are a wonderful lady!
My reason for fighting...
Chi-chan...
Chi-chan!
Oh, it's been a while.
You...
You're that Selector.
No, I'm her LRIG.
She disappeared.
I ended up with control of her body,
and I tried living as a human.
I lived in her home, walked
the streets of her town...
I just woke up, ate, used
the bathroom, and slept.
And then I did it all again.
No stimulation at all.
Just an eternity of dead days.
What are you sayi—
Living is an act filled with boredom and pain.
I'm done.
Goodbye.
What happened?
Did someone jump down?
There is no exit in the Selector battles.
Only an unending chain of hatred and pain.
Coin bet!
Blind.
Again...
Damn it! Attack! Attack! Attack!
Turn end!
Oh, my, too bad.
She missed.
Now it's our turn, Hanna-sama.
Roger.
Summon Oigona, Influ, Parainflu.
Activate effects!
Check.
One more attack, and you win.
Hanna-chan...
Hanna wins.
Come, Hanna-sama, your orders.
ARTS, Never End.
Congratulations!
The days I spent battling with you
were very fun, Hanna-sama.
Anonymous-chan...
This is goodbye, Hanna-sama.
I will return the memories I've borrowed.
Do you have a wish?
Hope.
I desire the memories of the
day my brother died.
Understood.
Then...
Yuuto, let's play hide-and-seek over there!
Okay.
Wait, Yuuto!
Hanna-chan, hurry, hurry!
Ready?
Not yet!
Yuuto, where are you?
Yuuto?
I give up!
Come out!
Let's go home! Yuuto!
Yuuto?
Did he go home?
Hurry, hurry!
Wait!
No!
Hanna!
Yuuto is...
Yuuto...
No...
I...
It's... my fault?
I've waited so long for this day.
I couldn't wait to see the look on your face
when you remembered everything!
Your face, twisted with despair...
It's wonderful.
Farewell, Hanna-sama.
Hanna-chan?
I...
Let's have a battle, right now.
Let's have fun, boy.
I couldn't do anything.
This will be the last.
What do I do?
I didn't think the battles were...
Okay, let's get started.
I'll stop it.
Next time: Devouring Prey / Tragedy and Comedy.
Devorarea prăzii / Tragedie și comedie