This is Lecty Eisenach.
Um, our team, Fireteam E601,
got a new instructor, and um...
Huh? Out of time?
So um, the instructor was...
A pervert!
That part?
Potențialul celor slabi
Here's today's special training.
As you know, special training is tough.
Becoming stronger isn't easy.
You may be disappointed, but this goddess has no intention of joining you.
You all can do as you like.
Hey Rico, wait!
It's okay, leave her alone.
But!
The question is, are you two really ready for special training?
Of course I am!
M-Me too!
That's the spirit.
Um, Kanata-san?
I'm done changing...
P-Please don't stare!
Why not?
You look good.
T-That's not the point...
Should we really be wasting our fireteam budget on something like this...?
Check this out! It's so cute!
If it's something important to us...
It looks great on you!
Then why not?
Important?
Here.
Your training for the day is to hand out fliers in that outfit.
What?!
Hm? I didn't tell you?
N-No you didn't!
What should we get for lunch?
I wonder what they're serving today!
Um...
Um, uh...
What is it?
Do you know her?
I, uh...
No.
Me neither.
I've never seen her before.
She's kind of weird.
I know, right?
What's with the outfit anyway?
What now?
Are you hungry?
Too funny!
Yes, I'm dying of hunger.
It's a maid outfit.
It is a maid outfit.
It's a maid outfit, yes.
Wow!
This is from way back in the continental era, yes!
The maid outfit, a maiden's most noble attire!
Huh? What's this?
Oh! Um, if, if, if...
If-if-if?
If you like, please take this!
Huh?
Ooh! It's got discount coupons!
We were just thinking about lunch.
Thanks, Maid-san.
I did it!
Hey, go find Rico's weakness.
Huh?!
Everybody has a weakness or two.
Rico might be trying to act cool,
but she could have a surprising weakness.
H-Hey, you!
I might not be on good terms with Rico,
but I don't want to stoop so low as to...
Shh!
There's our mark.
Y-You're touching me.
Oh, sorry, I didn't notice.
What do you mean you didn't notice?!
Are you saying they're too small to be detected?!
Anyway, look.
Go on!
Hmph!
What are you doing?
How did you know?!
Do you have super powers or something?!
Oh...
Did you fall in love with my divine retreating figure?
Um, this is uh, um...
Oh, spare the story.
You must have been bored.
S-Something like that, yeah.
Unfortunately, I have to do some shopping.
H-Hey Rico, can I go shopping with you?
Hey, cut it out!
I was worried someone might be casting an illusory spell.
Why are you suddenly taking interest in my activities?
Fine.
Follow me.
R-Right!
Oh, did you finish already?
Y-Yes!
I was really nervous at first,
but after the first one, I got some courage...
Okay, step two then.
Huh?
This place is looking for part-time staff.
Good luck.
I-I-I... I can't do that...
Excuse me!
Could you take my order?
Could you bring more water?
Order over here too, please.
Hey, maid girl!
Take this to table three!
I-I can't...
Kanata-san!
Of the known species of Devil Beetles,
the Archenar class is the most numerous...
Oh, I'm so sorry!
Oh no!
I'm so sorry...
Oh, what should I do...?
I'm sorry...
This won't come off...
I'm sorry, this might leave a stain...
Oh, I'm sorry!
I can handle this myself.
Yuri!
I'm fine.
Please, go on.
I'm so sorry.
Yuri, huh...?
Oh...
Welcome.
Credit card please.
Yes.
A philosophy book?
You actually buy those? Seems boring.
You do not yet understand the fun of pursuing truth.
You are still a child.
Sorry for being a child.
Let's go.
Next store.
You're still not done?!
This is, how shall I say, quite lovely...
I didn't know you like cute things.
I will excuse myself now!
Huh?
Time is precious.
We must be efficient in its use,
or we will run out before we know it.
Hmm...
Liking cute things isn't a weakness, is it?
Um, I uh, repeat your order...
Huh? What now?
I, re... re-re-re...
You really wanna kiss me?
Cut it out!
That's Kanata's...
I can't do this, Kanata-san...
Lecty?
What are you doing here?
Misora-san!
Are you better now?
Y-Yes...
How is this a special training?
Huh? Was your training more normal?
Huh? Well, more than yours, I guess.
Okay...
If I can help, don't hesitate, okay?
Really?!
What's going on?
What is it?
That's cute!
So cute!
So this is it, huh...?
Kanata-san only got these two outfits...
What is that pervert thinking?!
Sorry, can you take our order?
Oh, coming!
Oh...
Hi, welcome!
I'll have an iced tea to start.
One iced tea, okay.
What do you want?
I'll have iced coffee.
And one iced coffee, okay.
Excuse me, can I have some water?
Y-Yes!
Is talking to people difficult for you?
Huh?
Oh, I'm sorry...
If you find something difficult, in a sense,
that's the same as your weakness.
Don't worry.
Trust your instructor.
Trust...?
Besides, you have a great friend that you can follow as an example.
Here is your iced tea and hot dog combo.
Can I have the bunny too?
The bunny is not for sale!
Here is your curry rice meal.
Coming right up!
Hey, Usagi-chan!
I'll be right with you!
Number seven is up!
Understood!
Thanks for waiting, here is your pasta set.
Oh, one more coffee, please.
Sure! Thank you!
Wow... She's working so hard.
T-Thank you! I feel...
Can I have more coffee, please?
Oh, uh, um...
Start nice and loud, like Misora...
Yes, coming right up!
The meeting with the head supervisor of the academy is tomorrow...
Oh, division lead.
What's going on?
H-Hello, welcome.
A-Are you ready to order?
Here's your lunch combo A!
Excuse me?
Coming!
Can I have pudding with my pasta meal?
Yes, thank you.
Iced tea and iced coffee!
Sorry, are you coming?
I'll be right with you!
Um, can you take this?
And one more lunch combo B, please.
Gotcha.
Here's your spaghetti napolitan, with iced coffee!
Table eight, beef stroganoff, coming up!
What happened, Lecty?
You look energised.
It's thanks to you.
Me?
I don't get it, but keep it up.
Yes!
Isn't that the maid girl who was passing out the fliers?
The bunny girl is awesome too!
I see... Let's see what the traitor is planning.
Hey, what kind of training was that?!
Come on, Lecty, complain!
Uh, um...
Hmm?
Kanata, I...
Did you know I have social anxiety?
Huh?
Lecty, your sword style, it's the Eisenach Style Magic Twin Sword Art, right?
Created by the sword master, Albert Eisenach?
You know about my family?
Only those who have gone through rigorous training and
proven themselves with real skill can use the Eisenach name.
When we played tag yesterday, if you had kept your eyes on me,
it would have been a pretty good fight.
But you couldn't see me eye to eye,
so you couldn't show your true skills.
I... I've never been able to make eye contact,
or go to places where lots of people see me,
without getting very nervous and not being able to do anything right.
I hate myself for being that way...
But it gets worse when I think like that...
Don't worry about it.
Nobody in the world is completely satisfied with him or herself.
Now you know what you need to fix.
The rest is easy, just try your best to fix it.
Okay!
You did well, Lecty.
You're tickling me, Misora-san... But, thank you.
Huh? I didn't do anything...
No, I was able to try harder because you were there.
So, Misora?
How did you do?
I have to admit I failed.
I couldn't find a weakness.
I was surprised, though.
She reads difficult philosophy books and stuff, but also likes cute things.
Good, you've made progress.
Huh?
Thank you.
Hey, I told you, I failed!
Hello.
Two of those, please.
You two worked hard today, so here's your reward.
This is great.
Really?
Oh, you're right!
You're not listening!
I didn't know anything about Rico, let alone her weakness.
I didn't know Lecty had stage fright.
I fail as fireteam leader...
You learned that you have much to learn.
Isn't that progress?
Lecty, keep it up. Keep training like you did today.
U-Understood!
I'll follow Rico more then!
Huh?
Your exercise today was to clarify what your weakness was.
Overcoming that weakness needs a completely different workout.
Huh?
Oh, I didn't tell you?
N-No you didn't!
You can't just float in here like that.
This is the men's dorm, you know.
Where's the harm?
It's just like old times, right?
Hey, is this the girl in the bunny suit?
Her magic power reserves are higher than most A-rankers.
But she's so bad with the sword, it totally wastes her potential.
So, master instructor, what do you have planned for her?
What did you just say?
You're switching from vanguard magic cannon sword to middle guard Magic Cannon.
You have zero talent in sword arts,
but your flight magic and total magic power reserves are impressive.
I decided to make the best use of your talents.
I can't do that, no matter what.
Even if it's to make me stronger, I will never do that!
Stop being so selfish.
The magic cannon sword is too unbalanced, outdated, and difficult for a beginner...
I'm not being selfish!
I'm doing my best.
I will never switch from the magic cannon sword!
I don't know how hard you've tried,
but putting in the same effort will only get you the same results.
I was mistaken.
What?
I thought for an instant that you might be a decent instructor!
You know nothing about me, stop telling me what to do!
I'm leaving!
Misora-san!
H-Hello, this is Lecty!
I'll be in charge of this part of the show today.
Um... Today we saw the leader of the Sky Wizards division.
She manages and leads all of the Sky Wizards.
She's very important!
Her name is Freon Flamel.
Hmm...?
Anyhow, the next episode is The Unforgettable Past.
Data viitoare
Trecutul de neuitat
I will show my divine presence again.
Rico, when did you show up?!