How dare he suggest that I quit the magic cannon sword?!
I'll prove him wrong, I swear!
For that, I need to train!
Hard work always pays off!
I read that in a manga!
Recent manga heroes tend to appear to be hard workers,
only to be revealed later that they had special lineage or talents.
Did you have to ruin this?!
Trecutul de neuitat
There's too many of them!
We can't hold them off any longer!
Fall before Radgrid, Devil Beetles!
If that's how you want to play...
Good, magic power fully charged!
Strike Blaster!
I knew we could count on the Sky Wizards!
Our champion!
Socié Whitale!
Wow!
Go, Mama!
You're switching from vanguard magic cannon sword to middle guard Magic Cannon.
I'm not giving up!
I brought your coffee.
You're starting to get in good shape.
Thank you for your hard work.
Do you want to take a break?
Thanks.
I'm exhausted!
I caught a glimpse.
That girl is from Fireteam E601, is she not?
Is she still being trained like that?
If you are curious, you should ask directly.
I doubt that I would get a straight answer.
Rico-san!
I refuse.
A goddess like me has no time for sweaty training.
B-But, um...
Misora-san hasn't come to school the past couple of days.
I don't know what to do all alone...
I am not the person to ask.
I, as a heavenly goddess, soar high above these problems.
I see... I guess I have to rely on Kanata-san...
You seem to think very highly of that traitor.
Yup! Though, I was a little worried at first.
Like, making me wear this outfit...
Not an easy task, making Lecty say that...
But I know now that he thinks about us seriously!
Kanata Age...
Greetings! I am Real Nua, from the
Regular department Medicine division.
Thank you for your help the other day, Yuri-san!
G-Good!
What do you want, Yuri?
You know what I want, Kanata-senpai!
You haven't trained those girls at all for the last few days!
How do you know that?
Fireteam E601 hasn't applied to use the training airspace!
It's easy to find out.
Do you have nothing better to do?
W-What?!
You're the only one on the Special Duty Fireteam that has spare time!
I-I was just worried that you would betray them too.
Sorry. I have to go on a home visit, no time to spare.
Hey, I'm not done talking t-
Always the serious one, Yuri.
Whose fault do you think this is?
You're looking out for them, right?
Thanks.
Kanata-senpai?!
This must be the place.
Welcome.
Sorry, I'm not here as a customer.
What are you doing here?!
Hey, glad you're looking healthy, Misora.
Don't start with me!
Hey, don't be rude to the guest!
Shut up!
Stay out of this, Papa!
You're Misora's dad?
You look nothing alike.
She looks like her mother.
I'm done for the day!
Sorry kid.
This family relationship isn't exactly perfect.
Hey, your wife is really pretty.
You're right, Misora looks like her mother.
Yeah, she did indeed.
That photo's all that's left of her.
Here, this one's on the house.
Our famous menu.
Like I said, I'm not here as a customer...
Oh wow, this is great!
They say that steak was my wife's favourite.
Pops, are you a Natural?
Yeah. And she was a Sky Wizard.
I don't remember.
Heartless, right?
I can't help it, though.
The records are there, but it just doesn't feel like my memory.
It doesn't help my relationship with Misora.
She's been skipping school the past few days, but I can't even scold her.
You seem to know Misora.
Do you know what happened?
Well, sort of.
Before that, though, let me ask you something.
What is it?
Why does Misora fixate on the magic cannon sword?
You're not a simple acquaintance, are you?
Oh, I didn't tell you?
I'm Misora's instructor.
My job is to give her a chance to get stronger.
They say my wife was a great Magic Cannon
Swordsman in the other floating city we used to live in.
But one day, she went on a mission and never came back.
From that day on, we Naturals lost our memories of her.
Misora wants to pursue the magic cannon sword arts because she doesn't want to forget her mother, ever.
I'm never giving up!
Hey! Mama! Mama!
Misora!
Mama!
Mama! Mama!
I missed you, Misora!
Okay, here's your favourite move...
Hey, Mama?
Up, up, and away!
Socié.
Gale!
I was so worried, I couldn't sleep at night!
I did take some naps, though.
I was so lonely I could only eat four meals a day!
Welcome home, honey!
I'm home, darling!
G-Geez Mama, cut it out!
Oh Misora, you're so adorable!
Oh stop, Mama!
I saw the live feed, Socié.
It was awesome how you blew them all up!
Thank you again, Socié-chan.
Our city of Iris is safe with you!
That's right!
Leave it all to me!
Steak for breakfast?
Yep, breakfast is the foundation for the entire day.
It's got to be nice and heavy!
It's too heavy on the stomach...
Sorry, I must have messed up the water settings...
How messed up does it have to be to do this?!
Oops...
What happened, Mama?!
Well, I was cleaning, and the trash wouldn't stop coming, so...
I used some magic and uh...
You can't vaporise trash!
Misora's so mean!
I'm here.
A gang of Archenar class beetles, and a Chimera?
Understood, I'm on my way.
Mama?!
I'm sorry, Mama has to go to work.
But you just went the other day!
Gale!
Good luck!
I'll be back soon!!
Mama!
I'm home, Misora!
Welcome home, Mama!
Mama!
Look Mama, the town is so tiny!
Hey, that's our place! Papa!
That's right.
That's where Papa and the neighbours are.
Mama?
You can't see them, but there are countless more people living there.
Remember Misora, Mama is fighting to protect the people of the city.
Mama?
Of course, I'll protect Misora and Papa too!
Stop!
You, Sky Wizard! Stop right there!
You, Sky Wizard
Stop right there! Stop right there!
Mama, I thought you needed permission to fly above the city.
Off we go, Misora!
Huh? We're running?!
W-Wait! Stop!
Stop right there!
Mama forgot!
Don't be stupid, Mama!
Good luck with the job, Mama.
I'll have a steak ready for you.
Thanks!
I'll be off then.
Good luck.
Good luck, Mama!
Is Mama coming home soon?
Papa!
Hey, dinner's almost ready.
Today we have my special beef stew.
Huh? It's not steak?
Oh, did you want steak?
It's kind of late for that, now...
N-No, I mean...
Is Mama not coming home yet?
Hmm? We don't have a mama in this house.
What? What's wrong?
Misora?!
Mama, Mama?!
Socié? Who's that?
Your mama?
You've lived alone with your dad for a long time now.
Oh hey, wait!
I've never heard of that Sky Wizard in Iris.
Socié, your mother, tried to protect us.
She charged in alone towards the enemies...
She is the strongest, most noble magic cannon swordsman I know.
Remember Misora, Mama is fighting to protect the people of the city.
Of course, I'll protect Misora and Papa too!
I'm going to be a Sky Wizard!
I'm going to be a Sky Wizard, like my mother!
Why can't I win?!
Why can't I...?
Why...
Why won't all my hard work pay off?
But I won't give up.
I won't give up, for Mama.
What are you doing here?!
The Hills of Hope, the resting ground for deceased Sky Wizards.
I hear you visit this place every day.
Did Papa tell you?
How dare you barge into my privacy like that!
You're the worst, you and Papa both!
Don't blame your dad.
You won't tell him anything, and he was sincerely worried.
So I asked him why you fixate on the magic cannon sword.
That's why I chose this place.
Misora, vow to your mother's grave.
Give up on the magic cannon sword.
You'll never be strong like this.
Stop behaving like you know it all!
My father doesn't even remember anything!
But when I was handed her magic cannon sword, I was given her will and everything about her!
I guess a traitor like you can't understand that!
Hey, for the people who have
passed on, what do you think hope was?
To protect the people in the city!
Yeah.
They didn't want to be forgotten,
but more than that, they wanted to protect the ones they love.
That's what let them face the Devil Beetles.
Your mother was probably the same.
That's obvious.
But think about it.
Was the magic cannon sword your mother's goal?
Or was her goal to protect the people, as a Sky Wizard?
That's...
When Socié died, I felt nothing.
If Misora dies, I'll probably feel nothing again.
That scares me terribly.
If you stay stubborn, your risk of dying increases.
People would forget you.
I know.
I know I'm just being selfish.
Then...
But I don't want to give up!
I want to protect the people with this magic cannon sword.
If I become a great magic cannon swordsman like my mama,
maybe people who see me will recover their memories of my mother.
Hold on...
Naturals have never recovered their lost memories before!
So what?
I'll be the first!
So I won't die! Ever!
I knew you were crazy, but not this much!
W-What's that supposed to mean?!
I like people like you.
Wha-?!
So I'll give you a hint on how to become a better magic cannon swordsman.
Huh?!
Now I know how strong your resolve is, so I have to brace myself too.
Did you just... test me?
You know, this path you're trying to take,
it could be worse than death.
Are you sure you want to take it?
I am!
Then vow to your mother, and to your sword!
Vow that you'll be a better magic cannon swordsman than your mother.
Vow that you will be strong enough to protect everyone, and yourself as well.
Yeah!
I won't let her die.
I told you, didn't I?
W-Why...?
I'm your instructor.
I'll help you carry your burdens.
So become strong, Misora.
Yeah!
I'm sorry I worried you.
I-It's okay!
Just having you back is...
Come on, kids!
Start training now, or next time you'll be serving coffee in a swimsuit!
Y-Yes!
Hey, wait, Lecty!
Hm?
Y-You know, um...
Thanks!
That instructor is starting to get interesting.
Misora here!
There are many other floating cities, not just Mistgun.
For example, Oakis, Lyune, and Bevel are some famous ones.
I used to live in Oakis!
And so, the next episode of Sky Wizards Academy,
The Key to Victory.
Data viitoare
Cheia pentru victorie
Don't miss my superb performance!
I'll try my best to-
I'm thorry, I bit my tongue...
You're making it worse...