Lloyd here.
The city of Mistgun was attacked by a swarm of devil beetles.
The sky wizards were able to defeat them,
but it seems like something bad is happening to Kanata behind the scenes.
Concursul Mistgun
Stop floating around, stupid balloons!
Rico, can you provide cover?
Rico?!
How do you expect me to keep up with your erratic movements?
Do your own fighting.
Rico...
Help, just a little, please?!
Silence, know your place, Misora!
U-Um, my hands are kind of... full, too.
I said help!
I said I'm not in the mood!
Misora-san, Rico-san, please stop fighting!
Do something about this!
Kanata Age's fireteam seems to be unchanged.
Yes, they are still extending their losing streak.
One more thing I need to ask you.
Can you confirm that the incident was not your doing?
Most certainly. It was not us that defeated the new chimera.
I'm sure you haven't heard, but Kanata Age insists that his fireteam, E601, was the one that defeated it.
He asked that, in return, we let them off the hook for destroying civilian property.
So, what did you do?
I turned him down, of course.
There's no evidence, no eyewitnesses.
So, for the sake of fairness to other fireteams,
I'm considering disbanding E601 as punishment.
I can't manage these anymore!
R-Rico, cover me! I'll help Lecty!
Can't you see we're in no state for that?
Do you want me to shoot you?
W-When did I say I wanted you to shoot me?!
Please, stop fighting, Misora-san, Rico-san!
Shut up, Lecty!
Yes, Lecty, keep your mouth shut.
I guess it's about time we moved on to the next step.
I-I'm sorry!
So the instructor, Kanata, will be...
Relieved of that duty, obviously.
Is that a problem?
I agree.
Yuri?
I don't think a traitor like Kanata-senpai can be a good instructor at all.
Chloe, I hate to make you do this, since you recommended him,
but please bring Kanata Age to my office later.
Yes.
So, sky wizards division lead,
is that the only reason why you called us today?
No. This is the real reason.
Ouch...
I have more bruises now.
That's because your movements are too erratic.
Look at Lecty here.
You're tickling me, Rico-san!
Not a scratch on her.
T-That's because you won't provide any covering fire!
The real issue is, though, why no one will recognise
all of the great fighting we did against the devil beetles!
Misora aside, I don't see why a goddess like me should remain unnoticed.
Well, nobody saw you during that fight, so I think it's only natural.
N-Natural?!
You got yourself hurt and used that weird power to-
So, Misora, are you unsatisfied?
Well...
Let me ask you too.
Are you satisfied?
Yeah. Who cares about that stuff?
More importantly, check this out.
This sounds like fun.
Mistgun...
T-Tournament?
All fireteams except S-ranked ones can join.
The winning team gains two whole ranks.
And receives cutting-edge gear made by the alchemy division!
And gets a yearlong free pass to all dining establishments in Mistgun?!
Congratulations for your victory.
Good girl.
Mistgun tournament.
Rico-sama!
You are our goddess!
Mistgun tournament.
You have bested me.
You are the best leader!
Yo! Yo!
I have nothing left to teach you.
Mistgun tournament.
What do you think?
Well...
Becoming champions might be next to impossible, but...
We're still going to do it!
Y-Yes! I'd like to win at least once...
I have no choice.
Without me, even that one win would be impossible.
Good, it's settled then.
I'll fill in the application, so-
So I'm fired, huh?
That's right.
You have done nothing but extend their losing streak.
This morning, the fireteam was fighting amongst themselves during training.
Seems like you were paying attention.
Disbanding fireteam E601 is the logical thing to do.
They didn't seem motivated anyway, what's there to lose?
Nah.
I'll have to say no to that one.
I still have stuff to do.
What does that mean?
It is what it is.
I signed on to be their instructor.
And I vowed to myself that I would raise them to be real sky wizards.
You make me laugh.
You, a traitor, raising those misfits?
Chloe might have recommended you,
but I still have my doubts against your-
Keep your doubts, I don't care.
The only people I need to prove myself to are Misora, Rico, and Lecty.
Strong words.
But what will the other fireteams think?
If we win this, the others will have to accept us. Right?
The tournament is a free-for-all for all non-S-rank fireteams!
Your girls can't even beat a fellow E-ranker!
What if I said they could?
How is it?
Can you hear them?
Fine.
Hold on, I...
If that happens, I will forget about disbanding E601.
Disbanding E601?!
Fine.
What?!
W-What's going on?!
I-I don't know! But she said...
You guys?
What was that about, disbanding our fireteam?
Don't eavesdrop.
Anyway, let's go.
Wait!
P-Please wait!
Why the serious looks?
Well, we, um...
After what we just heard, it's obvious.
So, what do you want to do?
I...
I want to make this fireteam stronger.
I want us to become stronger together, and go up high!
M-Me too!
Being a goddess, I already am at the top of the world...
But if you two insist, I suppose I can play along.
Good attitude.
Don't take it too seriously.
You just need to win in the tournament, that's all.
That's all?  We're...
We are, um...
I know. Zero wins, eleven losses. Zero percent win rate.
How are you so calm, knowing that?
This tournament puts all teams on a clean slate.
Scores from previous ranked matches have no meaning.
B-But...
Right! We'll start a new training exercise tomorrow, so be ready.
With that, you're dismissed.
Huh?!
T-That's it?
Oh yeah, almost forgot.
The tournament matchmaking is tomorrow.
Don't forget to attend!
Later.
This is it.
You may have heard rumours about this place,
but I'm sure this is your first actual visit.
This is where we study devil beetles.
You mean, dissection?
Well, yes.
I'm sure you've seen it in your hostile organisms classes.
More than I could swallow, back in the preparatory department days...
What now, though? After that talk earlier...
You were against the idea of the tournament, correct?
Yes. I think it only serves to agitate rivalries.
Why do you ask?
Here we are.
Welcome, we've been waiting!
I am honoured to have the sky wizards division lead herself visit us.
Let me introduce the others, this is...
I am aware!
Special duty fireteam S128, the top of the sky wizards division!
Chloe Sevegny-san, Lloyd Alwyn-san!
Hello...
Nice to meet you.
And of course! Pleasure to see you again!
Yuri Flostre-san!
I'm very sorry about what I did that time.
Did it leave a stain?
Oh thank you for remembering me!
It is a great honour! Oh, about this...
C-Can you show us the sample?
Oh! Yes! This way.
Is this...?
A chimera... shard?
I don't know who took this down, but...
this new chimera is larger than Chimera Deneb.
We have assigned this one the codename Chimera Antares.
In addition to being larger than Chimera Deneb...
It... regenerated?
This is truly amazing!
The regeneration creates an infinite
number of samples for us to work with.
This could lead to breakthroughs in rapid regenerative medicine as well! And...
That would be enough, thank you for the explanation.
We will take our leave now.
Oh, uh... Thank you for coming!
Oh, by the way!
I saw your interview on The Monthly Mistgun the other day!
Yuri-san, it said that you are only interested in men who are stronger than you.
Oh, that one, um...
It does appear that way.
Is that so...?
So it is really true!
I'm so glad we were able to meet today!
Do you see now?
The enemy is evolving.
At the current rate, we will surely run out of manpower.
That's what the Mistgun tournament is for.
Yes.
Are you okay?
You look pale.
I'm okay... I think it was the air in that place.
Yes, the smell was truly terrible.
Okay, we'll head off now.
Oh, I almost forgot.
Yuri, I need you to do something for me.
Me...?
Fireteam E644, block B, slot 12!
First round against an A-rank?!
What are you doing?!
I'm sorry!
Oh yeah!
We've practically won already!
Against a B-ranker?!
Next up, fireteam E601!
Go ahead!
Y-Yes!
Good luck, Misora-san!
Put your spirit into it. Your spirit.
I-I know!
Fireteam E601, block D, slot 4!
Our first match...
Who is it?!
Another E-ranker.
You did it, Misora-san!
I wouldn't have minded fighting a higher ranker.
Oh, is it decided already?
Look! We're fighting an E-ranker!
M-Maybe we won't have to disband now...
Kanata-senpai.
Huh? I thought S-rankers weren't part of this tournament.
I'm not joining as a participant,
but my fireteam is participating.
Your  fireteam?
The sky wizards division lead has assigned me as an instructor for an A-rank fireteam.
I see.
It's unfortunate, though.
My fireteam, A227, and yours, E601, are in completely different blocks.
We can never...
That's interesting.
What is?
We'll be facing off in the final match.
What are you going to do, Yuri?
Afraid of losing?
I-I most certainly am not!
Why are you assuming that I would lose?!
Do you think you have a chance of winning?
Of course!
Okay then, in that case, if we win...
you get to join my fireteam.
There is no chance in a million, or even in a billion!
But fine!
I accept your challenge!
Yeah, yeah.
U-Um, Kanata-san...?
My ears betray me.
I thought I heard you talk about the final.
What was that about?
That was about what I told the division lead.
If we come out as the champion, we're no longer disbanded.
Oh, didn't I tell you?
No you didn't!
This is Chloe, sky wizards division lead.
Here in Mistgun, in addition to the sky wizards division,
there is Medicine, which has the secret lab we visited today.
Other divisions include Machina, Alchemist, Industrial, Logistics,
Economics, Information, and Relics.
Any questions so far?
Uh, um...
No questions? Good.
Next episode, Beyond the Rankings.
Data viitoare
Mai presus de clasament
Uh... This is Real. This is Real.