My name is Freon Flamel, leader of the sky wizards division.
Due to the presence of a fireteam that can never win,
a traitor, and a younger sister who won't listen,
my days are not the easiest. However...
Enemies? Understood.
It's time to show them what sky wizards are capable of.
Cerurile au fost luate
An air raid alert has been issued to all of Mistgun.
Regular students and non-combatants must evacuate to a nearby shelter.
This is not a drill.
I repeat.
An air raid alert has been issued to all of Mistgun.
Regular students and non-combatants must evacuate to a nearby shelter.
This is not a drill.
Status report!
Groups A and B have entered field S!
I'm sorry!
We're late!
There are more following behind them!
Assemble seven battalions centred on A-rank fireteams!
Assign them to defend the key positions.
Send the E-rank fireteams to assist in the evacuation!
This side is all evacuated!
My duties have been completed as well.
Good, this block seems clear.
Wait, why are you here?
You're a former ace.
Why not go to the front lines and take the enemies down?
Well, it's complicated.
Complicated? How?
A-Anyway, where's Lecty?
You're right.
M-Misora-san!
This girl was still here!
Where are we?
Hey, where are we?
Let's get her to a shelter right away!
Wait!
Would you look at that...
They made it through?
Impressive, Chloe!
I'm sure you could do that too, if you used that spear.
No, I'm not using spears anymore.
I don't think it's right for me.
Bad news!
A separate detachment of Devil Beetles have punched through our defences!
They've broken into Mistgun!
Devil Beetle group D has entered the city!
Over 300 of them!
Head supervisor!
Sky wizards, Mistgun is yours.
Understood.
All students, even those on evacuation assistance duty,
prepare for combat!
Don't let those bugs land in the city!
We are going all-out!
Everything is okay!
Please don't cry.
Remember Misora, Mama is fighting to protect the people of the city.
Mama?
Of course, I'll protect Misora and Papa too!
I'll protect everyone!
Maintain peripheral vision, properly acquire the enemy, and...
What?! Take this!
Yes!
Great job, Misora-san!
Your accuracy isn't perfect, but that was still a good shot.
You are improving.
It only took you one shot to correct.
Keep it up.
We'll protect this girl, and...
Misora!
Here I go!
I did it!
That's not my fault.
Releasing a Strike Blaster in the city?
That's terrible, Misora-san!
You're horrible.
What?!
I didn't mean to do this either!
It's a coincidence!
Coincidentally, you took out your dad's café.
What?!
Oh no!
Enemy count is over ten thousand now.
Fireteam attrition rate is 30 percent.
We have no chance, unless we strike their commander.
Look Mum, I found kitty!
Mum! Mum!
That's not good.
Chimera type confirmed!
Data match, it's a Chimera Deneb!
Location?
Block 24.
Send all intercepting units there.
Concentrate all firepower!
If we take out Chimera Deneb,
then all the other Devil Beetles should pull back.
Confirmed kill on Chimera Deneb!
All fireteams,
clean up the remaining enemies and set up a perimeter for...
Wait!
No change to the enemies' patterns!
I knew it.
So there is more than one Chimera?!
Oh, I didn't tell you?
Given the number of enemies, there has to be more than one Chimera.
No you didn't!
So, in order to protect the people of Mistgun,
we need to find this unconfirmed Chimera, correct?
That's about right, yeah.
How then?!
I suppose I must show a glimpse of my true power.
Rico-san?!
When I activate my Clairvoyance, I find it difficult to focus my eyes.
It pains me to wear something that covers even part of my beautiful face, but...
You look good with glasses too, though.
Really?! I guess it's no surprise!
There's an abnormally high concentration of smaller beetles, over there.
That must be it, block 68.
Chloe-senpai, Lloyd-senpai! Shouldn't we fall back?!
Well, even if we did...
We can't take all of these enemies back with us.
Reports say there are multiple Chimeras.
Without your abilities...
It's okay.
Mistgun has Kanata!
What?! That traitor would be the first to run away!
Yuri, you have to believe in Kanata.
B-But...
He won't leave the people of Mistgun behind.
Yes, he reacts so predictably to the peril of others.
All right, let's go!
Go where?!
You three are taking the Chimera down!
We can't!
This is our first real battle!
What kind of improv session is this?!
Misora is right!
This is insanity.
You didn't train so much just to die, right?!
You train to survive,
so that you can protect even more people. Right?
You can do it.
I guarantee it, as your instructor.
Hey, guys.
He might be a pervert, but he is our instructor, and he trusts us.
I trust you too.
Let's do this.
I-I'm training to be a Sky Wizard so that I can protect the people!
So if we have a shot at protecting everyone...
It would be a good opportunity.
Performing well here could show that woman who is truly superior.
That woman?
D-Don't worry about that...
Sounds like you're ready.
Let's go!
To take back Mistgun. To take back our skies!
Yes.
Right!
Yeah!
Enemies are concentrating on block 68!
All of our forces have their hands full!
What's happening?
Let's do this as planned.
Yes!
First step!
Lecty gets the Archenars' attention with close combat!
Yes!
No need to be shy, these are not people!
Wow, Lecty's great!
The Eisenach-style magic twinsword art is impressive as always.
Over there too?!
Just as planned.
Huh?
Second step, Rico covers Misora with long-ranged sniping!
Misora, now!
I-I know!
Third step, Misora uses her superior acceleration to approach the enemy and blow them away with a Strike Blaster!
End of story!
Got it!
There's too many of them!
Hold it together, Misora!
Misora-san, I have you covered!
Filthy monsters, you are no match for the beautiful goddess!
For Rico and Lecty...
For Mama...
We are the sky wizards of Mistgun!
Good!
We did it!
Misora!
K-Kanata?!
What is that chimera?!
I've never seen that type before.
Lecty?!
Lecty, Rico! Hey, are you...
That was a good shot.
But they blocked it! It was useless!
Normally, this fight would be over.
Didn't expect a monster like that, though.
Don't waste your energy!
I don't know why,
but your magic power reserves are really small, right?
I guess that irregular enemy demands special attention from me.
What I'm about to do is the worst example an instructor can give.
Make sure you never fight like this!
This is dangerous, stand back!
W-What are you doing?!
No way...
What did he just do?!
Yeah, way too slow...
It's not magic power...
A different force...?
Or maybe I'm just too fast!
I need to end this soon...
You're in its sights!
Get out of there!
Didn't I tell you?
This fight was over the moment I decided to show my full powers!
No you didn't...
Where's the chimera?!
Did you do that, Misora?!
Kanata!
Kanata-san!
Kanata.
Kanata!
How...?
Looks like he did it.
Did it? Who? What?
Isn't it obvious?
It's the man you love, Yuri.
Archenar class Devil Beetles are pulling back from Mistgun airspace.
Mistgun airspace is clear!
Was the unidentified chimera defeated?
But... by who?
Is Yuri-san all right?!
Is this...?
W-Wait, what's wrong?!
You didn't die on us, did you?!
Oh no!
No way.
You scared us!
You're too easily scared.
B-But...
Look.
That's our sky.
Now you're ready to win the ranked matches.
Of course we are!
Didn't think I'd be this late.
Kanata-senpai.
What's up, Yuri?
I wanted to see what your students are like.
I see. What else is up?
You seem to be in a good mood.
I'm not in any special mood!
By the way, Senpai,
I thought you were guiding evacuees during the raid.
How did you get hurt?
I don't know.
Maybe I tripped and fell while running away.
I still hate that about you!
Oops, gotta pay attention.
Don't be surprised, my fireteam is pretty strong now.
We did it!
No surprise there.
Know your place.
W-We lost...
Oh no...!
I made no mistakes.
Kanata-senpai, you said something about your fireteam being strong?
Ah, well... things like this happen, I guess.
Your suggestion has been accepted.
Excuse me.
Did the head supervisor sign off on your idea?
Yes. Now we can accelerate the Sky Wizard training program,
with more realistic fights...
In our new academy tournament!
Hey Rico, how far can you see with your Clairvoyance?
Well, for example, Misora, your lingerie designs are...
Wow, that's...
Stop! Stop looking!
Just joking.
I see in every direction over extreme distances,
but not through solid objects.
You scared me!
But if my skills improve...!
If they improve...?!
Data viitoare
Concursul Mistgun
Next episode, Mistgun Tournament.
You dodged the question!