Acum mult timp, rasa umană a fost forțată să părăsească suprafața.
Pământurile sunt acum acoperite cu monștri numiți Cărăbuși Demonici.
Oamenii au migrat în marile orașe
plutitoare ca să-și continue traiul.
Această poveste eroică are loc la
marea academie zburătoare, Mistgun,
și o are în rolul principal pe cea mai puternică și
frumoasă luptătoare împotriva Cărăbușilor Demonici...
Rico Flamel.
Încetează cu minciunile!
Hm.
Nu-mi spune "hm" mie!
Cel mai puternic trădător
Deci, perversule, cum se face
că tu ești instructorul nostru?
Nu-ți face griji pentru micile detalii.
Let's move this forward.
What do you mean move this forward?!
I bet you didn't even read the data,
and let your perverted desires drive you here!
Mai taci.
Strawberry Jam, your name is Misora Whitale.
Sky Wizards division, Preparatory Department, second year, age 14.
Report card says, classroom-learning grades are D.
Practical training, E.
The reviewer recommends that you leave the school voluntarily.
My true abilities can't be measured by exams!
Oh?
I-It's true!
I'm telling you, it's true!
Really...
Sky Wizards Academy
The Instructor of Aerial Combat Wizard Candidates
H-Hold on! Stop casting doubtful gazes on me!
Stop! No! Please...
Misora is a scrub, so her grades are no surprise.
Oh, let me reintroduce myself, just in case. I am...
Rico Flamel.
Again, Sky Wizards division, Preparatory Department second year.
Classroom scores are all As...
Actually, A-, due to missing homework.
Actually, you had an F- on your practical exam.
E is supposed to be the lowest, how did you get an F-?
I couldn't get my hair in shape that day, so I skipped.
Ah...
Whatever.
And, the last one...
Y-Yes!
Lecty Eisenach.
Of course, Sky Wizards division,
Preparatory Department, second year.
Your grades are horrible too.
Your classroom scores rival Misora.
Unstable practical exams... Winning and losing against the same opponent.
I, um, I... I'm sorry!
Ow...
Okay, so now that we've introduced ourselves, let's...
Hold it!
I won't let a traitor like you be our instructor!
Um...
I understand that he's a pervert, but a traitor...?
From what I heard, a little over six months ago,
he fought some Devil Beetles, and managed to make it home alive,
but has since then become a coward.
Now he skips his special missions all the time!
I heard that he also skipped the important ranked
match that was supposed to get his team in the S Rank.
After constantly betraying the expectations of others, the nickname he got was...
Traitor!
We can't let this irresponsible man be our instructor!
You can direct your complaints to the leader of the Sky Wizards division.
Anyway, you've never won a single ranked match.
Aren't you ashamed?
D-Don't underestimate me!
Of course I'm ashamed!
I want to be a fully-fledged Sky Wizard so bad,
I can't stand wasting my time!
Yes, your comments are ill-advised.
From quite a young age, I have been lauded as a goddess incarnate.
My skills are quite adequate.
I... I don't neglect training either!
You know they used to call me Chronos, the Black Swordmaster, right?
Well, I've heard that, yes...
Well that master is going to train you.
If you do well, maybe you can be as strong as me.
Or rather, stronger than me.
Imagine yourself...
Defeating higher-ranked fireteams one after the other,
contributing dramatically in the fight against the Devil Beetles...
What do you think?
Well, if you insist, I guess I could put up with you just once...
I object.
Misora the Ordinary, yes.
But I, the goddess, sweating and toiling? Why?
Rico! That attitude is what's stopping you from getting results!
You two are the ones without results.
Hey, let's take this outside!
There, I'm outside.
Hey Rico.
Your exam score was F-, right?
So what?
I have no need for exams, so it is natural.
But I've never seen your skills.
Given the data, I have to consider you equal to or lower than Misora.
Are you sure that's okay?
You would place the goddess beneath this?!
This what?!
You can show me what you're capable of in training.
I must reluctantly display my astounding talents, but once.
But beware,
don't let the divine performance make you fall in love with me.
Okay, and Lecty.
How about you?
I, um, I...
Lecty, I told you, if you're going to say something,
look the person in the eyes and speak loudly.
I-I'm sorry!
Sorry? You don't want to train with me?
N-Not that! I meant to say sorry to Misora-san!
Come on.
I-I'll do it!
Please let me join your training!
Good, it's settled then.
Look, over there!
So my task is to help with city security?
That's Chloe-senpai and Yuri-senpai, from the Special Duty Fireteam!
She waved at us!
You could wave too.
No, I... I'm still not used to being treated like this.
Tea again?
Oh, um, yes.
Is coffee still too bitter for you?
You haven't changed at all.
Say, um... Is Kanata-senpai still considered on sick leave?
Sixth time.
Huh?
That's the sixth time you asked me that this week.
Well, that's the official treatment.
He's not ready to go out on a real mission,
but he's now the instructor of an E-ranked fireteam.
An instructor?!
Yep.
I requested it.
I-I don't understand!
He won't assist his fireteam, spends time helping Logistics,
and now he's an instructor?!
How does he get away with being so selfish?!
Yuri, please.
Don't speak so badly about him.
Look.
Defending this peace is our job as Sky Wizards.
I'm sure Kanata feels the same way.
So right now, Kanata-senpai is...
If I were to say...
Up in the sky, I guess?
That's high enough, I guess.
Why are you riding that thing?
Huh? Oh, I'm used to doing this.
You choose to not use flight magic,
and instead use the flight assist tool, with inferior mobility...
Huh?!
Are you saying Mister Grand Master doesn't even need to fly properly to face us?!
Well, given our differences in skill, I guess so.
S-So, what type of training are we doing?!
Today's training is...
The training is...?
Tag.
Tag?!
Tag is for beginners who just learned how to fly!
You chose such a lowly program to test my godly skills?
P-Please, train us properly!
Oh, I forgot to say.
You can use your arcana-alchemical weapons to attack me, full-force.
If you can bring me down, the training is over.
Okay, that's that.
Begin training!
Wow, he's fast...
Sky Wizards Academy
The Instructor of Aerial Combat Wizard Candidates
Ah! Whatever!
We're going to take him down, okay?!
Sky Wizards Academy
The Instructor of Aerial Combat Wizard Candidates
Huh? What? Wait, Misora-san!
How foolish, chasing an escaping target without a plan...
Get back here, coward! Hey!
Wow, they really do have zero teamwork.
Her speed is decent, though.
Hey, do you really think you can catch me all alone?
Of course, why else would I be here!
Don't cry if you get hurt!
Oh, I'll be fine.
I don't intend to get hit at all.
Pretty decent stamina too.
I hope you're ready!
I don't go easy on traitors!
My Magical Cannon Sword, Radgrid!
You!
Hey, come on. That's not a club, you know.
You restless little...!
Can't you take sharper swings, instead of just flailing about?
Shut up!
Go down already, traitor!
Let's give this a shot...
Hey! Running away?!
Are you scared now?
Yeah, her speed and stamina are pretty impressive.
How's this then?
You're finished!
What did he just do?!
Where did he go?!
That simple manoeuvre threw her off.
She got behind me?
Um, Kanata-san...
Nice weapon.
What's the name?
Oh, uh, hm... They are called, Amano-Habakiri.
She could have scored a hit if she tried at that moment.
What's wrong?
Don't hesitate.
Here I come!
How can she be so inconsistent?
Hey, are you slacking off?
I-I most certainly am not!
Her moves are refined, her reflexes are good too...
But she seems constantly lost.
I guess she doesn't trust her own abilities.
Hey, Lecty, is Eisenach your...
That's...
I-I'm sorry!
Huh?
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
The Magic Gun Athena, as beautiful as the goddess that wields it, shall smite you.
He cut my Magic Bullet down?
Kanata-san?!
Are you okay?
Y-Yes!
She's not all talk, that was a good shot.
Of course, when a shot is too accurate, it's also easy to dodge.
How?
Your aim wasn't bad.
But your intent to kill was kind of telegraphed.
By the way, did you come up with that combination on the fly?
Y-Yes.
I was very scared!
Compared to Misora, who randomly flutters about wherever she pleases,
Lecty's movements are refined.
It is only natural that I should sync with her to land a good shot.
If you can calculate that far, why don't you worry about friendly fire?
I am a goddess, earthly life does not interest me.
Wow...
Anyway, I see what your characteristics are.
Traitor! Come out!
Where did he go off to?!
This sucks!
How come we couldn't catch him? There were three of us!
I'm sorry, my skills were inadequate...
Oh, let me help you with that.
Oh, hey, thanks.
And um, Lecty, it's not your fault.
I wasn't looking out for you,
and might not have given any instructions...
Yes.
As Misora says, the fireteam leader did not assess the battlefield adequately.
Unlike the beautiful one, me.
You little...
Do not feel sorrow.
It is only natural that my breasts are larger, and that I am taller.
That is what differentiates commoners and goddesses.
I'm not in sorrow!
Besides, breast size isn't a problem!
R-Really?
Um, Misora-san?
No, this can't be... This can't be true...
This is a dream, a dream...
How can Lecty have bigger breasts than me?!
Do not be concerned.
The size of one's breasts has nothing to do with one's skill as a Sky Wizard.
Rico...?
You may not be Boing! Bam! like us.
You may instead be splat, plink, swoosh-plop.
Isn't that right, Lecty?
T-That's right!
Misora-san's breasts might be splat, plink, swoosh-plop, but...
Rico-san?! How can you make me say that!
M-Misora-san... I don't think that! Not at all!
Rico...!
What kind of grudge do you have against me?!
Come on you two, calm down!
That is no way to address a goddess.
Misora is hot-headed and easily loses sight of her surroundings.
Lecty's low self-esteem gives her trouble when facing off with an enemy.
Rico is the exact opposite,
but distances herself too much from her allies.
What odd puzzle pieces these are.
But if I can make them fit together, this could be amusing.
I will never accepted Misora as the fireteam leader.
Besides, why should I, the goddess, be beneath Misora?
I started this fireteam!
Um, um...
The person who started it should be in charge!
Misora-san! Rico-san!
Being first in line does not guarantee respect.
Calm down please!
Don't stop me, Lecty!
I'm shutting this noisy mouth up!
So, for tomorrow's training, I...
You pervert!
Pervert.
It's a pervert!
Not this again.
unmei yori futashika na kuse ni
Chiar dacă este mai nesigur decât destinul,
tsuyoku hikareru namae no nai kimochi
Acest sentiment fără nume mă trage puternic
aragawanaide ukeireta totan
În momentul când am încetat să mă zbat și l-am acceptat
mujun mo nazo mo rifujin mo zenbu yuruseta
I-am iertat toate contradicțiile, misterele și absurditățile
kimi to nara asu wo mamoreru
Dacă sunt cu tine, sunt sigură că ne pot proteja viitorul
kamisama hitotsu dake oshiete
Te rog, Doamne, spune-mi un singur lucru:
donna yoru mo ibitsusa wo tamoteru sono sube wo douka
Cum pot păstra această distorsiune indiferent de nopțile care vor veni?
guratsuku tsumasaki de senobi shite yume wo miteru
Stau pe vârful degetelor ca să pot continua să visez
kimi to me wo awasete
Privindu-ne în ochi în același timp
I am Rico Flamel.
I, the goddess, will hold a special class for you.
A Sky Wizard's role in battle is determined by his or her weapon.
Lecty's Magic Twin Swords allow her to perform close combat in the vanguard.
I, on the other hand, engage enemies at long range with my Magic Gun,
which naturally makes me a rear guard.
Hey, what about me?
And so, the next episode is The Potentials of the Weakest.
Data viitoare
Potențialul celor mai slabi
I will show my divine presence again.
Wait, so what about me?!