Avem doar o imagine,
dar aceasta este o Garuda.
Se știe că aceste creaturi
există în lumea noastră.
Este o specie pe care știința
nu o poate descrie prea bine.
Acestea sunt—
Avertizare!
Echipa specială S128 și Cuibul Corbuui să vină imediat la punctul de întâlnire.
Repet.
Echipa specială S128...
Lecty, îngrijitoarea de animale
Un puișor?
Vino, nu trebuie să te temi.
Hei! Așteaptă!
Pleacă!
Ești bine?
Totul este în regulă acum.
Nu ar trebui să fugi astfel!
O Garuda?
Nu există nicio îndoială.
Imediat cum a fost reperată de echipa de patrulare, a dispărut.
Nu este foarte cunosc,
dar Garuda își depune ouălele în orașe.
Puii cresc absorbind magia
de la vrăjitorii rezidenți.
Deci...
Sunt șanse să își lase ouălele în Mistgun?
Da.
Priopritatea noastră de acum ar trebui să fie găsirea acelor ouă de Garuda!
Viitorul Mistgunului depinde de reușita acestei misiuni.
Nu uitați asta!
Da, doamnă!
Îngrijitoare de animale?!
De ce trebuie să ne irosim timpul făcând asta?
Este o lecție importantă pentru clasele E să înțeleagă semnificația vieții.
Nu v-am spus asta?
C-Cred că ai dreptate.
Mi-e teamă că trebuie să refuz.
Eu sunt o zeiță, deci nu pot atinge animalele murdare.
Atunci, și eu refuz.
Mai bine m-aș antrena decât să fac asta.
Atunci, rămâne doar...
Eu?
Da.
Este un coteț de găini aproape.
În spatele celei de-a doua clădiri.
Un coteț de găini?
Î-Înțeleg! O voi face!
Bine, este stabilit.
Animalele simt și răspund
la sentimentele oamenilor.
Dacă ești grijulie cu ele,
îți vor răspunde sentimentelor tale.
A-Am înțeles!
Ei bine...
Salutare, toată lumea! Am venit—
Vai! S-Sunt așa de drăguțe!
Unde este puișorul din această dimineață?
O, aici ești.
Vino.
Să mergem să mâncăm cu restul.
Ce este în neregulă?
Înțeleg.
Ești exact ca mine înainte
să-l întâlnesc Kanata-san.
Doar pentru tine.
Deci, cum ar trebui să te strig?
Ei bine...
Piyodo? Piyoletti? Piyonardo? Piyogore al treilea?
Sau poate Piyo-chan?
Piyo-chan!
Am înțeles!
De acum înainte, tu ești Piyo-chan.
Scuzați-ne.
At the moment, there's no sign of it.
Oh.
It's a dangerous situation.
After hatching from its egg, a Garuda can reach maturity in only 24 hours.
That fast?
Widen the search area.
We must find those eggs quickly!
Yes, ma'am!
Augh, another hard day.
That's because you move about too much.
And that's because you weren't supporting me properly!
Now, now. Calm down.
Yuri is going to be busy for a while.
Lecty's taking care of the animals.
Why not try something different?
What?
If Rico changes, it wouldn't be so hectic, would it?
Why not try swimming?
Huh?
In addition to being good exercise,
swimming also helps to reduce stress.
Well, it's true that Misora has been putting on more weight and is getting tired easier.
H-How do you know that?!
I was just guessing.
Piyo-chan, you're just afraid of the other chicks, aren't you?
With time, I'm sure you'll start to get along with them.
Oh? Wasn't that enough?
Oh, I know.
Somewhere here...
I was going to eat them later, but you can have these cookies.
That's strange..
I hadn't noticed before Piyo-chan, but aren't you getting a lot bigger than the other chicks?
We found nothing today.
At this rate, we may have to enlist the help of the other students.
You might be right.
I hope we can get them to help without causing a panic.
I haven't worn a swimsuit in so long!
Really?
I sometimes wear one and pose in front of the mirror.
Why do that?
To admire myself, of course.
Piyo-chan, you'll be fine!
There's nothing to be scared of!
Piyo-chan!
Yes! That's it!
That's wonderful, Piyo-chan!
Take it easy.
Well done!
Lecty?
Misora-san! Rico-san!
What's that?
Ah, I'll introduce you.
This is my new friend, Piyo-chan.
So cute.
Huh?
Uh... no, it's nothing!
Don't you think it's a little big for a chick?
He's just a little on the large side.
So I thought I'd put him on a diet.
Oh, that's great.
Piyo-chan, you've been praised.
I'm sure I've seen it somewhere...
Near here?
Yes.
Get everyone from Raven Nest and bring them here.
Search everywhere within a 2 kilometre radius.
Yes, ma'am!
Yo, Lecty.
You okay?
Oh, Kanata-san.
Oh? What's this?
He's called Piyo-chan.
But...
Don't you think he's rather large?
Misora-san said the same thing.
Let's see...
I'm sorry, but Piyo-chan is very shy.
I see.
Well, if you know that, it shows you truly understand your friend.
Thank you very much!
Ah! I've got to go!
Piyo-chan, wait!
Everyone, I need your help.
Please take it.
Oh, Yuri-san?
Hello.
Lecty-san.
Have you seen a bird like this?
That's...
Do you know something?
Oh! Ah... well... that's...
What's the matter?
Nothing.
Nothing at all.
Was that Lecty?
What's that?
Here you go.
This is...
Piyo-kun, come with me!
Let's go.
Put that chick down and come over here!
Lecty!
Girls!
Quicky! Get away from the Garuda!
It's dangerous!
There's nothing dangerous here!
He's just growing a little big.
No.
The main food source for a Garuda is... magic.
Magic?
They lay their eggs in places like Mistgun.
And then it grows by absorbing magic.
No way...
Do you understand now?
That's a very dangerous creature.
I don't understand!
Anyway, Piyo-chan understands me.
Is that really true?
A chick is always begging for food.
Are you sure you didn't confuse that with your desires?
That's not true!
Is it, Piyo-chan?
Calm down, Piyo-chan.
Piyo-chan, come on!
Piyo-chan!
That's...
We were too late!
Our magical techniques are nothing more than food to a Garuda!
Hit it with another salvo.
But if we do that, won't it just get bigger?
That's part of the plan.
If we overload it with energy, it will explode.
That's our best option for success.
Okay.
Piyo-chan, escape while there's still time!
Lecty! Get away from him!
Hurry, or you might get hurt!
Wait! Don't!
Don't hurt Piyo-chan!
Piyo...chan?
What's happening?
I'm losing... my strength.
Is it...?
It's absorbing magic.
Please stop it, Piyo-chan!
If you need magic, take all you want from me.
Don't you understand what I'm saying?
Run Lecty!
Hurry up!!
Lecty.
Kanata-san?
Sorry I'm late, but I'm here now.
Kanata-senpai!
You can still move?
You could really do that with so little magic?
Lecty...
Dar—
Please...
Kanata-san!
Lecty?
Piyo-chan.
Please.
Please don't hurt... Kanata-san or anyone else!
Stop it!
Piyo-chan?
Oh no!
Animals sense and respond to people's feelings.
If you take good care of them, they'll respond to your feelings.
R-Right!
Piyo-chan...
It stopped itself?
Why?
Could he have been responding to her strong emotions?
Piyo-chan.
Since she's your student, you should take care of her.
Yeah.
Lecty.
Call him by name.
Go on.
Eh?
Just do it.
Here.
Piyo-chan.
Piyo-chan?
Piyo-chan!
It can't be! What's going on?
If a Garuda undergoes a sudden transformation, it can reject the magic it collected,
and rise again from the ashes.
But you knew that, didn't you?
Oh? Didn't I tell you?
You didn't tell us anything!
There you are.
That's all right, isn't it?
That collar will feed it small amounts of magic.
I think it should be enough to stop it growing again.
Thank you!
Come on, Piyo-chan.
You're really clever, Lloyd.
Not really.
The research and development on this was arranged by the sky wizard academy's principal.
She knew this would happen?
Who knows? It's anyone's guess.
Hei!
Ce tot faceți acolo?
În regulă! Să mergem!
Da!