It's the Mistgun Tournament finals! What's all this commotion?
Amie?! Is it a devil beetle attack?! Nobody told me!
Calm down, Beach.
This is our chance to show off our special cheer...
I mean, the chance for our rival, Fireteam E601, to win the final.
Did that guy in the crowd have anything to do with this?
Wait Coela, you saw him too? The guy with the glasses?
I saw! I saw! I saw it too!
He was running towards the arena, while everyone was running away!
I wonder if squad E601 is okay...
With the alarms going crazy...
What's going to happen?!
Instructor of the Sky Wizards Academy
Why are you guys still here?!
You can't fight him alone!
Didn't I tell you?
I have friends too.
How horrible of you...
How dare you get in the way of my romance with Yuri.
Kanata! Yuri!
Are you okay?!
See?
My, my...
No warnings? That hurt.
Now is your chance to turn yourself in.
Yuri's right.
If you give up now, we won't have to kill you!
Who said anything about killing me?!
I am the chosen one!
How can you possibly hope to kill me?!
That skin...
It's like a devil beetle.
Well then...
No effect at all!
We aren't getting through this.
Now no one can interrupt us!
All that's left is for us make love to each other!
Isn't that right?! Yuri!
There you are!
I finally have you!
Hey, don't!
Kanata-san!
What's this?
Are the interlopers still around?!
What?!
Nu!
Don't be so arrogant.
Is he using the power again?!
What other time?
What are you talking about?
Ah, oh, um...
Hey, could you do me a favour and stop lashing out at my favourite students?
Oh? Not bad, for a human.
Kanata-senpai?!
Yuri, don't make any careless moves.
Don't worry about her.
I will protect her!
Oh, I see.
This feeling... So that's it.
You've been chosen by the devil beetles too.
I pity you.
Those whispers took you in.
What's this?
Do you perceive this power in a negative context?
Seems I am correct.
Now I get it.
No wonder you've decided to go rogue.
The public would lose it if they found out someone on the special duty fireteam was blessed like this.
Shut your mouth.
Ooh, nice try!
You were so close.
I will finish you now.
Senpai! Kanata-senpai!
This is goodbye, Kanata Age!
Didn't I... tell you?
My students are... very good.
Kanata-san!
Thanks, Lecty.
Back up!
Right!
Did you really think you could get away from me?
Yuri!
Thanks for killing yourself!
Kanata-senpai!
Stay back!
Run, Yuri...
A real tough boy, aren't you?
There's a hole in your stomach, yet you're still alive.
That ends now, though.
Kanata-senpai!
This isn't over!
Misora-san?
Misora?
He taught us a lot.
Yes, over and over again.
What we need as sky wizards.
Actually, there was one thing.
The most important thing I taught you.
To never give up.
Well then...
I would have let you live if you stayed out of this.
But it looks like you need to be punished!
Lecty Eisenach, moving in!
Are you first, little girl?
Misora!
Yes!
Good!
My Amano-Habakiri?!
That's enough, back up Lecty!
This is good...
The weaker you seem to him,
the more careless he will become.
Oh well...
Do you really want me to kill you?!
He took flight.
On to stage two.
It's almost like you want me to finish you off!
Hmm? Where did Yuri go?
If you tell me honestly, I will give you all a passionate, bone-crunching embrace!
Well?!
Now!
I hope you're ready!
Oh Yuri, finally you've come to accept my love!
Kanata-senpai, for this moment only, I forgive you.
I will use the power of this spear, that you taught me!
Don't worry, Yuri...
This won't... This can't...?!
Ow!
What?! My body... from a simple spear?
If you didn't know, I will teach you now.
This spear is named Trishula.
It is equipped with a high-frequency oscillation mechanism
that cuts matter apart on a molecular level,
specially designed to counter the chimera threat.
My... My body!
It's over.
W-Wait! Just wait!
I know what you are thinking.
That's why you should stop.
If you did that, I would never be able to forgive you.
I... I... I...!
I!
I have not lost yet!
You had your warning. I knew what you were thinking.
That's why I told you to give up!
Didn't I tell you?
You've been dancing on the palm of my hand.
Phew. I guess the case is solved now.
It was thanks to you that we were able to defeat him.
What are you talking about?
You finished him off.
I was just running around scared.
How's your wound, Kanata?
Oh? It's okay.
Really? Be careful, okay?
Hmm?
Hey! Who took the enemy down?!
Here comes our division lead.
Oh, I'm so tired. I think I'll go to bed now.
Bye!
Hey, wait!
Don't leave us!
Oh my, there goes our instructor.
He hasn't changed one bit.
Huh?
Kanata always does everything by himself,
never takes credit for it, and just leaves.
Indeed.
I have no idea what he's thinking.
Kanata-senpai.
The culprit was a student of the Medicine division.
Driven by stress, he set up a bomb in the Sky Arena...
Hey, do you think that's true?
I feel it is adequate, as an official announcement.
So, now that E601 has become the champion of the tournament,
you will give them a two-rank boost as promised,
raising them to the C rank, right?
About that...
What?!
I tried to argue.
But they said this would cancel out your debts for destroying the city,
so you will not get a promotion this time.
T-That can't be!
Typical response from that woman.
B-But we still get the other prize, the cool weapons, right?
Of course.
Here.
Um...
That is...
What is that?
It seems the weapons got hit by the explosions in the arena...
So winning...
Got us...
Nothing, it seems.
I wouldn't say that.
We worked so hard...
And that's all we get.
Indeed...
Come on, don't be that way.
I know very well that you worked really hard.
Isn't that enough for you?
Misora, Rico, Lecty.
You worked hard, and did well.
Congratulations on winning the tournament.
As team leader, I want to say thanks too, Rico, Lecty!
D-Don't mention it!
I suppose I can forgive you for hiding this man's secret.
I said I'm sorry...
Oh, and one more thing.
Fireteam E601 has a new member.
What?!
Come in.
Huh?
What?
Yuri-san?
This is Yuri Flostre, the defeated commander.
Everyone, be nice.
W-What defeated commander?!
You lost to us.
Okay, defeated commander, please introduce yourself to the others.
I am here to receive instruction from Kanata-senpai as a new member.
My name is Yuri Flostre.
I need to stay in Special Duties as well,
but it is great to work with you!
There, do you like that?
What's wrong, guys?
Your new friend is introducing herself.
Pleased to meet you, too.
I guess that'll do.
That'll do for who?!
What's in the box?
T-This is, uh, a cake.
Oh, how considerate!
Way to go, newbie.
Okay everyone, let's celebrate our victory together!
Here? Now? So suddenly?!
Where else would we eat cake?
It doesn't have to be now!
How about when we're alone?!
Come on, Kanata-senpai, give it back please!
But how will I feed those three the cake if we're all alone?
Come on! Please!
Cake is best when eaten in a big party.
Oh?
You know, Yuri...
I knew about your tastes from that magazine interview, but...
Is it Misora?
Lecty?
Or could it be Rico?
Kanata-senpai, you idiot!
What's wrong, Misora-san?
Oh, it's nothing.
Okay, we'll get that for you!
Okay, everyone!
Here we go!
Fireteam E601!
Moving out!