Sky wizards school for kids!
Hey, hey, Kanata-oniisan, tell us about Lecty-chan's Eisenach-style magic twinsword art!
It's a super powerful style that uses two swords.
I see!
What about the magic cannon sword, Misora-chan's weapon?
Slashes nearby enemies, snipes distant ones.
An all-in-one wonder-weapon, though difficult to master.
Is that so!
What about Rico-chan? What's her skill?
Cheia pentru victorie
How long are you going to stay in bed?
Do you plan on being tardy again?
Do as you like.
What a bothersome woman.
A goddess like me, bound by petty school rules? Unspeakable.
Hey, let's sit over there.
Sitting near the traitor would ruin our lunch.
Kanata, you impress me.
How so?
Why don't you tell him clearly, Lloyd-senpai?
How can you stand being hated by the entire city of Mistgun?
And these are the next opponents.
Fireteam E-571, is it?
I believe they are on the fast-track to promotion.
Don't ignore me!
Your strategies are useless.
Your fireteam is weak to start with, and now it has the traitor in it.
There's no way you can win. Everyone thinks so!
That's good.
They won't be feeling any extra pressure.
Are you saying it's natural for them to lose?!
What kind of instructor are you?
That's not what I said.
We just have a better chance of winning, that's all.
W-Well, I hope you're not all talk!
Okay, okay. I'll go cheer her up.
That said, I'm still missing a piece...
Oh?
I did not realise you ate so much.
Hey, Rico, getting lunch?
No, I just got here.
Oh, come on...
It couldn't be helped.
I was in the shower when an otherworldly
beauty appeared suddenly in front of my eyes.
Huh? Did you see a ghost or something?
Well, it turned out to be myself, in the mirror.
Nice punchline.
When you think about it,
there is nobody else in the world as beautiful as I.
You really are funny!
Goddess? What kind of idiot is she?
She might be a little pretty,
but she's nowhere near as good as her sister.
Hmph.
Is this...?
Yeah, your next opponent.
They won't go down easily.
If Misora and Lecty can complete their training,
we might have a fighting chance, but...
Remember, I have no intention of training with you.
Sure. Do as you like, I guess.
And I shall.
A goddess like me has no use for sweat and toil.
But... Please! I can't... Oh, no!
Sit still! I can't do this properly!
O-Okay... Please be gentle...
Okay... Here I come...
Oh!
That's soothing!
Okay, my turn.
Okay.
You know, isn't Kanata-san's training getting tougher lately?
Yeah...
I hate to admit it, but his training is working.
I can feel my skills gradually improving.
At this rate, we might have a chance in the next match!
You're right, but...
Hey! Are you done changing?
What are you doing?! Voyeur!
Naked kids don't interest me.
Since you two are working real hard,
I thought I might treat you both to some ice cream.
Ice cream!
Um... Sorry, but we have business to take care of.
I know!
But we have to think about the next match!
Ice cream...
I'll get you your ice cream later.
So?
My time is precious, as I am a goddess, after all.
I'll be blunt with you.
Rico, I want you to join us in training.
I don't want us to be called losers anymore.
I don't want to keep losing.
And for that, we need all of us to be together.
Lecty gave me the same invitation before, but the answer is still no.
I, being a goddess, have nothing to gain from training.
There's no way that's true!
Kanata would definitely be able to teach you something!
I hate to admit it, but I think he can make us stronger.
But I know now that he thinks about us seriously!
Sure, do as you like, I guess.
That is because you are mere mortals.
The man doesn't try to train me, don't you see?
T-That's...
Is that all? Then I shall...
Fine. No training, then.
But I want you to at least join us in the match.
I have no interest in humiliating myself by joining a match I know I will lose.
Rico-san...
Please.
Misora-san!
Please...
W-Wait...
Join us in-
What...?
What are you doing?
A D-ranked fireteam was downed last night while on patrol.
Has a chimera appeared?
Indeed.
They are the commanders of the smaller Devil Beetles.
We can't let that thing near Mistgun.
So...
Be at ease.
That is what the Special Duty Fireteam and I are for.
By the way, how is Kanata Age's fireteam?
I believe their ranked match is coming soon.
What is it?
It's just...
I believe you were asking about E601 just the other day, too.
Just a coincidence.
Ouch!
You'd never turn down a treat unless you had something on your mind.
Stop treating me like a greedy pig!
We're not scheming anything!
You're right, fighting when you know you'd lose is pretty uncool.
That is correct, as I always am-
But whining about not having a chance isn't my style, either.
You know nothing about-
Hey! What are you...
That's why, Misora, I'm going to hand you the key to victory.
The key... to victory?
Wait... Wait...
Nee-san...
Unfortunate.
I had a bad dream. That is due cause for tardiness.
Why can't those fool instructors see?
Yuri-san...
Why would such a wonderful person... be so close to that traitor?
Did he trick her, the pure-minded Yuri-san?!
Would you happen to be... a stalker?
What a scoundrel!
I suppose it's only natural.
My irresistible beauty is at fault.
Here, feel free to-
Misora, I'm only going to show you this move once.
Pay attention.
The Gladius!
The sword of destruction that you used, as Chronos...
A magic cannon sword battle art: Strike Blaster.
This is the move you're going to learn.
T-That powerful move, for me?
Don't release any excess magic power.
Knead it inside your body, and pour it into your sword.
Like this?
Misora, to be honest, your sword skills and shooting skills are both very amateur.
I knew that, but...
I can't be bothered to start you from basics.
That's why I'm teaching you this move.
Is this really the key to victory?
Your most powerful asset is your magic power capacity.
Using it to power a one-shot, one-kill attack...
That's the only plan we have.
Now, shoot!
Strike... Blaster!
I did it!
Huh?
I didn't expect the magic power load to be so heavy.
How do you keep so calm?
Really?
I'm adding this to the regular cannon fire training.
But you'll only get three shots per day.
Understood?
He's showing signs of magic power exhaustion.
I thought he used to be an elite.
Use it to cut open a path for you and your friends to move forward.
Y-Yeah...
Hey, are you just going to leave your hand on my head?!
It's at exactly the right height.
Let me go!
My head is no handrest!
With Misora's magic power reserves,
we can definitely turn the tide of a battle.
But...
Why are they flirting like that?
What's wrong, Lecty?
You don't seem to be concentrating.
Um...
Don't I get something?
Like with Misora-san?
No.
Oh, okay...
Created by Albert Eisenach, the Sword God.
Honed and improved by his descendants thereafter...
The Eisenach-style magic twinsword art.
It's been drilled into you thoroughly.
Remember the training we did to let you bring it out?
If you get it, then come at me!
Y-Yes!
I still wasn't able to score a single hit...
You've made some huge improvements, though.
You can land straight blows without looking away.
I'm just frantic...
But I do feel less nervous.
Yeah, you're doing well.
Does he have to touch girls so often?!
But it is true, both Misora and Lecty have improved.
If I study under him, will I be able to reach her...?
Foolish.
Where did he go?
Rico? I was wondering who it was.
W-Why are you here?!
Hey, you're...
This is nothing!
Oh, do you need them to activate your Clairvoyance?
Yes, that is correct...
Wait, how do you know about my Clairvoyance?!
Clairvoyance is the the highest-ranking Detection-type skill.
Well, how else would you see us from this distance?
The move you taught Misora-
Is that the key to victory that you spoke of?
Yeah.
I see.
If Misora masters it, she would truly be formidable.
However, it is useless in a match.
Oh?
It does not take a goddess like me to realise that the move's long charge-up time is the prime opening for a strike.
To use that move, one would require a skilled Vanguard and Rear Guard who can protect-
That's right.
And your ability to see that right away is the cornerstone of our fireteam.
Sniping, analysis, wide-range battlefield awareness and decision making...
Those skills that you learned by yourself-
They are more valuable than your Clairvoyance.
Wait! Wait! Just you wait!
Um, so, wait a moment.
What are you saying?
You just said Misora is the key to victory!
Hmm? I didn't tell you?
There are multiple keys to victory.
You did not!
Misora, Lecty, and Rico.
You three are each the keys to victory.
But you never forced me to train.
You never even showed interest in me!
Oh, that.
I was waiting for Misora and Lecty to catch up.
What?
You really do have godly skills.
I think so, at least.
Hmm? Is that so?
What is it?!
Please, Rico.
I need you.
I want you.
W-What are you saying?!
Have you gone mad?!
You know, I can train you, and make strategies.
But the most important thing is your will to win.
Will...
Do you want to be called losers for the rest of your lives?
Or do you want to climb out of that?
It's for you to decide.
I...
Rico didn't show up at the fireteam room today.
Is she really going to skip the match, too?
You two are late.
And here my godly self went through the trouble of coming to training.
How dare you keep me waiting?
Rico-san, you came!
Who do you think did more waiting, idiot?
Looks like the keys to victory made it just in time.
I'm so glad it's 601!
Easy win guaranteed!
Let's have a victory party afterwards!
So annoying!
It is the nature of people of poor calibre to look down on others.
Doesn't that include you?
I'm starting to get nervous!
Didn't I tell you?
Upsetting this atmosphere is really a blast.
You didn't.
You did not.
No, you didn't.
Here we go!
Yes!
W-What is it?!
Air raid alert!
Devil Beetles approaching Mistgun!
All fireteams of rank D and above, prepare to sortie!
Air raid alert!
Devil Beetles approaching Mistgun!
You had to choose this moment, didn't you?
Devil Beetles...!
All fireteams of rank D and above...
Chloe-senpai, the enemies are here!
The Archenar class is the smallest Devil Beetle we know.
They attack in swarms, so we have to be careful.
The mantis-like Procyon class is one step bigger.
Thanks for the instructions!
Wait! This is not the time for that!
Sorry!
Next episode, The Skies, Taken.
Data viitoare
Cerurile au fost luate
Keep your eyes open for Chloe and her adventures!
This is not the time for that, either!