Cu 3 ani în urmă
Și noi ar trebui să luptăm, căpitane.
Nu am ajuta cu nimic.
Niciuna din armele noastre nu reușește să rănească chestiile alea.
Nu avem de ales decât să
ne punem baza în Vânători.
Interceptați-i!
Prima linie va cădea dacă
vor reuși să treacă de noi!
E-E de rău! Rangul nostru e prea mic ca să avem vreo șansă!
La naiba... Îmi...
pierd cunoștința...
Magie de vindecare?
Uimitor. M-a vindecat într-o secundă!
Ai grijă!
Byung-gu, nu te mișca!
Yoonho!
Mă ocup!
Vânătorii de rang S...
Vânătorii de rang S sunt aici!
Ai luat-o mult prea în față, Byung-gu.
Scuze. Voiam să ajut cât mai mulți oameni.
În plus, știam că voi doi mă veți proteja.
Nu cred că acela e bossul.
Probabil e doar liderul acestui grup.
Byung-gu, ocupă-te de răniți.
Am înțeles, Yoonho!
Să mergem, Eunseok!
Recepționat!
Ține asta!
Ești un adevărat monstru.
Ce?
Se pare că nici liderul grupului nu e.
Începe să devină interesant.
Se pare că au ajuns la timp.
Bănuiesc că e rândul nostru acum.
Dle Choi, oricând sunteți pregătit!
Bun.
La atac!
Cu mai bine de un deceniu în urmă,
niște portale, care conectau lumea noastră cu o altă dimensiune, și-au făcut apariția.
Dincolo de acele portale se aflau ființe bizare numite „creaturi magice”,
imune la armele obișnuite.
Cei care reușesc să obțină abilitățile necesare luptei împotriva acestor monștri
sunt numiți Vânători.
În funcție de puterea
magică pe care o au,
Vânătorii primesc unul din următoarele ranguri:
S, A, B, C, D sau E; enumerate în ordine descendentă.
Dar, o dată ce și-au obținut puterile, oricât de multe efort ar depunde,
nu pot deveni mai puternici.
3 ani mai târziu
În prezent
Mult succes în raidul de astăzi.
Mulțumesc.
Hei, Kim!
A trecut ceva timp!
Hei, dacă nu este
chiar Park! Ce faci aici?
Am crezut că renunțasei
la viața de Vânător.
Asta era înainte să
am un al doilea copil.
Înțeleg. Dacă raidul va merge bine, vei reuși să faci niște bani frumoși.
Dar pot spune că am emoții.
A trecut atât de mult timp încât nu știu dacă mai sunt în formă.
Și nu pot spune că eram prea puternic.
Hei, uite-l pe Sung!
Cum merge, Sung?
Ne bucurăm să te vedem
pe o vreme așa răcoroasă.
Mă bucur să lucrez cu voi din nou.
Hei, Sung! Ai mâncat ceva înainte să vii?
Da. Am mâncat bine.
Care-i treaba cu el? E un Vânător important? Văd că toată lumea îl salută.
De fapt, e exact opusul.
S-a alăturat după ce
renunțasei tu, iar acel puști...
Ei bine, porecla lui este
„Cel mai slab Vânător din lume”.
Cel mai slab? Serios?
Da.
O „plimbare” printr-o temniță de rang E l-a trimis direct la spital.
Nu cred că există vreun
Vânător mai slab decât el.
Serios? Chiar atât de rău e?
Ca regulă de bază, orice raid la care e chemat și el va fi floare la ureche.
Am înțeles.
N-aș vrea să ne audă bârfind despre el,
deci haide să ne oprim aici.
Am auzit deja tot ce ați spus.
Deși, e purul adevăr.
O, nu, Jinwoo! Ai fost rănit din nou?!
Ah, Joohee... Se pare că
vom lucra din nou împreună.
Lasă asta. Ce ai pățit la față?
Cam același lucru ca de obicei...
Chiar trebuie să fii mai atent!
Am auzit că ai ajuns și la spital.
Era o temniță de rang E,
deci eu am fost singurul rănit.
Nu era nimeni care să
aibă vrăji de vindecare?
Toți ceilalți erau de rang mai mare, deci... au decis că nu era nevoie.
Serios?!
Asta e îngrozitor!
S-au gândit numai la ei!
E în regulă. A fost vina mea
pentru că sunt așa de slab.
Doar știi cum stau lucrurile când vin vorba de mine, Joohee.
M-am obișnuit cu asta.
Se pare că a venit momentul să intrăm.
Haide.
Eu voi fi liderul vostru pentru acest raid.
Numele meu e Song Chiyul.
Mă bucur să lucrez cu voi.
Yeah, that makes sense.
Mr. Song's got the most
skills out of anyone here.
It's a relief to have him in charge.
Pleasure to be working with you, Mr. Song.
Bun. E toată lumea pregătită?
Să mergem.
Hei, Sung.
Try and hang in there behind us,
and don't get injured this time.
Bine.
Haide să dăm tot ce putem.
A knife with barely any magic power in it...
Asta e tot ce mi-am putut permite.
Totuși, e mai bun decât nimic.
Today, I'm gonna see this through!
Bine ați revenit, dle director.
Cum au mers lucrurile cu administrația?
The usual talking points.
Dungeon breaks are a problem,
but they still want the resources that
can be collected from inside dungeons.
Their demands make logical sense.
And we hunters make a living
by selling those resources.
The stones collected from defeated beasts—
these essence stones.
They're valuable.
Am reușit!
În sfârșit, am obținut una.
Jinwoo!
Stai în spate, Joohee!
Merg să mă ocup de ceilalți monștri.
Joohee, tu ocupă-te de Sung!
Bine!
Vei fi bine! Te voi vindeca acum!
The essence stones collected
from high-ranked beasts
can be turned into powerful weapons
and gear for fighting other beasts.
Mana crystals that can
be collected from dungeons
have a similar application,
but they're less potent.
But the government's
interested in a different use.
As a new power source.
Safer than nuclear, more efficient
than water, wind, or geothermal,
and one that doesn't pollute
the atmosphere like fossil fuels.
The ideal clean energy source.
They're working on a way
to generate electricity
using essence stones and mana crystals.
A rare fuel source that only
hunters are able to collect...
Which is why the duty that rests on
hunters' shoulders is such a great one.
Am reușit!
Da! Am învins bossul!
That's Mr. Song for you!
We did it!
Jinwoo, you're not staying on as a hunter
just because you're stubborn, right?
If you keep this up, it's only a matter of time
until something much worse happens.
It's not just your midsection.
You're hurt all over!
Sorry...
I don't want an apology!
I'm worried about you!
Have you all collected your loot yet?
As much as we could, at least.
There's not much in the way of
mana crystals here, either.
We're not gonna earn much
at all, at this rate.
I guess it's over.
And all I have to show for it
is an E-Rank essence stone.
Hardly worth almost dying for.
Hey!
Take a look at this!
A cave?
Some kind of tunnel?
It seems to go pretty far.
A double dungeon, huh?
I'd heard rumors before, but...
We beat the dungeon boss,
but there's no sign of it shutting down.
Yeah, I thought that was strange.
Which means...
Yeah, there's more loot
to be found down here.
Listen up, everyone.
When encountering
unexpected cases like this,
standard procedure is to wait
for orders from the Hunter's Association.
Hang on a sec, Mr. Song...
Doesn't that mean that the new guys
are gonna hog all the good stuff?
It's still part of a D-Rank dungeon.
It should be fine, right?
He's got another kid on the way.
And we didn't find many mana crystals.
It'd be okay to bend
the rules a bit, wouldn't it?
Or no?
I understand how you feel.
But the fact remains that it'd be a risk.
Let's take a vote.
I dunno...
I'm in!
I say no.
No.
Let's check it out.
Same.
Yeah.
I don't think so.
I say we go.
Likewise.
Sorry, but... I don't want to.
That makes six in favor, six against.
You're the only one left, Sung.
What do you think?
I-I...
Even a D-Rank dungeon is dangerous for me.
But... Now that Dad's gone missing,
I'm the only one who can
provide for my family.
I need money for Mom's treatments...
and to send my sister to college.
I need this money!
Let's go.
Now, if you could touch the black
crystal with one hand, please.
Next, please.
You're a C-Rank?
We'd love you to join our guild.
Here's the contract.
You can find the labor
conditions detailed here...
Right. One B-Rank and two C-Ranks
have agreed to sign.
Things are going smoothly so far,
Guildmaster Choi.
That's wonderful to hear.
Age and gender aren't a factor.
If they seem like an asset, make an offer.
Not that we're likely to find anyone
who can compare to Cha Hae-in.
Someone! Catch them!
Out of the damn way!
Move! Or do you wanna get run over?!
E-Excuse me...
Here.
Thank you! Thank you so much!
That's Cha Hae-in!
Cha Hae-in!
The S-Rank hunter!
Oh, damn!
It's really her!
This is awesome!
I'm a huge fan!
E-Excuse me...
Can I shake your hand?
Look at her go!
That's an S-Rank hunter for you.
How long's it been since we entered the cave?
About 40 minutes.
The gate shouldn't close until an hour
after the boss is beaten,
so we'll have 20 minutes to spare.
Um... I'm sorry.
About what?
It's because I voted the way I did
that we're searching for the boss now.
You don't need to worry about me, so stop it.
Are you sure you're okay?
Of course...
I'm not!
Have you already forgotten?!
If that attack had hit just a little higher,
you'd be dead right now, Jinwoo!
I was barely able to heal your arms
and legs, too! This is insane!
Are you sure you didn't hit your head?!
Because it seems like it!
Sorry...
It's true that having a B-Rank healer like
Joohee around has saved me more than once.
Do you actually understand the problem here?
Yeah.
Well, in that case, maybe you should
treat me to show your gratitude.
Or what? You don't like the thought
of taking me out to eat?
Th-Th-That's not it at all!
We're here!
It's the boss chamber.
Rare to see an actual door on one of these.
It's kind of intimidating.
Well, I'm going in.
No way am I going back empty-handed now.
Same here. Let's do it.
The team moves onward together.
That was the call, right, Leader Song?
Yeah, you're right.
To the newly awakened: I am the chairman
of the Hunter's Association, Go Gunhee.
Among you there are bound to be those
who choose to be hunters,
and those who decide not to.
It's been over ten years
since the gates first appeared,
and yet there's still a great deal
we don't know about the dungeons.
To become a hunter is to risk your life.
Even those who have grown accustomed to raids
cannot afford to let their guards down.
You must never grow arrogant, or careless.
Dacă vreți să supraviețuiți, acesta e cel mai bun sfat
Please, be afraid.
Hey, the place lit up.
Dig the atmosphere!
I've never seen a dungeon like this before.
What's with the statues?
They look so old.
And some have instruments.
This one's way bigger than the rest.
Damn, that's huge.
What it supposed to be?
There's something creepy about it.
Gotta say, I'm not seeing any beasts.
Good point.
Not a single one...
What is this? A magic circle?
Mr. Song! Something's written over here!
In the ancient script? Let's take a look...
"The Commandments of the Cartenon Temple."
"First, revere God."
"Second, praise God."
Jingwoo!
"Third, prove your faith to God."
That big statue... I saw its eyes move.
It's been watching us!
"Those who do not follow these laws..."
It can't be. You must have imagined it.
"...will not leave alive"?
Hey! The door just shut!
But why?!
Are we trapped in here now?
This is what I was worried about!
You guys didn't take this seriously,
and now look!
We never should've come this way!
I'm leaving!
You can have the treasure,
or whatever else you find in here.
See ya!
Get away from there!
No!
Are you kidding me?
They moved!
Are we supposed to fight those things?!
The guy who just died...
Was he D-Rank?
If nothing else, he was stronger
than me and my E-Rank.
And he was just... in an instant...
This doesn't make sense!
This is supposed to be a D-Rank dungeon!
There shouldn't be magic beasts
like this down here!
If these statues are moving... That means...
I've stood on the precipice of death
plenty of times before.
In my first raid ever, I got separated from
everyone else, and ended up stranded.
I've been attacked by E-Rank beasts
and spent weeks in a hospital afterward.
I almost starved to death
in a labyrinth before, too.
No matter how low-ranked the dungeon was,
I was always fighting for my life.
Most hunters are able to buy gear with the
money they make from selling essence stones,
so they can beat even stronger beasts,
and reap even bigger rewards.
But this cheap knife is the best I can afford.
If it breaks, I'll have to fight empty-handed.
These shoes are done for, too.
And so, day after day...
I've endured being mocked,
and put up with a life-threatening job
where the risks outweigh the rewards.
But even then, in order to survive,
I've learned to keep my eyes open
and look for opportunities.
That might be why I was able to tell...
Toată lumea, la pământ!
Ce naiba?!
Nobody mentioned this!
Ce se petrece aici?!
De unde să știu eu?!
Sunteți bine?
Da. Dar tu, Kim?
Și eu sunt bine.
Nu mai vreau...
Nu mai vreau!
Ce se petrece?
Cum e posibil așa ceva?
Suntem închiși aici.
S-a zis cu noi.
Vom muri. Vom muri.
Vom muri cu toții!
Can't remember to forget
Little boy who lost the bet
Now I'm racking up the kills
I got to pay the bills, the bills
Short cut to be a star
Wasn't born to raise the bar
Dreptatea înșelătoare e precum o alarmă
care nu poate fi pornită de nimeni
Failing feeling
Don't clean up the emotions of joy, anger, sorrow and pleasure
Let your voice be free
Let's get 'em
So givin' yourself
Ya givin' yourself the best shot
Be givin' yourself
Don't you gotta get solo?
What you gonna get? Swear it!
Don't you dare forget solo
Ya give it your best shot!
Go reach out to get ya
Gotta go reach out to get ya
Just go reach out to get ya
Get up, reach out for it
Go reach out to get ya
Gotta go reach out to get ya
Just go reach out to get ya
Just get in, get out, get on to it
Ayy, game over but they gave him all the cheat codes
Little kiddy in the gutter with the bloody nose
On the cover but he doesn't even read those
The headlines, the headlines
So jacked but he hasn't got an ego
Local boy and he came up from a zero
Cu fiecare luptă vedem cum puterea îi crește
Și crește
S-o facem!
Episodul 2: Dacă aș mai fi avut o șansă