No way...
Brother?
You feeling lonely, Gear?
I'm sad to see you going away, too.
But it's dangerous here,
and you don't want to cause
trouble for people, do you?
So I have to send you somewhere safe.
There are things you have to do,
whether you like it or not.
Someday you'll understand.
See you.
Stay safe.
When I grow up, I'm joining the army.
I'm going to join the
army and fight with you, Dad.
By the time you grow up,
the war will be over.
I'll end it myself!
Dad?
Lost Star & KID
So you're a decoy?
It doesn't matter.
The only things past me is the prison,
and it's a dead end.
When the rest of them come back,
I'll destroy them then.
Until then...
I'll have my fun with you.
No, you won't!
What? An exploding round?
Take this.
What's your skin made out of?
Your weak weapons can't touch me.
If my bow won't work,
then I don't have a choice.
So you're going to surrender?
Nope.
This is perfect.
I'll try it on him.
My new weapon...
Shooting!
No way...
It didn't work?
Don't tell me, the reason you were so
confident is because you had Shooting?
If it was...
did I just crush your pride?
It's okay.
Even if our Shooting is even,
there are lots of things
I'm better than him at.
So I'm going to win!
It hit him, so why didn't it work?
What's happening?
I guess you don't know
that you can protect yourself
from Shooting with Force Field.
What?
It's useless.
It'll take more than one of your
shots to break my Force Field!
If you admit defeat,
I won't continue to hurt you.
I'd rather you be unhurt when I have fun with you.
Admit defeat.
Admit defeat?
No way!
I haven't lost yet.
There are still things
I'm better at than you!
More exploding rounds?
It's useless.
She hid?
It doesn't matter.
No matter where you hide,
or where you attack from,
it won't work on me.
It's not much of a chance,
but there's still hope.
He said he could block one shot,
but if many hit him at the
same time, it might work.
To fire a shot, I need to gather
life energy in my fingers,
and keep it from overflowing
until I release it.
If I could store up many shots,
instead of just one...
I could maybe shoot a
Shot several times more
powerful than a regular one.
It's all speculation,
but I won't know until I try.
First gather the energy for one shot,
and then more...!
I did it!
But it's really hard...
I can't hold it in...
The blood in my whole body is boiling.
My fingernails are going to tear off...
My fingers are about to break.
But if I make the slightest
noise, he'll find me!
This is hard... But if I don't charge up more,
I won't be able to beat him.
Enough for three shots!
No!
This is it.
I can't hold it anymore.
I can't!
No, I can still do this!
I'm better at this than anyone.
I've held so much in for so long.
For such a long, long time.
So...
I can hold it in better than anybody.
There you are!
Take this!
7-way Shot!
I won, somehow, but...
Holding it in isn't good for you.
I've not seen my dad
since the day we said goodbye,
and now he's right in front of me.
Dad...
Is that you, Gear?
You're alive?
I thought you died during that attack.
I see.
I'm glad.
I'm really glad.
Sorry to interrupt this emotional reunion,
but there's no time.
We'll continue the plan.
Right.
We need to get him out of here.
No, we don't.
General Alex.
Gear is going to absorb you.
Is that all right?
Ramses's orders?
That's just like her. It's a good plan.
Yeah, that's fine.
Please do.
We're not going to save him?
Absorb... what?
I told you.
His life.
If the general was well,
we were to rescue him.
But if he was hurt to the point
where he couldn't aid in the fight,
you, his son, are to absorb his power.
That's our plan.
Wait.
We may still be able to save him!
Are you stupid?
You're going to take me back like this?
Give me a break.
If you move me, I'll die.
No...
Just do it.
Absorb me already.
To absorb someone,
you need merely touch them.
If you touch them and think
about wanting to absorb them,
and they want to give you their life,
you will absorb them in an instant.
You guys are Killers, right?
Please! Any of you! Absorb me.
You simply absorb.
Other's lives.
If you want to get better, that is.
I want to be stronger.
I knew that you could do
it if you tried, brother.
I can't!
I told you there'd be things
you'd have to sacrifice
if you want to be strong.
Isn't that the path you chose?
The strongest Killer in Segua's army.
He's the best person
possible to absorb.
I want to be stronger, yes...
But not like this!
This isn't just to make you stronger.
It's for Segua, and for
General Alex himself.
For my dad?
If he dies now,
he leaves nothing behind.
But if you absorb him,
he will live on within you.
Shouldn't you, his son,
carry on his power to stop
his death from being meaningless?
I understand how insane it
is to end your reunion
with your father like this.
But you understand, don't you?
What you really need to do right now.
For Segua.
For my dad...
Even if it's not what I want to do...
There are things you have to do,
whether you like it or not.
Someday you'll understand.
There's no time, right?
What's stopping you?
I'm telling you to do it.
But I...
When this happened,
meeting my father and learning about
the Killers was all just so sudden,
I felt like it was a dream.
But I knew what I had to do.
Now that I can relax,
I'm getting sleepy...
Dad!
Accept my power, Gear.
Gear...
Before I entrust everything to you,
there's something you need to know.
Long ago, Segua had two Killers.
We were the Segua Army's main force and always fought on the front lines.
We were bound by tighter bonds than anyone.
But one day we were badly wounded,
and surrounded by the
enemy with nothing left to do
but wait for death.
So the two of us are
going to die together?
No, there's still a way to survive.
If one of us absorbs the
other's life and power,
they may be able to break
through the enemy.
But this plan was an awful one.
One of us would die,
and the other would lose
someone they cared about.
We couldn't decide who would die.
We couldn't decide at all...
So in the end we chose an insane way
to decide who would kill the other.
Take care of Gear for me...
The great power I gained from absorbing
the one I loved let me survive.
Even after I made it home alive,
my regrets never left me.
The reason I sent you
away from the battle
when you were young was
because I was afraid
of having someone I
cared about so close.
I wanted to ensure my loved ones
were never caught in the fight again.
So I wanted to keep all
of them away from me.
I'm a failure.
Even in the very end,
I'm still making you suffer.
I'm no father at all.
I'm sorry, Gear.
That's not true!
I was happy... I was happy
to see you in the end.
I was happy.
Thank you.
My dad gave me
the greatest power in the Segua Army,
and the resolve to accept whatever
happened, no matter awful it was...
He gave me those things.
My whole body feels
numb and I can't move.
I hope the enemy doesn't find me.
Ooh... Well, what do we have here?
D. Fisher bought it?
Awesome.
Let me go!
Did you kill Fisher?
I did.
I guess the Tatoland army
isn't that strong.
True.
You're pretty impressive, girl,
killing that monster all by yourself.
Of course...
It looks like you can't move now.
We have to ask you a lot of things.
You're in for a lot of torture later.
No, I can't move!
You're hot enough that torturing
you will be lots of fun.
Gear...
Thanks, Opal.
The mission is complete, Opal.
Huh? What's all this?
Looks like you just came
from the prison,
but I don't see General Alex.
Let me guess: you came to absorb him,
but you freaked out and despaired
when you saw him, right?
He's Boys.
Bays's younger brother.
That's right.
I'm Boys, the younger brother
of the ultimate warrior, Bays.
I'm the one who defeated General Alex.
And I'm the one who
tortured him down here!
He never said anything,
so I accidentally overdid it.
But what did you think?
He was torn apart so badly,
it was practically a form of art,
but he was still barely alive, right?
That's what makes me
a genius at torture!
Tejirof, the mission's over, right?
Of course, I'd have
more fun with a girl—
You told me when the mission was over
I could fight all I wanted, right?
I did.
This was the birth of
Segua's new messiah.
I'm going to fight here until
I've taken over Hope Fortress!
My, my...
I guess I'll fight a little more.
Nel, take care of Opal.
I'll be going for a bit, too.
Where?
I'm going to finish things.
In battle and you-know-what,
taking care of them when
you're done is important.
What the hell is he?
I can't leave my dad's body like that.
I'm going to take over this fortress!
Hey, there.
So you made it out
on your own after all.
Impressive.
Didn't have much else to do.
The mission succeeded.
Did it.
One of ours is kicking butt inside.
But well, I figured if you interrupted him,
he wouldn't be able to finish.
So I'll finish you here.
Finish me?
This time I won't let my guard down.
You won't get the drop on me this time.
Yeah, you're strong and I
don't want to fight you.
I really didn't want to get serious
in a fight I was just hired on for...
But if he's working that hard,
then I think I should, too.
I can do anything I want, you know.
Eh, whatever.
I'll pass.
Looks like Tatoland lost
this fight anyway.
I'll withdraw for today.
Glad to hear it.
If you'll leave, that makes this easy.
I don't want to get hurt.
Can I ask something?
That wall of light you used to seal me.
What is that?
Oh, that?
That's a type of Puzzle.
Puzzle Magic Academy.
I learned all the
techniques I use there.
If you're interested, drop by.
Thanks.
Segua wins!
Gear's attack drove the
enemy from Hope Fortress.
And the battle of Hope Fortress ended.
In the end, Gear came
to the battlefield.
I wanted to save him from the pain.
I think it's okay.
You did everything you could.
You did everything I would've
hoped for, as well.
You must be tired.
Our time is over.
Let's leave Segua... to our son.
Yeah, you're right.
After the battle of Hope Fortress,
Segua lost its hero, General Alex,
but the whole country was excited
over the arrival of their new hero,
and their first major
victory in a long time.
And the rumors of the
Segua warrior who took
Hope Fortress spread over the
whole continent in an instant.
People called him "Blue Sonic."
Tatoland
Mister, it didn't work this time.
Sometimes you win,
and sometimes you lose.
We can retake Hope Fortress.
This is getting fun.
There's plenty more fun to be had
on the continent of Consume.
Ruler of Tatoland and the Legendary Invader
I. Vazer
Havid Republic
Destruction is the
beginning of creation.
The die has been cast.
Havid Republic Samurai CEO
Kichou
We will be the ones to build
a new era: Kichou Land.
Ganp Federation
Blue Sonic?
I didn't know there was anyone that
strong still on the continent.
Ganp Federation Wave Motion Warrior
Tofig
If he's stronger than I am,
I'd love to meet him.
Kingdom of Slovia
Segua? I'm not interested.
Kingdom of Slovia Ultimate Queen
Crystal
The only man I want to defeat is him.
Elil Republic
That's another big one
you hunted today!
Are you fired up because you're
concerned about Segua?
You're not?
You're concerned about Segua, right?
But you're thinking about the guy
they call Blue Sonic, right?
Elil Republic Hero
Myomuto
Yes.
Ninteldo Empire Gambling Hall
Hey, who's that guy?
I can't believe it!
And supposedly he just
learned the rules today!
I'm doing great today!
Zelig?
Good grief.
You really were playing
here, weren't you?
Know your role.
You're the general of the armies.
Right, right.
So does this mean it's
time to get going?
That's the genius, General Zelig?
We're taking four generals?
Pretty gorgeous.
Ninteldo 6 Generals : Infinite Warrior
Karvey
Yeah, let's go, Zelig.
I wouldn't underestimate them.
Ninteldo 6 Generals: Miss Reset
Fae
Overconfidence brings destruction.
Just don't forget the words of Marcus.
Ninteldo Six Generals: Royal Prince
Guligi
Ninteldo has but one goal!
Ninteldo Six Generals: The Man Who Solves All Mysteries
Zelig
Guess we'll go finish this, then.
Hey there, hero.
What are you doing out here alone?
Playing with yourself?
Tejirof?
You're looking pretty normal, actually.
I thought you'd be more depressed.
About my dad? Not really.
I was ready for it.
Actually, maybe I'm more happy than anything.
Fighting and winning made
someone I know so happy...
But I still don't really
understand things.
Too much has happened at once.
I'm sure.
But that's the path you chose.
Yeah.
Nobody will admire you just
because you're strong.
People respect the ones that
choose the difficult path,
even if they're weak.
Stronger than anyone. Faster. Cooler.
I could never be like you.
You really amaze me, brother,
but I don't respect you!
I know.
But even so...
I'm going to keep running.
To the center of the world!