I don't have many memories
of my dad from when I was young.
All I remember...
I win.
Is that we used to play
rock, paper, scissors a lot.
That's not fair!
I only got to eat two!
You're telling me it's not fair
to decide by rock, paper, scissors?
There are lots of things in
the world that aren't fair.
But accepting them all is life.
I didn't understand the
meaning of the words he used,
or what he was trying to say.
But I remembered it for some reason.
Like he knew what was going
to happen in the future...
Killer
You've gotten a lot better.
I suppose since you don't have any
preconceptions getting in the
way, you're learning fast.
You can still get stronger.
Because you're a Killer.
I've heard that a lot
since I came here.
But what's a "Killer"?
All right, I'll tell you.
There once was a nation that conquered
most of the land of Consume.
The Great Atarika Empire.
The Atarika Empire was on
the verge of conquering
the continent with the overwhelming
size of its forces.
But before that could, it fell apart.
In order to expand its armies,
it would gather soldiers of any
kind, no matter what they were.
But because they brought in
bandits and thugs, as well,
it decreased the quality of their troops
and cost them the people's trust.
In the end, a coup d'etat
brought them down.
This was crash was
known as the Atarika Shock.
I know that, but what does
that have to do with "Killer"?
Let me finish.
After the Atarika Shock,
Consume fell into chaos.
But all the nations
avoided unnecessarily
increasing the size of their armies,
in order to avoid a repeat
of what happened to Atarika.
They would make strong
individual soldiers
and put them into elite squads.
In other words, quality over quantity.
A race of people with
power greater than that
of normal humans were
created: the Killers.
But why am I one?
Perhaps one of your mom or dad's
ancestors was a Killer?
I'm told it's genetic.
My family...
Come to think of it, I heard my mom
and dad were both pretty strong.
Maybe they were.
They say wars these days
are decided by how many
Killers are in an army.
Anyway, that's basically it.
So basically it's just
a very strong person?
Tejirof didn't tell me at that time...
what the real meaning of
the name "Killer" was...
or how cruel it was.
Hey, Big Tits.
Gear's training is taken
care of for a while.
Now it's my turn to train you.
Alone with him?
Hell no.
I-I don't have anything
to learn from you.
Nice shot.
See?
My skill with a bow
is perfect, isn't it?
The bow and arrow's perfect, yeah...
What?
Come out and say it.
You're right.
You have a good eye and
you're an accurate shot.
But I think you're a little
lacking as a fighter.
But I can put something better than
an arrow into your open hole.
Better than an arrow?
Ranged tactics.
Shooting.
Shooting?
You've never heard of it?
My my...
the Segua army's full of
cherries and virgins, huh?
Every Killer has a style of
combat they're best with.
In Gear's case, for example,
the ability to change life
energy into power, Action.
In my and Ramses's case,
it's Puzzle, the ability to rearrange life
energy into other kinds of energy.
And yours is Shooting.
A method of combat created
by the legendary invader
of Consume, I. Vazer.
If you can master it,
you'll be able to fight at long range
while still taking advantage
of your skill with a bow.
I'll show you how to
do it the first time.
A girl like you should be able
to take it the rest of the way.
Concentrate your mind
on these three fingers.
Don't relax until I tell you to.
What?
Something's gathering in my fingers...
My fingers...
are going to explode!
Hey... stop!
Not yet. Endure it.
How long do I have to endure this?
No!
I...
I can't hold it in anymore!
That's the basic skill
of Shooting. "Shot."
For the next four days you
need to learn to master it.
Four days, huh?
Fine. I'll do it.
I understand the theory.
Hold... and then fire, right?
Don't be in such a hurry.
First practice gathering the energy...
I can't control the power
as much as I'd like to yet.
But I can do this.
If I've got four days.
There he is!
There you are, Tejirof-san.
You're Gear's little sister,
Nel-chan, right?
Yes.
You remembered me!
My brother's looking for you.
He says he wants more training.
Yeah, I was just on my way.
Don't rush me.
I'm surprised you knew
I was here, though.
Shooting practice is dangerous,
so I'd thought I'd chosen a
place where no one would come.
Um, I thought I could hear
your voice coming from here.
My voice...
Did she find me just from my voice?
I'd heard that when Maxley
village was attacked,
she survived, even though she
was only a child, but...
Does the power of a Killer
sleep within her, too?
Hey, Ears.
How do you feel about
helping your brother out?
W-Wow...
She was really able to dodge all
those arrows at this range?
Did I really do this?
Yes. Your power was just dormant.
There's no doubt about it.
You're a Killer.
How does it feel to be awakened?
Amazing...
I can see far away.
I can hear perfectly, too.
And my body can feel even
the slightest breeze.
This is
my...
It seems you have the power
to attune your senses to the
surrounding area: Online.
I'm sure it'll grow to be
something more in the future,
but even now, you could go into combat
and be very helpful.
I won't force you.
I'll leave the decision to you.
Combat?
Me?
Til...
Brother...
All right.
I'll... I'll fight, too!
So all four are ready?
That's good.
Ramses, I want to confirm something...
Does Gear know?
Since I first saw him,
I thought that might be the case...
A survivor of Maxley, and a Killer.
And when I saw that power, I was certain.
He's the son of General Alex.
And you're going through
with this cruel plan?
Segua can't lose all of its generals.
Does it bother you?
Nope. Not at all.
If I get paid, I'll do any job,
no matter how dirty.
I'm a dirty guy to begin with.
Take care of Gear.
Hey, Tejirof.
How many Killers are there?
How many of them?
I don't know.
Maybe hundreds?
Then just tell me the strong ones.
Let me see... the strong
ones would be...
The Emperor of the Ninteldo Empire,
the perfect Killer: Marcus.
Ninteldo's number two,
the genius who's known as the
"Man who solves all mysteries:"
Zelig.
The princess of one of
their allied nations,
Slovia, said to be of the highest
quality in Consume: Crystal.
The Samurai CEO of the
republic of Havid: Kichou.
The undefeated martial artist
of the Ganp Federation: Tofig.
And the man who's
known as the only hero
on the continent,
Myomuto, of the Elil Republic.
Even Marcus avoided fighting him.
They would be the ones to look out for.
Of course, there are Killers in Tatoland,
which we're attacking tomorrow.
D. Fisher, said to be three times
the size of an ordinary man.
The younger of the cursed
Brothers, the drinker, Boys.
The older of the cursed Brothers,
said to be the strongest
in Tatoland, Bays.
But all of them are people
we'll have to defeat.
If you want to get better, that is.
Yeah, I know.
We'll have to defeat them.
Sometimes you have to sacrifice
something to become stronger.
Are you prepared for that?
Yes. I still want to become stronger.
Hey, kid.
When did you realize you
wanted to join the military?
I don't know...
Maybe it was because
my dad was a soldier?
I haven't seen him since
I went to the village
when I was five, so I don't
really remember, but...
I do remember watching him defeat lots of
soldiers at once during practice matches.
It may have been watching that
when I decided to join the military.
I thought if I joined,
I might be able to see him.
But so far, I didn't see
anybody who looked like him.
I wonder what he's doing now.
Maybe he's dead.
I don't know.
Well... Maybe if you're a good boy,
you'll get to see him.
Our primary objective for today's operation
is to rescue General Alex,
who's being held in an underground cell.
While the decoy force draws
the enemy towards the front,
we'll go in from the back,
and head straight to his cell.
We'll avoid standing out or getting
into any unnecessary fights.
So Ears will use her Online
to search for traps and enemies.
Right.
Opal will snipe from far away.
Leave it to me.
And if we need you to, Gear,
you'll break through with your speed.
Yeah.
And if things get bad,
just remain calm.
I'll handle it.
Advance!
It's the Segua army!
The Segua army is attacking!
Everybody to your posts!
It's started.
Okay, let's hurry.
Hold up, guys.
There's a Seguan who's
collapsed over there.
Who?
A scout?
You're one of the scouts...
We underestimated them.
Be careful.
He's waiting at the rear gate.
The strongest warrior of Tatoland.
Bays!
Bays, huh?
That's a problem.
I'm done for.
I'm going to die here.
But... you guys are Killers, right?
Please! Any of you! Absorb me.
Please... absorb me...
Absorb you?
Impossible.
You know that.
You're not powerful enough.
Give up.
We'll avenge you, if nothing else.
So rest in peace.
You're right...
Bring victory to Segua for me...
What did he mean by absorb?
That's right.
You don't know yet, do you?
I guess you wouldn't...
You don't know why we're called "Killers."
Killers are people who
are strong to begin with,
but there's a way for
them to get stronger.
And it's easy.
You simply absorb.
Absorb?
Absorb what?
Other's lives.
Absorb their lives and become stronger.
That's why we're called "Killers."
People's lives?
I-I don't understand...
But then, shouldn't we have absorbed his?
It's not that easy.
There's a limit to how many
one person can absorb.
You have two marks,
so you can only absorb two.
There's a limit,
so you should only absorb someone
when it's more effective.
Effective?
You mean someone stronger?
Well, well...
Looks like we don't have time to talk.
He's come to us.
That's him?
Yes, that's right.
That's the strongest Killer in Tatoland,
Bays.
Yeah, I did.
I was bored.
I'm glad I won't be bored now.
This guy is the strongest
warrior in Tatoland, Bays?
I want to see how far my
strength can take me!
Okay, let's do this!
I can't advance...
This is a real fight?
Good.
You can judge these things now.
The fact that you can tell how strong
he is means you're growing.
If you'd jumped in, you would've died.
He's strong.
If we were to seriously fight him here,
we could lose two of us.
Two?
Don't you mean four?
What do we do?
If we waste time here,
the operation will fail.
Very well.
I'll...
stop him here.
Stop me?
You?
Alone?
Yeah. That's right.
Sorry, since you took the
trouble to come here...
But you're going to vanish
from the stage here.
Now, run.
Huh?
A wall of light.
I can't attack you from the outside,
but you can't attack it
from the inside, either.
Stay there and play with
yourself for a while.
See ya.
How's it going, Ears?
The decoy squad is working.
There aren't many enemies
within the fortress.
The wall of light holding Bays
will last twenty minutes at best.
If he gets out we have a problem.
We need to keep going before that happens.
Wait, guys.
There's a strong aura up ahead.
He's big... like a fish?
A fish?
Probably D. Fisher.
What do we do?
Stop him with another wall of light?
No, that won't be possible anymore.
It's not something I can use that often.
It's a bit risky, but we'll
have to use another decoy.
Okay.
Then I'll be the decoy.
Don't rush ahead, kid.
Your job's to destroy the doors
while the decoy draws him off.
And you've got a bigger job coming up.
A bigger job?
So, Opal, you're the decoy.
All right, I'll do it.
Just so we're clear, the fish
man is stronger than you.
Draw him off and buy time,
then withdraw when you have a chance.
Got it!
There's no time, right?
Let's go.
I'll lure him away from you guys.
Wasn't that funny?
Not at all.
The guys fighting outside
must be having fun.
I want to smash somebody.
I hope somebody gets this far.
There you are.
Stop moving around!
Crap!
Tejirof told me to pull back...
But I'll defeat him here!
This is the prison where General
Alex is being held captive.
General Alex.
The man who's said to be
the strongest in Segua.
I wonder what he's like.
No...
Why?
Dad?
I can hold it in better than anybody!
I was happy...
I can do anything, if I want.
Even so, I'm going to keep running,
towards the center of the world...
Episode 3 is Being Worked On Right Now!