Go forward...
Forward!
I won't run away...
Not anymore!
I won't go back!
Go forward...
with all my power!
I knew that you could do
it if you tried, brother.
I wish I could have seen you do more.
Til! Til! Til!
I swear I won't run away anymore.
I won't go back.
I won't stop.
Even if my legs break,
even if I can no longer see,
I'll keep running forward.
And you'll be watching
me from somewhere,
won't you, Til?
And so I started running to
the center of the world.
The continent of Consume,
a land where war never stops.
There, the blue-eyed Segua Kingdom
and the Red-Eyed Ninteldo Empire
struggled for control of the land.
But for the last few years,
with the ascension of Emperor Marcus,
the forces of Ninteldo rapidly grew in power,
and they and their allies
controlled 90% of the continent.
The Segua Kingdom was losing the war.
The Hard Wars of Consume
Capital of Segua, Outori
We finally made it, Til.
Vice-General Ramses!
You're being very loud.
What's wrong?
M-My apologies, Vice-General Ramses.
A strange man is asking to
be let into the military.
Who?
He's definitely a Seguaian,
but I don't know about him...
He says his name is Gear.
Gear?
So you're the one who wants
to join our army, right?
Um, I want to join the Segua army.
Please!
I knew it. He's...
Very well, I understand.
Gear, correct?
If you want to join the army,
you must fight here and
prove your strength.
Fight everyone here.
B-But that's crazy!
Does that not satisfy you?
No, I understand.
There are 50 of the regular
army's best men here.
Now show me your Killer Power!
Begin!
Wow!
He moved so fast!
Could you see that?
What was that?
I won't run away anymore.
I'll go forward!
I'll prove my power!
He wiped them all out?
In just a few minutes?
He's far beyond what I imagined!
Stop right there, kid.
Not yet.
It's still too early to get cocky.
The strongest man in the Segua army.
Harris, the Captain of Defenses.
You're fast, I'll admit that.
But do you have power?
What?
There it is!
He's what I've been waiting for!
With him here, I can make it real.
A new era for Segua!
That was great, brother!
I can take back our share
of Consume from Ninteldo,
and end the Hard Wars!
Ninteldo Territory
I told you!
Games like you don't know a thing!
Here in Consume...
things won't work that way.
It's over.
People kept going on about how great
their specs were before
they actually showed up,
but they were crap.
There's no one left on Consume
who can stand against us.
I guess all that's left is Segua.
I heard rumors they're going
to try something soon.
Segua?
It doesn't matter what Segua does.
Ninteldo has but one goal.
And I believe that
heaven has entrusted us with it.
To be honest, things don't look good.
Ninteldo and its allies control
90% of the continent.
But the next operation is the
beginning of our counterattack.
Our target is Hope Fortress,
in one of the countries allied
to Ninteldo, "Tetrand."
We'll rescue General Alex,
who's being held there.
Gear, I'm putting you in charge
of the first special forces
squad for the mission.
This is all moving a little too fast...
It's the most important task
in the upcoming operation.
Is that not enough?
No, it's plenty.
You can beat up those Ninteldo guys!
You're great!
Go get 'em!
Let's all do our best
in the next operation.
I didn't know Segua still
had warriors like you.
Where have you been?
Opal!
What are you—
Just saying hello.
I was watching from above.
You're putting him in the
special forces squad?
This is Opal,
one of the special
forces, just like you.
She's the second strongest
in the Segua army.
General Alex is the strongest,
but he's been captured by the enemy.
So right now, she's the strongest
we have in our army.
I'm Gear.
Nice to meet you.
I-I'm Nel!
W-Well, for today you should rest.
I'll have a room prepared.
We can go over the details tomorrow.
It's so soft!
I haven't slept in a
bed like this in ages.
A letter?
Yeah, looks like it.
I'm tired.
Let's get to sleep.
Yeah.
What do you want?
Calling me out at this hour.
I'm amazed you didn't run away.
I'll be up front with you:
I don't like you!
What?
I don't want to fight in the
special forces with you.
Fight me!
If you win, I'll do whatever you want.
But if I win...
You leave the castle!
All right, if that's what
it takes to satisfy you.
That's the attitude I hate!
You think if you show how strong you are,
everything will go your way.
You get off on beating
people weaker than you.
Just like him...
I hate men like you
more than anything!
I saw your power back there.
It's not fair unless I show you mine.
Throw that rock there at me.
Like this?
Got it?
No matter how fast you are,
I'll never miss.
I'm not stupid enough to
kill another Seguaian.
Whoever lands the first
solid hit wins.
Got it?
Yeah.
Then let's get started.
When this pebble hits
the ground, we begin.
Okay.
I've won.
My victory is already assured!
He's probably going to go
around to dodge the arrow,
but he has to get close to attack.
He'll leap towards me.
And when he does, he's mine!
You're just a barbarian.
You can't beat me.
Unlike you, I've fought
for years and years.
You're just an arrogant rat who's
come down from the mountains!
And that arrogance ends here!
He's coming straight
at me, and he's fast!
Huh?
Oh, you're awake?
What are you doing?
Put me down!
You were out cold.
Let me go!
I couldn't leave you out
on the beach at night.
Maybe everybody thinks
I'm full of myself
because I beat them,
but that's not true.
I just wanted everyone to accept me,
and to help Segua as fast as I could.
You're right. I've been hiding in the
mountains until a short time ago.
I wasn't trying to go forward.
I didn't realize how stupid I was.
Until my best friend died...
You guys have been fighting
for years, right?
So I respect all of you...
All of you that had already
been moving forward
years before me.
I guess he's not so bad.
He's just really straightforward.
I'll have to apologize later.
That's far enough.
I can walk the rest of the way.
So, what should I do?
Huh?
Well... you know...
I said that if you won, I'd do anything...
This is bad.
I was so sure I wouldn't lose,
I got carried away!
But that wasn't really my victory.
You hesitated because that arrow
would've hit me right
in the head, didn't you?
I thought to myself that
you were a lot nicer
than you looked.
A loss is a loss!
Give me your order already!
Okay, got it.
Then...
Let's fight together from now on, okay?
Okay...
Ramses-san, when does the
special forces mission start?
The two of us will execute it perfectly!
We can do this!
If Gear and I work together,
and the gears mesh...
Was that not hilarious?
No, it wasn't.
I'm glad the two of
you are friends now.
Why are the two of them
friends all of a sudden?
I called you here to introduce
the other member of the special forces.
Other member?
Is it somebody I know?
No, he's not a Seguaian.
So he's a mercenary?
You paid money to hire him?
That's right.
Will that really be okay?
Yes. I'm confident in his skills.
There aren't any warriors
who are a match
for you two in Segua.
His name is Tejirof.
He was my upperclassman
at Puzzle Magic Academy.
What's he like?
Hmm...
I guess the best word
would be "genius."
A genius at theory.
A genius at theory?
He'll be here soon.
He's supposed to arrive
in about five minutes.
He sounds like the kind of guy
who'd show up right on time.
Yeah.
I can't wait to meet him.
One hour later...
Isn't he late?
This is strange.
This isn't exactly the best start.
He's here.
Oh, hey there.
I was busy pleasuring
myself and so I'm late.
Ramses, it's been a while.
You're as hot as ever.
Let me stick it in later.
Just go sit down.
I heard things are bad because
your general was captured.
Well, don't worry.
I'll plug my stick in the
hole left by your general.
Is this really going to work?
I see.
I more or less understand
the situation.
It's going to be hard
with just these two.
The girl with the big
rack and the new kid.
My breasts don't have
anything to do with it!
What about the girl with the ears?
No, I can't fight...
Well, that's fine.
How much time do we have
left until the operation?
Four days.
Four days, huh?
That's plenty.
Okay, got it.
I'll train you hard for the four days
until the operation starts.
Your defenses are full of holes.
I'll poke my stick in all over.
Okay.
Then let's get started.
Is this really okay?
Let's start with you, new kid.
You think I'm weak, don't you?
That's fine.
First come at me as hard as you can.
And I'll carve this into your memory:
"The first person I met
who was stronger than me
was a pervert with a
thing for dirty jokes."
Ready?
Let's see the power that got you into
the special forces squad
on your first day!
He's fast!
But...
This stops him.
Brother!
He was able to see through Gear's speed?
You weren't running with
your best technique.
Maybe it feels good to run as
fast as you can like that,
but that only works on the first stage.
If you want to survive,
cast aside those feelings.
Do you understand?
Fighting on a battlefield
means killing.
You can't fight a real battle
based off how you feel.
I lost.
I completely lost.
Til.
Am I really unworthy of your respect?
No, I made a promise!
Nobody starts at the goal.
I swore to run to the goal!
No matter how many times
I go down on the way!
Are you okay, brother?
Brother?
Morning.
How did you enjoy your first beating?
Sure, you're strong.
But there are a lot of people on
the battlefield who are stronger.
I'd imagine you'll meet a few
of them during the operation.
Are you prepared to go anyway, new kid?
Or will you give up and
go back to training?
No,
I won't stop.
I'm going.
I decided I'd go straight ahead!
No hesitation.
I see.
For your dead friend?
How did you know?
Was I right?
Well, it was the only
logical deduction.
I figured something like that was
the only way to get a
coward to come down from
the mountain he was hiding on.
You're trying to go straight forward,
to make up for all the time
you spent at a standstill?
Pretty simple.
No matter what you say,
I'm going to follow my own path!
No, I'm not saying it's a bad thing.
I think it's fine.
I think there's nothing
wrong with your answer.
I don't like people who aren't
straight with others.
You should go as deep
as you can with it.
A stick...
doesn't feel good unless
you stick it straight in.
Go straight ahead.
I hope you find your real answer there.
Tejirof, I'm sorry!
I had the wrong idea about you.
I want to be stronger.
So help me train!
Sure.
But rest a bit more today.
You can read these
while you're resting.
What's this?
The map of Hope Fortress,
where we're headed.
It was close to the port,
so I took a look before I came here.
I got a little too into it and so
I was an hour late in arriving,
but well, nobody told
me to look for it.
So this was me pleasuring myself.
Bye.
Nel, the world's a big place.
Til, I'm going to keep running!
That was the incident known
as the Atarika Shock.
"Shooting."
No, I can't hold it in anymore!
You seem to have a knack for Online.
Like how that girl's nice...
I want to be strong anyway!
Episode 2 is Being Worked On Right Now!
Is that why this operation is so cruel?