Kazuha, Shino. It's almost time.
Yes, mother.
Coming!
Looks like all of you are getting really good at preparations.
It's a huge help for such a busy period.
Here.
You should all go for something sweet occasionally.
Thank you!
Mai, it's "much appreciated" when expressing gratitude.
Yes. I understand.
Well then, you have to give your best today, too.
Yes.
Kazuha-san and Shino-san always seem so pretty.
Yeah.
Right.
Ouch....
Have you not gotten used to the boxed pillow, Midori-san?
Not at all.
You seem to be doing well, Riko?
I am largely used to it.
Mai, you?
Yeah, but my neck still hurts a little.
But lying on top of this,
gives me a sense of really being an actual Maiko. I'm pretty happy.
I just hope this apprentice period can be easy.
There is no helping that.
Now, let's start breakfast preparations.
Ok.
Right.
Making breakfast for the land lady and the other sisters at Kikuya.
That's our responsibility as apprentices.
Riko-chan, Kamado (stove) is called Okudosan in Kyoto, right?
Yes, you really know quite a lot.
I wonder when will we be able to use the stove?
Seems like it'd be delicious.
Yes.
Have you decided on what go with Miso soup?
Let's decide together.
One, two!
Wakame and Aburaage.
We've been going with that recently.
Mai-san remarked that it was delicious the other time.
Then, let's go with that today.
I'll handle the laundry.
I will do the sweeping.
It's not too bad.
Delicious.
What are you grinning at me, Mai-chan?
Well, no.... Do you want another bowl of rice?
Dance recital?
Correct. Invitation from the tourism board.
Asked if we could assist them.
Good. I think it would be fun.
The few of you are going be to taking lessons from Miyagawa on Ondo starting today.
You will have to dance on the Maiko test. The three of you have to buck up.
Yes.
Good day.
You three are always together.
All the best.
Our teacher was said to be a famous Maiko known as the "period flower" back then.
We are in your care for today, teacher.
We are in your care.
Shall we start?
Whoever dances well today gets a Hanamaru.
We will try our best.
We privately call her as the Hanamaru teacher.
Riko, you danced well. Have a Hanamaru.
It is much appreciated, teacher.
Midori, you have to be softer.
Your stance now is stiff like Karate.
Much appreciated, Teacher.
Mai, it is good you grasp it fast,
but you have to put more heart into your dance next time.
It's... much appreciated, Teacher.
Hey, wanna drop by somewhere?
Down by?
Midori-san, do you have somewhere in mind?
Cafe.
Cafe!?
Onee-san gave us some allowance a few days ago, didn't she?
Let's have cake with that.
What a long queue!
Looks like it's best we give up for today.
Hanami-koji is a really popular tourist attraction.
Let's come next time.
I crave for it.
Speaking of which, I've been here before during my school excursion.
Kyoto was at its rainy season.
What are you doing alone somewhere like this?
Are you a student from the excursion?
Let me do it myself!
If Kazuha-san did not tell to me that day,
the thought of being a Maiko never would have crossed my mind.
More importantly, I can never forget those words she said.
I am a Maiko.
I feel this is a job rich in heritage.
In addition, this is a job that most represents Kyoto.
Um, could you take a picture for us?
Sure.
Get ready.
1 + 1 = ?
Thanks so much!
Welcome.
Are you on a field trip?
Yes, are you from Kyoto?
Well... I guess you could say that.
We are students learning the art of Maiko. Everyone of us is.
Is that true!?
Hey, they are Maikos.
Maiko!? Amazing!
It's kind of embarrassing.
Yeah....
A year ago, I was the one asking for to take photos.
But Mai-san and Midori-san are already Kyotolites.
What?
Really?
Perhaps.
Hey, shall we look for the granny at the draper's store?
Oh, right. It's been a while.
Yes.
The draper's granny we are referring to
is the owner of Itami; a draper store in the district.
She is an old friend of Kikuya's land lady.
You came at the right time. Try some of the snacks.
Right on!
Thank you so much!
It is very much appreciated.
That is correct. You should use "much appreciated".
It's not too bad.
It's really good.
I agree.
Our Kimono and cakes are the best in business.
That is really beautiful.
Isn't that right? I especially like this one.
Indeed.
It's gorgeous.
You really love Kimonos, don't you? Mai-chan.
Yeah, for some reason, I've liked them since I was a child.
When you become a full fledged Maiko,
i'll send you a Kimono.
Me too.
You should ask your father, Midori-chan.
Your family is so rich, they will surely get you piles.
I don't want to depend on my dad.
Well, what a waste.
But this is what I admire Midori-san for.
Then I'll have the cake!
That was mine....
Didn't you say you admired me?
What have you written today?
About how we met the field trip students.
I see.
Do you want to write too, Riko-chan?
I shall do that.
The two of you love to write.
I can never bring myself to write diary or things like that.
We will write your share on your behalf.
Right, this year's Gion Festival
will feature a dance recital organized by the tourism association.
Speaking of which, this morning my mother seemed to have mentioned something like that to Onee-chan.
It's a good chance for aspiring Maikos to take the stage.
Oh, the recital?
Mother have mentioned about it.
Saying we have to contribute to the programme.
But apparently we are only sending two.
Shino-chan, I failed!
What are you doing?
Two people, which means only two of us get to perform.
What should we do...
Which means Riko is definitely selected.
There's only one left.
It is not confirmed that I will be selected.
You will make it since you get the most Hanamarus.
What's left is whether Mai or me gets it.
But my mom has yet to formally speak to us about it.
Wanna go ask?
But did the draper granny not mention?
Before the land lady brings up the topic,
keep it a secret about me bringing up the matter.
That's right. I don't think it's appropriate for us to ask now.
Well, regardless of who gets picked, no hard feelings and we'll all work hard.
Yeah.
Yes.
You're up early, Midori-chan.
Normally, you won't wake up no matter how much I try.
We are afterall going to be rivals from today on.
What?
Well.... how should I put it?
We have to work hard.
I'll feel bad for making you two look after me like before.
I'll head down first.
Midori-san has this side of her.
Yeah, we have to work hard.
Yes.
Wrong! Wrong!
What's with you, Midori!
Yes.
Your shoulders have been less stiff lately and your movements have improved.
Now it's as stiff as before.
Your face looks scary, too!
I'm back to square one....
That's not true.
Yes.
Both of you have it good today. Managing to get the Hanamarus.
Sheesh, I have to buck up.
Hey, Midori-chan. Wanna drop by the draper's granny store along the way?
Ingredients for dinner have also been bought, so it's fine.
I'm not going. Both of you should go.
Knowing Midori-chan, she's probably practicing on her own right now.
Yes.
It feels sad.
One of us will not perform at the recital.
That's not right.... Gentler.
Midori-chan, wanna take a break?
We have cake for you.
I'll skip for now. I've to practice or I won't be able to catch up with you two.
I wonder if Midori-chan is still practicing...
Seems like it.
What will happen if these feelings persist until the recital.
If only the three of us can perform.
Good night.
Night.
Let's decide what goes with goes with Miso soup!
OK.
There's no need. Just go with what you what?
No, let's all decide.
One, two! Wakame and Aburaage.
I'm fine with that.
Midori-san seems really sleepy.
Looks like she practiced late into the night.
Is she not getting enough sleep?
Before hearing about the recital,
it's always the three of us, be it housework or lessons.
Since we are all working hard, I'd prefer we do it together.
I'll do the laundry.
Here, the Kimono I promised.
Convey my greetings to the land lady.
Yes.
Did something happen?
I'm here alone today to run an errand for my mom.
But I'd still prefer the three of us together.
Ah?
It's nothing.
It's strange. You're not like the usual Mai-chan.
You're right. It's gotten really strange.
I feel as if we have become distant.
Unknowingly, the Gion Festival approaches.
The Gion Festival is coming soon.
Yes.
What about the recital?
Are we really performing? Mom hasn't told us anything yet.
I'll ask granny about it!
That's right. It's more natural for you as her niece to ask.
Yes!
If you'd please.
Much appreciated.
Grandma!
During work, call me Mom.
Yes.
Mother, it's regarding the dance recital.
Oh, so you knew?
Yes.
That's right. It's going to be a first job.
It's natural to wonder.
I guess it's time to make a decision.
There's really a recital.
Which means that very soon, one of us is going to be left out.
That's surely me.
You never know...
It's yet to be decided.
I'm fine. No need to console me.
My dance is inferior compared to you two. I know that very well.
Midori-chan!
I don't wish for this.
If I knew this would happen, I wouldn't perform at the recital or anything.
What are you talking about! This is a chance to perform!
Passing up the opportunity for me. You can't say something like this!
It's been two months at Kikuya for me.
Maiko training is tough.
But as I have friends working hard together, I was about to carry on.
Because Midori-chan and Riko-chan are with me.
Hey, why is it that only two of us can attend?
I'll ask mother why can't the three of us perform together!
Wait! Mai!
Mai-san!
Mother!
What's wrong. You look conflicted.
It's regarding the dance recital.
Why restrict it to two persons?
Can't it be the three of us?
What do you mean?
Well, it's the dance recital.
We heard only two of us would be chosen.
Are you perhaps mistaken?
The recital is for all Okiyas.
Of course everybody has to attend.
But Kazuha-san said
only two of us may go.
She said that.
Wrong. The restriction is for two performances.
EH!?
But when you said it's about time to decide....
It means to ensure we don't clash with programs of the other Okiyas,
we have to decide soon.
So that's what it meant.
Which means we....
can perform together?
Of course.
That's great!
What a relief.
Isn't that great!
Yes.
Yeah.
Did I say only two of you can perform?
You did.
Sure did.
The manner of speech might differ, but we clearly heard you.
Oh dear. I'm really sorry.
But isn't that great?
The three of you having your maiden performance together.
We didn't have such good fortune.
That's right. How envious.
Well, give it your best shot, everyone!
That's how it is....
Kazuha-san is quite a handful....
But it's wonderful that we be together.
Yeah.
Then we should also decide that today.
Yes.
One, two!
Wakame and tofu.
Oh! Fantastic.
We got tofu right.
And aburaage is what we usually go for.
The three of them are really closed.
Yes.
You three look gorgeous.
Give it your best shot!
Sure.
You called out to me when it is pouring
ame moyou ga watashi wo yondeta no
Time started moving from that moment on
soko kara jikan ha ugokidashite ittandane
Words that are hard to honestly say
sunao ni ienai koto
Stuff that we cannot seem to do well
umaku ikanai koto
We may be frustrated whenever we reach a hurdle
kokoro kara nayande butsukatte mo
But we have to keep embracing those never changing feelings
zutto kawaranai omoi daiteiyou
Even when we feel useless and lost
bukiyou nari ni mayoi nagara
we want to continue searching for things we can do
nanika dekiru koto wo mitsuketai
Chasing a common dream is something really enjoyable
onaji yume wo oikaketeku sore ga sugoku ureshii kara
If we make it through, that's right, towards the bright future
isshoni norikoete yukereba sou hikari aru mirai he
I firmly believe our bonds at this warm and gentle place
tsunagatteiku to shinjiteru atatakaku yasashii kono basho de
It was really fun.
Yes.
Let's make sure the three of us become Maikos.
Yeah.
Sure.