Kazuha. Shino. It is nearly time.
Yes, Mother.
All right.
The three of you have certainly grown
adept at helping with the preparations.
It is welcome assistance during the busy season.
Oh, that reminds me!
Here.
Go treat yourselves to some sweets.
Thank you very much!
Mai!
We say: "Many thanks."
It slipped my mind.
Now, I expect dedication again today, girls.
Yes, ma'am.
Kazuha-san and Shino-san always look so beautiful.
Yeah.
Indeed.
Ow, what a pain...
Midori-san, are you still not
accustomed to your neck support?
Not even close.
It doesn't give you any pain, Riko?
I am quite used to it now.
What about you, Mai?
Same here. My neck still gets a little sore...
but sleeping on this thing makes me feel like a maiko, and that puts a smile on my face.
I'd hoped being wet behind the ears
as apprentices would have spared us.
Keep at it.
Right! Let's go prepare breakfast!
Okay.
All right.
Here at Kikuya, it's up to us as the apprentices to prepare the meals for the proprietress and our geiko and maiko sisters.
Riko-chan, you call kamado stoves "okudo-san" here in Kyoto, right?
Yes. I'm surprised you know that.
I wanna cook rice on an okudo-san someday.
Don't you think it'd make it taste great?
It would.
So what are we putting in the miso soup today?
Let's decide on the count of two.
One, two...
Seaweed and fried tofu!
That's all we've been putting in our soups lately.
That's because the soup was delicious when
you used those ingredients the other day.
We'll go with them again today, then.
Okay. I'm gonna go do a round of laundry.
I shall busy myself with cleaning.
Okay.
Not bad, huh?
This is delectable!
What's gotten into you, Mai-chan? You're grinning like a cat.
Oh, uh, nothing...
Would you like seconds? There's plenty left.
A dance performance?
Indeed. It is an event organized by the tourist board.
They want to view fledglings from each geiko house in action.
That sounds splendid.
It should be fun.
Now, you girls...
I hear that today is the day you finally begin learning the Miyagawa Ondo dance.
Your maiko exam will require all three of you to dance,
so ensure you learn the steps thoroughly.
Yes, ma'am.
Oh!
Good day.
I always see the three of you together.
Keep it up.
Our instructress was apparently a popular maiko back in the day, who went by the name of Chiyobana...
We appreciate you sacrificing your day to coach us, Madam Instructress.
We appreciate it very much.
Let us get started then.
If you do well today, I will give you your usual gold stars.
We will strive for perfection!
...but to us, she's known as the Gold Star Instructress.
Riko, you danced beautifully.
A gold star for you.
Many thanks, Madam Instructress.
Midori, you need to be more delicate.
At present, your movements resemble karate techniques!
Many thanks, Madam Instructress...
Mai, being a fast learner is an admirable trait,
but next time, put more feeling into your dancing.
Uh, okay...
Many thanks, Madam Instructress.
Hey, why don't we take a detour?
A detour?
Is there someplace you wish to go, Midori-san?
A café!
A café?
Remember the spending money our maiko sisters gave us the other day?
We can get cake with it!
That's a really long line!
Looks like we'll have to scratch that idea for today.
Hanamikoji Street is a popular tourist destination, after all.
Let's return another day.
I really wanted some...
This reminds me of the time
I visited this street on a school trip.
The rainy season had hit Kyoto.
Why are you out in the rain?
Are you here on a school excursion?
Ah, I can wipe my own cheeks.
If Kazuha-san hadn't called out to me that day,
I never would've considered becoming a maiko.
And I'll never forget those words...
I am a maiko.
I view it as a profession imbued with history.
And one in which you become a true daughter of Kyoto.
Excuse me...
Could you take a picture for us?
Oh, sure.
Okay, wait for it...
Say cheese.
Cheese!
Thank you so much!
Don't mention it.
Are you here on a school trip?
Yes.
Are you a native of Kyoto, miss?
Uh...
I guess I am now.
We're training to become maiko.
Apprentices, basically.
What? Really?
Hey, girls, these three are gonna become maiko!
Maiko? That's amazing!
That was kinda embarrassing.
A year ago, I was the one asking other girls if I could take photos with them.
Still, the two of you have transformed into natives of Kyoto.
What?
You think so?
Most probably.
Hey, can we go visit the draper lady on our way back?
Well, it's been a while, so why not?
Indeed.
By "draper lady," we mean the owner of the long-established draper's shop, Itami,
who is an old friend of Kikuya's proprietress.
Thank you for dropping by.
I'll fetch you some puddings.
Awesome!
Thank you very much!
As always, many thanks.
Yes, you must say "many thanks" to show your appreciation.
Not bad, huh?
It's really good!
Indeed it is.
Naturally.
We only stock the finest kimonos and cakes.
That one's very beautiful.
Isn't it just?
This kimono is my favorite.
I knew it!
It's really wonderful!
You have a fondness for kimonos, don't you, Mai-chan?
Yes! I don't know why, but I've
liked them ever since I was a child.
Then, when you officially become a maiko, I shall
present you with a kimono from my store.
I-I want one too!
Midori-chan, you should ask your father.
He is a wealthy man. I am certain he would buy you a plethora of magnificent ones.
I don't want to depend on my father.
Why would you not? How wasteful.
I, however, respect that aspect in you.
Good, 'cause I'm taking your cake!
That was mine!
As a token of your respect, yeah?
What are you writing today?
About meeting those girls on their school trip.
Oh, I see!
Do you want to write too, Riko-chan?
I would love to.
You sure are dedicated.
I just can't get into writing diaries and stuff like that.
Then, we'll write your bit for you, Midori-chan!
That reminds me...
I've heard that there will be a dance performance
hosted by the tourist board in the Gion Festival this year.
Oh yeah, Mother said something about that to our maiko sisters this morning.
It would be the perfect opportunity for you
apprentices to appear onstage, don't you think?
Ah, the show?
Yes.
Mother did mention something along those lines, yes.
About how we have two spots to fill.
We are sending out two girls, I believe?
Ah, Shino-chan! I've gone wrong!
Honestly. What are you doing?
Two girls?
So only two out of the three of us will be up on stage?
I don't know.
In that case, you're more or less a dead cert to be picked, Riko,
so that leaves one other spot.
There is no guarantee that I will be cho—
You're a shoo-in for it.
You always get the most gold stars.
It's between me and Mai for the second spot.
But Mother hasn't actually said anything to us about it yet.
Should we ask her?
Though, remember what the draper told us...
Keep what I've said a secret until your
proprietress brings it up of her own accord.
Oh yeah...
It wouldn't be a very good idea to ask about it right now.
Anyway, let's keep working hard. Then, there'll be no hard feelings, no matter who gets chosen!
Yeah!
Indeed.
You're up early, Midori-chan.
It's usually a struggle to get you out of bed.
Well, starting today, we are rivals, you know.
Huh?
Uh, let me rephrase that...
Each of us needs to do our best.
I'd feel bad if I relied on you as a safety net.
I'll be downstairs.
That epitomizes Midori-san's character.
Yeah.
We should be diligent too.
Yes.
No, awful! Absolutely awful!
What are you playing at, Midori?
Oh...
You've improved lately when it comes to keeping your limbs loose,
but you are still too stiff!
And your expression is much too stern!
Back to square one, huh?
No, not at all.
I agree.
It's all right for you guys...
You got gold stars again today.
I need to work harder.
Say, Midori-chan, why don't we drop by the draper shop?
We have ample time to do so as we're under no obligation to buy groceries for tonight's dinner.
I'll pass. You two can go.
Knowing Midori-chan, I bet she's back at the boarding house, reviewing today's lessons.
Probably.
I find it sad that one of us will be singled out to be precluded from performing in the show.
This isn't right.
It has to be smoother, like this...
Midori-chan, why don't you take a break?
We brought some cake back with us.
Nah, I need to practice some more so I can catch up to you two.
Is Midori-chan still practicing?
It seems likely.
I would rather forgo performing in the event if it meant sparing us of these horrible feelings.
If only the three of us could perform together...
Good night.
Night.
Let's choose what we're putting in the miso soup on the count of two.
All right.
Just go with whatever you want.
No, the three of us will decide together.
One, two...
Seaweed and fried tofu!
I'm fine with that.
Midori-san seemed sleepy.
Looks like she stayed up late last night, practicing.
She probably didn't get enough sleep.
Before we found out about the dance performance, we did all the housework as a group and we practiced together too.
I much prefer it when the three of us work together.
I shall busy myself with the laundry.
Here is the kimono you requested.
Give my regards to your proprietress.
I will.
What's the matter?
Being here by myself on an errand for Mother...
It just doesn't feel the same as when the three of us come here together.
What?
Oh, nothing.
You're acting very strangely.
You're not your usual self, Mai-chan.
I know. I feel strange.
Something just feels amiss.
Time flew by, and the next thing we knew,
the Gion Festival was just around the corner.
The Gion Festival is coming up soon, isn't it?
Yes.
I wonder what'll happen with that dance performance.
Is it really going ahead?
Mother hasn't mentioned anything.
I will ask my grandmother outright!
Good idea. It might work if her granddaughter just drops it casually into conversation.
Exactly!
Here is your tea.
Many thanks.
Grandmother?
Call me "Mother" for the duration of your instruction.
Y-Yes, ma'am.
Mother...
I-I wish to inquire about our upcoming dance performance.
Oh, you have been made aware of it?
Yes, ma'am.
I see.
It will be your debut, so I have been thinking it over, considering the best course of action,
but I should come to a decision soon.
So we are taking part in the dance performance...
It's time for one of us to be left in the wings.
And it's definitely going to be me.
Don't be so negative.
There is no decision either way yet.
It's fine. I'm not looking for your pity.
I know better than anyone that I'm
a mediocre dancer compared to you two.
God!
Midori-chan!
I hate everything about this.
I would rather eschew performing at the event than go through this ordeal.
What are you saying?
This is your chance to dazzle in the spotlight!
You want to miss out on that just for me?
Don't ever say that!
It's been two months since I came to Kikuya.
Training to become a maiko has been tough,
but I've made it this far because I've had
friends sharing the experience with me.
Midori-chan and Riko-chan have always been by my side.
Say, is it really only going to be two of us performing?
I'll ask Mother if all three of us can perform together!
Wait, Mai!
Mai-san!
Mother!
You have something urgent to tell me?
I wanted to ask you about the dance performance.
Do you have to choose only two of us?
Can't all three of us perform?
What are you babbling about, girl?
Well, we heard that only two out of the three of us will get to perform in the event...
I think you may have got the wrong end of the stick.
Each geiko house will present their apprentices.
It goes without saying that all of you will be performing.
B-But Kazuha-san told us...
...that only two of us would be performing.
That's what she told us!
No, no...
Not two people. Two programs.
What?!
S-So when you suggested you had a decision to make, you were talking about...
I must decide on the programs we will perform so that we do not overlap with the programs of the other houses.
S-So that was what you meant...
Wait, are you trying to tell us...
...that all three of us will be performing?
Naturally.
Th-That's great.
Thank goodness.
Isn't this wonderful news?
Yes!
Yeah!
Did I truly say that only two would be performing?
Damn straight!
Yes, you did!
The phrasing might have been different, but we definitely heard you say it.
Oh, then, accept my apologies.
That is marvelous news, though.
It means the three of you will debut together.
We certainly were not afforded that opportunity.
Indeed. This is an auspicious occasion for you.
Give it your all!
She's always like this.
Jeez Louise, Kazuha-san...
Still, thank goodness we are able to perform together.
Yeah.
Right, time to decide on the count of two again.
Yeah!
All right.
One, two...
Seaweed and tofu!
That was amazing!
We all said "tofu" at the exact same time!
Especially amazing as we usually say "fried tofu."
The three of you certainly get along well.
We do!
The three of you look so elegant.
Break a leg out there!
We will.
That was fun.
Indeed.
Let's become maiko together, and let nothing stand in our way.
Okay.
Yes, let's.