Dansează?
Pot simți ritmul!
Este culoarea vântului din nou!
Vântul!
Any more?
That unit...
Pilotule! Ești în regulă?
Stai, cine ești tu?
Unde sunt Walküre?
Unde este Mikumo?
I'm going crazy, at the boiling point
You can paint me your color
Destruction and rebirth is my life
Y-Yack...
Song...
Walküre, nu?
White Knight! Terminate operation.
Return to the Branch.
Why? We can win this fight!
We have the data we need.
This is an order.
It is love that brings me back to life
Roger.
All units return to the Branch.
Roger...
It is love that I need, coming back to you
They're backing off?
Were they just testing us?
May the sea of stars
be blessed by the goddess!
Avem o singură șansă ca să ne îndrăgostim
Deci haide să ne distrăm înăuntrul tău
Haide să împărțim un sărut egoist
Petalele acestei flori se leagănă în vânt
Există prea multe stele ca să le pot număra
I could place all the blame on you,
swallowing back my tears,
but I can't tell anyone about how my heart races
(Încearcă să ajungi)
Until it all breaks apart
Until you can take flight
(la capătul)
Adânc în inima mea
(timpului)
There is a prayer
Just feel, just believe
and speed through it all
We've only got one shot at love,
so let's have fun inside of you
Let's share a kiss faster than light, just wait for me
Îmi las corpul în urmă
Îmi las inima să bată puternic
Mă voi elibera de aceste lanțuri care mă
Just come get me, in my purest form
If you're injured or not feeling well, please come here!
You, civilian!
Hey, thanks for saving me.
What the hell was that for?!
Do you realize you just hijacked a military unit?
Make one mistake and the whole operation falls apart, putting the city at risk!
Even the smallest lapse can cost you your life!
Calm down! Listen to me firs—
Don't tread on the battlefield so lightly!
You screwed up too!
I saw you.
Earlier, you were off beat when you took off!
Aren't you the one taking this too lightly?
Mirage, what are you doing? We're leaving.
Please report any complaints to my superiors.
Excuse me.
See you!
Mikumo!
I'll be at your audition next week!
I'm gonna sing next to you!
That girl...
Yeah.
We could hear you sing!
Your singing is so cute!
It resonated inside my chest. It felt nice.
It felt great!
Oh my gosh...
Perhaps, she may...
We're looking forward to seeing you
on Ragna!
Yup!
I sang alongside them for real, huh?
With Walküre... And Mikumo...
Get those on the launch pad on the double!
Delta Leader, done.
Every video signal is jammed.
We have no matching data either.
Nice performance out there.
Want some Barrette shredded jellyfish?
I'll pass.
Thanks for the help earlier, Messer.
Just doing my duty.
What did you want to show us?
This.
What's that shining on her head?
A rune. She's a Windermerian.
She has a fold receptor factor?
Yes. And it's abnormally high, to boot.
Even Mikumo's output reacted to her voice.
And this is what you asked for.
Hayate Immelmann, huh?
I can't accept this, Lord Keith.
I request an explanation.
Likewise.
Understood.
Roid, why did you stop us?
You'd completed your objectives.
There was no change in plans.
We should strike when we have a chance.
We have no time to spare.
I know. We can't forget about Prince Heinz's health.
Open the windows every now and then.
There's no wind in here.
Planet Ragna
Barrette City
Delight your taste buds with Ragna's specialty: the Barrette jellyfish!
So cute!
Totally!
Wow, we're on Ragna!
There are so many sparkly sounds!
Ugh... Damn mercats all over the place...
What are you doing here?
I came to see you fail the auditions.
I'm not gonna fail!
Wear these and you'll become a Ragnan!
Buy some for yourself!
Ragnans are a seafaring folk, they say.
Ew! What's this icky thing?!
It's cheap! Buy one!
It's a phone! Cell! Number one!
A phone?
Contract established. Commence payment process.
Get it off me!
Thanks for your purchase!
Time to run!
Huh?
Cities are so scary.
Look at that.
Oh my gosh, it's so big!
That's Macross Elysion, the HQ of Xaos' Ragna branch.
So they hold the auditions there?
My rune's running high!
Rune? You mean that tentacle thing on your head?
Don't stare at it, you perv!
Huh? It's supposed to be arousing?
The long-awaited auditions for the new Walküre member are finally here!
The chosen girls are gathering here at the feet of Macross Elysion.
Will one of them become a goddess?
So many cuties.
Can't we just let them all in?
Do they really understand what it means to sing on the battlefield?
What do you mean I can't enter the audition?!
As I said, today is the final round.
You'd need to pass the qualifier rounds first.
There's qualifiers?
Are you for real?
What are you doing here?
Oh, hey, it's dancer boy.
Are you here to complain about me?
The world isn't all about you.
You're from the Delta Platoon!
Please let me take the audition!
Huh?
They've both arrived.
What are the qualifying requirements?
She's cleared them on paper.
For crying out loud...
Please! Give me an audition!
Ah, right. In that case...
Please! Audition!
Um, miss? You've received special permission
to take part in the audition.
Really?
So damn lucky.
And also...
Are you Hayate Immelmann?
I am.
Commander Arad from the Delta Platoon wants to see you.
The commander?
Me?
Gee whiz, that's a deculture and a half!
It certainly is big.
Hayate?
Take care, then.
Hey, wait!
Um, thanks for—
I'm not giving you a ride back home.
Once you're done failing, you're on your own.
I'm not gonna fail!
I can fly if I ride the wind!
Aren't you the one taking this too lightly?
Damn kid!
I can fly if I ride the wind.
I can fly if I ride the wi—
What's going on?
I'm gonna get eaten!
Wow! It's Kaname!
Oh my gosh! It's her for real!
I'm the leader of the tactical sound unit Walküre, Kaname Buccaneer.
And with me here...
Ernest Johnson, the captain of Macross Elysion.
We will now begin the auditions.
However, before that...
Remember that we Walküre risk our lives during each performance.
If you're not willing to take that risk, please leave now.
That's all.
I'm so nervous!
She said we're gonna risk our lives...
What are these?
I think they're for recording our singing, or something.
Really? Let's do our best then!
That's her!
All right! I'm gonna show them the Windermerian spirit!
What? You lost him?!
I'm so sorry!
DGS status normal.
Hand me the wrench, will ya?
Yeah, yeah.
Who's that?
That's a new face. You a rookie?
Kind of.
S.O.S. is echoing around
Love's halation THE WAR
For sure, now, there's more
More, now, hold me tight
Hold me tight, hey, gently
Checking for fold receptor activity...
Only four girls...
What about that girl?
She has it too, but the values are lower than required.
She must be nervous.
You're a Windermerian, right?
Yes, ma'am.
I heard that Windermere has been very strict on interstellar travel since the revolution.
Also that they've started cracking down on terrestrial culture.
You might never be allowed to return home if you join Walküre.
I'd still want to become a member of Walküre!
I will announce the results of the third Walküre auditions.
Everyone...
has failed.
You showed off some impressive moves the other day.
I'm the commander of the Delta Platoon, Arad Mölders.
I was taken down in a flash.
It was my first time flying a plane.
But you seemed proficient at controlling a Battroid.
I've used Workroids for work.
I see.
You seem to move around a lot.
Listania. Airberl. Gregorl. Different jobs on every planet.
So what?
Commander Arad, this is a waste of time.
Hold on now.
You're the one who asked for me.
Who do you think...
Well, I thought you could fly for us if you felt like it.
I wonder if he's still inside.
How did flying feel?
Come here.
If you fall, you die. You risk your life.
But you still take off.
That's the fate of those who've tasted the wind.
You've tasted it too, haven't you?
The rest is whether you fly or not,
whether you're willing to risk your life.
We stopped?
What happened?
To all passengers:
A Vár riot has broken out in Barrette city.
A Vár outbreak?!
Look at this!
More and more people are affected by the Vár.
The citizens are in a panic.
That's awful!
What are the Walküre doing?
What's wrong? Are you okay?
It's the Vár syndrome!
What's going on? What's this?!
Help! Help!
What are you doing?! Come here!
Why am I here?
To sing...
Switch into gear... Screaming... No stopping now
Switch into gear! Screaming! No stopping now
S.O.S. the sirens are howling
What is she doing?
Is she nuts?
Love's halation THE WAR
My own story begins as I wake up
This morning feels different. I rub my eyes
Risk my life, huh?
Ready to fire! Three, two
onepiece flying as I spin
My engine is now in extreme speed
Then we crash and a galactic level
Boom comes for your deculture!
All power starboard! I'm setting you on fire
Feel it? Diving! There's no turning back
S.O.S. the signal's on fire
Love's changing THE WORLD
What are those numbers?
You've got guts.
He rode the wind?
That felt nice.
This is yours.
It's important to you, isn't it?
I know your voice.
Welcome to the world of Walküre.
Mikumo?
What's going on?
This is the final audition.
Your voice earlier resonated in my chest. It felt nice.
You pass, Freyja Wion.
I pass?!
What is this?
As of today, you're one
of the Walküre.
I'm one of...
the Walküre?
Congratulations!
Sorry for scaring you!
Good job, girl!
You were at the audition's entry counter!
That was quite impressive.
Sorry. It's fake blood.
Just as you predicted, Kumo-Kumo.
I feel a bit let down, though.
I flew...
I can't believe this is happening.
I hate the army.
So do I.
Taking orders too.
So I'll play by my own rules.
Feel free to.
Commander Arad?
I'll fly the skies with this beauty.
Get away from her!
Don't you lay a finger on my plane!
Resolute Audition
Are you ready?
I heard a rumor that the world's gonna end someday
Just kidding, it's obviously a lie
I remember looking up at the sky
and feeling like I was in the future
I felt completely in sync with your wind
You make me truly feel like a girl
so I've got no choice but to do it. I can't stop now!
You better be ready!
If my rune shines with a flash
wow woh wow woh
I fall in love
Lalali lalala you make me
Lalala rune pika invincible
Next Time
Whirlwind Dogfight