Ha-Ha-Ha-Haideți să facem versuri magice
Dacă vom cânta împreună
Atunci sentimentele noastre fericite vor ajunge la tine
Haideți, să începem cu 5-7-5
Acesta este modul nostru de a comunica
Se va răspândi precum magia
Haideți să facem versuri împreună
Sentimente
Matcha!
They're going to be selling crepes at the park today!
You don't get it, do you?
The pond there is like the gateway to hell.
A lot of evil spirits lurk there at night.
I heard they'll be selling that special green tea and red bean flavor again!
We've gotta go!
I'm telling you, that pond is the gateway to hell.
You say that now,
but you're just upset because you got wet when you accidentally fell in the pond, right?
No way!
C'mon, let's go, Matcha!
What about the ideas for 5-7-5?
That's right! This counts as looking for ideas.
All you have to do is wait for me by the entrance!
#02: Uniforma mea este fleașcă exact ca ultima oară.
I'll be right back. Wait for me.
Meow, meow meow meow meow?
Hmph! Meow meow meow meow, meow.
Meow, wait!
Huh? That's weird.
You shouldn't do that. Get away from there!
The gateway is right there!
Man, I messed up.
The crepe truck's here tomorrow!
Hey!
Why'd you fall in again?!
Here, take my hand!
It's a kite!
Oh no! It's going to eat me!
I'm all warmed up!
I told you that a lot of evil spirits lurk there at night!
But it's daytime right now!
Aw c'mon, stop crying.
"I do not want to. My uniform is soaking, just like the last time."
Oh. That's 5-7-5!
That was nice of them to let us borrow the yukatas.
It looks good on you, Matcha!
Let's go get some crepes tomorrow!
Sure. I don't mind going with you.
Really? Awesome! I love you, Matcha!
Hey, quit sticking so close to me!