Iadul sunt ceilalți
Jean-Paul Sartre, "Cu ușile închise"
Așteaptă!
Antropologul Edward Hall a împărțit spațiul personal în patru zone.
Una din acele zone este "spațiul
intim", cu "etapa de izolare" acolo.
Această distanța este destul de
mică încât să accepți pe altcineva
și mulți se opun încălcării ei.
Totuși, este mult prea tare!
Oricum, există și excepții.
Nu chiar, mie-mi cam place.
Îmi place ceva mai moale—
De exemplu, Kushida.
Ați văzut o fată cu ochelari?
Chiar dacă se apropie foarte mult, ea reușește să nu declanșeze reacția spațiului personal.
Și totuși, Sakura i s-a opus.
Îi este teamă de legături.
De asta...
își ține privirea în pământ.
Îmi cer scuze că v-am făcut să
veniți cu mine pentru asta.
Eu sunt cea care ar trebui să-și ceară scuze.
Eu ți-am stricat camera foto.
N-Nu, eu ar trebui să fiu mai atentă...
Asta este așa de drăguță!
Mergi la magazinul de electronice
din mall ca să îți repari camera foto.
Înțeleg asta...
Dar chiar aveai nevoie de mine?
De fapt...
Of, privește. Asta nu e bine.
Tejgheaua pentru asistență tehnică
Înțeleg. Este o problemă de pornire.
Da, asta nu e bine...
Ai garanție la ea? Garanția...
Ai adus garanția?
Nou
O, încă este în perioada de garanție.
Partea stricată poate fi...
înlocuită... fără a plăti ceva.
Înțeleg de ce îi este greu
lui Sakura, căreia îi este teamă de străini, să vorbească cu acest tip.
Presupun că voia putere în număr.
Ne poți spune cât va dura?
Două sau trei zile. Da, două sau trei zile.
Poți completa acest formular?
Chitanța obiectului pentru reparare
Avem nevoie de adresă, nume și...
număr de telefon.
Sakura-san?
D-Da...
Îl pot împrumuta?
Când reparațiile sunt gata, te rog să mă contactezi pe mine în schimb.
H-Hei, tu...
Camera îi aparține ei, nu-i așa?
Nu sunt sigur că putem...
Garanția producătorului confirmă locația și data cumpărării.
Ai spus că este valabilă acum câteva secunde.
Nu-mi pot imagina cum ar putea fi o problemă legală.
E-Ești sigur?
Ei bine, vom face așa, atunci.
Hei...
Vă mulțumesc pentru că m-ați ajutat astăzi.
Nu e nicio problemă. Oricum, fusese vina mea.
Dar, Sakura-san, poți vorbi cu normal cu noi, bine?
Suntem în același an.
Da, ai folosit numai limbajul formal.
B-Bine...
Am... S-Sigur. Voi încerca.
Nu trebuie nici să te forțezi s-o faci.
S-Sunt bine.
În regulă.
Scuzați-mă o clipă, bine?
Voi merge până la toaletă.
It's awkward being alone with her.
Ce e în neregulă, Sakura?
Is there something you wanted to—
Um...
What do you think would
be the best thing to do?
Regarding Sudo?
You should do whatever you want to do.
Whatever I...
Yeah.
If I don't say anything,
I think I'll regret it.
Why are you telling me this?
Your eyes weren't scary.
Eyes?
Sorry. It's hard to explain...
If you need advice,
Kushida would be more amicable.
She was today, too.
Is it intuition?
She's grateful, but for some reason,
she can't fully trust Kushida.
That's what it seems like.
You said you would regret it
if you didn't say anything.
Yes.
I think that's the only answer you need, then.
"For Sudo." "For Kushida."
"For my classmates."
Throw away all of those thoughts.
Throw them all... away?
You don't have to burden
yourself with all of that.
You should testify for your own sake.
For my... sake?
That's enough on its own.
Sorry for the wait.
W-Welcome back.
Well, think we should call it a day?
It is pretty late.
Yeah.
Can I come by your room later, Ayanokoji-kun?
Huh?
Coming in!
What did you need to come
all the way to my room for?
I was actually looking some things
up on the Internet earlier.
Does this girl look familiar to you?
Is this Sakura?
It's hard to say just from the
face and the build, but...
This picture was taken in one of our dorms.
So it is her!
And I thought it was strange that
Sakura wore fake eyeglasses, too.
They're fake?
There was no distortion behind the lenses.
So she's trying to hide her face?
Is that why she wouldn't testify?
New Messages: 1
Sakura Airi
This is Sakura.
It's from Sakura-san.
Let's see...
She says she might be able
to help with Sudo-kun!
I guess going with her today was worth it.
I'm glad she decided to trust
us, but I wonder why...
Hey.
Ayanokoji-kun, isn't there
anything you're trying to hide?
Tokyo Metropolitan Advanced Nurturing High School
At this school, class membership remains the same from enrollment through graduation.
It is assumed that the students of each class will come together to overcome
various challenges and grow through doing this.
Student Council Room
I've sent out the notification
for the arbitration hearing
between Class 1-D and 1-C.
Oh?
Class D...
Huh?
What is it?
Did you spend your day off with Kushida-san?
Yeah, because of the thing with Sakura.
Though we couldn't get her word that
she would share what she knows.
I see.
What's the matter?
What do you mean, what's the matter?
Well, you have quite the
expression on your face.
Really? I don't agree.
This is how I always look.
Although I am impressed by how
self-serving you've been lately.
You hesitate when I ask you for a favor,
but when Kushida-san asks,
you comply immediately.
I'm attempting to analyze,
rationally and carefully, the factors
that account for the difference.
Well, it doesn't matter.
It doesn't?
What's more important is that the
student council's picked the day
for Sudo-kun's hearing.
When is it?
Today after class.
Student Council Room
We will now hold deliberations
regarding the violent incident
that occurred last Tuesday.
As Student Council Secretary,
I, Tachibana, will preside.
The student council president,
coming in over a little brawl like this?
Wonders never cease, I suppose...
Due to my busy schedule, there are some
agendas I'm forced to miss participating in.
As a rule, though, I do attend.
So it's just a coincidence, is it?
Yes.
She wasn't expecting the
president to be here.
Horikita can't bring out her full potential.
To both sides: I wish to ascertain which
version of the events is the truth.
Is that acceptable?
Begin.
Komiya and the other two,
you insist you were called to the special
annex by Sudo and then attacked by him.
Sudo denies this. He insists that Komiya
was the one who called him there.
Your versions of the
events are contradictory.
There is only one fact we can be certain of:
that the aggressor, Sudo,
injured Komiya, Kondo, and Ishizaki.
They are the victims.
I'll admit that I hit them!
But they're the ones who started it!
I don't recall doing that.
Having the main discussion
be about the injuries
You damn well did!
I was only defending myself!
and giving Sudo free rein
are both bad for us.
Horikita.
You just kept running your mouths!
You're jealous because I'm on
the list of potential regulars!
And at basketball practice,
you always get in my—
Silence, please.
Without new testimony or evidence,
we will proceed under these assumptions.
Is this acceptable?
It seems there was no need for discussion.
It's clear from the state of their injuries
that the violence was one-sided.
I believe I should base my decision on that.
Class D's insistence that it was
self-defense is contradicted
by Sudo-kun's lack of injuries,
and the condition of
Ishizaki-kun and the others.
Aya—
What?
S-Stop it! What are you—
When someone's spacing out,
a strong physical stimulus will
snap them back to reality.
Hey!
If you don't fight, we're going to lose.
I beg your pardon.
I would like to question the witnesses.
May I?
President?
I'll allow it.
What were the circumstances under
which Sudo-kun called you out?
Answer me.
After practice ended, he said
he wanted to talk to me.
And what was Ishizaki-kun doing
in the special annex with you?
He is not in the basketball club.
There was no reason for him to be there.
I... wanted insurance.
Insurance?
Everyone knows what a violent guy
Sudo-kun is. He's a big guy, too!
You thought he might attack you, then?
That's right!
That's a prepared response.
And so you brought Ishizaki-kun,
who had a reputation as being a
strong fighter in middle school,
as a bodyguard?
I did it to protect myself!
I have some knowledge of martial arts myself.
Fighting multiple enemies increases
the difficulty exponentially.
For you to be beaten so one-sidedly,
especially with Ishizaki-kun present,
makes no sense.
Well... that's just because
we didn't want a fight!
If you had no desire to fight,
and you weren't fighting back,
it's extremely unlikely that
all three of you would be hurt.
That does sound like common sense.
Common sense doesn't apply
when Sudo-kun's involved!
He's an incredibly violent man!
There was a student who
witnessed the entire fight.
Would the witness step forward, please?
Would the witness please state her name?
C-Class 1-D, Sakura Airi.
Please take your seat.
Okay...
Sakura-san.
I did see it.
The Class C students attacked Sudo-kun first.
I'm... sure of it.
Sakura-kun, was it?
If you really did see it,
why didn't you step forward sooner?
Well... because...
Honestly, you Class Ds...
I'm just... telling the truth...
Sakura-kun. Sakura Airi-kun.
Are you sure you're not being forced
to lie for the sake of your class?
To save Sudo-kun?
That's not good.
The fact that Sakura-san is here proves
that she really did witness the incident.
If she hadn't, she wouldn't be sitting here,
even if we'd asked her to.
If we just needed someone
to make a statement,
don't you think I would
have chosen someone else?
Perhaps you chose to use someone
like her to lend further credibility.
Credibility?
Stop twisting everything.
Sakura-san came here in good faith—
Stop taking advantage of your well-meaning
but weak-willed classmates.
That is not what I'm doing!
But look at her trembling!
Don't put any more burden on—
I have proof!
I do have... proof!
Please don't dig this hole any deeper.
This is proof that I was in
the special annex that day!
Display it.
Okay.
That day... I was looking for somewhere
deserted to take pictures of myself.
It's dated, too.
Dates on a digital camera
can easily be altered.
It's rather insubstantial, as proof goes.
But, Mr. Sakagami, this picture is different.
With this...
I hope you will believe
that I was there that day.
Thank you, Sakura-san.
I see.
It seems you were telling the
truth about being present.
But we still don't know who instigated it.
It doesn't prove that you saw
everything that went down, either.
But...
Might I propose a compromise?
A compromise?
Despite your pictures,
you have no definitive proof.
However, it does appear that the Class C
students may bear some responsibility...
A two-week suspension for Sudo-kun,
and a one-week suspension for the
Class C students. How about it?
The difference in punishment is based
on the difference in harm done to them.
Without Sakura's testimony and evidence,
Sudo's suspension would
have been a month or more.
It is quite a compromise.
Ms. Chabashira, what do you think?
It seems the conclusion
has already been reached.
Sakura, you did very well.
That's that, then.
Then, Class D representative Horikita-san,
please tell us your opinion.
Very well.
I believe that Sudo-kun, the instigator
of this incident, has a serious problem.
He never thinks about the trouble that his
daily actions will cause those around him.
Incidents like this are inevitable.
Wh-Why you...
I want you to realize that it's your
attitude that's at the root of all of this.
He should reflect,
but not about this incident.
I mean that he should re-evaluate
the person he has been in the past.
Horikita?
In regards to the incident
we're discussing right now,
I believe that Sudo-kun is free of guilt.
Because this was not an unfortunate incident
that just happened to take place,
but an intentional set-up
instigated by Class C.
I assert Sudo-kun's complete
innocence in the matter.
An intentional set-up?
How funny.
I think the president's little sister is—
As the witness testified,
Sudo-kun is a victim.
Please make the correct judgment.
We're the victims, Mr. President!
Shut the hell up! Listen up—
As I thought, this was a waste of time.
Everything you say is completely at odds.
Which means that one side
is offering false testimony.
I agree.
Let me ask Class C... Can you
say with absolute certainty that
your testimony here today is the truth?
Y-Yes, of course!
What about you, Class D?
Certainly.
Then I'll give my judgment tomorrow at 4:00.
If I receive no proof
of your opponents' lies,
or admissions of your own guilt by then,
I'll be putting expulsion
on the table, as well.
That is all.
Do we have a chance?
Drawing Room
I don't intend to lose. I don't give up.
I'm sorry...
I should have just spoken up from the start,
but I didn't have... the courage...
Hold your head high, Sakura.
But...
Student Council Office
You're still here?
When you showed up with Suzune,
I assumed you had some strategy in mind.
I'm neither Zhuge Liang
nor Kuroda Kanbei.
I have no strategy.
So Suzune went rogue in proclaiming
his innocence, then?
I guess it's a wild idea, huh?
It is.
Sakura, was it?
Yes.
If you can't prove it, it's just a lie.
Your mask is nothing but a shackle.
I... I only told the truth...
I believe her.
I see.
In that case...
Can you prove it?
That's a good question.
Ayanokoji Kiyotaka       8020 PPt
Horikita Suzune           36259 PPt
Kushida Kikyo             39523 PPt
Sakura Airi                   15125 PPt
Sudo Ken                              1 PPt
Yukimura Teruhiko      52330 PPt
Sotomura Hideo           10029 PPt
Komiya Kyogo             74987 PPt
Kondo Reon                 69621 PPt
Ishizaki Daichi             25335 PPt
First Year Class Points
Class A              1,004pt
Class B                 663pt
Class C       In Deliberation
Class D        In Deliberation
There are two kinds of lies;
one concerns an accomplished fact, the other concerns a future duty.
Jean-Jacques Rousseau, "Emile sau educația"