I'm sorry we have to drop you off here.
You're releasing me?
We can't just drag you around.
It's yours.
I can have it?
I don't care if you feel
the need to draw it on me.
Be careful now.
See you around, Sayaka-chan!
So have you gotten all you
needed from your conversation?
More or less.
For now, we've decided on a place to meet.
It's probably best that I don't ask, then.
What's this?
Meeting place.
Just delete that app, too.
They're probably all over my place now.
They're likely also tracking this car.
Huh?
There's a thing called the N-system—
Figures, there's the police.
I'll have to let you off here.
Ah, Rui-san, I'm sorry for all the trouble
and not being able to properly thank you.
Don't worry about it. Get going.
We'll be going, then.
You've got a tough road ahead. Good luck.
Where are we going?
Ebisu.
Katana Maidens
Sunlight is the best, but...
Episode 4  The Burden of Resolution
It's still way too early in the year for this.
Take that!
Sorry!
Won't you play, too, Kaoru?
I'll pass.
Hi!
Huh, a mission? That's sudden.
No way. Tell them we're on vacation.
"No way, we're on vacation," she says.
God damn it, Kaoru, stop screwing around!
But even if there is a mission,
I don't have Nenekirimaru.
I sent it home via express service yesterday.
I'm sending it back.
Wow.
What a waste of tax dollars.
Are you prepared to kill her, then?!
I won't kill her!
Thank you so much.
We appreciate the help.
I'm pretty tired.
What about you, Hiyori-chan?
Hiyori-chan?
Kanami...
What is it?
You have helped me out considerably.
I am grateful, but we should part ways here.
But I said that I would go with you.
After this point, there is no way
you can continue with me.
Why not?
I realized last night that your sword
and mine are completely different.
My sword is one that kills,
while yours is one that protects.
Only a sword that kills is needed now.
Don't just decide that by yourself.
You just think that's the case.
Kanami, have you ever
actually cut down anyone?
Not their utsushi?
Yes, or a human controlled by an aradama.
I haven't.
In recent years, there haven't been many
cases of humans being taken over by aradama.
But not too long ago,
at least until my mother's generation,
it wasn't so unusual.
Humans controlled by aradama
are no longer human.
While they may retain their memories and
are able to speak and answer questions,
an aradama is an aradama.
You get rid of them by
killing them with okatana.
There is no other way to save them.
We Toji are priestesses who bear the
burden of the sins of our ancestors
and continue to appease them.
I know that.
What I am going to do is
exterminate the aradama,
but it is essentially murdering someone.
I will kill Origami Yukari and
anyone who tries to stop me.
It has come extremely
close to being a grudge.
But you cannot kill,
so we will part ways here.
Wait!
You're slow.
You should go back. Go back and
protect people from the aradama.
I'm sorry for worrying you, Shibata-san.
Yes, please make sure my father, mother,
Miu, and Shiori won't worry, too.
How long are you staying here, Yanase-san?
As long as President Hashima
remains here. What about you?
I'm going back today.
I see.
I wanted to go back with Juujou-san,
since we came here together.
Sayaka!
Come with me.
I believe that's Itomi-san from Renpu.
President's Office
What do you mean, they were
protected by jurisdiction?
I am sorry.
Determining the enemy's location,
carrying out a sneak attack,
and then slinking back after
failing to destroy them.
Seems that I overestimated you.
I have no interest in foolish tournaments,
but your worth is measured by getting
a 100% success rate on your missions.
Perhaps I have been a bit too overprotective.
It is open.
What do you want?
Yukari-sama ordered me to bring you.
Yukari-sama did?
Renpu President.
Y-Yes, ma'am!
I do not remember giving you
permission to pursue them.
W-We ascertained the
location of the traitors,
and I thought they might get away,
so I made the decision myself.
I will not permit unauthorized actions.
B-But I cannot forgive them!
The traitors who turned their okatana on you
are running around freely,
right within our reach!
Why will you not allow me to go after them?!
President Takatsu,
you have said quite enough.
Damn you.
Yukina...
Y-Yes!
Do what you need to do first.
Yukari-sama...
That's enough. You're dismissed.
Yomi...
Stretch!
Are you all set?
Yeah.
Well then, mission start!
Found you!
You're Minoseki Academy second-year
middle school student Etou Kanami, correct?
That's right.
I am Kohagure Ellen, first-year high
school student at Osafune Girls' School.
And this is Kaoru.
Prepare to fight, scoundrel, for turning
your blade on the head of the Origami family!
By the way, where's Juujou Hiyori?
Hiyori-chan isn't here,
but if you're after her, I'll deal with you.
That will make things easy.
What a pain in the butt.
Yakumaru Jigen style?
What was that?
Such power...
I missed. What a pain.
If I'd hit you, you would've been smashed.
Kongoshi?
Taisha style and martial arts using kongoshi?
I can't just keep my distance
if I'm going to face her.
I have to get closer!
I can't get any closer like this!
These two, it's like they're
two working as one!
Darn it!
Yes, I caught you!
Now, Kaoru!
That was close.
Hiyori-chan? Why?
Why aren't you running away?
But...
Now it's finally two-on-two.
It's no use,
they're completely working as one.
That's because Kaoru and
I are the best partners!
Well, then...
If I turn the impact back around on her...
What? An aradama?
That's right. You have good eyes.
What's going on?!
I lost in our match the other day.
I wonder how today's will turn out.
You're going to fight like this?
I'd get in trouble if I fought
like this in a match.
En garde!
So our assassins are from Osafune this time?
How did you know where we were?
That is a secret.
What? An aradama?
It apparently obeys her.
So you're using an aradama?
Answer the question. Otherwise...
Hiyori-chan!
I will complete my objective
and kill anyone who tries to stop me.
Please wait a minute.
Feel like talking now?
Um... in a bit, after about five seconds.
Five seconds?
That's...
S Equipment.
Used for completely annihilating aradama.
I've only ever heard about the
S Equipment once before, in class.
Same here.
Changing complete.
Meet armored Kaoru.
Our situation has reversed now.
Hiyori-chan...
Right.
Ready, let's go!
What? Huh? Huh?
Hey! This is the star mecha's big scene!
All those from Renpu are being withdrawn.
We are backing out from this case.
I was of no use at all.
What's wrong?
We have an inquiry from Yokosuka Base
asking whether or not we dispatched
S equipment to the south.
S Equipment?
We have not received any such report.
Here is the image.
Those do look like the launching containers.
Our withdrawal is postponed!
Find out exactly where those landed!
Shidou-san, Konohana-san,
your dispatch orders from
Yukari-sama have come.
Please get ready.
They're not coming after us.
The equipment is still in development.
So it should only be usable for
a limited amount of time.
It's raining again.
Looks like it's going to come down.
For Yukari-sama to let us go now...
This must be important to her.
It's unusual for you to
leave Yukari-sama's side.
My abilities will be useful
in searching for the enemy.
Will Yume be remaining behind?
Needless blood would be spilled
if she were sent along.
Ah, I'm so bored I'm gonna die.
That's true.
But it is unlikely
that S Equipment would exist outside the
Origami family's jurisdiction.
There aren't any other organizations
beyond the Origami family
or the Administration who
can develop that equipment.
If there was, that would
mean the Administration is...
We would have to use that plan.
If there actually is a rebel faction in
the special military, as the rumors say,
then it's not so unlikely.
Yukari-sama is trying to ascertain
if they have contacted those girls.
Or perhaps that's already the case.
So, how did they do?
Ability-wise, they were fine.
Other than that...
What did you think, Kaoru?
Seems like they weren't just being reckless.
Thank you for coming to help me.
When I faced off with you earlier,
I thought about something.
Your sword is heavy.
When it comes to killing people,
I believe that the girl from last night,
Sayaka-chan, is superior.
And as far as power goes, the girl with
the oodachi earlier is better as well.
But your sword is the heaviest.
What are you trying to say?
I realized that your sword is
weighed down with your will.
Achieving an objective takes a
strong will. That's why it's heavy.
That time, in the final
match of the tournament,
I could only think of how
you were going to attack me.
My mind was only stuck on you,
but you never really did see me, did you?
I was pretty upset about that.
You were?
Yeah, since you ignored me.
Later, if I'd just stayed back and watched,
they would've killed you.
It's like you said. I wasn't prepared,
nor did I have any particular intention.
But now I can say that I do.
If my sword is one that protects,
then I will protect you and your objective.
Then that would just be
aiding in someone's murder.
It won't.
You will kill the head of the family...
No, an aradama pretending to be human.
I won't allow you to kill anyone else.
That's my resolution.
The reason I want to
defeat Origami Yukari...
You told me I could talk about
it if I ever felt like it, right?
I'll tell you now.
Okay.
Kanami, you know about the
great aradama incident
that happened twenty years ago, don't you?
The Great Disaster of Sagami Bay?
The worst aradama ever in history,
which appeared in Enoshima,
and was vanquished by Origami Yukari-sama,
the current presidents of the Five Schools,
and the Special Religious Military Units?
Yes, and my mother was part of a Special
Religious Military Unit at that time.
No records of her remain.
Not surprising, considering
everything is a matter of doctrine
since the incident is
well-known around the world.
What do you mean?
The truth of it all is
written in this letter.
It talks about what you saw,
the true identity of Origami Yukari, and...
the great aradama that was
said to have been vanquished.
The worst thing to have threatened the
existence of this country, no, the world,
lives even now, wreaking havoc.
That's what she is.
And the only one among the gathered Toji
who possessed the power to
destroy it was my mother.
Your mother?
But she couldn't completely destroy it.
It became a part of
Origami Yukari and survived.
After exhausting her Toji powers,
I watched my mother waste
away over the years.
And last year, she drew her last
breath as I watched over her.
That night, I made a vow.
I would destroy the thing
that stole my mother's life
and even now continues to sneak
around in the human world.
I would finish the task
my mother left undone.
Part of the heaviness you
mentioned is my duty as a Toji,
but the other half is my own personal grudge.
That is why you do not need to accompany me.
You're right.
It seems pretty heavy, though,
so I'll take on half of it.
Perfect timing. The rain has stopped.
Now, then, to the mountain hunt.
Next Episode  A Night of Mountain Hunting