What's wrong, Nene?
There's something I want to look into,
so I'm going to be late getting back.
Please see off the caged birdies.
Thanks!
Stupid Ellen...
Kohagura Ellen, first-year high school
student from Osafune Girls' School.
You participated in the
tournament matches, didn't you?
Oh, how embarrassing. That was
a very disappointing result.
I see you've decided to feign ignorance.
Um... may I put my hands down now?
I don't have any intention
of fighting with you.
Then hand over your okatana.
And your cell phone.
My hands were going numb.
So, what were you doing here?
Well, you saw how my
match turned out, right?
I knew that if I went back empty-handed,
I would get a serious scolding
from my school's president,
so I thought that I would get credit
by catching Yukari-sama's attackers.
Then the reason you brought out
S Equipment was to catch the traitors?
S Equipment? What are you talking about?
Last night, two S Equipment
containers of unknown origin
were launched toward
the middle of Mount Izu.
We believe they were prepared
for the escaping traitors.
It's only natural that we would
think they belonged to you
and the one other representative
from Osafune, Mashiko Kaoru.
I'm hungry!
It seems we need to ask you a few things.
Katana Maidens
Episode 6  The Space Between Humans and Disgrace
What do you mean, you don't
want me to interrogate her?
I mean exactly that.
Do you intend to ignore that
Yukari-sama placed me in charge?
Goodness, using your position
as a shield to get your way
isn't like you at all.
You're not going to let that
girl see your eye, are you?
She might be a part of Mokusa.
I seem to be lacking calm after
falling behind in last night's fight.
Where are you going?
To calm myself.
Perhaps I teased her too much?
I am also lacking calm myself.
If you are indeed their friend,
I will have to make you pay, Kohagura-san.
Thank you for the food.
Was it to your liking?
It's a bit annoying
that they microwave the pickles with the
convenience store lunch boxes though.
Really? I don't really mind it so much.
You're an interesting person.
About that S Equipment...
It's already been carried away.
That's really nothing to do with me.
Kohagura is certainly an unusual name.
But I felt like I had
heard it somewhere before.
And I remembered why a little bit ago.
It seems the chief engineer
of the S Equipment
development team that transferred
from DARPA had that name.
I believe her name was
Jacqueline Anne Kohagura?
Jacqueline is my mother.
And let me also just say that my father,
Kohagura Kimitake, works with her, but...
Even the head of development cannot
launch an unregistered unit.
The development and creation
of the S Equipment
is all being done under the
control of the Origami family.
But I wonder about your grandfather?
My grandpa?
Grandpa is...
Yes, Richard Friedman, the brilliant
scientist who became the forerunner
of noro's military use and pioneered
the development of the S Equipment.
Five years ago, after selling off the
technological development company
he founded himself,
he suddenly disappeared, right?
Yes.
Are you aware that there is evidence
that Dr. Friedman has entered Japan?
And he has been in contact with Mokusa.
No, rather, what if he was one of the
people who formed the core of Mokusa?
Mogusa? Is that like moxibustion?
You insist on playing dumb?
Well, it's no matter.
Oh, that's right.
About your friend, Mashiko Kaoru...
Are you aware that she faced off against
our comrade Satsuki Yomi last night?
It seems this is the first you're hearing
of it. Or are you still just playing dumb?
Well, regardless of the reason,
turning your blade on a
member of the elite guard
is the same as turning
your blade on Yukari-sama.
That sin is remedied with death...
Regardless of whether or not you
and Mashiko-san are part of Mokusa.
What happened to Kaoru?
Who knows?
I will speak with you again.
Irozaki
Only six more kilometers.
I wonder if Ellen-chan and Kaoru-chan
are safely on their way, too?
N-Nene-chan?
If he's here, then that means...
Kaoru-chan, you're all right!
I'll help you reach the meeting point.
Kaoru-chan?
What is it?
What's wrong?
Apparently, he wants to take us somewhere.
Nene!
What happened to the other girl?
Where's Ellen-chan?
Come in.
Sorry, it's just me.
Where did Yukari-sama go?
Who knows?
When I got here, she was already gone.
Even though I came all
this way to play with her.
I see.
I know, why don't I go look for her?
No, thank you.
So boring!
Just rest for now.
Do you know the meaning of the word "limit"?
What do you want?
We're heading out.
Did we find the others?
It's unconfirmed,
but we've obtained a report that they
were spotted in the mountains of Minamiizu.
I don't believe there are any
other middle school girls running
around the mountains in their uniforms.
Let's go, Suzuka.
I'm the one who came to get you.
Squads One and and Two with me!
Squad Three, wait here for
further communication!
Roger!
Well, then, I guess it's
time I got moving, too.
Hi! It's been a while, my sweet Yasutsugu!
I must be useful, no matter what.
I see. So this is the reason
Kaoru drew her okatana on her.
What poor manners. If you knew I
was here, you should have said so.
Such considerations are not necessary
for those who wrong Yukari-sama.
Then I will show no restraint, either.
I'm pretty skilled with my fingers!
Here I come.
There will be no end to them this way.
I'll have to destroy the source.
Toji aren't necessarily just
skilled in the use of swords.
Not enough.
More...
More power...
A-A horn?!
Are you a demon?
For my master.
I'm not holding back then!
My deadly stomach blow didn't work?!
This is just a little bit bad.
Kohagura escaped?
Yes. Squad member Satsuki
is currently pursuing her.
Isn't that for the best?
The fox is bringing out its tail.
No, I guess "tanuki" would
be more fitting? Or else—
Yes. This is Yomi we're talking about.
She won't get away so easily.
So you can no longer generate utsushi?
En garde.
Kaoru?!
You're still alive, Ellen.
Yes!
Then use kongoushin.
Home run!
Y-You idiot!
A-Are you okay, Ellen-chan?
K-Kanamin? What are you doing here?
Hiyoyon is here, too! See?
Don't get the wrong idea.
I only came to make sure which
opponent I should be fighting.
The members of the elite guard
really are using aradama.
So this is the "human experimentation"
the letter mentioned.
Can a human really become so repulsive?
Kanami, take the blonde with you.
What about you?
I'm going to stop her, with shorty here.
Got it! Let's go, Ellen-chan.
Why did you come?
You could be in Irozaki by now...
Yeah, we thought about going,
but we heard about her from Kaoru-chan...
About how she was using aradama yesterday.
So that's why?
Kaoru-chan was so worried about you.
Nene-chan told us.
Nene did?
First my pet and now my partner...
I keep increasing my debt to you.
It's over.
Over?
Is it really, now?
What?
That's...
Yomi!
What is it? What happened?
Hiyori-chan, what's wrong?!
Kanami!
Hurry, and go! They're coming!
Kaoru!
Hiyori-chan!
Don't move, Kanami!
She is beyond help...
Over here!
I'll be your opponent now!
Yomi...
She's taken on more noro
than she can control.
We have to hurry.
Right.
Kanami!
Cut her down, Kanami!
She is no longer human!
You're going to die!
Kanami!
What's happening?
I'm saved?
It seems so.
She probably couldn't balance
the power of the noro.
Injecting the human body with
noro is beyond reckless.
It's because they use the aradama that way.
What a relief! She's still alive.
What are we going to do now?
Other elite guards will come running
because of this commotion.
No problem.
Ellen...
Yes, roger that.
Please arrange a taxi for us urgently!
Taxi?
Stuff like this is a piece of cake
for an organization like Mokusa.
There's no way we can escape
on a boat like this.
You there, contact the Japan Coast Guard.
There's no need to worry!
This isn't the taxi I summoned.
That is!
This was unpredictable.
Withdraw.
Inbound from the US military,
no response on the patrol network
They have been unable to spot the target.
They completely managed to escape.
How could you fail with three
members of the elite guard?
Not to mention, one of you ended up like that.
How regrettable.
Yukari-sama!
My apologies.
I have no excuses for this failure—
Enough. Don't trouble yourself.
But...
The presidents from Minoseki Academy
and the Heijou Institute
are dismissed from this special
mission at the present time.
Return to your usual duties.
Yes, ma'am.
Renpu President...
Yes!
I believe I told you not to leave your post.
Yes, ma'am.
The two birds are right in
the palm of my hand even now.
Why don't we guide them some more?
Now, Ema-chan, don't overdo it.
Huh?
Sayaka, come with me.
Yukina...
Sayaka-chan.
I'm glad you can leave.
We'll be going back to Minoseki tomorrow, too.
I see.
Bye.
Your cookies were delicious.
Thank you.
I'll make some again if you'd like.
Okay.
Hey, do you have a cell phone?
Let's exchange contact info.
Sayaka!
Coming.
Still the same as ever, Yukina.
Sana?
Ah, thank goodness! Ema-senpai? I have
just a teeny tiny favor to ask of you.
I don't have a single good memory
attached to hearing you sound like that.
Don't say that! It's a request from S-a-n-a!
I must have Yukari-sama's approval.
It's Renpu and my reason for living...
Next Episode  Heart Ache