That's enough!
Your coordination still has some weak spots,
but you've gotten pretty good.
Huh? Is she actually praising us?
She most certainly is.
Praise from Takako is rare.
Yay!
Don't get cocky.
You still haven't managed to get a point yet.
Yes, ma'am.
Ah, bath time.
Katana Maidens
Episode 9  After the Festival
Gosh, your back is so
small and adorable, Saaya.
I don't know whether it's that
I feel I can't leave you alone,
or that I feel I need to protect you,
but you just set off my maternal instincts.
What the heck?
Individual fights are fun and all,
but team fighting is fun, too!
We still don't have a lot of
actual battle experience,
so having things like an attack
squad and a mobile squad is new.
Yeah.
You're so strong, Kanami-chan.
So are you, Mai-chan!
When we were facing off against Satomi-san,
you attacked at the same time as Kaoru-chan,
and hesitated for a moment, didn't you?
If you had attacked like that I'm
sure we would've gotten a point.
So you saw that much.
I'm not sure if it's that I saw it,
or was able to see it...
You really are strong, Kanami-chan.
Even after hearing that story about
your mother, you're still trying to fight.
No, I guess it's because you heard
the story about your mother,
but for me...
You have no reason to fight, do you?
If you don't have a reason,
then you don't need to fight.
Just stay here.
I'm sure Mokusa will harbor
you until things settle down.
But you and Kanami-chan are going, right?
Because we have a connection.
Those two will also likely face
battle because they're with Mokusa.
But you and Itomi do not
need to come with us.
I will destroy Origami Yukari.
Mai-chan...
It's pretty noisy outside.
Of course it is. After all,
today is the festival.
Festival?
This village has one twice a year, apparently.
Did you hear that, Mai-chan?
Practice is over and everything,
so let's go check it out later.
Okay, sure.
A festival! This is so exciting!
Huh?
My uniform is gone.
So is mine.
Don't tell me...
If you're looking for your uniforms,
they've been sent to the cleaners.
They'll be ready later tonight.
In the meantime, here you go.
Wow! Yukata! So refined.
Professor Friedman prepared them for you.
He said you should wear these,
and go enjoy the festival.
That's my grandpa for you!
He's so understanding.
Wow, it's the perfect size.
How did that old man figure that out?
That's my grandpa for you.
Come on, put yours on too, Hiyori-chan.
This isn't the time for such frivolity.
It's a festival!
If we can't celebrate today,
then when will we ever get to?
Come on, put it on.
H-Hey...
It looks good on you, Hiyori-chan.
Aren't we going to the festival?
Yeah! Let's go guys!
What series is that from?
Ellen, it's about time.
You're right.
There's something we want you all to see.
What's that?
My grandpa wishes to invite you to
the main event for today's festival.
Main event?
It's so beautiful.
I found you, Hiyori-chan and Kanami-chan!
Rui-san?!
How are you two doing?
What about you? Were you all right
after everything that happened?
Of course she wasn't.
Ruippe was apparently arrested,
as a suspect in the assault
on Origami Yukari.
So then that was because we intruded on you.
Don't worry about it.
President Hashima pulled some strings,
and I was released immediately.
So that's what happened.
You're Mai-chan, aren't you?
And Sayaka-chan, it's been a while.
Do you know her too, Sayaka-chan?
I attacked her home.
Huh?!
Now, let's go then, shall we?
You've been invited, right?
All of you, by FineMan.
It's Takako-san and Satomi-san!
That's a shintai?
I wonder what's in it?
It's noro.
There's still noro that the
Origami family hasn't collected?
Surprised?
There aren't as many as there
used to be, but there are still
shrines in this country that
worship noro like this.
Worship?
Yes, they worship it
politely and respectfully.
Do you know how noro was created
to begin with, Kanami-kun?
Um....
While refining the tamahagane steel
used to forge okatana,
noro is separated out as an impurity.
You're very good, Mai-kun.
Noro that is separated from
tamahagane steel,
which has the power to become an okatana,
has almost the same divinity
as the okatana itself.
Even with the technology we
have today, we cannot erase it.
But we were told that if it's left alone,
it'll turn into an aradama, and that's
why the Origami family manages it.
And that is incorrect.
Huh?
Let's try continuing this somewhere else.
Noro was once worshiped in shrines
like this all over the country.
We started managing the
collection of it as we do now
around the end of the Meiji period.
The government at the time
wanted to reduce the number
of shrines primarily for economic reasons,
and so they were consolidated together.
Naturally, as a result, the noro was turned
into spectrum meters or became aradama.
In order to prevent that,
the Origami family at the time
strictly managed the amount of noro.
However, as the signs of an
oncoming war intensified,
voices calling for military
use of noro increased,
and the restrictions were removed.
For military use?
They sought to amplify the
divinity of the noro...
In short, its power to interfere with
the netherworld that, until then,
had only been expressly permitted
for you Toji to use in battle.
After the war, the collection
of noro was accelerated
as the United States Army joined the study.
Officially, they said that it was safer
to gather the dangerous noro in one place
and manage it that way
rather than dispersing it,
and they began gathering
noro all across Japan.
But there were unforeseen consequences.
The more noro from spectrum meters
that was gathered together,
the more it acquired intelligence.
Then does that mean if
you gather lots of noro,
you can create an intelligent aradama?
To put it simply, that is what happens.
Currently, the Origami family
has stockpiled a vast amount of noro,
more than has ever been in one place before.
That's...
Why you believe Princess Tagitsu is god-like...
That's not the only problem.
If that massive amount of noro is stimulated
by something and becomes an aradama—
no, a great aradama, there is
no way we could control it.
Much like what happened in the
Great Disaster of Sagami Bay.
What do you mean?
That disaster is an accident that
happened as a result of trying
to transport a fully-loaded tanker
of noro to the United States.
In other words, it was a man-made
disaster caused by human arrogance.
We should never have disturbed its sleep.
Noro is a victim, so to speak,
forced into existence by humans
who wish to create okatana.
If we can't go back to the
way things used to be,
we could, at the very least,
enshrine it and let it rest peacefully.
That is the only thing
we can do to atone now.
The aradama are victims?
Then that means everything
we've been doing...
Toji use their okatana to purify noro
that has become an aradama.
That does save people's lives. But...
The first Toji are said to have been
maidens who served in the shrines.
Which means you all have to properly take on
the duties of a shrine maiden,
rather than just defeating aradama.
How did they take it?
They bore it, as we expected.
Of course they did.
Even the five schools teach a version of
the truth warped by Origami Yukari.
They won't be able to accept
everything so easily.
Especially an honor student like Mai-kun.
They have to accept it.
All the more because they are Toji.
What will they do?
I do not know.
But whatever decision they make,
I would like to respect it.
That's our job as Mokusa, as well.
You changed, too?
The festival was a lot of fun.
Yeah.
I wonder if our mothers
went to it together, too.
Who knows?
Kanami...
Kogarasumaru?
Chidori, too.
Maybe it was fate.
We carry the swords our mothers used,
and we found each other.
They probably went.
Hm?
To the festival. Your mom
and my mom, together.
Yeah, I'm sure they did.
What can I do, though?
You can do anything.
Huh?
I'm also trying to think of what I can do.
Sayaka-chan...
The festival will be over soon.
If the noro is broken up
and enshrined again,
then there will be festivals
like this all over Japan.
When that happens, let's go play together!
All together with Hiyoyon,
Kanamin, Maimai, and Saaya.
Sure.
It's so shiny!
So, you're going to work together with us?
Yes, if by that you mean
to correct the distortion
and return the Toji to their original
roles, then our goals are the same.
I will defeat the main
cause, Origami Yukari.
I think it would be a pleasure to
have more skilled Toji.
You're so...
All right.
I understand how you feel.
Mokusa will welcome you. However...
There's trouble!
What is it?
This is the special military unit.
This area has been designated
a special disaster prediction zone.
Please move quickly according
to our instructions.
I repeat...
The Origami family?
They don't seem to be hunting aradama.
So we're already being treated as criminals?
But how did they find out about this village?
Now is not the time to investigate that.
Are they trying to detain
everyone in the village?
Probably.
And then they likely intend
to screen out anyone
involved with Mokusa and arrest them.
Now, then, what shall we do?
We cannot be captured here.
Then we will carry out a strategic retreat.
How are we going to retreat?
It might be a bit difficult like this,
but we will take the submarine.
That ship remains affiliated with the US Navy.
They are not an opponent a police
organization like theirs can handle.
Will that work, Akane-sama?
It's settled.
Let's split into two groups.
I will take Akane-sama and
the others to the pier.
I will gather up the other Toji,
and we'll stand our ground here.
Satomi, I leave the rest to you.
Right.
Um, what should we do?
You all come with me.
That includes you, Ellen, and Kaoru.
This is our escape route?
This used to be a naval base back in the day.
It has been thoroughly
prepared for emergencies.
Now, let's go!
Come at us already!
Sorry for the wait!
You're—!
I'm Tsubakuro Yume, the fourth member
of Origami Yukari's elite guard.
While I may be the fourth member,
I am the strongest.
Draw your swords!
Nikkari Aoe...
Such strength...
You ladies are too weak.
As expected, they've already secured here.
Are they going to strike?
Probably.
I mean, take a look.
They're equipped with spectrum finders.
All of the members of Mokusa are human.
Why would they need those
for detecting things?
Then...
Please try to remember what happened at Izu.
Even though you could
see aradama before you,
the spectrum finder had
no reaction whatsoever.
Does that mean the government-issued
devices have been modified?
Most likely, that is the case.
Those devices are made from technology
developed by the Origami family,
just like the S Equipment.
At this point, yes, it means the devices
have been set to react to okatana.
Several aradama have been detected.
They're very close.
Be careful!
At this rate, we will be treated as aradama.
So aradama are calling humans aradama now?
Damn it, let's go!
Wait.
Those men are only following orders.
I know.
Toji have really become aradama?
Fire! They aren't human, they're aradama!
Don't remove your utsushi!
Be careful!
Hang in there!
If she removes her utsushi now,
the arrow will remain behind in her body.
This is going to hurt a bit.
Do it!
Here we go.
These are...
Weapons that seal a Toji's movements.
Nee-sama... I can't believe you
would use something like this.
Not enough. This is not nearly enough.
They're over there, huh?
Akane-sama, hurry!
I'm sorry.
Etou! Yanase! Hurry up! Everyone get in!
Mai-chan, hurry!
Okay!
You go first.
Take care of Akane-sama!
Takako-san?
Man, I didn't make it? Shucks.
What happened to the Toji at the shrine?
Toji? Them?
They weren't able to resist at all, though.
But the girl who used this
okatana was a bit better, I guess.
Satomi...
You're gonna fight like that?
I'll wait for you, so why
don't you take out that arrow?
Or should I help you?
Not necessary.
I won't lose to Toji who rely on aradama!
Is that so?
I've never used even a
bit of aradama to fight.
This is entirely my own ability!
I wonder how Yume is doing now?
That girl doesn't know the
meaning of the word "restraint."
Next Episode  Resolve for Tomorrow