Kanami-chan...
Send an urgent message to the heads of both
the Heijou Institute and Minoseki Academy.
Katana Maidens
Episodul 2: Distanța dintre ele
This is far enough. Let's split up.
H-Hang on, you can't do this by yourself.
You're in no condition to generate utsushi
after using such a powerful jin'i.
What?!
You said you wanted to finish
our match, did you not?
Then I shall face off with you now.
I-I'm telling you, that's not a good idea.
You accompanying me any
further would be a nuisance.
Will you face off with me here?
If not, then leave.
What are you going to do now, Hiyori-chan?
There's something that I have to finish.
So that means getting caught
would be a problem, right?
That's right.
Then all you can do is run away.
I'll go with you!
I mean, if we work together,
we can manage like we did earlier.
Do you even realize what you're saying?
I do.
I know that means things might get rough.
And that it might cause
problems for a lot of people.
But I'll keep running away with you like this!
Come on, hurry!
What are your actual intentions?
Like I said, to get away somewhere safe...
Why?
Because I want to spar with you
properly once you've recovered.
I don't know what you're after, but I
will abandon you if you get in my way.
Does that mean I can go with you?
Do as you wish.
Okay, I will, then!
Juujou Kagari-sama
Under these circumstances, I should probably
dispose of this as soon as possible.
Did you hide that here earlier?
Before I ran into you in
front of the gate yesterday.
I didn't think I would be able to escape
after crossing blades with Origami Yukari.
Crap! I totally left my cell phone
and luggage behind at the inn!
Forget about it.
In any case, they would be
able to find out where we are
if you had the phone you were
given by the Sword Administration.
I wish I'd eaten all the cookies
Mai-chan gave me yesterday.
I cannot think of any
reason why she would do that.
We aren't very familiar
with Juujou-san either.
Was Etou Kanami acting
strangely at all yesterday?
Not that I could tell. She really
was acting like she always does.
When they escaped, I do not believe they
would have been able to cooperate
to repel the elite guard, even for an instant,
without some kind of training.
I don't know about that, either.
Yanase Mai likely doesn't know anything.
Iwakura Sanae was the same way, though.
For them to be able to draw
their swords on Yukari-sama...
I am ashamed of myself as
one of the elite guard.
But why did Yukari-sama stop us that time?
I am sure she has her reasons.
We will likely come to understand
why she did it later.
More importantly, do you think this incident
has something to do with that organization?
It's hard to tell right now.
Do you mean until both the
schools' presidents arrive?
That worked out well!
Okay, we're on the highway.
So this is all we have for money.
Is that an analog spectrum meter?
It's an antique!
There's noro inside of there, right?
I've used one in class before.
Everyone used to use one before the
restrictions on collecting noro were enforced.
Whose is this?
Was your mother a Toji, too, Hiyori-chan?
Too?
My mom was a Toji. They say
she was really powerful.
What was the name?
Of my mother?
Your name.
How mean, Hiyori-chan!
You don't know my name?!
It's Kanami! Etou Kanami!
You're too loud!
Looks like they haven't caught those two yet.
How much longer are they
going to leave us like this?
I want to take a bath and go to bed.
Ema-chan, it's been a while.
I hope you've been doing well, Iroha-san.
Indeed, I have been well.
Thank you for coming.
Goodness, Maki-chan, you've grown
into the elite guard uniform well.
Yukari-sama has summoned you.
Please come this way.
Where are we?
I think we're in Tokyo.
Look at that!
It's so tall!
So we're on the eastern side of Tokyo?
Are you both students?
Just the two of you?
Um... Well...
Oh, you're here for some kind of concert?
W-We are!
There have been a lot of those lately.
We managed somehow.
Nice to see you again.
It has been a while, Commander.
It's been ages. You truly haven't changed
a bit in all this time, Yukari-chan.
I apologize for the trouble
my students have caused.
There's no need for any formal apologies.
Do you know where they might be hiding?
I'm sorry, but I'm not sure.
Me, either. My apologies.
Where is my student named Yanase Mai?
Yanase Mai and Iwakura Sanae
have both been cleared of any
involvement and released.
I see.
Now then, let me ask another question.
Heijou Institute president, according to
your report to the Sword Administration,
Kogarasumaru was in the care
of the Heijou Institute,
but was not currently matched with anyone.
My apologies for the delay
in reporting to you.
Kogarasumaru chose that girl.
Kogarasumaru?
Etou Kanami is matched with Chidori and
Juujou Hiyori is matched with Kogarasumaru.
Chidori and Kogarasumaru?
Înapoi
Modificare
Etou Kanami
Hello?
Mai-chan?
Kanami—?!
Where are you right now?
Well, I'm not really sure.
I'm sorry for all the problems I've caused.
I'm totally fine. You don't need to worry.
You can't just tell me that...
This is the Taito disaster
prevention broadcast...
I'm sorry, I'm running out of change.
That broadcast...
Um, please take care of my stuff, bye!
Wait!
I'm back!
I bought us some dinner.
That was my first time
ever using a coin shower.
I was so nervous wondering if I
could finish washing myself in time.
You have no sense of apprehension, do you?
Well?
I think I can generate the utsushi.
That okatana is even bladed on the backside.
It's an ancient style called a
double-edged blade.
It also called Kogarasumaru-style.
Oh, I see. So that's why you used
that thrusting technique that time.
That time?
You know, when you were stopped
by the head of the Origami family?
You were able to see that?
Yep! Just barely!
I'd never seen a jin'i that fast before!
That technique was really amazing,
but I really want to see more
Shintou-style techniques.
You used the shigi no hagaeshi technique
when you faced that blonde girl, right?
That would've been dangerous for you,
had she been able to figure it out.
Now then, we will secure
Juujou Hiyori and Etou Kanami.
You both will remain here
and assist in this matter.
Understood.
Of course.
I wish she would have said they
wouldn't be rough, though.
Renpu has offered to help, too.
Things will only get more complicated
once Yukina-chan becomes involved.
President!
Yanase-san? What's the matter?
Shouldn't you be with—
Well, I have a favor to ask you.
Please allow me to search for Etou-san.
I can't believe they're
not letting us go home.
I heard they called in President Hashima, too.
Mai-chan hasn't come back yet, either.
I wonder what's going to happen to Kanami...
Lady Mai,
we have managed to pinpoint the location
from the vocal data you sent us earlier.
So it's from Taito Ward and
Arakawa Ward, understood. Thank you.
Excuse me, please head
to the designated place.
You're a weird one.
Huh?
Why won't you ask me anything?
Like what?
Why I'm after Origami Yukari's life.
So the thing you have to finish is
attacking the head of the Origami family?
Yes.
I see...
When you're ready to talk
about it, I'll listen.
We don't have to now.
You really are weird.
Um, excuse me!
Y-Yes?
Do you have two Toji staying here?
T-Toji-san?
Kanami-chan?!
They were faster than I thought. How did
they figure out where we were staying?
Sorry, that's probably my fault.
I called my friend from a payphone yesterday.
Well, I figured you'd do something like that.
Sorry...
There's nothing we can do about it.
And I've managed to recover a bit, too.
Stația Nippori
l
Autobuz non-stop
What'll we do?
Let's see...
We probably won't stand out as much
in places with lots of people.
Just because I said that, doesn't
mean we're here to sightsee!
But you said somewhere with lots
of people, and this is all I know.
There are lots of girls like us and
girls wearing uniforms around,
so it'll make it hard to find us, right?
It's Sunday. That's why it's so crowded.
We'll stand out if we
just keep standing here.
It's more natural for us to at
least look like we're having fun.
Sorry, I'll definitely pay you back sometime.
What's the matter?
Let's go there.
We need to go over our plans for
what we're going to do next.
Oh, okay.
You like mint chocolate chip, Hiyori-chan?
Y-Yes, I do. It is probably the
most palatable ice cream flavor.
Don't you think it's bitter, though?
It leaves you feeling refreshed,
kind of like toothpaste.
Stupid!
Stupid?!
That example has already been exhausted
in the list of pros and cons
regarding mint chocolate chip.
You may consider it a forbidden phrase.
O-Okay then, sorry.
We should look for somewhere to stay.
Kind of like where we stayed yesterday?
Or somewhere like an internet café.
What's making that noise?
The spectrum meter? An aradama?
There's one close by.
It's only reacting to one?
Apparently, it hasn't moved yet.
Over there?
Let's go.
No, let it go.
Now isn't the time to be
doing something like that.
Huh? W-We can't do that!
We have to exterminate it right away,
or else it will destroy things.
The Toji with jurisdiction here are
probably already apprehending it.
Encountering them would be a pain.
But...
They have spectrum finders.
It will not take them long to find it.
Besides, even if we could exterminate
the aradama on our own,
we cannot collect the noro.
It would just scatter.
That's still better than it causing damage.
Let's go, Hiyori-chan.
If you abandon the aradama now,
simply because you don't want to get caught,
it will start to affect you, too!
You—!
Let's go!
Why now?
Excuse me, an aradama has
been detected nearby.
I'm going to head that way!
We are from the Special Religious Military
Unit! Please get away from the aradama!
I'll go, you try to corner it!
Roger that!
Kanami!
Got it!
Hachiman power!
We did it!
What should we do about collecting the noro?
Um...
I will claim it.
Mai-chan!
Our pursuer is from Minoseki?
Wait, Hiyori-chan!
Mai-chan is my best friend.
What are you doing here, Mai-chan?
The spectrum finder detected an aradama.
You seem to have already
exterminated the aradama.
I was able to find you thanks to that.
If you're her best friend, then why
are you pointing your okatana at us?
I am Kanami-chan's best friend.
And because I'm her best friend,
I'm going to save her!
H-Hang on a second, you two!
Put away your okatana!
It seems she doesn't intend to.
Mai-chan!
Listen to me, Kanami-chan.
President Hashima promised me
that if you come back with me,
she'll do everything in her power
to help lighten your punishment.
Kanami, this is your chance. Go back home.
No way, Hiyori-chan.
But on one condition.
Juujou-san, you have to accompany us
back to the Origami family mansion.
Unfortunately, I'm not going to be
able to cooperate with you on that.
You don't have to cooperate.
I will make you do so by force.
Try it.
For the last year and a half,
I've always been on the receiving
end of Kanami-chan's sword.
Juujou-san, your sword is sharp,
but it is far more straightforward
and easy to avoid than hers.
I also noticed yesterday that
you have no skill with a blade!
Kanami-chan?
I'm sorry, Mai-chan.
Hiyori-chan and I can't let
ourselves get caught just yet.
Why?
I saw it!
When the she was stopping the blow
from Hiyori-chan's technique,
she pulled out two okatana
from an empty space,
and there was something bad behind her.
Something bad?
So you were able to see it, too?
Only for an instant. I thought
I was just seeing things.
It was...
an aradama.
Aradama?!
That can't be...
She's the head of the Origami family.
She's the legendary hero who
vanquished the great aradama.
No! That is...
The great aradama in Origami Yukari's form!
Then, the Origami family, the Sword
Administration, and the five schools...
All of it is being controlled by the aradama.
Anyway, I can't leave
Hiyori-chan alone right now!
So please, Mai-chan!
You're... serious about this?
Okay, then.
Mai-chan...
I understand. You're always serious
about the things you do, Kanami-chan.
You forgot these.
They seized the rest of your things
and I couldn't get them back.
Thanks.
We'll be going, then.
Okay. See you later.
Oh, Juujou-san...
Please look after Kanami-chan.
I will simply do what I have to do.
It's so good, Mai-chan.
What's this?
Dacă ai vreo problemă,
te rog să suni la acest număr
Data viitoare: Sabie inocentă