Sayaka, the greatest
vessel I have ever found.
This is the result of the monumental
research Yukari-sama ordered Renpu...
No, me to carry out.
Once you are granted this power,
you will be complete as a vessel.
You will think nothing and feel nothing.
You will simply be a Toji who strikes
those who wrong Yukari-sama.
Nothing...
Sayaka, what are you doing?
I'm...
Katana Maidens
Episode 7  Heart Ache
We're low on bandages,
so stop playing around!
Hey, put this aradama outside right now!
Like I told you, Nene is my pet,
Ow, ow, ow! Just because we're low
on bandages doesn't mean you have
you eternally flat-chested woman.
to wrap it so tight, Hiyori-chan!
Eternally?
Please don't blame Nene, Hiyoyon.
It's my fault we don't have
enough bandages, since I used so much.
Anyway, what a shock that was.
I can't believe FineMan
is Ellen's grandfather!
That's true.
What a huge taxi.
It is an honor to meet you two rebels.
Today is certainly a perfect day.
Could it be...
Are you FineMan?
FineMan is an alias I use to conceal myself
from the world, but my true identity is...
Richard Friedman!
Creator of the S Equipment, and my grandpa.
Oh, no!
You spoiled it, my beloved granddaughter.
So your grandfather made this, Ellen-chan?
Not just me.
I also had help from many other engineers.
More importantly, why is a foreign
engineer working with Mokusa?
Because I've watched the Origami
family more closely than anyone.
Shortly after the Pacific War, collaborative
development of the S Equipment by the US Army
and the Origami family began as part of
a plan to divert noro for military use.
However, when development
stagnated without progress,
and the technology came to a
dead end, we had a breakthrough.
That was about 20 years ago.
Twenty years...
The Great Disaster of Sagami Bay.
After the Great Disaster, when she
became head of the family,
Origami Yukari purged the traditional
forces and started to streamline things.
Streamline?
As you know, noro was once
divided up into smaller pieces
and enshrined in various parts of the country.
The Origami family gathered up all the noro
and began to manage them themselves.
From then on, the level of the technology
in development suddenly increased,
and the S Equipment was completed.
And the one who brought about that
technology was Origami Yukari.
Origami Yukari did?
But from the perspective of a scientist,
this was technology that should not exist.
Gathering up the noro and the
technology that it brought about...
I wonder just where it all came from?
Where from?
It can't be!
Which is why I formed Mokusa in
cooperation with a certain person
who was suspicious about
the Origami family, like me.
A certain person?
Since then, we have been polishing
the blade of our resistance against
Origami Yukari behind the scenes.
Your mother, Juujou Kagari, was part
of those I sought help from.
I am truly glad to meet you,
the daughter of our savior, like this.
Thanks to Hiyoyon's mom,
our preparations gradually finished,
but we couldn't have predicted that just
when we were finally about to strike,
that you would charge Origami Yukari
head-on, almost ruining our secret plan.
In short, it's your fault that
everything has gone to crap.
I just did what I had to for my objective.
Oh, Hiyori-chan...
But there was a good thing to come of it!
If we give this to Sana-sensei,
she will analyze it in detail.
Which means, if we can prove the Origami
family is conducting inhumane research
to turn people into artificial aradama,
we could deal a great blow to
Origami Yukari's regime.
So, our mission is done.
The old man and president are
going to handle the rest.
What's the matter, Hiyori-chan?
Nothing, I just can't believe the Osafune
president is a member of Mokusa.
They say boys grow a lot in three days.
But they shouldn't forget about girls, either.
I like the look on your face.
I-I guess so?
Have you decided on a plan?
It's probably not as impressive
compared to my friend,
but I've decided to do my best.
Why?
I don't want to let her to die.
Yeah, yeah, I totally understand
where you're coming from.
I, too, wouldn't mind giving
half my life for a friend.
That's not all of it.
Anyway, Kanami! Come on,
let's hurry and do this.
Right.
I'm definitely going to
get a hit on you today!
Juujou Kagari-sama
The sky here looks different
than it does at Minoseki.
I wonder how Kanami-chan is doing.
Who would be calling at this hour?
Hello?
What's the matter, Sayaka-chan?
Thanks for calling. I'm so
happy you called me so quickly.
Shall we be chatty night owls together?
Thank you for coming.
It's all right, I'm listening.
Um...
It's nothing.
Sayaka-chan?
What did you just say?
I said that the elite guard cannot
assist in your search for Itomi Sayaka.
Our job is to guard Yukari-sama, anyway.
We have no right or obligation
to meddle in the interior problems
of Renpu Girls' Academy.
It is precisely because
it is for Yukari-sama!
Sayaka is the most suitable person
to be Yukari-sama's right hand!
She's different from you incompetents,
who couldn't even capture the traitors!
Elite guard! Bring back Sayaka
immediately for Yukari-sama's sake!
I am sorry that we cannot measure
up to your expectations.
Damn you, Shidou!
Be quiet.
You are the one who is tormenting
Yukari-sama, President Takatsu.
Those useless brats! They're just
afraid of being replaced by Sayaka.
President Takatsu...
Yomi?
Unable to control your precious powers,
and yet you call yourself a member of the
elite guard while in that pathetic state.
You're just a prototype that Yukari-sama
took in out of the kindness of her heart.
Learn your place.
My...
If you want my power, then here.
If I want your power?!
The power you have been
given is nothing more
than overflowing garbage that
is for completing Sayaka!
But you were summoned by
Yukari-sama, so you've gotten
so full of yourself that you
think you can look down on me?!
Don't forget!
As long as Sayaka is around,
you lot are no longer needed!
Wow, that old lady is pissed.
Sayaka-chan is about the same
age I was when I ran away from home.
Wasn't everyone saying she's
a genius or something?
I bet everyone would be shocked if I got her.
Yanase Mai
Mobile
Riot Police Headquarters
Unknown
Missed Call
Riot Police Headquarters
Unknown
Why did I...?
Sayaka?
Sayaka? Wait!
I've always done as I was told.
But I would surely disappear
if that got into me.
Totally disappear.
Wait! Sayaka-chan!
Found you.
I'm sorry I'm so late.
I went around to all the
convenience stores in the area.
Why? I didn't...
Are you hungry?
Let's get something from
the convenience store...
Oh, but they wouldn't let
middle schoolers buy anything at night...
Oh, right!
I still have some, thank goodness.
Cookies.
I told you about my younger
sister yesterday, right?
Yeah.
She's basically really selfish,
and it's to the point
where I've asked her if she just
makes it a hobby to bug me.
Because of that, though,
when she's really in trouble,
she absolutely will not ask me for help.
Strange isn't it?
Even though it's so obvious.
How do you know?
I just do, because I'm her big sister.
This is just like that time.
Found you, Sayaka-chan.
You're from the elite guard.
Now, then, let's get back.
Old Lady Takatsu is waiting for you.
What's this? Do you not want to go back?
I see, what a bind.
Hey, what do you think I should do, miss?
Sayaka-chan?
If I go back that'll be the end of it.
Are you sure?
I don't know what's going on,
but are you really sure?
Tell me how you feel.
H-How I...?
I don't...
I don't want to.
Okay, then.
Well, then, how about we play hide and seek?
I'll give you till the count of ten.
If you can get away from me,
I'll pretend that I don't know
or haven't seen anything.
One, two, three, four...
Sayaka-chan!
I knew that would work, otherwise I
wouldn't get to show you how amazing I am.
Done already?
There's still more fun to be had!
Just kidding.
They're amazing.
You're good, Sayaka-chan,
but that's not all, is it?
Sayaka-chan!
I know you can use some kind
of amazing technique, right?
Wasn't it being free from all emotions?
You won't be able to cut anything
with a soulless sword like that!
What? You're not gonna do it?
It's a little unsatisfying,
but I've already wasted
my time, so let's end this!
Oopsie.
What a surprise. You're pretty
good yourself, miss.
Only just a bit, though.
Let's keep going!
Ooh, you're pretty stubborn!
N-No, stop...
I'm fine. It's okay.
Why?
Because.
I'm older than you, Sayaka-chan.
That's reason enough for me.
It hurts. It hurts so much,
but it's so warm and hot that
it's filling my emptiness.
I don't want...
Are you finished already?
Then it's time for a break!
Sayaka-chan?
I don't want to lose this!
No way!
Sayaka-chan!
I'm fine.
You're great! So great, Sayaka-chan!
Sayaka-chan!
I was just starting to get serious,
but you're not what I thought you were.
What are you doing, Yume?
Renpu's President Takatsu...
Stand down! This isn't the business of
a defective product, such as yourself.
Okay, okay, I got it.
Yume! Damn you, what have you done?!
What a waste of my time.
Thanks.
Sure.
Sayaka! Enough of your selfishness.
Now, come back to Renpu.
Sayaka-chan...
Right.
That's right, Sayaka.
You're different from those defective
models in the elite guard.
You'll be a perfect Toji—
I can't be the Toji you want me to be.
No, I don't want to be.
Eh? What are you saying?
I thought I was fine being empty,
but I don't want to lose the
warmth that has filled me.
That's why I want to fight,
and be with the people who
gave me this warm feeling.
What?
You are the successor of Myouhou Muramasa,
and you're supposed to serve Yukari-sama
in my place! No, as I serve her!
You are a tool only for Yukari-sama!
Thank you for taking care of me.
Wait...
W-Wait, Sayaka!
Sayaka!
Let's do a bunch of things...
No, all the things you want to do.
Kanami-chan and I are both with you, okay?
I want to eat.
What?
I want to eat your cookies again.
Okay, with pleasure!
Lady Mai,
I have come to get you.
Shibata-san, why are you here?
Because I asked him to.
President Hashima... U-Um, I...
I have a rough grasp of the situation.
You two need to get away from here for now.
I wonder whose fault it is
that I'm so good at
cleaning up after reckless girls.
Hello, Sana?
Yes, you just need to hide them.
What they do from there is up to them.
Oh, me?
I've... Yes, I've accepted my fate.
Mai-chan!
Kanami-chan!
Let's see, Mai-chan, um, um...
Anyway, there's lots I want to tell you!
Yes, yes. I have lots to tell you, too.
Sayaka-chan!
It's just like they said!
You really did come!
Welcome! Mokusa warmly welcomes you both!
Have some restraint, you pervert.
Juujou-san...
Welcome to Mokusa.
Young Toji, my name is Origami Akane.
Next Episode  Day of Disaster