Looks like the rain has stopped.
There's enough moonlight for us to make it.
Let's go, Kanami.
We need to head to the designated
meeting spot as soon as possible.
Right!
We finally found you.
So this is where you two
were waiting out the rain.
The girls from earlier!
Congratulations!
You both pass!
Huh?
Katana Maidens
That was a huge success!
Episode 5  A Night of Mountain Hunting
Damn it! It got all wet!
Stop messing around!
Hiyori-chan?!
If you insist on getting in our way,
then I'll really have to get serious!
It's fine. You don't need to be in such
a hurry. Irozaki isn't going anywhere.
How did you know that's where we're going?
Before I tell you...
We have to clean up first.
We can't just leave our trash
on the mountain. No way.
Now then, how much did we talk about?
You haven't told us anything yet.
Um, you're Ellen-san and Kaoru-chan, right?
What did you mean by saying we passed?
Wait, I'm the same age as Ellen.
And I'd like to be called Ellen-chan!
Okay! Ellen-chan, Kaoru-chan!
Damn it. It's been settled already.
We mean that you passed in the literal sense.
You both passed the Mokusa test.
Mokusa?
You mean Mokusa, as in the place that is said
to be the origin of the Japanese sword?
It's a pretty nice name
for an organization that
opposes the revisionists led by Origami Yukari
and aims to restore okatana and Toji
to how they should be, right?
An organization that opposes
the Origami family?
Then you're on the same side as Hiyori-chan?
Yes, our objectives are the same.
Wow! Isn't that great, Hiyori-chan?
Mokusa, huh?
Are you familiar with the name "FineMan"?
That avatar just doesn't work,
and I'm always telling them to change it.
I see.
So you are the ones who will decide
whether or not we can join Mokusa.
And we're supposed to trust people
who test others like this?
Well, now that you mention it,
that's a tough one, isn't it?
If you got a problem with it, take it
up with the old la—the higher-ups.
That's not all.
A Toji using an aradama? That means
you're no different than Origami Yukari!
No, Nene is my pet.
Nonsense!
But Hiyori-chan, it's so cute.
That's not the point!
Kanamin, Hiyoyon, do you know the history
of Kaoru's okatana, Nenekirimaru?
H-Hiyoyon?!
The history?
Long ago,
there's a tale about a youkai
known as Nene that was rampaging
near Futarasan Shrine in Tochigi,
and an okatana came to life to punish it.
That is how this okatana came
to be called Nenekirimaru,
but for some reason,
it didn't destroy the youkai.
Then that means...
Nene is certainly an aradama.
But at the same time, it is the
guardian beast of the Mashiko family,
through which Nenekirimaru
has always been passed down.
An aradama that protects humans?
I don't recall it ever protecting me.
There's still quite a lot about aradama and
the netherworld that we don't understand,
and in order to try and understand a bit more
Nene has been deemed a special
case by those in charge.
What a ridiculous story!
Also, here, please look at this.
There's no reaction on the spectrum meter?
Neither on mine?
So do you understand now
that Nene isn't a problem?
That tickles!
See, Hiyori-chan? It's a nice little thing.
Wh-What's wrong?
That's right, Nene loves
girls with big busts.
And it can tell if a girl's breasts are
going to grow bigger in the future.
Come on, that's so mean to Hiyori-chan!
What's wrong, Nene?
Aradama! We're surrounded!
Wait, Nene!
Kaoru, don't!
They're coming!
There're so many! Why are there so many?!
I don't know! They're small ones,
but we can't let our guard—
We'll have to continue this conversation
when we get out of here!
Got it!
I've become completely
separated from everyone.
But what is going on with these aradama?
Their movements are strangely controlled.
No reaction on the
spectrum finder, either.
This is the latest version provided
by the Origami family, though.
There's definitely something
sinister going on.
Now then, meeting up with Kaoru
and the others is important,
but on the other hand, I feel like
we need something more definitive.
Let's go with this!
They're not coming after us. What's going on?
I'm not sure, but it's like
we were being chased here.
By the aradama? Can't be.
I wonder if Ellen-chan and
Kaoru-chan are all right?
This might be their doing, too.
So you really don't trust them?
Figures. Then why not just
use them to your advantage?
You should, if they're
important for your objective.
That's why you brought me along
with you to begin with, wasn't it?
She pretends to be clueless, but...
I can't keep my guard down around her.
But now you trust me a bit more, right?
What?
That's why I know you'll come to
trust Ellen-chan and Kaoru-chan, too!
H-Huh? Or do you still not trust me?
Well, who knows?
What? Hiyori-chan!
Yomi is amazing. She did a good job.
Yes, thanks to her, we will be able to
capture the traitors without any trouble.
You are...
...from the elite guard!
Your childishness has gotten
a bit out of hand, kouhai.
We will not go easy on
you like your friend did.
Wait! Please listen to what
Hiyori-chan has to say!
The head of the Origami family is—
First member of the elite guard, Shidou Maki.
Second member of the elite guard,
Konohana Suzuka.
Here we go!
What a pain you are.
You're always giving me trouble.
Have you forgotten about how you used
to run off like this and get lost?
No other choice.
Damn it! Such a pain!
So annoying!
It's a bit easier to see—
They just keep coming.
Damn—?!
Nene!
I have to replenish them.
Be on your way.
For her sake.
They've found the traitors?
Are you sure?
Yes, Satsuki has already trapped both of them.
Shidou and Konohana are
currently engaging them.
Yomi...
That half-wit, who can't
even use an okatana...
We have to hurry and complete that project.
The strongest Toji, who will
live and die for Yukari-sama...
Excuse me, Itomi Sayaka-chan?
Do you have a moment?
So Kanami-chan is safe? What a relief!
Oh, I'm sorry.
I really shouldn't be saying that to you.
No matter. The truth is that I lost.
You're from Renpu, right, Sayaka-chan?
Aren't you going to go back to your room?
I received orders not to leave this room.
Huh? From President Takatsu?
Um...
Huh?
Your cheek is wounded.
Excuse me for a moment.
That should help.
I'm sorry that it's such a childish design.
My younger sister loves these things.
It's fine. Don't worry about it.
Oh, that's right. I hope you'll like this.
Hold out your hand.
Here.
Cookies.
I was trying to calm my
nerves and made too many.
Do you like sweets, Sayaka-chan?
Yeah.
Good! Then it would make
me happy if you'd eat them.
Happy?
Well, if they find me here,
I'll get in trouble, so I better go.
Oh, right, challenge Kanami to a bout again.
There's no need to hold back.
Enter.
Yukari-sama!
Let's play!
Got you!
Dang it, I lost again!
Are you that bored?
Yeah, and if you'd let me leave, I'd take
care of things faster than those weaklings.
Be patient for now.
I'll prepare an entertaining
game for you soon.
Really?! Then I'll wait like a good girl!
Damn it, what have I done?
Nene...
Stop following me, aradama!
Toji destroy aradama.
I found an aradama!
Grandpa! Mommy!
Grandma! Daddy!
Nene?
That's right.
You've always been there.
But this time...
Hold on tight.
Honestly, I only got involved with Mokusa
because I was going along with Ellen,
but now I'm going to get serious.
I've already seen through that!
Hiyori-chan!
You think you can afford to look away?
She activated her jin'i to match with mine?!
It's as if...
Your expression says, "It's as if she
knows when to activate her jin'i."
She's definitely powerful!
Again?
How many more times can you do it?
Or is this the last time?
I'm not finished yet!
That's a crow a for you, always evading.
This swordsmanship... So this is Shidou Maki.
This is it.
Hiyori-chan!
I am your opponent!
Are you underestimating me,
Konohana Suzuka, of the elite guard?
What? She's worrying about me right now?
She should worry about herself instead!
No, is she really just worried?
That can't be it!
She's always calmly observing the
situation and conditions on the spot,
and looking for a way to break through!
Lost in thought right in front of me?
Aren't you feeling confident.
Look at me!
Think! Think!
So that's it!
You trust me, right?
Yes!
Foolishly attacking head-on?
That's fine. I'll end it now.
Knock it off already!
Hiyori-chan!
What?!
You're wide open.
Maki-san!
Hiyori-chan, run!
Got it!
They got us good.
...was cut...
Maki-san?
I was cut down?
I... I...
Me... The one who's supposed
to be Yukari-sama's blade?!
Understood, Konohana-san.
Yes, I will release the reinforcements soon.
That's impressive.
Aradama created by a human? No, born from one.
You're a member of the
elite guard, aren't you?
The Origami family really has awful taste.
I am the third member of the
elite guard, Satsuki Yomi.
I see. You're from Mokusa, aren't you?
Who cares?
However, your pets did a number on my pet.
I'm simply here to return the favor.
Is that so?
By all means, then.
I simply destroy.
So obnoxious!
I'll destroy you all in
a second! No, an instant!
It won't be so easy with the other three.
Like I care?
I'm tired.
I'll look for Ellen... after a nap...
You there, stay where you are!
I'm no one suspicious.
I'm just a Toji who
happened to be passing by.
Next Episode  The Space Between Humans and Disgrace