It seems the Central Nations have made their move.
We believe they're planning a Third Crusade
in order to revive the church's dwindling influence.
The White Night King, the one man the Centrals could influence,
was essentially dethroned after his disastrous loss.
Then the heroic Winter King appeared
and captivated the people's hearts,
just in time for them to feel the effects of the food surplus they really owed to the Crimson Scholar.
With their guard dog off its chain, the church must be panicking.
What do we do?
If we're going to do anything as the Alliance,
we must first form a new Council of Ten.
Which means...
I'm coming in.
A diplomat from the Ice Country is here.
Maoyuu
the hero and the demon king
I want to be annoying for you
I don't mind being conceited
Hide a tree in a forest, they say
It started with a little mistake
Let's redo our meeting from there
Let's oppose the strand of time
Strength alone is no weapon
You taught me that just now
I want to show you what lies
beyond these days
The wind is strong
I'm sure you know that too
I can't fly
Sharing makes you dependant
Now, take my hand
Hold it tight
Now...
Chapter 9
I Am Human
Would you be willing to help us?
Me?
You hail from the Bard Country,
where dance and flowery words rule all, which is exactly what we need.
What would you have me do?
I want you to stop whatever the current Council of Ten is doing
and gather some information for me.
If you need help, just ask him.
Hey, wait. Why me?
So basically,
you're attempting to buy time?
Yes.
I require not victory, but time.
Does the same not go for your teacher, the Crimson Scholar?
I accept.
My only skills are dancing and spreading rumors, though.
Well, the place we're headed is a battlefield all its own.
Yes, I know.
But I can definitely say
that nothing will get the better of me there.
You're lying!
The Crimson Scholar can't be a heretic!
It's pretty crazy down there.
Some of them are saying she's a goddess.
The peasants all love her.
You can say that again.
Whenever my sister and I walk down the road,
everyone smiles and waves...
"Look at all the potatoes we harvested this spring."
"This fall, we're raising plenty of wheat."
They offer us berries
or give us eggs to take back.
Or even quails.
There was never a day when our table was without some gift from them.
They were all wonderful people, and they loved us.
"Take good care of the Scholar," they would say.
"She's done so much for us,
but we can't do anything for her."
I see.
Sometimes, they'd bring a baby
and have me touch its tiny little hand.
"So that she may grow to be smart and kind like you."
I was a mere serf.
But they called me important because I served the Scholar.
It's a nice place.
Everyone's doing what they can to help each other.
It's sad to say goodbye.
We should get going.
I should get going, too.
As the leader of the Lakeside Convent,
having to listen to some silver-tongued messenger's lecture annoys me.
Don't be afraid.
You don't need to worry about anything.
The Hero will save you.
Yeah...
We'll see each other again.
I'm off, too.
I'll keep an eye on the surrounding area.
Okay.
Um... I...
Nothing.
Okay.
Just wait and have faith.
Right.
Why...
Why am I...
so powerless?
I can't do anything...
There are so many of them.
Yes...
The peasants of the surrounding villages have come in force.
I hope nothing will happen.
The Messenger will be here soon.
I'll post more guards.
Look at that!
The King!
No,
our King couldn't be so pale and seedy.
Then that's the Messenger?
He works for whoever is calling the Scholar a heretic?
The King...
The King is here!
Everyone!
Thank you for coming.
You've brought her as promised, yes?
Of course.
We'll turn her over to you.
The Scholar...
It really is the Scholar!
Surely, this is her.
You won't be able to fool us with a double.
That would be inconceivable.
It seems this is her, indeed.
Arrest her!
The church thanks you for your cooperation.
I'm sure you must be pleased that we have found
no connection between you and the heretic.
Indeed.
People of the Winter Country!
Take a good look!
She is a servant of the demons!
Align yourselves with her, and her fate awaits you.
We'll take her to the Capital.
Yes.
Scholar...
Scholar, you couldn't be a heretic, right?
Look at all that blood...
She'll die!
Why are they hitting my sister?
On your hands and knees!
Please control yourself, sir.
Innocent girl, I am sorry.
Someday, the world will have to atone for what it's done to you.
Look at the disobedience in her eyes.
They're the eyes of a heretic.
Does the servant of the demons who dares disobey
the Holy Light's teachings have something to say?
I...
As someone who has a soul not unlike you,
I have something I must tell you.
I was...
I was born a serf.
I was the third of seven siblings.
My brother broke his arm in the fields,
and he was left to die.
One night, the land owner summoned my sister,
and she never returned.
On a clear winter morning,
my youngest brother went cold and failed to wake from his slumber.
Another sibling caught smallpox.
I was powerless.
Only my sister and I survived.
And then, while we were on the run, we were given a chance.
It always seemed like fate,
but something troubled me...
For so long...
Fate had been warm and kind to me.
"Don't worry. I'll take care of it."
But everyone...
Nobles!
Soldiers!
Pioneers!
And serfs!
I must reject it,
even after all it's done for me.
I must reject it because of all it's done for me.
Because I am human!
I still doubt myself.
"The blood in your veins is that of a filthy serf."
"You're just an insect, less than human."
That is why
I must declare
that I am human.
Because I believe the first step to being human is to say you are.
Have you ever felt a warmth in your heart?
Like the summer sun on your cheeks
when you close your eyes, can't you still feel its blessings?
Do you ever find happiness in simple acts of kindness?
That is the proof that you are human,
the Holy Light's beloved children!
Enough!
H-Heretic!
It doesn't matter whether I'm a heretic.
As a human...
As one to whom Winter's Passage Village has given so much...
I speak to my brethren.
Everyone, you must never stop wishing, hoping, thinking, and working!
With her miracles, the Holy Light brought life to humanity.
And with the earth's blessings, she brought us wealth.
And with her soul's fragments, she brought us freedom!
Freedom?
That's right.
The freedom to do better than you do now.
To be better than you are now.
The Light did not create us to be perfect.
She gave us the freedom to keep bettering ourselves, every day.
Because that brings us joy...
So don't relinquish that, just to make your lives easier.
The Light's gifts are holy treasures!
Not even the King
or the church,
can take them from you!
Heretic,
hold your tongue!
I will not!
I am human.
I will never surrender those treasures again!
I won't return to being an insect!
No matter how much pain they bring,
I won't return to that haze of darkness...
Because there is light!
Because they were kind to me.
S-Stone this heretic whore!
What are you doing?
Anyone who refuses to stone her is an enemy of the church!
Throw them if you wish!
Perhaps you must,
to protect yourself and your family in this cruel world.
I will not blame you for that.
The freedom to choose also belongs to you, as a human.
I will shed blood in equal measure to that which is flowing in your heart!
But if you would stone me because someone else has ordered it,
then you are an insect!
You are an insect
without a will of your own, for you have given the Light's precious gifts to another,
and you have ceased to think!
No matter how much peace that brings you,
anyone who abandons those treasures is no better than an insect.
I despise insects.
I refuse to become one.
I...
I am human!
S-Stop it!
Throw the rocks at the filthy whore!
Stop this,
you disgusting, brainless serfs and peasants.
You're all enemies of the church!
What are you doing, Winter King?
Arrest them all!
Guards,
her heresy is clear.
Cut off her head at once!
No!
I'm sorry, Hero.
You asked me to leave it in your hands, but I just couldn't.
Head Maid...
I never got the chance...
But may I call you "teacher"?
Kill her!
There is no need.
Can you stand?
What are you doing?
I am the king of this nation!
Until now, I've been under the yoke of the Central Nations.
I thought I knew the pain, suffering, and disgust of that fact.
But it seems that, at heart, I had become an insect.
To be shown this by such a young girl...
I am ashamed of myself.
I had no idea such pride dwelt in the hearts of my people.
King...
You...
Messenger!
As a servant of the Holy Light, your actions shame me.
As do the actions of the church.
"You must master your sinful nature,"
said the Holy Light.
The freedom to sin
is another gift we've been given.
D-Do you know what you're saying?
I declare, here and now, that my country extends
its protection to the Crimson Scholar!
The Lakeside Convent
hereby recognizes her as a saint!
The King protected the Scholar!
She wasn't a heretic, after all!
The nun said she's a saint!
Our Scholar is a saint!
Get lost!
Go back to your own country!
Leave, Messenger.
I'm sure this is all part of your plan,
but we will meet again under different circumstances.
For now, leave.
I'll get you back for this, you nation of blasphemers.
After you've disobeyed the Holy Light's children,
don't you dare think this will all go away!
Honestly...
Why has my sealed eye gazed upon this girl?
I am the one who shall rule all the world eventually...
What is it trying to tell me?
I told you to wait.
I'm sorry.
That was really amazing, though.
Words alone can make an entire army withdraw.
The light is far
The night is foggy, and the darkness
holds me captive
All I can sense
are unreal flower petals in the fog
Slowly we are drawn apart
The door of the sky is a solid color
My heart feels the thunder above
It echoes the thunder
into the distance
The light is dim
Before this hour, many lights have vanished.
On this little big planet...
Each time a light disappears, pain shoots through my body.
The blinking lights are birth and death.
Just as he and I had hoped, the world may be saved.
However,
I'm sorry...
I'm so sorry.
I am the one who tore the world asunder.
This sin cannot be forgiven.
The warmth of fingers combing black hair...
A long, long time ago...
The words and caresses we shared,
wind from the sky on our cheeks.
When we meet again, what should I say to you?
What do I want you to say to me?
I can say but one thing now...
"Salvation to all people,
and eternal peace to all the world.
And if I could, I'd like to see you again."
Next Chapter
There's More to This Story
Than Useless Flesh!