Three-point increase!
Buy
everything you can.
We've found a ship carrying copper.
Acquire it. Pay double if you must.
Emergency.
The church is backing the Holy Capital's effort to issue new currency.
The exchange rate?
Twenty-eight old-currency gold will get ten of the new.
The possession or use of old currency will be forbidden.
I've also heard that
they plan to issue more of the new currency than required by the exchange rate.
What does this mean?
Basically,
they're replacing 10,000 in old currency with 5,000 of the new,
and then claiming the new amount is worth 14,000 in old currency.
Wouldn't that mean
the government makes a 4,000-gold profit, as measured by the old standard?
It does indeed.
It's quite clever, isn't it?
However,
I wonder if they'll be able to maintain the new currency's value at 2.8?
All the soldiers and knights in our territory,
654 in total, have gathered.
The Ashen King brings his royal knights and axe brigades.
The Mountain Country's heavy cavalry
and the Treetop Country's archers will also arrive soon.
What of enemy movement?
Holding position in the forest, at only several hundred.
It appears that they're slow to gather.
Maybe they're afraid of us?
How many have you brought?
Four hundred veterans.
You'll be paying us well for this.
My lord, dinner is prepared.
The local landowners have donated barrels of strong drinks.
Twenty barrels of high-quality iced wine.
So that is how they hope to keep us from trampling their fields?
I'll give some to the mercenaries as well.
It's one of the lady's students!
It's been a while.
Have you been well?
What I learned from our teacher's lessons has kept me going.
But why are you here?
We're compiling a book of new teachings.
The Crimson Scholar's alive?
Our spies report that
she's making many blasphemous books in the Iron Country.
Impossible!
The Inquisition has judged her to be a demon! A blasphemer!
The serfs have been crossing the border into the Iron Country.
At this rate, my country...
The White Night Country will be destroyed!
Then steal them.
A surprise attack...
They'll be focused on the punitive force.
In the meantime, we'll ambush the Iron Country and destroy it.
I'll share the darkness in my right eye with the entire country!
Maoyuu
the hero and the demon king
I want to be annoying for you
I don't mind being conceited
Hide a tree in a forest, they say
It started with a little mistake
Let's redo our meeting from there
Let's oppose the strand of time
Strength alone is no weapon
You taught me that just now
I want to show you what lies
beyond these days
The wind is strong
I'm sure you know that too
I can't fly
Sharing makes you dependant
Now, take my hand
Hold it tight
Now...
Chapter 11
I just destroy and kill,
without creating anything.
Then we'll maintain a strong defensive formation and wait for snow to fall.
I'll have the winter gear handed out at once.
Could I ask you to minimize the casualties?
The army of the Central Nations
will be at least 20,000 strong.
We'll be fortunate to field even 4,500.
It'll depend on their actions.
Leave it to me.
I'll ensure as few casualties as I can.
Message from the southern ice seas!
Demons!
Numbers?
We're not sure,
but based on what we can see, at least 1,500!
Why now?!
Hero...
Has something happened to the Demon King?
No, not to her.
I'm sorry, Hero.
We have no troops to spare.
Don't worry.
I'll take care of it myself.
But would you be upset if I said I don't want to fight the demons either?
Th-Then...
We must avoid a fight on two fronts at all costs.
My king...
Thank you, Winter King.
Are you the Financial Minister?
Yes, though only just appointed.
I'm sorry to visit so suddenly.
Not at all.
I've been waiting for you.
You're the one who's been playing a game across the whole continent,
aren't you?
What makes you say that?
If I were the one playing, I'd visit in person.
You were the one who established that tariff, right?
Yes.
I like you!
Well, let's negotiate.
I have four things to discuss.
I'll summarize.
First, I'd like you to give the Alliance
an exclusive exemption from the tariff.
An exemption?
The exemption would only apply to goods passing through your realm,
not to any that are purchased within.
That would prevent the exemption from affecting your economy, correct?
That's true.
Second, lease rights for Bright Light Island.
I'd like to lease part of the island in the same way a lord is granted a manor.
In this matter, I represent another party.
Who would want that place?
The only thing there is salt—
Third,
are you familiar with the banking organizations within the Alliance?
I'd like permission to establish banks and other Alliance facilities
within your three nations' capitals.
That would be wonderful, but well...
Fourth, we're prepared to purchase
your entire potato stores.
That is all.
Um, the Inquisition has banned potatoes.
The Central Nations have reissued the currency to try to raise its value.
But that's not going to work.
The value of food products, such as wheat, is far more stable...
And the Alliance is the group with the most wheat.
If it's the army's job to end a war,
it's the king's job to find a place for it to end.
Sorry, but I'm a Hero, not a king.
So I couldn't find the place for it to end.
If you'll accompany me to the other side of the hill, that's enough for me.
I definitely want to see it too!
You and me, the Knight and the Old Man,
the King, the Maid Sisters, and the Head Maid.
Mage, Gate City, the Southern Nations,
and everyone in Winter's Pass Village...
I want the Central Nations and the demons to see it as well!
Because I...
I just destroy and kill, without creating anything.
Azure Demons?
They're equipped for long-distance travel.
And they have provisions.
If I'm going to make them withdraw, that's where I should aim.
Okay!
You included me.
Good.
I'm finally out.
I'm so hungry
and tired.
That was terrible.
What's wrong,
Head Maid?
It's okay now.
Let's return.
To where?
The battlefield.
What are you doing, insect?
I'm no insect!
Oh, but you are an insect.
You'll see when you're flat on the ground.
Her Majesty would never have such a crude laugh.
This is how I'll be from now on.
Her Majesty
is brilliant, an intellectual,
logical, calm, cynical,
pragmatic, but still has a cute smile!
That's my master!
She's lazy, and she hates to change or wash her clothes.
She can't clean or cook, but...
But she is the one I chose!
She is my destiny!
Impressive.
My strength is far greater than the Fanged Beasts, yet you match me.
But you are still a mere demon.
I went easy on you in hopes that you might serve me.
I am a maid!
Die!
Where have you been?
Communication channel established.
I never get used to this.
Go.
The Demon King is waiting.
You know her?
I'll act in your stead.
Once I've dealt with them,
you must destroy the gate with the strongest spell.
If I do that, no one will be able to go to the Demon Realm!
That's okay.
It's all right to destroy it?
...needs you.
She needs you.
You aren't interested in the wheat as a trade good!
But as a pseudo-currency!
Yes.
And you plan to invest that wheat in the Southern Triads.
Indeed, I am.
A-And you're after...
What?
The continent functions as one international market due to its unified currency.
So when inflation begins,
throwing around additional coinage in one nation accomplishes nothing.
Also, if you want increased competitiveness with the surrounding regions,
it's best to have more than one currency.
A dual-currency system...
That's correct.
True, with the Central Nations' economy weakened, now is the perfect time...
Which naturally means our next step
will be to invest in an emerging market with growth potential.
Are you
intending to go beyond our territorial waters and open trade relations with demons?
Yes.
Why would you...
Because I'm a merchant.
Everyone has an opinion as to what's right or wrong.
We will never see eye-to-eye on that,
but everyone wants to be a little happier than they currently are.
So isn't our job to compromise on that one point,
and then to trade?
B-But...
I ask that you consider this as well.
H-Horns?
She's the Dragon Princess.
A representative of Gate City, the one place in the Demon Realm
where humans and demons coexist.
Total number of demons: 2,670.
Initiating range-finding.
Locking on target.
Spell-decompression algorithm in progress.
15% complete.
37%.
59%.
81%.
Designate current area as target.
Removing conflicts.
The Hero...
To save the Hero!
I've had to use Time Stretch and multiple compressions
to save up all these spells!
Do you know what that took? How many years?
She's losing her cool again.
When something happens to the Hero,
my job is to go him and grant his wish!
Is she seriously teleporting each of them?
Do you understand what it did to my pride,
that twilight day when I could do nothing?
Can you understand?!
Complete.
Go.
R-Right!
Maziodyne!
Mass destruction confirmed.
Maybe I overdid it a little.
Use your magic to fly into the pillar of smoke.
Damn White Night! Only barbarians would consider a surprise attack!
Even if they outnumber us,
we must destroy them all!
You mustn't be impatient.
We're facing their cavalry.
The only countermeasure for their mobility
is to isolate them and work together.
Enemy approaching!
They'll arrive in a minute or so!
All forces!
Ready crossbows!
Primary targets are stationary or any dismounted soldiers!
The enemy is comprised of light cavalry, which emphasizes speed!
They lack the plate mail to stop our crossbows!
Don't force any risky shots! Aim for the center of the horse!
What?
What's happening?
Why are you stopping?
Enemy trap!
Use your speed to push through!
All troops, advance!
The enemy numbers few!
Crush them!
What are you doing?
Use your mobility!
Push forward and spread the rear lines to the left and right!
Keep firing!
New conscripts are to divide themselves between weapon loading and defense.
Defense squads are to eliminate any troops
that make it into our trenches, move any horses, and keep them out!
Archers and loaders, concentrate all fire on the right flank!
Our side attack is working.
The right flank is weakening!
Good! Send all our forces in!
Yes, sir!
The enemy is heading for the left flank!
Then the right flank drove them off.
Our defenses are on a sloping hill.
Any cavalry that makes it past the front lines won't break through,
but they'll be drawn into a small, cramped area.
Now it's time for us to do our jobs, Lieutenant.
Everyone,
check your bows once more!
It's time for our assault!
It's getting brighter?
What's this wind?
Where am I?
The Demon Realm?
That's correct.
The Demon Realm is underground?
Yes, it's not a separate world.
It's connected to the Human World.
What's happening with her?
She's nearly become the King of Evil.
The King of Evil?
But the Demon King is waiting for you.
What are you talking about?!
She's waiting for you, you damn virgin!
Move your ass!
She's at the center of the Demon King's castle, at the lowest level...
Your Majesty,
just try once more.
Remember how black,
fluffy,
and warm it looked?
You bitch!
Trying to buy time is useless!
If she comes out again, I'm going to die...
This body is mine!
I am the Demon King!
But even so, I...
I'll go straight there.
Accelerate!
I've never seen magic particles like these.
Is the Demon King really this strong?
The Central Nations' army has begun a full conference.
They have 40,000 all together.
Of those, 28,000 are soldiers.
9,000 are cavalry.
So what did we send them today?
Thirty barrels of iced wine, three boars, six pigs.
Good.
They'll hold another banquet tonight.
Next we'll need horse fodder.
Fodder?
Yes.
With that many horses, they'll require a great deal.
This time, inform more farmers.
The army's here, and if you have no fodder for them,
they could hurt you.
And sell them the dried grass and oats we prepared.
Giving it to them is fine.
What's the point of that?
The grass and oats
have been soaked with filthy water.
Just enough to gradually sicken the horses.
Ah...
I get it.
That'll make it harder to start a conflict.
I feel bad for the horses,
but I'm sure they'd prefer that
to death on the battlefield.
The Iron-Arm King has
instructed us to treat the wounded!
Don't help our side alone.
Start with the worst off
and use a handkerchief, so the doctors know the priorities!
Move any lightly wounded to the outside tents!
Have the citizens help them.
Move the moderately wounded within the Convent,
treat their wounds, and use distilled alcohol for disinfection!
You're a general now.
A g-general?
In this country,
that's the term for soldiers who perform above the call of duty.
I wasn't even thinking.
I was only doing as I was taught.
Reporting.
Our forces sustained 18 fatalities,
and 221 are wounded.
The White Night suffered 304 fatalities
with 892 injured.
450 prisoners.
In addition,
several enemy troops escaped into the city,
and we are in pursuit.
The one-eyed man we believe to be their commander is among them.
Give anyone who can still move a meal,
let them rest, then send them on patrol.
Yes, sir.
I'll keep watch on the city.
Out of my way!
Demon King!
Hero!
Demon King...
Be careful, Hero!
That isn't really her.
The evil spirits of the ancient Demon Kings have corrupted her.
Next Chapter:
—I'm back, Hero. —You sleep too much, Demon King.