The wind marking the end of summer is a little sad.
But I still like it because it carries the scent of the harvest season.
Today, the mistress is again spending
the day with the Hero, and she's very happy.
With the Head Maid away, I'm glad she hasn't encountered any problems.
The Knight didn't have any training scheduled, but she came anyway.
Today's excuse was having caught a boar.
The atmosphere in this country has really changed.
Ever since the young Winter King assumed the throne,
many refugees and freed serfs
have volunteered for the army.
The King is trying to root out the corruption that was rampant till now
and to develop the economy in the right direction.
Mistress got the Merchant Student a job at the palace.
I wonder if he's working hard.
There are more smiles in Winter's Pass Village.
I like this...
But...
I...
Maoyuu
the hero and the demon king
I want to be annoying for you
I don't mind being conceited
Hide a tree in a forest, they say
It started with a little mistake
Let's redo our meeting from there
Let's oppose the strand of time
Strength alone is no weapon
You taught me that just now
I want to show you what lies
beyond these days
The wind is strong
I'm sure you know that too
I can't fly
Sharing makes you dependant
Now, take my hand
Hold it tight
Now...
Chapter 7
I'll Be Back Soon
We'll See Each Other Soon
That's not fair.
In a fight, there's no such thing as "fair"!
Come on. Swing and slide!
Don't treat me like a kid.
You've improved.
That's because I don't have to hold back while fighting you.
Once more...
Okay!
This pump thing's great.
It really is.
The Demon King's inventions are great.
This is wonderful...
Once more.
Got it!
Hey, I'm still hot and sweaty.
Jerk.
This is great...
Hey, one more...
What's wrong?
Why are you just wearing a towel?
Because I was pouring water on myself.
Y-Yeah, but...
What're you doing?
Soap from the priory.
If we don't wash you, you'll look like a big dog.
This country's wonderful at the end of summer.
Yeah,
the chestnuts'll be ripe soon.
I wish it could be this way forever.
Yeah.
Alas, it can't.
We should settle who's the wife and who's the mistress.
The demons will take some kind of action soon.
That's right!
The war's currently at a stalemate.
But there's no guarantee it'll stay that way.
But...
She told me that
with extraordinary power,
we could end this war.
But we can't extinguish the sparks of conflict.
And whether humans or demons win,
the losers are in for hell.
Just because the war ends
doesn't mean there'll peace.
However,
she's trying to save both humans and demons.
That's...
That's why you...
Yep, that's why I think she's amazing.
I can't compete with that.
Huh?
You're amazing too.
Me?
You once practiced cutting a feral pig demon butt into three-centimeter slices and said,
"We need to improve the quality of life for the peasants!"
I didn't really plan that.
Does it matter? It still worked out.
All I can do is fight,
so I envy the two of you.
What's gotten into you?
This is great, great, great!
Orange water is super amazing!
What's this?
It's cold.
I cooled it down with well water...
I figured out how to do it!
And the drink she made is like magic.
Try it.
I told her about the carbonated spring,
and she came up with this.
She could grow up to be a great cook.
Hooray!
She's cheered up a lot.
When we first met, she hid behind her sister's skirts.
Everyone's truly amazing.
More importantly...
Your hair's a mess...
It doesn't matter.
It does matter.
Consider your position.
Don't you have a meeting
with Gate City's council tomorrow?
Oh, that's right.
I'll be attending as the Dark Knight, representative of the Demon King.
When you're finished, be sure to come straight back.
Don't let the Dragon Archduke catch you.
Lately, he's been helpful.
In particular, his daughter, the Dragon Princess,
has been a council member representing the local demons.
That's the heart of the problem...
Never mind.
You come straight back once the meeting's over.
Okay, okay.
Oh no!
They said there's a festival on the main street.
A festival?
The Eastern Fortress General suggested it.
They bring rare and inexpensive foods and hang up pretty lights.
And they're having a band too.
An attempt to bring demons and humans together?
Yeah.
The human merchants and the demons are still on edge.
We're just lucky the Eastern General enjoys having a good reputation.
You ran from battle like a coward,
abandoned Gate City—which was won at the cost of many lives,
and betrayed the hopes of all 95 million of the Holy Light's disciples.
This is the greatest sin imaginable.
I fought to the end!
Th-That's right.
I fought and fought.
It was a fight to the death!
What's so funny?
Over 8,000 of the 9,000 troops stationed there
headed to Bright Light Island to keep fighting.
What kind of fight to the death leaves so many unharmed?
But it was my reinforcements that won the battle at Bright Light Island.
Your army appeared at the last second,
lost many forces, and allowed the demons to retreat.
That was... No!
I was tricked.
The Eastern Fortress General was in league with the demons...
Now you are nothing but a sick dog.
Your sin merits the death penalty!
W-Wait...
Just give...
Just give me a little time!
I'll take ale... Two mugs.
Eastern Fortress General!
It's ice-cold.
This is great.
You bite into the burnt part, and it's soft inside.
And then wash it down with this cold ale.
Wonderful!
There you are!
U-Um, h-hello.
There she is.
What do you mean, "There she is"?
I'm the Dark Knight's wife!
No! No, no, no, no.
Why are you so cold?!
I could make a river with my tears.
I'm not your husband.
No one even asked me.
You act so embarrassed.
You're so cute...
Your Majesty!
That's the second this month.
The interval between them is decreasing.
We may need to move things up sooner than expected.
We knew this would happen eventually.
I'm honestly surprised we lasted two years.
Yes.
Have my bed sent to the Underworld Palace.
Understood.
Don't make that face.
I'll be back soon.
We'll see each other soon.
The air here's humid...
You okay?
My head's pounding...
Take a deep breath.
That's the Iron Country?
It's huge.
One of the workshops there
has completed the prototype I requested.
But why are we bringing her?
Recently, I've been teaching her my work.
She's better than a noble or a general.
I think that education will prove
the most powerful force in this world.
The world's so large. No one knows how big it really is.
But everyone's quick to apply their own knowledge and experience
because they know everything.
I can understand that...
Education is so important
because you need education to know you need education.
I understand.
The serfs don't know much.
They don't realize there's a better world.
I didn't know how to get there.
No,
I didn't even know I could get there.
It takes a lot of time
for one person to share everything they've learned,
especially if they're trying to share it among many people.
Knowledge is a precious commodity.
I doubt there's any way to fix that.
And that's another limit you've imposed upon yourself.
Okay, bring your friends over here.
Is this it?
It's huge!
What is this?
It looks like a threshing machine...
There are a lot of those!
You put these inside.
Stamps?
Yes, they're called movable types.
This is our new weapon.
We call it the printing press.
You can make thousands of these in a single day.
Everyone really is amazing...
What are you doing here?
I could ask you the same thing!
What are you doing?! And with that pillow...
Well, I...
A midnight tea party!
Then I'm having one too!
Who holds a tea party in a man's room while wearing silk pajamas?
You idiot!
Better than the idiot who claims she's having a tea party while holding a pillow!
Let's stop this, Knight.
You're basically my only friend in the Human World.
You're right, Demon King.
So please let me go.
No.
Please! I have my reasons!
So do I!
"Swearing my undying loyalty to my love."
The Dragon Princess sent this to the Hero.
He wasn't sure what to do, so he gave it to the Holy Light,
and I swiped it.
So as you see, I can't give up tonight.
That doesn't count!
And I only have a few more da—
Never mind.
Anyway, I can't give up either!
Then I shall go.
That'll prevent any friction, don't you agree?
I won't be long.
Hey, hey, hey...
This and that are different things!
As a knight, I also cannot allow that.
Then stop arguing. The two of you...
No, the three of you can have a good time.
Wh-What?
What are you doing?
Wh-What do we do?
I don't know!
Let's resolve this through negotiation.
How?
I'll take the bed, and you take the floor.
And Hero?
The bed, of course.
That's not even remotely fair!
I guess not.
Then how about sharing?
How?
We can take turns on the bed.
Okay?
You can have the Hero's bed during the day.
I'll take it at night.
That's even less fair!
Don't fall asleep, Hero!
You can't fall asleep!
This is your answer?
Yes.
Are you nervous?
Of course not. It's just a bed.
You're so warm...
And your hair is all fluffy.
It's more comfortable than I expected.
The Hero's hair is all fluffy.
He's like a big dog.
I'm the one who does his hair.
I've known him for longer, so I know all about him.
Embarrassing stuff, for example...
Like what?
I can't say in front of him!
I have embarrassing memories with him too.
Like what?
I can't say in front of him.
Then...
Tell me later!
Hey, Knight...
What?
I'm probably returning to the Demon Realm next week.
Basically, I need to renew my Demon King's license.
License?
That's something you need?
Yes.
If I'm lucky, it won't take more than a few months.
I must visit the graves of the previous Demon Kings.
And I need to bring the demons together,
or some tribes will lose control and possibly start their own war.
Most of the Demon Realm tribes want to invade this world.
Won't that be dangerous?
Shouldn't you bring someone?
Only I can enter the Demon Kings' grave.
And the Head Maid will accompany me.
I see.
And that's why...
I wanted to feel his warmth a little.
I'll leave notes about what needs doing here.
I've given the Older Sister Maid the details.
So...
Take care of the Hero.
Will do.
I swear by my sword, I shall see it done.
You really don't think I should go?
I hear the White Night Country is destabilizing.
I've heard that.
After Gate City, I know that you're more than a warrior.
At this point, you're like another me.
So I'm leaving you in charge here.
Got it.
What's this?
An earth fairy ring that can change your appearance.
There'll be times
when I'll be required to attend to trades and other things in person.
In those cases, you can use this ring to become me.
All right.
It's been a long time since I've been here.
Be careful.
Yeah, see you soon, my Hero.
Yeah, see you, my Demon King.
Let's see each other...
...soon.
What's this drink?!
You seem upset.
My eye aches...
Yes, I'm quite grateful
to you for using a double
to sneak me from that cell, where I awaited death.
Can you remember that darkness?
The rats...
The rats crawled all over me.
And took my eye...
I'll kill you, Eastern Fortress General.
Accursed demons!
That's right.
They've made a mockery of us.
Just like that child in the Winter Country!
Exactly!
I shall teach them true shame.
Those traitors...
I'll make them taste the hell of scorn and humiliation!
Winter King, your treasure, your kingdom...
I'll tear them apart!
The light is far
The night is foggy, and the darkness
holds me captive
All I can sense
are unreal flower petals in the fog
Slowly we are drawn apart
The door of the sky is a solid color
My heart feels the thunder above
It echoes the thunder
into the distance
The light is dim
Next Chapter
Take This Sword, My Lord