What's that?
That?
A fire arrow.
A fire arrow?
Yes, it burns as it flies.
The fire will spread on impact.
It uses naphtha, and it's effective for wide-area attacks.
What's wrong?
What is war?
Why does it happen?
Why does it not end?
That's a difficult question.
I wonder why...
Maoyuu
the hero and the demon king
I want to be annoying for you
I don't mind being conceited
Hide a tree in a forest, they say
It started with a little mistake
Let's redo our meeting from there
Let's oppose the strand of time
Strength alone is no weapon
You taught me that just now
I want to show you what lies
beyond these days
The wind is strong
I'm sure you know that too
I can't fly
Sharing makes you dependant
Now, take my hand
Hold it tight
Now...
Chapter 6
Welcome back,
Hero!
Yeah, Old Man...
I'm back!
War is a type of large-scale conflict.
And conflicts occur when two separate forces collide.
Still no movement, huh?
No,
nothing unusual.
Um...
We've been here for two weeks.
Has it been that long?
How long will we be staying?
We don't know either.
But I'd guess we're preparing a surprise attack.
A surprise attack?
Two children meet.
"That child isn't like me."
"I'm not like them."
Conflict always arises when you meet someone new or different.
But wars don't happen just because you meet someone.
You could resolve the conflict by greeting them, helping them, becoming friends, or playing...
True.
But that only means conflict is a part of those wonderful things.
At their core, they're all the same.
But...
Search your feelings. You know it to be true.
I don't want to believe that.
Neither do I.
War is one form of conflict, but not all conflict is war.
The village boys competing to give flowers
to a pretty girl are engaged in conflict.
And conflict is a type of relationship,
but not all relationships are conflicts.
There are friendly relationships and supportive relationships.
Then why is there war?
Escalation is necessary sometimes.
It sounds contradictory, but it seems possible to me.
Just as no one is born an adult.
Ma'aaam,
we're ready to gooo!
Don't extend your vowels.
That's right.
And don't run.
Where are you going, ma'am?
Here.
Is that where you'll meet the Hero?
Well, the Hero's, uh, how should I say...
I guess you could say he's beyond this point.
Again!
The Death Knight has been here, as well!
It's a curse!
Save us!
Who's there?
So this is humanity's strongest force, the Holy Crusade?
His head!
The Death Knight!
Save us!
Cowards.
The Dark Knight is the best!
They were just wimps.
That's pretty spooky, though.
Fairies create the best illusions!
Keep scaring the hell out of them with illusions.
Okay.
Nightmare Thrush, you here?
By your command.
Open a dream channel into the Crusade's HQ.
Haunt them with bad dreams nightly.
As you wish.
No movement yet, huh?
It gets exhausting.
For you too, General?
Don't call me "General."
It's only temporary.
Does it weigh on your nonexistent chest?
Wanna die?
No!
Damn it...
Stupid demons...
Commander!
What is it?
It's the Death Knight again!
Kill him!
Use the whole army if you have to.
But...
Our commanders, sir.
Spit it out!
Many of them fear the demons, so they're requesting to go home.
Persuade them with wine and money!
If that doesn't work, round up some demon girls!
But the slaves at HQ are already...
Steal as many as you want from town!
That's why I didn't want this job!
Why am I stuck in the middle of nowhere with these savage demons?
Pardon.
The Crimson Scholar has arrived.
She's here?
The brilliant scholar I hear so much about?
What's she doing at the battlefield?
You want to win, right?
That's why I'm here.
Hold it right there!
He sensed her demonic aura?
May I examine your lovely chest more closely?
A pleasure to meet you.
I'm the King of the Winter Country.
They call me the Crimson Scholar.
I'm sorry I haven't been able to thank you personally
for what you've done for my country.
It's nothing.
But I must ask,
why do you need to retake Bright Light Island now?
To restore our pride.
If we take back the island, several trade routes will open.
Then we'll no longer be slaves to the Central Nations' companies.
I'm glad to hear that.
Then my gift should be of use to you.
Okay.
Split into groups and pour seawater into the places where they meet.
Keep an eye on your surroundings,
and slingers, an eye on the sky!
After the seawater, the salt!
If you mean to win, I thought this might help.
I've prepared six carts of salt.
What?
That's three times the amount we secured.
What do you ask for in exchange?
Time.
A full day before we engage.
So you expect us to do nothing for a whole day?
I have a plan.
Victory isn't enough,
so I'll handle what can't be won through battle.
What?
The humans did what?
Fools.
They cannot beat us at sea.
Well...
They're fighting on land, not at sea!
Our first target is the coast!
Slingers, at the fore!
Keep an eye on the water and sky.
If you see any water demons, fall back while you attack
and await reinforcements!
Volunteer forces are to guard the sleds and our supplies.
Once we reach the coast and create a beachhead on Bright Light Island,
we can secure our supply lines.
Okay, we've landed!
Push them back!
Squad three, forward!
A giant squid has emerged from the sea to the right side of our rear!
If we can defend this place, reinforcements will arrive!
Stay strong!
For the kingdom!
For the Winter King!
Victory for our Princess General!
Behind our left flank!
A thousand beast-like demons!
Heavy infantry, group four!
Push them back! Don't let them advance!
Ready spears!
Charge!
Anyone!
Is anyone here?
Dispatch messengers every 20 minutes to keep lines of communication open.
Yes, ma'am.
We have our beachhead.
We've taken out the demons' second line of defenses.
How many casualties on our side?
Approximately 500.
What?
That's a huge success.
But that's as far as our luck goes.
The rest of the island is covered in natural caves.
And the castle at its center is an impenetrable fortress.
And inside is the Ice General, fiercest of the demons.
He'll try to make us lay siege.
How many forces do they have left?
Approximately 8,000.
I'm told it takes three times as many attackers
to force a siege's conclusion.
We have 12,000 soldiers.
Not even twice, let alone thrice.
Normally, this would be a long, drawn-out battle, but...
You have a plan?
What is it?
Reporting!
A huge army has appeared
farther to the south, beyond the island, near the Demon Realm.
What?
How many?
Over 9,000!
The demons sent reinforcements?
No.
This is going just as planned.
That force is comprised of Gate City's soldiers.
I didn't expect them to just up and leave.
I suppose with him as their leader, I can understand.
You're running, Commander?
Well, uh...
This is...
I know.
Reinforcements!
We'll send all our forces to reinforce Bright Light Island.
Are you insane?
This city has many civilians
who are here to help with our supplies!
What about them?
They're traitors.
They're befriending the demons!
Let them die.
You bastard.
You...
I what?
I know...
You're the commander now.
I'm putting you in charge.
If you want to protect them so much, then go ahead.
It's much quieter.
You're still here?
Well, I'm your aide.
What now?
We have no choice.
We must plead our case to the influential demons.
We don't have the troops, so we have no other choice.
We'll establish an emergency government.
As of today, this is no longer human territory,
but a city where demons and humans meet.
The demons are withdrawing from their fortress!
About 7,500 of them!
That's all of them.
The demons are charging the gate, which our reinforcements hold.
They didn't want us to reach them.
This is their last chance to break though.
If our reinforcements are the Crusade of the Holy Key,
they're the best the human world has to offer.
Who's there?
What's going on?
The strongest in the human world?
You're...
I dunno about that.
They weren't what I expected.
Hero!
Hero?
Hi.
Welcome back, Hero!
Hey, Knight, get off me!
Well...
Anyway, did this work?
I did everything I could to delay and lose them, so the timing would work.
They're pretty exhausted.
Then perhaps the battle will be even.
What?
A large demon heads this way.
He calls himself the Ice General!
He wiped out a whole platoon of light infantry!
Have everyone withdraw!
Yes, ma'am!
I had hoped to let the demons escape without sustaining heavy damage.
You can't...
He has faith in something.
I'll go kick him around a bit.
No.
That's my job.
A warrior's last request.
As general, I'd like to be the one to do it.
Retreat.
I shall be your opponent!
I'm glad you accepted my challenge.
I'd never pass on a fight I can win!
Taste my ultimate technique!
Too slow!
There was nothing "ultimate" about it!
Your last chance to retreat!
I won't accept the enemy's pity.
Take this! Freezing Blizzard!
Hero's Technique:
Rock Wall Reflector!
Not bad.
What can I say? I learned from the best.
But it's time to end this.
Finally something we can agree on.
What?
What splendid swordsmanship...
We won!
We won the battle!
It's too early to celebrate.
Clean up the remaining enemies.
Search the island!
It's over.
People of my kingdom, I am grateful for your efforts.
Bright Light Island is ours!
It will not be easy to defend,
and we'll have much to rebuild.
But as the Winter King, I swear to treat you well!
Tonight is a banquet.
Enjoy yourselves!
Cheers!
Now then...
Listen with a drink in hand.
I wish to offer honorary titles to the two who enabled this victory.
These two!
It's been a long time.
Oh, Old Man.
Please proceed to the hall.
My king would like to properly greet you.
It's fine.
I said hello already.
Hero...
You are too strong.
If you wished, you could fight an army of thousands.
Yeah.
That's why I couldn't abandon you.
No normal human could accept your strength.
Your strength isolates you from humanity.
You left so that we wouldn't have to bear that isolation, right?
But you're human, too.
And we also left you alone.
That's not true.
I'm sorry for making you feel alone.
Not at all.
You taught me all sorts of things.
Boobs, butts...
And how to tell breasts apart!
Fake boobs usually mean a burly guy!
Since we parted, I've been making some efforts of my own.
Can you hear that laughter?
You see the lights down there?
Yes.
It's a lovely country.
This country won't make you suffer your punishment alone.
I'm sure that you won't be isolated here.
Yeah.
Welcome back, Hero!
Yeah, Old Man.
I'm back!
The light is far
The night is foggy, and the darkness
holds me captive
All I can sense
are unreal flower petals in the fog
Slowly we are drawn apart
The door of the sky is a solid color
My heart feels the thunder above
It echoes the thunder
into the distance
The light is dim
Next Chapter
Other Soon
We'll See Each
I'll Be Back Soon,