A war is beginning.
The Holy Capital, with the church this time, has devised a plan to retake Bright Light Island.
The church is set on this.
Without the fight against the demons, their power as a unifying force wanes.
I'm sure the papal election also has an effect.
There'll be more naval skirmishes around Bright Light Island.
So we're making more compasses?
Warships, as well.
I've taken control of the Tin Country's naval yards.
If we gain control of Bright Light Island, we'll be able to open new trade routes to the west.
Transporting goods that way will be far cheaper than by land.
My jurisdiction, the Southern Nations, continues to see gains in productivity, and I don't want that to stop.
And I've also been asked to provide a large quantity of South Sea herring.
At least five times my current holdings.
Are they planning to build a palace of herring?
They have a magic spell that changes herring into wheat.
So it's that princess, then...
Yes, she's my shining star.
I thought money was the only thing you could ever love.
However, it'll be a serious problem if we don't succeed.
The war will still benefit us somewhat.
The war will last as long as the demons do.
And in the south, power changes hands rapidly.
All will depend on the war's outcome.
Maoyuu
the hero and the demon king
I want to be annoying for you
I don't mind being conceited
Hide a tree in a forest, they say
It started with a little mistake
Let's redo our meeting from there
Let's oppose the strand of time
Strength alone is no weapon
You taught me that just now
I want to show you what lies
beyond these days
The wind is strong
I'm sure you know that too
I can't fly
Sharing makes you dependant
Now, take my hand
Hold it tight
Now...
You Smell Good,
Demon King
And I Feel Safe
in Your Arms, Hero
Chapter 5
What are you doing, demon?
I'm sorry!
I'm sorry...
You're pretty cute.
Come. I'll give you a chance to make up for it!
Sir, please...
Shut up!
Who do you think keeps your town safe?
Stop it.
She wants you to release her.
Who are you?
The time has come!
It's been 15 years since the foolish demons first tried to steal our world of light!
A foolish commander's failed strategy cost us Bright Light Island.
A grave loss!
That's not true!
You dare to insult the Winter King?!
Listen to me, men...
Warships have rallied from across the world behind us.
Two hundred of them!
When you valiant warriors board them,
these two hundred ships will stab two hundred daggers into the demons' hearts!
With this simpleton commanding us, we'll end up losing a war we could easily win.
Now it's time to set sail.
The sun shines for our victory!
So the Crusade of the Holy Key's troops run Gate City?
Yes.
What of the forces outside?
Do they watch the surrounding area?
There are four armies...
They enter the town on a rotation.
What's the difference between the forces outside and those within?
When they return, they're rowdy,
and they do terrible things.
The soldiers in town are the more highly ranked ones.
Like the king's children or relatives.
So mostly nobles?
So they stay in the safety of the town while taking advantage of the demons.
Because we lost.
And that gives them power over you?
We can't do anything to stop them...
because we lost.
This...
This is what we won?
If the humans win, will the entire demon world end up this way?
And if the demons win, will the human world end up like this?
B-But...
The people in the Eastern Fortress don't really do anything bad.
So when the demons run, they always run east.
The Eastern Fortress?
That's good information.
Is it?
But it's not enough...
What would the Demon King say?
Probably to follow the money...
This is a temple.
It's a mess.
Dark Knight, if you're a human,
why are you the Demon King's knight?
Ah, well...
I belong to the Demon King.
You belong to the Demon King?
That's right.
Then you lost to the Demon King...
Die! Die, humans!
U-Uh, let's go.
Who's that?
It's better that you don't know.
You won't...
You won't like it.
Die!
You stole our lives! You stole our peace!
You took everything from us!
You deserve to lie with the maggots!
I'm sorry!
It's okay.
May you be cursed for 3,000 years!
May the human world be cursed with darkness and Oblivion take you all!
What you just said...
You don't belong to someone because they beat you.
That doesn't give them the right to do anything they want to you.
I belong to the Demon King, but I didn't lose.
Winning doesn't make you right, and it doesn't mean you can do whatever you want.
I'm proof of that.
I am
the path that extends beyond the hill.
Winter King!
We're meeting with the White Night King's forces.
Okay, we'll make landfall before dawn.
Wh-What's that?
Enemy attack!
Calm down!
The Winter Fleets will not fall so easily!
Focus on their vital point and fire!
Ship 18 has sunk!
The White Night King's ship, too!
We can't let them sink our flagship!
Stop them now!
Going for a walk?
Well...
I saw you.
I arrived too early...
So I figured I'd look at the flowers.
I see.
A disaster.
What is this?!
The Winter King died in order for you to escape!
His sacrifice does not atone for his failure!
What happened to your southern warrior's pride?
Who cares if we lost 200 old, rundown ships?
We'll get new ones!
My father died doing what he believed in.
That is fine and well.
But responsibility for the defeat is a different matter!
Your failure to plan ahead cost the lives of 6,000 soldiers!
As a king, you should know what that means.
Very well.
I'll assume responsibility for whatever you like.
However, Winter Prince, I've heard
that you have the Lakeside Convent and some scholar
bringing you riches you've kept to yourself.
You've also involved the Alliance, and received a large sum of money from them.
It's true that we've adopted a new method of farming.
Yet you still desire financial support?
You're a greedy man.
This is farewell.
I take for myself the name of Winter King.
Before winter's end, I shall carry out a second plan to retake Bright Light Island!
Are you certain?
My weakness meant I had no influence over anyone,
but I feel the weight of this sin on my soul.
We pushed a burden that should've been ours
upon the shoulders of a single hero
and consequently lost his guiding light.
As child of the last king, I will take back Bright Light Island,
He was a soldier, like any other
and bring the Southern Nations some tiny fraction of the light
the hero was to bring us!
My lord?
Send a messenger to her at once.
We require a commander.
I see...
You're finally leaving.
Yeah.
It's sooner than I expected.
Be well.
That's all.
Wait!
Well, um...
I only have one other friend of my gender.
And that's the Head Maid, but...
What are you talking about?
Well, I...
I've always
wanted to be something like a friend to you!
This war involves me as well.
It's easy to imagine that my will has had a butterfly effect.
But there are still some things I cannot bring myself to do.
They feel like betrayals to me.
I'm lying to you.
I've been lying to everyone.
I am the Demon King.
You know I am the Prioress of the Lakeside Convent, yes?
Yes.
And that I serve the Holy Light?
Then as a servant of the Holy Light...
I shall hear your confession.
You have lied to everyone.
You have confessed this to me and to the Light.
Your sins have been forgiven.
There are no more problems.
Even though I'm the Demon King?
Your sin was lying, was it not?
Or do you think being the Demon King is a sin?
Do you regret trying to take the Hero from me?
Then we're done here.
The Lakeside Convent doesn't like annoying rituals.
But then...
There's no problem at all.
Please!
She's the Demon King, but she isn't a bad person.
She would never go back on her word.
There's no problem at all.
Listen, Demon King...
What?
It's true the Hero made a contract with you.
Perhaps there is a special bond between you two...
But there's more than one kind of bond.
The Hero trusted me.
That is my treasure.
I...
I won't betray him either.
With this, we can now be friends.
I'd like that.
There's no way in hell I'd fail.
And I won't give up on the Hero.
Ta-da!
What's this?
A present for the New Year's festival.
It's nothing special.
This is for you, miss!
What's this?
A doll of the Hero!
That's embarrassing.
That's amazing!
I'd like you to have this "lily of the valley" perfume.
That's so nice...
Thank you.
Oh my, oh my!
The two of us made this for the lady with the glasses.
For me too?
Yes...
It's a frilled apron.
My sister did the embroidering!
Lily of the valley?
Just like me.
Yep.
Thank you...
This...
But I'm sorry.
I had forgotten all about the festival until you just mentioned it.
I didn't get you anything.
That's okay!
Yeah, don't worry about it.
You've been so kind to us
and gave us such a warm place to work.
It's like we're getting a present every day.
Happy New Year!
You're sure you won't go, miss?
Yes, I don't like big crowds.
Then we'll be leaving you alone for a while.
It's been a whole year.
I haven't touched you for a year.
I haven't had the chance...
And I belong to you...
I've grown weak.
I'm afraid to change the world.
I'm a demon, so war and bloodlust run through my veins.
But now, I'm afraid of blood.
I'm still doing my best, though.
Are you doing your best?
I want you to praise me.
Yeah, you're great, Demon King.
Hero!
Hey!
Hero...
Yeah.
Hero!
Demon—
Wh-What?
You moron!
Ow! Wait! Ow! Stop hitting me!
Where the hell have you been this past year?!
I've been sending you reports!
Those are just picture diaries!
Why didn't you ever come to see me?
I've been busy with Gate City.
I'm trying to figure how to get things into the Northern Fortress...
Why are you doing that?
You're the one who ordered me to stop anything that could help the extremists.
You could just use your Ultimate Destruction magic to take care of them!
No, I can't!
Everyone there is alive.
They're doing their best...
Every day, they cling to the slimmest hopes.
I can't just destroy them all!
Hero...
The Fairy Queen,
the beautiful forest songstresses,
the Dragon Princess!
The mechanoid girls,
the girls at the tavern...
All of them are trying their hardest!
I can't destroy them just because I'm the Hero.
Sure you weren't simply enjoying your popularity?
Of course not!
Really?
You're absolutely certain?!
What about you?
Weren't you getting all kinds of passionate glances from nobles in the capital and rich merchants?
Head Maid, I told you not to tell him.
You're serious?
No, it wasn't like that.
It was during a negotiation, like a duel...
What's with that look?!
Weakling!
What do you mean by "weakling"?
I was doing my best...
You...
flabby Demon King!
Flabby...
Flabby?!
Did you say flabby?!
Was it this mouth?
This mouth?
That hurts! Stop it...
I've been doing stretches and calisthenics every single day!
You're the Demon King, so why spend your time on something so petty?
It's not petty, you stupid Hero!
What? You're just a dumb recluse!
And you're an idiot who can't even stay in one place!
The music of the New Year's festival...
Can I turn the lights on?
No!
You just suddenly returned,
so I look like a mess.
It's fine.
No, it isn't!
Yes, it is!
No, it isn't.
I haven't put on any perfume.
And...
Enough.
You're always pretty and wonderful, so it's fine!
What?
How about a dance?
If you'll take the lead...
I'm not good either.
Um...
Push out your chest a little more.
Like this?
Don't get mad if I step on your feet.
Half step to the right.
And now the left.
Yeah, you've got it.
I should've worn a nicer outfit...
You smell good, Demon King.
And I feel safe in your arms, Hero.
Is this enough?
I mean, for your New Year's present...
I...
I didn't get you anything.
D-Don't worry about it...
I wasn't expecting anything.
Hero...
Well, if you want...
As your owner, I could reward you.
Of course,
I still have a lot of useless flesh,
so maybe it's more a punishment than a reward.
Y-Yeah.
My...
I-It's over.
R-Right.
Shall we let go?
Y-Yeah...
Seeing you gave me courage.
Sure you don't want to see everyone?
Yes.
Don't wait so long this time.
I'll retake Gate City in under a month.
Can you do that?
Talking with you gave me an idea.
Same here.
The next time we meet...
It'll be on a battlefield...
I'm going to the sea as well.
Don't fall behind.
Of course not!
I am your sword and your path.
You are
my light.
The light is far
The night is foggy, and the darkness
holds me captive
All I can sense
are unreal flower petals in the fog
Slowly we are drawn apart
The door of the sky is a solid color
My heart feels the thunder above
It echoes the thunder
into the distance
The light is dim
Welcome back, Hero!
Yeah, Old Man.
I'm back!
Next Chapter