Mage!
I'm sleepy.
This is one of the legendary heroes?
What are you doing there?
Where have you been?
Sleep...
You can't!
Did you meet the Hero?
Yep.
What was he doing?
Going to the Demon Realm.
But more importantly, the Demo—
I have orders from the Crimson Scholar.
Orders?
You know the Scholar?
But
she doesn't know the war's started.
As such, this may not do you any good.
But I'll tell you anyway.
With livestock of the Artiodactyla order,
one can deliberately infect patients with an attenuated,
and thus less dangerous version of the virus,
resulting in an induced immunity to all related forms.
Develop a method, then find a way to instruct and inoculate the populace.
Could you perhaps explain that more simply?
Exterminate smallpox.
Is that even possible?
That accursed disease kills three million a year!
It's so serious that any house with one smallpox infection is burned to the ground!
But it is possible.
How?
This contains the details.
Once you recover, you won't catch it again.
Take advantage of this.
It works for seven years.
This is hard to believe.
But if this is what the Scholar says...
If...
If all Southern Triad citizens and their allies
could receive such treatment for one gold piece,
that'd be great.
I see now.
This could change everything.
We could work for a ceasefire!
And I'm a demon...
or something?
I'm sleepy.
The demons brought a cure for smallpox?
Is that what you want us to say?
You want to bridge the gap between humans and demons?
Why?
I'm tired of silly nightmares.
Sleep should bring good dreams.
It's true that
demons are large and strange to look at.
But they're intelligent beings who're capable of language.
Just as there are many human nations,
perhaps the Demon Realm has many countries and factions, as well...
That's why...
If you like, you may take me prisoner.
But please consider my request.
Please consider her request!
Chapter 12
Maoyuu
The Hero and the Demon King
I'm back, my Hero
You sleep too much, my Demon King
I hope we don't have a war.
Let us believe
in the words the Hero sent from the Winter Country.
Just hold out until snowfall.
If the fighting stops,
then there'll hope.
A girl from the Winter Kingdom who wields a strange machine.
You must be her.
I've found you,
Crimson Scholar!
Come back to me, Demon King!
You said you were just getting your license renewed.
Don't sacrifice yourself!
Because you decided on self-sacrifice,
the maid, your double, has become a real saint!
You will be mine, Hero.
I refuse!
If you join me, I will give you half the world.
Why?
You're behind the times, Demon King!
The world doesn't belong to you!
So it isn't yours to give!
Furthermore...
This body belongs to me.
You can corrupt it or take it over,
but it's still mine alone.
It's the most important thing in the world to me!
What?
Just wake up already,
my Demon King.
What are you talking about?
Shut up...
Shut up!
Don't ruin my sweet reunion!
You call this sweet?
You greedy Demon King.
I'm back, my Hero.
You sleep too much,
my Demon King.
Release my sister!
Then kneel, heretic!
Apologize to the Holy Light.
I believe in the Holy Light.
Kneeling means nothing to me.
How dare you speak the Holy Light's name?!
Beg for forgiveness!
Confess your sins and shed tears of humiliation!
Behold, Scholar!
This sword has shed sufficient blood
to be worthy of your name, "Crimson."
You will be judged by this blade
and descend into the red-black hell within my eye!
Who are you?
Just a soldier.
Did it work?
Yeah.
I doubt there'll even be a scar.
Thank you.
There's a lot happening back on the surface.
Where do we start?
Wherever you like.
Tell me everything.
Tasteless bean soup and stale bread crusts.
I'd heard that grain prices had risen, but...
I guess the army brought a lot of money,
but barely any food.
Why not bring food?
Can't you guess?
Money is easier to transport
and more efficient.
But the nobles are starting to panic.
Money's great, but without food, you'll starve in winter.
That's why they began a war with the Southern Triad,
which still has food.
So why aren't we attacking?
Actually...
What?
And also, they're arguing at Command HQ
over who receives the southern territories, once they've fallen.
What the hell?!
Fuck that!
Calm down.
The High Priest is here as well.
He'll settle things with them.
So you're saying
everything we've been through is some test by the Holy Light?
You're all a bunch of idiots!
What?
They still haven't decided when to start the war!
Well, a few of the mercenaries have attacked on their own...
No...
We must mount an immediate defense.
There's no need.
I'll head out at once.
But...
If the battle is prolonged,
we'll hand 20,000 Central soldiers the excuse they need to attack.
We attack right away with our best equipment.
Yes, ma'am.
Fewer than 200 have that good of equipment!
At most, they number a thousand.
This doesn't even qualify as a war.
And I can't let a real one begin.
Not now.
What's wrong, kid?
There are some things you can't protect, no matter how much you want to.
Give up.
This is reality.
How?
How can you block with your wrists?
I wrapped steel arrows around my wrists to protect my forearms.
Your tricks won't save you!
Soldier!
We strike once, then withdraw!
Charge!
Don't try to be a hero.
Withdraw!
They've turned around!
Behind us!
On the right!
Where are they?
I can't see them!
Charge!
Pull back!
Form ranks!
Formation 16!
After them!
They aren't many.
But Captain...
The horses are tired.
We can't keep this up!
I don't care!
Just a little more!
They split up their ranks?
Which way do we pursue?
You take the right side!
I'll take the left!
Once we catch up, they're ours!
They split up again?
Wh-Which way do we follow?
Both!
Chase both!
They're following us.
Fine.
We'll head to the rendezvous.
We've split them enough.
Where's Soldier?
Over here!
Everyone's here.
A few are lightly wounded, but all are accounted for.
Excellent.
We reform as one, then attack again.
But this time, just unseat them from their horses.
It isn't for us to kill them.
They, too, are the Holy Light's disciples.
We oppose each other now, but we are brothers.
It came.
Reinforcements.
Yes,
the strongest we could hope for.
And you claim to be the Demon Realm's mightiest army?
You couldn't even make it across the snow?
I don't want to hear that from cowards who ran without putting up a fight
because they lacked food.
You babysit the Prince, so don't take that tone.
What'd you say?
Silence, all of you!
This went just as planned.
The Alliance caused the rise in prices.
Those accursed merchants have no plan!
When our goal has been reached, you will have
the Southern Triad's territory as promised.
Rule it as you see fit.
We will forever play the church's enemy
to make certain that you will always rule.
The church must always be united.
Yes.
And to ensure this, I shall raise a Third Crusade of the Holy Key.
It will destroy the Southern Triad,
recapture Gate City, and even slay the Demon King.
But the Demon Realm is huge. How can you conquer it?
We have a secret weapon.
That's...
It uses black powder to propel projectiles that pierce the enemy.
That heretic,
the Crimson Scholar, hired someone
in the Iron Country to develop it.
Mass produce it, and even an army of slaves
will be several times more powerful than what we have.
I hear a voice.
Tell us its words!
Obtain the key.
The Demon King's life...
The desire of the church...
The bones of the Light Spirit...
Attain them all.
Hey, master.
There's nothing out here.
There is.
Dispelling invisibility.
What is this?
The spatial density is incredible.
I feel the power of a strange spell...
The spell creates a high-density pillar of force.
Magic from the age of the gods.
This is a liquefied magic circle!
I'm a fake, anyway!
It's crazy to think I could be the original, no matter how hard I try.
If you and the Hero are the ones to see the result, that will suffice.
I shall remain the spare.
Maybe I'm redundant?
The Demon King's really popular.
Not at all, compared to previous ones.
In the Demon Realm, the more you excel at fighting,
the more you are respected.
If she were the previous Demon King, at least a hundred would've fainted.
My comrades...
My people!
As you can see, I am well.
And
I am glad that you all have also endured these harsh days.
I have returned
to the Demon Realm!
That sounds like your cue.
R-Right.
I am glad to see that Gate City was retaken in my absence.
That city will remain under my direct control and protection!
And my loyal sword and general, the Dark Knight,
has punished those who rebelled against me
and broke my laws!
H-Huh?
Flashier!
Flashy!
Huh? Flashy?
Plasma Annihilator.
Whoops. I overdid it.
It's been 20 years since first contact with humans!
We've now come to the crossroads of our destiny.
And now I
call for a meeting of all the Greater Races, a Quriltai!
It's here!
The day has finally come!
Full-scale war with the humans!
This time, we will win!
No! That isn't what I wanted!
No!
Listen to me!
At the Quriltai, the chiefs of each of the races will decide!
Spread word to the entire Demon Realm
that their King now summons them!
Are you okay?
There's still a lot of work to do.
Don't worry.
I'll be with you the whole time, no matter how long it takes.
Hero...
Demon King!
The Southern Triad's potatoes
were sold to the Central Nations via the Alliance.
If they can taste them
and realize for themselves that they aren't a demon fruit,
it's possible that several countries may lean toward the south, right?
It's the first step toward a dual-currency system.
And a more mature economy.
What surprised me were the words from the man of the Alliance.
I'd like you to agree to immediately end hostilities against demons,
as well as allow the Alliance to trade with them.
Trade with the demons? Impossible!
I can do it.
I propose this as a merchant.
I'm willing to bet my life on it.
I can't give you an answer right now.
But I wish to hear more about the demons.
It's possible that both worlds are more similar than we believe.
He said, "Right now, that is how I feel."
So what is it?
Um, well...
Basically...
While you were gone, I gave it to him.
What?!
M-M-My sword!
Not my body.
Oh...
I'm sorry I did it while you were away.
I may have forced him into it...
Why are you telling me?
Because you belong to him.
That's part of it, but mostly...
Because you said you were my friend.
I don't want to come between you.
Even if Hero never touches me,
I can live with that.
I'm sure the Hero would prefer a human girl.
Part of me still feels that, and it saddens me.
Demon King...
But I love the Hero.
As my owner...
As a man.
I love him, too.
As the master of my blade.
And as a man.
I want to be annoying for you
I don't mind being conceited
Hide a tree in a forest, they say
It started with a little mistake
Let's redo our meeting from there
Let's oppose the strand of time
Strength alone is no weapon
You taught me that just now
I want to show you what lies
beyond these days
The wind is strong
I'm sure you know that too
I can't fly
Sharing makes you dependant
Now, take my hand
Hold it tight
Now...
I never expected the seeds I sowed to bloom like this.
Indeed.
Her, more than anything.
This, and this alone, wasn't something I left.
It's the beginning of liberalism,
born of her wounds, pain, and blood.
Indeed.
Aren't you happy?
How much could I really do for her?
Humans amaze me.
Their world is so boisterous and chaotic.
But I love it more than anything.
Are you crying?
I don't know why.
Maybe...
I'm a little proud.
Not that it was my doing.
I'm glad
you two met.
Yeah.
I love
this world.