I-I-I've brought some tea for you!
Thank you.
You needn't be so nervous.
I-I-I'm not nervous...
E-Enjoy!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Maoyuu
the hero and the demon king
I want to be annoying for you
I don't mind being conceited
Hide a tree in a forest, they say
It started with a little mistake
Let's redo our meeting from there
Let's oppose the strand of time
Strength alone is no weapon
You taught me that just now
I want to show you what lies
beyond these days
The wind is strong
I'm sure you know that too
I can't fly
Sharing makes you dependant
Now, take my hand
Hold it tight
Now...
Chapter 8
Take This Sword, My Lord
It's been a long time, Scholar.
And what brings you here today?
I'm delivering balance sheets and other documents.
I realize they're normally sent by ship,
but I wanted to see you personally,
so I came in person.
I-I'm not sure how to respond to that.
Very well, Scholar...
Why don't you slip into something more comfortable?
H-Huh?
Retaking Bright Light Island
has paved the way for many new trade routes and also many counterfeiters...
Y-Yes.
But only a fool would be deceived by them.
When I was younger, I had a bad experience with one.
U-Um...
I'll wait as long as it takes.
I've come to see the real you.
W-Well...
That's enough.
You can leave.
B-But...
He's already seen through it.
I'm sorry...
I didn't mean to deceive you, but...
I know.
Appearance plays an important part in negotiations.
Some kind of illusion magic?
I'm impressed.
It didn't fool you at all.
No, that was just intuition.
I've learned to trust my intuition in these situations.
More importantly,
it's good to see you again.
You finally acknowledged it.
You didn't seem at all surprised, so I thought you had forgotten.
I'd never forget you, Hero.
I was the guy dumb enough to get excited over 15 gold pieces.
Yes, that speech turned quite a profit.
Thank you.
Somehow, that pisses me off.
I'm relieved to see you doing well.
I think you've changed a little.
You used to be more aloof, more obsessed with perfection.
It's the island.
Have I changed that much?
You seem a far more formidable foe now.
What a coincidence.
I was just thinking the same thing.
They say when you encounter
something big, something that runs counter to your experience and knowledge,
you change.
And, Hero, your appearance now only makes me more certain.
That you can change the world?
Yes.
Come to think of it, you haven't fulfilled our contract.
Oh?
You said when I returned,
you would treat me to a banquet with lots of hot busty girls.
Oh, that's true!
When shall we hold it?
Now.
What?
Where are we?!
Taking deep breaths will help with the teleportation sickness.
One more time.
I never thought I'd experience teleportation magic...
For some reason, rainbows appear in this region at night.
I was told it has to do with magnetic fields,
but the explanation was too complex for me.
We can have our banquet here.
I've dispatched him to tell the demons to ready some drinks.
Demons?
Then is this...
Yes, the Demon Realm.
I decided to believe in you because of what you said,
so I've brought you to her world.
Then she's...
A demon.
That's Gate City.
Until recently, thousands of soldiers occupied it.
The place that demons retook after the commander fled?
That's a lie.
The human merchants are still there, and they're still in business.
Could I get some drinks over here?
Where are we?
Within Gate City.
It isn't safe enough
to reestablish contact with the Human World, but it's peaceful, isn't it?
Those merchants are from my Alliance!
Right now, it's the only place in the world
where humans and demons coexist.
A population of approximately 32,000.
Larger than the Lake Country's capital.
The Demon King has recognized it as neutral territory,
and it's governed by a local body.
A third of the representatives are human.
Actually, I'm a representative for the demons.
For the demons?
As her representative.
Why do this?
It seems very dangerous.
Because I'd be lonely...
if I went back to just being a hero.
My lord!
My lord, I've come to answer your call.
I swear on the pride of the Fire Dragons
that we will give your guest the finest banquet possible.
Um... Go easy on us, okay?
You should drink.
Refuse her drink, and she'll bite off your ear.
That's horrible!
You have to ensure the cup is overflowing, or it doesn't count.
Now gulp it down.
Oh, my... Wait a moment.
I don't even care anymore.
What do you think, Merchant?
Of what?
The boobs... You know, her boobs.
Well?
Oh, yes. Understood.
Pretty nice...
The rainbows are amazing at this hour.
Yes.
What are your thoughts on Gate City?
It's like an orchard with fruits of gold ripe for picking.
I see.
Then, with my authority, I shall sell it to you.
You can do that?
Yeah.
And in return?
Merchants always view things in terms of loss and gain.
Yes.
That's why people call them
stubborn or greedy monsters who are only interested in profit.
But when I look at her, I think that may not be true at all.
I think merchants,
the ones who think longer and harder than anyone about loss and gain,
may be the first to find
what cannot be measured by loss or gain.
Hero...
I want you to show it to me.
That's my price.
Did you see her?
Yes, at the Outer Library.
Was she awake?
No, but I managed to leave a message.
The magical energy in the air is thicker now.
The ancient Demon Kings are restless.
What about the seal?
It's holding, but barely.
It'll stabilize once I enter.
Head Maid...
Yes.
If, when I emerge, I am no longer myself...
I swear on my life that I shall end yours.
What?
What's happening, Knight?
In the Lake Country, I received the Holy Light's blessing,
and I became a servant of the Light.
This sword has long journeyed beside you.
I offer it to you, along with myself.
My sword, my power, my body.
The loyalty and purity of my soul belong to you.
You are the master of my soul, the place where my hope dwells.
Hey, wait...
I won't wait!
Hero, this sword belongs to you!
Just stand up, okay?
The Demon King is amazing.
She is smart, kind-hearted, and she has a dream.
She sees far into the future.
So I shan't ask for you because you belong to her.
However, I belong to myself.
So if nothing else, I wish to offer myself to you.
As a knight, I've never sworn my sword to another,
so I've never been a real knight.
I shall give my sword to you, and you will be my master forever.
That's the kind of knight I desire to be.
Are you sure you want this?
Is it that important to you?
It doesn't matter when or where!
I want to do something too.
If you're leaving for the future, I wish to be near you.
I don't...
I don't want to be left behind again!
I'm sorry.
Take this sword, my lord...
I shall never betray you.
Good.
Reverse it, and hand it back.
Now my blade belongs to you.
My body and soul as well.
I feel really fulfilled somehow!
Um, well...
It comes with a one-week return period, right?
I can get out of the contract?
You really believe that?
Nice job, little one.
You have a good eye!
This is a lovely partridge.
Want it?
May I?
No! You shouldn't take things...
C'mon, it's fine.
But...
Thanks to the Scholar, pigs are plentiful, even in winter.
It's great.
Yeah.
This is the first time we've had enough
to eat in the winter after paying our taxes.
And we owe a lot to the Head Maid too.
You do?
She brought us soap and warm clothes.
All the settlers and serfs are grateful to her.
The serfs too?
I dislike insects.
She taught us how to make herb baths,
and last winter, no one died to the cold weather.
This village has really changed!
What?
Are you certain of this, Messenger?
You forget your place!
As a faithful servant of the Holy Light,
you should be well aware that His Holiness is infallible, Winter King.
Mobilize your army.
If they are allowed to escape, you may be declared a blasphemer!
No way!
Is it because of the elections?
I can't believe I didn't see this coming!
Something horrible has happened...
Where is the Prioress?
She's in the Winter Country right now.
Recall her at once.
There's no time!
Partridge! Partridge!
This looks good...
You're a great chef now.
Really?
All right!
Now I won't have to go back to being a serf, right?
Um, and what do you want to be?
Sister, you should be glasses!
H-Hey, now...
I'm sorry to call so late!
Is anyone here?
Is there anyone at home?
The Scholar is a heretic?
The potato is a demon crop.
The new agricultural methods introduced
are evil and go against the Holy Light's teachings.
And the church has no place in her studies.
Thus, the Crimson Scholar is a heretic
who must be handed over immediately.
They're using the Holy Light for their petty schemes!
What do we do?
She won't return for a minimum of two months.
That's why
she left the ring I showed you.
If she were here, I'm sure she'd have some idea.
Why have we received this trial?
I know!
If we use that illusion...
I won't allow that.
However, Hero...
As King, I...
Finish that sentence, and you'll get a face full of lightning.
You can think it.
But if you say it, you've failed as a king.
Well then, I'll take care of it.
Hero...
I'm sorry, but let them arrest you.
And once you're out of the Winter Country, I'll save you.
If you hand her over and she crosses your borders,
they can't blame you for what happens.
That'll take care of it.
Then once again, you'll...
Yeah.
Disobeying the church will complicate things.
Once again, I'm forced to abandon you.
I have two people with me this time,
and the Scholar will be home soon.
And while it may not be in public, you'll see me again, right?
Hell no!
I'm going with you!
You have a place you must protect.
If I could sacrifice myself in her stead...
Don't be sad.
I'm used to leaving in the night.
Are we moving, Sister?
Yep.
What about my promise to teach the hunters how to make pie?
Sorry, but...
You could wipe out the entirety of the Holy Capital's army on your own.
She wouldn't let me do that.
I can't fight and win or divide and conquer.
But that doesn't mean I'll let them take anything from me.
And so,
I must be going.
The light is far
The night is foggy, and the darkness
holds me captive
All I can sense
are unreal flower petals in the fog
Slowly we are drawn apart
The door of the sky is a solid color
My heart feels the thunder above
It echoes the thunder
into the distance
The light is dim
Next Chapter
I Am Human