Horie
Ce?!
Vrei să lipsești de la excursia cu clasa ca să mergi la meditații?
Îți interzic!
Dar tot ce face toată lumea
este să se prostească!
De asta se numesc cele
mai bune zile din viață!
Nu ți le irosi făcând meditații.
Știi că toată lumea
"se distrează" împreună noaptea?
Așa sunt adolescenții.
Self-Censored
Înainte să-ți dai seama,
totul se transformă într-o mare orgie!
SEX
LIFE
Sunt cele mai bune zile din viața ta,
deci mergi și trăiește-ți-le!
Și te mai numești părinte?
Ao's Too Horny to Study
There are so many things I don't understand
And whenever I try to, it's all just nonsense
Ao's Too Horny to Study
I'm always torn by what you say
Your charms are like a Wonderland
Best days
of your life
Study
Best days
of your life
Study
Best days
of your life
Study
Best days
of your life
Study
Best days
of your life
Study
Best days
of your life
Study
Best days
of your life
Study
Best days
of your life
Study
Best days
of your life
Study
Best days
of your life
Study
Best days
of your life
Study
Best days
of your life
Study
Best days
of your life
Study
Best days
of your life
Study
Best days
of your life
Study
Best days
of your life
Study
Best days
of your life
Study
Best days
of your life
Study
Best days
of your life
Study
Best days
of your life
Study
Best days
of your life
Study
Best days
of your life
Study
Best days
of your life
Study
Best days
of your life
Study
Best days
of your life
Study
Best days
of your life
Study
Best days
of your life
Study
Best days
of your life
Study
Best days
of your life
Study
Best days
of your life
Study
Best days
of your life
Study
Best days
of your life
Study
Best days
of your life
Study
Best days
of your life
Study
Best days
of your life
Study
Best days
of your life
Study
Best days
of your life
Study
Best days
of your life
Study
Sex Life
When the bell rings,
I'll be coming for you
Make me go crazy and scream like
SEX LIFE
Lust
DESIRE
SEX LIFE
Ready,go!
Ready, go
Starting counting to one hundred
There's a limit to how close I can get to you
high
distinction
Simple and Clear
My heart isn't that complicated
My batting average might be close to zero
But I'm not gonna waste the best days of my life worrying about it
Our relationship isn't that simple and clear
Wonder, wonder, wonderful wonder
Ao Can't Protect Her Lower Half
Nu pot fugi acasă ca de obicei, deoarece suntem în munți, deci va trebui să fiu super atentă.
Aia era Horie?
Se comportă mai
antisocial ca de obicei.
Aș vrea s-o cunosc mai bine.
Depravare, dezmăț, destrăbălare...
E ca și cum nimeni nu știe ce gândește.
Ai grijă!
K-Kijima...
Îmi pare rău!
La naiba, ai făcut-o să fugă din nou.
Mai taci.
Horie pare destul de dificilă.
De ce nu te dai la o fată mai ușoară?
Prostule.
Exact asta o faci și drăguță.
O, ce a fost asta?
Trebuie să aflu!
Hei, Horie! Așteaptă!
Ce?
Putem vorbi puțin?
Și nu doar să vorbim!
Ci să facem și alte lucruri distractive!
Da! Putem înlătura toate inhibițiile!
Haide să ne distrăm astă-seară!
Ș-Știam eu!
O-O, p-păi, vedeți v-voi...
Știu! De ce nu-l invităm și pe Kijima?
Ce?!
Ne vedem mai târziu!
Ce? Ce a fost asta?
Nu-mi spune că vor să ne privească
pe mine și pe Kijima cum "ne distrăm"!
Ce mă fac? Port chiloți de babă astăzi!
Acel fel de chiloți care-ți trec de buric!
Credeam că toate fetele poartă chiloți sexy.
Asta e ceea ce ar crede Regele Relațiilor.
Să facem prostii iese din discuție!
Trebuie să-i spun lui
Kijima să le refuze invitația!
Scuzați-mă!
Omule, mi-e somn deja.
Ce vreți să facem în seara asta?
Nu puteam să ne culcăm
la ora zece ca de obicei?
Ce?
Auzindu-i vocea mi s-a activat instinctul de a mă ascunde.
Haideți, băieți. Nu lăsați ușile deschise.
Ce?
Este blocată?
Voi fi prinsă!
Kijima.
Merg să iau ceva de băut. Voi vreți ceva?
Voi veni și eu
Hmm, să mă gândesc...
Au plecat?
Acum, cum mai exact o să ies de aici?
Ce naiba...
M-Mâna lui Kijima este pe piciorul meu!
Ce naiba este asta?
Este moale și... cald?
Oprește-te!
Este cumva o pisică?
Hei, ieși afară.
M-Miau?
H-Horie?! Ești aici
deoarece voiai să mă vezi?
Nu!
Păi, ei bine, oarecum da...
Hei...
Pleacă înainte să se întoarcă ceilalți.
M-a salvat fără măcar să i-o cer...
Prostul.
Apropo...
Ce atingeam mai exact?
Era foarte moale și cald.
De ce îți miroși mâna?!
Mergi și spală-te! Chiar acum!
Bine! Nu trebuie să—
Hopa, Horie este peste Kijima!
Ba nu! Nu este ceea ce pare!
Presupun că ați vrea să vă distrați fără noi.
Ar trebui să plecăm?
Nu plecați!
Unde să mergem?
Ascultați-mă!
H-Haideți să ne distrăm
împreună! Luați-mă cu voi!
Păi, dacă insiști.
Vom merge până la altar
și ne vom întoarce?
Nici vorbă! Nu, nicio șansă,
nu se va întâmpla!
Nu puteți vorbi serios.
Și de ce trebuie s-o facem
în pereche băiat-fată?
Vrei să fii singură cu Kijima, nu?
Ca să vă cunoașteți!
Man, I bet this'll go on our permanent record if we get caught.
Pari în regulă cu asta...
Știam că nu trebuia să
vin în excursia asta stupidă!
Ce? Horie?
Te-ai schimbat?
Ești foarte drăguță.
Cred că ți se potrivește.
I know, right? We lent her some of our clothes.
She said she didn't pack anything casual.
Aren't you gonna thank us, Kijima?
Yeah! Thanks, everyone!
Okay, go for it, Horie!
Kijima will be your bodyguard!
I-I'm fine going on my own.
All alone? On this old mountain trail?
It was closer than it looked.
I never got scared because I was too busy thinking about Kijima.
Oh, Kijima?
I guess there was nothing to be worried about after all.
K-K-Kijima!
A h-h-hand!
Huh? What is it?
A gh-gh-gho—
Calm down, Horie! I'll go check it out!
Sorry...
No worries. That's what I'm here for.
Don't get the wrong idea!
I won't.
You know, you're really jumpy all the—
H-Horie...
Give it to
her straight
Beat around
the bush
Give it to her straight?
No, that'd embarrass her.
Beat around the bush?
Beat around
the bush
That's the way to go.
Horie.
What?
Are you sure you didn't forget something important in the bathroom?
Oh, right. My flashlight.
That's important too, but...
If she goes back like this,
everyone will see it too.
Should I pull it down myself?
No, that's too creepy.
Maybe I should be upfront.
I don't want to make her cry though.
Hold up. Don't get too far ahead.
Why not?
Uh, well...
I mean, this trail isn't exactly safe.
Oh, good point.
I keep telling myself not to look,
but I can't help it!
You're not good with scary stuff, are you?
Not really.
You're not feeling chilly are you?
You know, around your lower half.
Why do you ask?
Oh, uh, you know...
Your legs aren't exactly covered.
Just wondering if you're being conscious of your lower half?
Excuse me?
What's wrong with him?
Lower half this and lower half that.
Why is he so fixated on that?
That perv!
He can't get the feeling of my thighs out of his head,
so he's trying to weasel his way back to them?!
What the hell is wrong with him?!
I'm protecting my lower half, thank you!
Horie! You really shouldn't do that...
Wh-What?
It makes me think about your lower half.
What a creep!
So you're finally showing your true colors!
You've been after my body the whole time, haven't you?
I can't stand guys like you!
I'm going back by myself,
so don't follow me!
You can't!
Why not?
Because other people will be there...
Exactly! I wanna go somewhere brightly lit, with lots of people.
Bye.
Wait!
I can't let you go! I need you to stay here!
He's stripping!
Is he gonna use his shirt to tie me up?
He doesn't just want to touch my thighs?
I'm done for!
He's going to tie me up and see everything!
I'm not ready for that!
No!
A-Are you okay?
Look, I'm sorry I've been acting real desperate.
I should've known better
than to go alone with you.
I know what you want...
Just promise you'll be gentle.
Îmi pare rău, Horie.
Am încercat să fiu cât
mai blând cu putință.
Însemni mult pentru mine, Horie.
Te rog să mă crezi.
Așa este.
Mereu ai fost blând cu mine...
Nu trebuie să-mi spui asta.
Ce... tot... faci?
Păi...
Ți se văd chiloții.
Horie?!
You're making my brain go haywire
120% of my thoughts are about you
I clutch my pure, innocent feelings
Entrance
Ceremony
Then toss them with all my might at you
Even before I realized I was in love,
I was enraptured by every facet of your being
Even before I realized you were the one for me,
I fell for your smile that filled my stomach with butterflies
Do you know what you put me through?
Data viitoare: "Miyabi nu vrea să piardă".
Next Time
Miyabi Doesn't Want to Lose
Vrei s-o facem în trei?!