Oprește-te în clipa asta!
Mereu mi-am dorit să spun acest lucru.
Nu pot să înțeleg de ce ai da cu piciorul unei șanse de a avea un atac surpriză.
O, haide. Prezentările sunt importante.
Dacă reusești să-i provoci, își vor
concentra toate atacurile asupra ta.
Cum de știați care era locul
nostru secret de întâlnire?
Am avut o bănuială doar.
Ce?!
Vă cunoaștem planurile malefice.
Nu mai puteți scăpa acum.
Exact!
A-Acea sabie sfântă! N-Nu se poate!
Eroul tocmai a sosit!
Și astfel,
Eroul a apărut și a înfrânt
toți monștrii Lordului Demon!
Se pare că Eroul este o fată drăguță!
Nu-i corect... Și eu vreau să
merg într-o aventură cu Eroul!
Nu ai face față.
Poftim?
Doar pentru că este un erou nu înseamnă și
că i-ar putea înfrânge pe toți de una singură.
Altminteri am rămâne fără slujbe.
Nu deveni așa... îngâmfat.
Hei, ai auzit? Eroul a învins
monștrii Lordului Demon—
Nu contează.
Trebuie să ucidem niște goblini.
Locația este Orașul Apei.
Recompensa este o
punguță cu aur de fiecare.
Ucigașul de Goblini în Orașul Apei
Este decizia voastră dacă veniți sau nu.
Serios acum...
Credeam că mi-am dat seama de asta, dar acum sunt sigură.
Nu aș rezista dacă m-aș lăsa surprinsă în continuare de fiecare mișcare a ta.
Ascultă acum.
După cum ți-am mai spus,
nu este o discuție atunci când
nu avem din ce să alegem.
Dar aveți.
Tu doar ne dai două variante!
Dacă spunem că nu vom merge,
tu te vei duce de unul singur, nu-i așa?
Normal.
Deci avea dreptate.
Asta nu este o discuție.
Totuși, faptul că Tăietorul
de Bărbi ne-a spus despre asta
înseamnă că a devenit
puțin mai moale, poate.
Într-adevăr. Cred că asta este un lucru bun.
Nectar dulce, nectar bun.
Atunci, voi face ce vreau.
Voi merge cu tine.
Sunt mulți goblini.
Cu cât ai mai mulți vrăjitori, cu atât mai bine.
Foarte bine. Tocmai ce ne
rezolvasem cheltuieile de călătorie,
deci vom merge cu tine.
După ce vom omorî acei goblini,
vei merge într-o aventură cu noi.
Ești de acord cu asta, Orcbolg?
Da, sunt de acord.
Și nu ai voie să îneci golbinii.
Sau să-i ataci cu foc.
Sau să-i otrăvești.
Nu am voie nici să-i otrăvesc?
Desigur!
Foarte bine.
A acceptat destul de ușor.
Înțeleg.
Acela este...
Orașul Apei?
Am mai fost aici.
Datorită canalelor navale,
au multe mărfuri și mâncare.
Ce am putea mânca bun pe aici?
Păi, să vedem...
Probabil ar fi ficatul de miel făcut cu vin și peștele prăjit de râu.
Se pare că grâul de aici este foarte
aspru și se face un aluat grozav din el.
O, se pare că știi multe despre asta, domnule Ucigaș de Goblini.
O persoană pe care o cunosc știe.
Când i-am spus că vin aici, ea mi-a spus asta.
Este vorba de acea persoană de la fermă?
Da.
Deci acesta este Templul Legilor... Este prima oară când îl văd.
Este incredibil, nu-i așa, Ucigașule de Goblini?
Serios?
Doamne...
Deci, persoana care a
făcut misiunea se află aici?
Da. A spus că o vom întâlni aici.
Clientul este un preot al Zeului Suprem?
Nu, este arhiepiscopul Zeului Suprem.
Poftim?!
A-Arhiepiscopul?
Să mergem.
F-Fecioara Sabiei.
Persoana care administrează
legile în zona frontierei vestice.
Arhiepiscopul preaiubit de Zeul Suprem.
Acum zece ani, a fost unul din aventurierii care l-au învins pe Lordul Demon reînviat.
Un aventurier de rang aur,
al doilea cel mai înalt rang.
Nu este un eroul din vreo legendă.
A luat naștere din trup uman și
a devenit o legendă de una singură.
Ea este...
Fecioara...
Sabiei.
Ce?
Vai... Pe cine avem aici?
Am venit să ucidem niște goblini.
N-N-Ne cerem scuze!
Vă mulțumim că ne-ați primit. Este o onoare să vă întâlnim.
Un războinic curajos și o
preoteasă adorabilă... Și ceilalți?
Suntem membri ai grupului.
Deși nu am fost chemați,
vom fi bucuroși să ajutăm.
Bun-venit, aventurierilor.
Vă urez bun-venit din adâncul inimii.
Deci, unde sunt goblinii?
S-a întâmplat cam acum o lună.
Am trimis una din fetele de la templu să îndeplinească o sarcină noaptea târziu
și i-am găsit corpul neînsuflețit
pe o străduță la răsăritul soarelui.
Am primit un raport care
spunea că arăta de parcă
fusese ciopârțită cât încă era în viață.
Cât încă era în viață?
Deci se întâmplase acolo?
Da.
Avea vreo parte mâncată
sau a fost doar ucisă?
Ce altceva ne mai poți spune?
Ai puțin grijă cu cuvintele.
Continuă.
A fost un incident cu adevărat îngrozitor.
Am crescut numărul de gardieni care patrulează orașul, dar crimile au continuat să aibă loc.
Omorurile păreau comise
de hoți sau ucigași simpli...
Acțiuni violente asupra femeilor...
Chiar și câțiva copii au fost răpiți.
Și apoi s-a întâmplat ca un
aventurier să vadă și să doboare
o creatură mică și întunecată
care atacase o fată.
Acel corp mic...
Era un goblin?
Goblini?
Sunt sigur că nu sunt doar câțiva...
Dar cum au reușit să ajungă în oraș?
Mă îndoiesc că au intrat pe porți.
Poate au intrat prin subteran... sau prin canale.
Dar par cam multe victime ca
ei doar să fi hoinărit înăuntru.
Goblinii se află în subteran, nu?
Acest oraș a fost construi pe o veche așezare,
deci probabil există niște ruine subterane.
Dacă aș fi în locul lor,
m-aș stabili sub pământ.
Nu sunt creaturi prea inteligente, dar nu sunt nici complet proaste.
Mereu gândești ca un goblin.
Desigur.
Dacă nu aș știi ce gândesc,
nu aș putea lupta contra lor.
Și noi am dedus că sunt subteran
and sent out a quest for the
adventurers in this town, but...
What happened to them?
I see...
And that was when I heard the song of the
brave Goblin Slayer from the frontier.
What song?
You didn't know?
There's a song about you, Orcbolg.
It's sort of disappointing,
having actually met you, though.
That's not my problem.
You mustn't say that. Bards singing songs
of brave feats is how these tales survive.
Why do they need to survive?
Don't you get it, Beard-cutter?
The more the words of your
deeds spread throughout the land,
the more requests you'll get to slay goblins.
Kind sirs, I beg of you...
Will you save our town?
I don't know if I'll be able to save it,
but let's kill some goblins.
Goblin Slayer! Can't you say it a bit nicer?
It's the truth.
It's because it's the truth that you
should be more tactful with your words!
Sir Goblin Slayer, shall we
head to the sewers, then?
We're going to go in and wipe them out.
The underground is huge. It'd be annoying if one got away.
Remember, no using water, fire, or poison!
I know.
But why not just have the city guard or
the troops of this town take care of them?
I'll admit that I do not know
everything about this town,
but surely this couldn't be
out of their jurisdiction.
Well...
Were you told that there was no point in
mobilizing the military against mere goblins?
Yes.
Well, you can't really blame them.
They're in the middle of battling with
the armies of the Demon Lord, after all.
I guess that means goblin slaying
is a job for us adventurers.
I'll admit that human politics and money
issues seem rather troublesome.
I have no interest in that.
How can we get down there?
Hey.
Oh, yes. I do beg your pardon.
I believe your best option
is to go down the well
behind this temple, into the sewers.
Is this accurate?
Well, this is an old sketch from
when this temple was first built.
But the water flow indicated
here should be correct.
Even if there is erosion or damage,
it shouldn't be severe.
All right.
You get to navigate.
Understood.
Let's go. We don't have time to waste.
Well, I guess I wouldn't expect
you to be any other way, Orcbolg.
Miss.
Yes?
This may seem rude, as I am
the one who requested this...
but are you not frightened?
Well... Yes, I'm frightened, but...
I'm sure...
I'm sure that everything will be all right.
That should take care of things.
Yup.
And done.
To think that there were this many
goblins dwelling underneath the town...
It's about what I expected.
Just so you know, I'm not copying him.
This is going to be a long battle, right?
Unlike Orcbolg, I don't want
to use the goblins' arrows.
They're terribly made.
Are they?
They are!
But this is the fifth attack just today.
At this rate, who knows how many
goblins are actually down here?
Seriously, how long is this going to go on?
Don't worry. These walls are made of stone.
There shouldn't be any
surprise attacks through them.
Please don't remind me of
such a terrible memory.
Sorry.
With all the waste down here, you
probably don't need to mask your scent.
Please don't remind me of
such a terrible memory.
What is it, long-ears?
I just felt something weird.
The sound of water?
Is it coming from above?
It appears to be raining...
But is rain underground even possible?
It must be raining on the surface.
I'm sure all the water from the canals
and sewers flows down here.
What do you think, Beard-cutter?
We'll be at a disadvantage if
our light source is extinguished.
What's the matter, Goblin Slayer?
Be on your guard.
Something's coming this way.
Beard-cutter!
A boat...
...full of...
...goblins?!
O merciful Earth Mother,
please protect us, the weak,
with the powers of the earth.
Protection!
I can't hold this for long...
What do you want to do?
What else? The same as usual.
The goblins must die.
That's one.
Jeez... Just leave that to me, all right?
How many spells do you have left?
Plenty!
Then use Tunnel. Dig a hole.
Are you trying to destroy the town above us?!
Not up. Dig down.
Dig a hole in the channel
and let the water run down.
But that's going to back up the sewage!
But it's not water, fire, or poison.
Think of something else!
I can't hold this any longer!
Do you have another transfer
scroll like last time?
If I did, I would've brought it with me.
I'm going to throw this as
soon as Protection goes down.
Once I do, use Protection again
to strengthen our defense.
R-Right.
Just a moment, Sir Goblin Slayer.
O sickle wings of the velociraptor...
Slice, fly, and hunt!
I believe that might be to your liking.
Oh, but if possible, please don't throw it.
I'll do my best.
Just... a little longer...
We're jumping.
Five.
Fearsome dragon,
behold your descendant in battle!
Nine.
Ten.
They're wearing armor. It's easier
to just knock them off the boat.
Understood!
Sixteen.
But you know... there sure are a lot of them.
An elf's arrows hit their mark,
even when their eyes are closed!
Here you go.
Ugh. Such an unrefined arrow...
Protection!
Thanks!
I'll block the attacks from the rear guard,
so please continue your attacks.
You got it!
Time to work, you gnomes!
Roll bits of sand together,
and it shall become rock!
Beard-cutter! Scaly! Get back here!
Stone Blast!
Now... what's next?
For now, let's rest for a while.
No, we need to keep moving.
I agree. We did cause quite a ruckus.
The rain is masking some of the noise,
but the others may have realized we're here.
What's that?
Is it a goblin?
That's not a goblin.
Thanks for stating the obvious!
Run!
Who knew a swamp dragon would be down here?!
Swamp dragon... An alligator...
Scaly, isn't that a relative of yours?
Do something about him!
I'm afraid that I regrettably
have not kept in contact
with my relatives ever
since leaving my house!
Not to mention, I haven't a
relative who is so violent, Sir Mage!
Well, this sure beats walking!
Steady your breathing.
I-I'm fine...
You have one miracle left, don't you?
I can't have you fainting here.
Let's feed the dwarf to that thing and run!
It'll definitely get food poisoning!
Why, you little—
Something's coming from the front.
Another goblin ship... Actually,
there might be a number of them!
Wh-What should we do?
There is a way.
Hey! I don't know what you've thought
up, but no poison or burning!
We'll go with your idea.
O merciful Earth Mother, please bless us,
the wanderers in the
darkness, with holy light!
I get it. You cast Holy Light
on the swamp dragon's tail
and lured out the goblins.
Since I can't use poison, fire, or water,
this was all that was left, really.
But to think they'd be so easily
fooled by just some light.
They've learned that adventurers
travel around with light.
Oh, really?
I don't know when they learned it,
but they all seem to know it.
First of all, their kind only pillages.
They don't think of building
anything on their own.
Again, they're not bright creatures,
but they aren't complete fools.
They quickly learn how to use various tools.
If they're taught how to use boats,
they will quickly catch on.
Well, aren't you knowledgeable?
I did some research.
That's why I won't give them any more ideas.
I'll slaughter them all.
Which means... someone showed
them how to use boats?
Yeah.
But it's possible a goblin shaman
could have figured it out...
Could be.
But if they naturally increased
in numbers down here,
why didn't they... What was that thing again?
Um... the swamp dragon?
Yeah, that.
The goblins didn't know about that thing.
If they had, they wouldn't
have thought to use boats...
because they're cowards.
What are you suggesting, Sir Goblin Slayer?
The goblins down there
didn't multiply naturally.
Someone, or something,
is artificially causing all this.
Data viitoare
Înainte spre moarte