Cu mult, mult timp în urmă,
când erau mai puține stele pe cer...
Zeii luminii, ordinii și destinului
alături de zeii întunericului,
haosului și coincidenței
au hotărât să dea cu zarurile ca să
determine care parte va conduce lumea.
Zeii au aruncat zarurile iar, iar și iar,
până când începuseră să se simtă slăbiți.
Legate de mine
Visurile mele de adolescentă
Mă trag și mă târăsc în adâncuri
Întregul corp mi-e expus
Însemnat de umbrele tale
Întărește-te și amorțește-ți simțurile
Porcii nu merită corectitudine
Râsete deasupra ta
Și zâmbete jucăușe
Moartea este aruncată
Înecat în tristețe
Viitorul meu este clădit pe trupul tău
Ucide-i pe toți din specia ta
Ca să revendici ce este al meu de drept
De fiecare dată când vom intra
Vom fi primii care vor reuși
Ca să revendici ce este al meu de drept
Ultima temniță
Un viitor plin de regrete
Am un motiv
Nu despărți râurile
Încojoară-i, taie-le capul
Botează-mi cauza
Fii primul care observă
Ultima temniță, plină de monștri și lipsită de speranță
Mă ascund printre voi
Înăbușindu-mi focul interior
La noapte voi visa cuvintele unui vis la malul mării
Vizitatori neașteptați
Hei, privește-o pe tipa aia frumoasă de acolo!
Hei.
Oh, scuze.
Este un elf de rang înalt. Ei sunt
descendenții de sânge ai zânelor.
Chiar are urechile mai lungi ca ceilalți elfi...
Te-am întrebat de Orcbolg.
Oak... Adică stejar?
Nu. Orc. Orcbolg. Am auzit că este aici.
Te referi cumva la un aventurier?
Prostuțo.
Suntem în ținutul oamenilor.
Nu-ți vor înțelege vorbele
tale stranii, urechi lungi.
Atunci, cum ar trebui să-i spun?
Tăietorul de Bărbi, desigur!
Păi... Mi-e teamă că nu am
auzit de niciunul din ei...
Serios?
Voi piticii sunteți inutili. Sunteți
încăpățânați și înguști la minte.
Mereu credeți că sunteți
cei care aveți dreptate.
Tu vorbești, elfule?
Pieptul ți-e la fel de plat
precum ți-e inima de mică.
Ce—
Dacă tot suntem la acest capitol,
femeile pitici arată ca niște butoaie!
Vrei să spui că sunt voluptoase!
Păi... Ei bine...
Scuzați-mă, voi doi,
dar dacă vreți să vă certați, puteți s-o
faceți undeva unde să nu vă văd?
Îmi cer scuze pentru zarva
provocată de cei doi.
O, este în regulă. Sunt obișnuită...
Dar ce grup ciudat.
Un elf de rang înalt care călătorește cu inamicul ei străvechi, un pitic...
Un om-șopârlă, o rasă
pe care o vezi foarte rar.
Să nu mai spun că sunt cu toții rang argint.
You see, we're looking for a fellow whose
nicknames are "Orcbolg" and "Beard-cutter."
I'm also not well-versed
in the human tongue, but...
Înseamnă "ucigașul de goblini".
Oh! Goblini...
Hei, tu!
Am terminat.
Bine ai revenit, Ucigașule de Goblini!
Huh?
We've returned.
I'm glad you're safe.
Yes, somewhat.
You just mentioned goblins. Where are they?
Well... You should ask them.
Are you goblins?
Of course not! Are you Orcbolg?
You don't look it.
Why would I? I've never been called that.
There's something we'd like to
discuss with you, Sir Goblin Slayer.
May we have a moment of your time?
Fine.
If you'd like, there are some
meeting rooms upstairs...
Then let's go.
U-Um, sh-should I...
You should rest.
We'll just borrow him for a bit, okay?
Hey.
Yes?
You're porcelain-ranked, too, right?
Why don't you join us?
No... I appreciate the offer,
but I already have—
The guy who never takes
off his helmet, right?
We know.
There's something off about him, though.
He's silver-ranked, but all
he ever does is slay goblins.
Silvers would usually go
for bigger prey than that.
I've heard rumors that he's just dragging
newbies around to use them as bait.
That's not—
Now, now...
You shouldn't... talk nonsense...
Nonsense? But we weren't—
It's all right...
Leave the rest to me, okay?
Well... then...
You are... the girl...
traveling with him... right?
Y-Yes, ma'am. He's letting me accompany him.
Accompany... eh?
He's...
a handful... right?
He's quite dense.
Right?
Inflammarae.
A truly powerful word...
and I'm wasting a spell... right?
You see...
he also asked a strange favor of
me once... that friend of yours.
What?
You just imagined something
naughty... didn't you?
N-No...
He wanted some help with a scroll.
It's difficult... accompanying him... isn't it?
It's taking everything I have
just to keep up with him.
All I do is cause him trouble.
No to mention... he's a bit crazy... right?
I mean...
He might only slay goblins...
but he's been doing that for years
with barely any rest... you see?
He is definitely helping out in the world...
Much more than other unskilled
monster slayers...
But that being said,
one shouldn't just keep slaying... goblins.
There are many demons in the capital,
and the world is filled with monsters.
If you wanted to help people...
you could do so with those two you
were talking to... couldn't you?
Well... Yes, you're right, but...
I'm sorry.
There are many paths... right?
There is no... right answer.
It's difficult.
If you are going to accompany him,
you should really make up your own mind.
Make up my own mind...
Are you truly a silver rank?
The guild thinks so.
Unbelievable.
You look so weak.
Don't be a fool, long-ears.
That leather armor is easier to move in,
and the chain mail would
stop a sudden stabbing.
That goes for the helmet, too,
His sword and shield are tiny,
but easier to wave around in tight spaces.
Shouldn't you at least
keep your equipment clean?
It's a necessary precaution
to cover the metal smell.
Those bastards have keen noses.
You may be a high elf, but you're
still an inexperienced whelp who
just left the forest because she was bored.
You really ought to learn from your elders.
I'm 2,000 years old.
How old were you again?
One hundred and seven...
My, my, you definitely look much older.
You at least look old enough to be wise.
That's enough talk about age.
It shames those of us who
won't live nearly so long.
What's your business with me?
I'm sure you've heard about the growing
number of demons in the capital...
Nope.
The reason for it is that the
demon king has been resurrected.
He's gathering forces so
he can take over the world.
I see.
And that's why we want your—
Ask someone else. I have no
interest in anything but goblins.
Don't you understand what I'm saying?!
Hordes of demons are going to attack!
Do you realize that the
world is at stake here?!
Yes.
But before the demons destroy the world,
the goblins will destroy the villages.
The world being in danger isn't
an excuse to let the goblins live.
Listen here—
Hold it, long-ears!
We didn't come here to ask him to do
something about the chaos to begin with.
Sir Goblin Slayer, we've come
to ask you to slay some goblins.
I see. In that case, I accept.
Where are they? How many are there?
How big is their nest?
Have you confirmed if they
have a shaman or a hob?
What's with this guy?
As my companion mentioned...
a horde of demons are
ready to make their move.
So the chieftains of my kind,
the kings of men,
and the elders of the elves and
dwarves are going to hold a meeting.
We're adventurers who've been
hired as their representatives.
There's eventually going
to be a great battle...
Though I'm sure you don't care.
The problem is, those goblins are currently
becoming more active on elven lands.
Have any champions or lords emerged?
Champions? Lords?
Goblin heroes or kings.
They're basically equal to
platinum-ranked adventurers.
We have found one giant
nest during our investigations.
The military won't move for goblins, as usual.
The human kings don't see us as equals.
If we brought our soldiers into this,
they'd think we were plotting something.
That's why they sent us adventurers,
but we still need a human.
And that's why, Orcbolg, we've chosen you.
Do you have a map?
Right here.
Ruins?
We believe so.
How many?
We only know that there are many.
I'll leave immediately.
Huh?
You can decide how much you want to pay me.
Is he planning to go alone?
Miss Receptionist!
Goblins.
Oh, Goblin Slayer.
So they did come to offer you a quest.
That lizardman will give you the
details of the quest. I'm heading out.
Give me my pay for that last quest.
But you haven't made your report yet...
I'll make an exception for you, though.
Who does he think he is?
Come, now... No pouting.
Give the rest to her.
Oh, are you going alone?
What about her?
I'm going to let her rest.
Goblin Slayer!
U-Um, you received a quest, right?
Yes. Slaying goblins.
Then I'll get ready immediately!
No.
I'll go on my own.
That's not fair!
You could've...
discussed it with me, at least...
I am now.
Oh... So this is a discussion?
That was my intention.
Not giving the other person a choice
doesn't really qualify as a discussion.
It doesn't?
I'm going with you.
I can't leave you alone.
Do as you wish.
Indeed, I will.
Even we're not that hard to read.
I look forward to seeing what
that young'un does next.
If I were to put in the quest
and not go with him,
I wouldn't be able to face my ancestors.
A strange and incomprehensible being, huh?
I left the forest to see something like that.
Honestly... Don't you think you
ought to respect your elders?
So why did you all become adventurers?
Why, to eat all the delicious
foods, of course.
They're ready.
What about you, long-ears?
I've always longed for the outside world—
This is delicious!
Hey, listen to me!
I'm glad you find it to your liking.
What kind of meat is this?
That is the meat of a swamp creature.
Swamp? Really?
A rabbit like you who only eats vegetables
could never understand this bliss.
So good!
Would you like some soup?
I'd love some.
It has such a gentle taste!
I seek to raise my status by rooting out
heresy so that I may become a dragon.
That's the reason I became an adventurer.
I-I see...
So I could slay...
Yeah, I think we can figure out your reason.
I'll have to give you something in return.
These are elven traveling rations.
We're not supposed to give them to others,
but this is a special occasion.
It's delicious!
Really? Glad you like it.
Now I guess I'll have to offer something, too.
Our cherished dwarven fire
wine created in our cellars.
Fire... wine?
You aren't suggesting you're a
child who's never had wine before,
are you, long-ears?
D-Don't mock me! Of course I have.
A-Are you all right?
Would you like some water?
Go on, Beard-cutter. Have some.
Not bad, kid.
Why don't you at least take off
your helmet when you're eating?
So I don't get knocked unconscious
in the event of an ambush.
Yeah, she's out of it.
Quit eating and share
something of yours with us!
He's lost in thought.
You can tell?
Will this do?
What is it?
Cheese.
It's made from fermented cow
or goat's milk, then hardened.
You've never heard of cheese before, Scaly?
My people hunt beasts.
We do not raise them.
Gimme! I'll cut it up.
This is some fine cheese!
Nectar!
This is surely the nectar of the gods!
Goes great with the wine.
It's so sweet! It's almost like a banana!
Is this from that farm?
It is.
It's delicious.
Good.
Sneak...
Don't touch that.
It's dangerous.
I-I just wanted a peek...
Don't. It's dangerous.
That's a scroll, right?
I've never seen one before.
Scrolls contain ancient magic
that is now lost to us.
Once you unroll one, even a child
could use the spell within.
Indeed.
But it could be any one of many spells,
and it can be only used once.
Most people would just
sell them off as antiques
to a collector or researcher at a high price.
He wanted some help with a scroll.
Then at least tell me what kind
of spell you've got in there.
No.
What if the goblins capture you
and you tell them what's in it?
You don't like me, do you?
I'm not particular.
It's no use, long-ears.
He's far more narrow-minded than any of us.
He's Beard-cutter, after all.
He's Orcbolg, after all.
He's Sir Goblin Slayer, after all.
Oh, jeez...
I'm Goblin Slayer.
Hey!
There's one thing that's been on my mind...
Where do the goblins come from?
I was taught that they came
from an underground kingdom.
We're taught that when someone makes
a mistake, a goblin is formed.
What's that supposed to mean?
Folks say it to keep children in line.
Children are told that if they make
a mistake, goblins will come.
That's awful!
That means if we'd left long-ears to her own
devices, we'd be neck-deep in them now!
How rude!
Tomorrow, I'll show you just
how skilled I am with my bow!
Ooh, how scary. I'm terrified.
I heard...
I heard they came from the moon.
Moon? You mean the two in the sky?
Yes.
The green one.
The goblins come from that green rock.
Does that mean shooting stars are goblins?
I'm not sure, but the moon has
no grass, trees, or water.
It's a desolate place with only rocks.
It makes them envious and jealous,
and makes them want what they don't have.
That's why they come here.
Which is why, if you ever feel envious
of someone, you become like a goblin.
Who did you hear that from?
My older sister.
You have an older sister?
Yes... I did.
So you believe that goblins
come from the moon.
If nothing else...
I know my sister never made mistakes.
He fell asleep.
Looks like the fire wine finally kicked in.
Well, he did have plenty of it.
We should also sleep.
If we don't get enough rest,
that could very well lead to mistakes.
The lookout will be who we agreed upon.
Head on back. Time to go home.
He didn't come back again today...
Whatever you do, don't miss.
Hush.
Where in the world are you aiming?!
Let's go.
Măsura talentului tău decide
această lume crudă și instabilă
Folosind aceste mâini micuțe oferite de Dumnezeu
Toate urmele au fost șterse,
iar eu nu ți-am putut proteja zâmbetul
Poveștile mărețe despre eroi adorați
se dovedesc cu tristețe a fi numai minciuni
Rugăciunile sunt doar niște monștri
Mă voi zbate până îmi voi da ultima suflare
De ce?
Lacrimile mele încăpățânate se agață de mine
și refuză să fie șterse
Dă-mi-le înapoi,
dă-mi-le înapoi,
promisiunile mele de mult uitate
și viitorul care mi-a fost furat
Doar țiuitul continuu din capul meu
îmi străpunge conștiința distrusă
Data viitoare
Cel puternic