Long, long ago, when there were
fewer stars shining in the sky...
The gods got tired of playing with dice,
so they created all sorts of beings
as well as worlds for them to live in.
Humans and elves...
Dwarves and lizardmen...
They went on adventures
where they sometimes won,
but sometimes lost and died...
Amazing.
Splendid. Is this some form of magic?
It's hard to tell the difference
between mastered technique and magic.
You're really saying that in front of me?
One... two...
H-Hey, what are you doing?
They're highly sensitive to smells.
Huh?
Especially the smells of
women, children, and elves.
N-No way! Somebody stop him!
You get used to it.
Cel puternic
I wonder... Is this a shrine?
Apparently there was a war
here during the age of gods.
It might be a fortress or something from then.
Regardless, it appears to be man-made...
After the soldiers left,
the goblins called it home.
What a cruel fate.
Speaking of cruel...
This is so gross!
Um... It does wash off... somewhat.
You'd better remember this when we get back!
I will.
I'm used to being underground,
but somehow being down here just feels wrong.
Looks like it's a spiral.
Perhaps it's like a tower.
Wait.
What's wrong?
An alarm?
I think so.
I spotted it because it's brand new, but...
Those conniving little goblins...
This is strange.
What is it?
I don't see any totems.
Um, that means there
aren't any goblin shamans.
Hey, it'll be easier for us if
there aren't any spellcasters.
Actually, it seems the absence of shamans
is precisely what concerns him.
Correct. Ordinary goblins wouldn't
be able to set traps like this.
You're saying they have someone leading them?
We should assume as much.
I've heard that you've destroyed large
nests in the past, Sir Goblin Slayer.
How did you do so?
Smoke them out,
then crush them individually...
Set them on fire,
drown them in the river...
There are many methods,
but those won't work here.
Can you see their tracks?
Maybe if we were in a cave,
but on a stone floor like this...
Let's see...
Their hideout is to the left.
How can you tell?
The wear on the floor.
They either come from the left
and go right, then go back,
or they come from the left and go outside.
What is it, Sir Goblin Slayer?
Let's go this way.
But aren't the goblins on the left?
Yes... But it'll be too late.
What an awful smell...
Breathe through your nose.
You'll get used to it.
What is this place?
The goblins' waste heap.
Waste?!
What in the world?
Sir Goblin Slayer...
...ill... Kill...
She's still alive!
Use a miracle! Hurry!
Right!
Goblin Slayer!
Kill...
I understand.
W-Wait! She's still—
Stop!
Kill... this thing!
Three.
I don't know what you're all thinking,
but I only came here to slay goblins.
Kill... all of them.
Of course.
O horns and claws of the father, Iguanodon,
be four limbs and walk upon
this earth with two legs...
A miracle from my ancestors...
A dragontooth warrior.
I wrote a letter and explained everything.
I'm counting on you.
My dragontooth warrior should be able to
deliver her to the Elves' Forest safely.
What the hell is going on?!
I don't understand...
It's here, as I thought.
What is that?
A map of the ruins. I found it in a rucksack.
That elf must've been using it.
There's a gallery on the left.
Seems the left was the correct path.
You didn't believe me?
I did, but the more information
we have, the better.
You take it.
Let's go.
Hey! You don't have to say it like that!
It's fine.
We have to get going, don't we?
Yes.
The goblins must be slain.
How many spells do we have left?
I just used Heal, so that leaves two.
I have about three,
but the dragontooth warrior
requires these catalysts.
I can only use this spell once more.
As for myself... I'd say about four or five.
I see.
Would you like some?
Thanks.
Don't overfill your stomach.
It'll slow your blood flow,
dulling your movements.
Goblin Slayer! Can't you be more—
There's no need to act tough.
If you can come, come.
If you can't, head back.
It's as simple as that.
Don't be ridiculous.
I'm a ranger.
Who's going to find all the traps
and do the scouting if I go back?
We'll just make do with those we do have.
Ugh, you're so... There's no way I can go back!
After what they did to that elf...
And my home isn't far from here, either...
I see.
Then let's go.
Calm down, long-ears.
We shouldn't cause a
commotion on enemy ground.
Dwarves consider goblins
mortal enemies, as well.
We'll make them pay for what they did to her.
I hate taking advice from
dwarves, but you're right.
I'm sorry.
Looks like you're back on your feet.
Well?
It's just as it looks.
There are quite few.
Not a problem.
What?
Sir Goblin Slayer, do you have a plan?
I do.
Drink and sing, spirits!
Sing, dance, and sleep like a log!
Show me dreams of fire wine!
O merciful Earth Mother,
grant us the peace to accept all things.
Stupor and Silence...
By combining those two spells,
they'll all fall asleep without making
a sound or causing a commotion.
And then the three of us
will slay them, one by one.
They're slick with blood...
I see... He's using their weapons...
He... had been doing this all by himself?
An ogre!
I thought those goblins were awfully quiet.
They don't even make good foot soldiers.
You people aren't like that elf from before.
You dare set foot in our fortress?
Oh... So you're not a goblin?
That's an ogre! An ogre!
Haven't you heard of them before?
Nope.
You!
Are you mocking me, the one granted this
army by one of the Demon Lord's generals?
I knew there were more powerful beings,
but I've never heard of you
or these Demon Lord generals.
Then I'll just have to show
you my power firsthand.
Carbunculus... Crescunt!
A fireball's coming!
Scatter!
Look at the size of that thing!
Where can we go?!
O merciful Earth Mother,
please protect us, the weak,
with the powers of the earth.
Iacta!
Protection!
O... merciful Earth Mother,
please protect us, the weak,
with the powers of the earth.
Protection!
You saved us.
Leave the rest to us!
Foolish little girl.
Don't think you'll have it
as easy as that elf did!
Create a dragontooth warrior.
There aren't enough of us.
As you wish, Sir Goblin Slayer.
O horns and claws of Father Iguanodon,
be four limbs and walk upon
this earth with two legs...
O sickle wings of the velociraptor...
Slice, fly, and hunt!
I request backup!
You got it!
Time to work, you gnomes!
Roll grains of sand together,
and it shall become rock!
You measly little dwarf!
You damn dwarves are too slow!
We have our own way of fighting!
Stone Blast!
Did you really think you could defeat
me with that stone magic trick of yours?
Now, Sir Goblin Slayer!
Impudent fool!
Orcbolg!
Goblin Slayer!
Don't mistake me for a mere goblin!
You shall pay dearly for this humiliation.
First, I will shatter your limbs,
and make sport of these
females in front of you.
You shall not have your way, ogre!
I'm counting on you, Lady Priestess!
Goblin Slayer! Goblin Slayer!
Out of my way, you swamp lizard!
Sir Mage! Lady Ranger!
Hurry up with that spell, dwarf!
I know, I know!
You insolent little insect!
Stop your incessant buzzing!
This is nothing!
Stone Blast!
You puny insects!
Goblin Slayer!
I can't... see well.
What's... happening?
Everyone's still fighting.
I see.
I need a healing potion and a stamina potion.
Right!
Thanks.
Here you go.
Let's do this.
Where's my bag?
It's right here...
Thanks.
All right.
Don't be reckless!
I'll be reckless if it means I'll win...
But if that always worked,
this wouldn't be so difficult.
Orcbolg!
I have a plan.
All right... Go for it!
All right, Beard-cutter.
I'm putting my faith in you.
Things are indeed getting a bit difficult.
I see that the human girl has
used up all her miracles.
Carbunculus... Crescunt...
Fear not.
If she manages to survive, I'll let her live.
I'll use her as either food or a plaything.
I need more goblins now, after all.
Iacta!
You fool.
What... What did you do?
This is a gate scroll. I linked
it to the bottom of the sea.
The bottom of the sea?
Then that was seawater?
The water under the most
pressure at the sea floor
must've been swiftly unleashed, like a blade.
But to think it was a scroll
used for transfers...
It allows you to escape from
anywhere in an instant.
It serves as a lifeline for adventurers.
And yet he used it as a
last resort in battle...
You see...
he also asked a strange favor of
me once... that friend of yours.
I was going to use that
scroll to destroy a nest,
but this is fine.
Now, then... What were you called again?
I guess it doesn't matter now.
Goblins?!
You would use this to kill mere goblins?
Goblins...
are far more troublesome than you.
Thank you.
We received your letter and
arrived as soon as we could.
How many more goblins are insi—
Well, anyway, we're going to go scout inside.
Please rest until you get to the town.
Hey.
What is it?
Does he always do stuff like that?
Yes.
He's always like that.
I see.
But despite how it seems,
he's quite aware of his surroundings.
He isn't obligated to
teach me so many things.
I see.
Guess we should sleep.
Yes.
Yeah, I still don't like Orcbolg.
I mean, adventures are supposed to be fun.
The joy of experiencing the unknown
and discovering new things...
Feeling elated or accomplished...
That's what my adventures are like.
This is no adventure.
Someday, I'll take you
on an actual adventure.
Welcome home.
Data viitoare
Aventuri și viața de zi cu zi