Tsurayuki! Ce naiba ai făcut?!
Îmi pare rău, bine?
Îmi era foame și nu era nimic altceva care să arate bine.
How's that make it okay
to eat other people's stuff?!
Serios, chiar îmi pare rău!
De asta ți-am luat în schimb niște Sukiyamon! Vezi?
Sukiyamon
cu sos de soia
E cu sos de soia!
Umakatoyo
Umakatoyo is tonkotsu-flavored!
They ain't the same thing!
I don't get the big deal.
They're both instant ramen.
Starting this spring,
along with enrolling in art school,
They can be the same kinda food,
but that don't make them the same food!
I've started living in this share house
with some of my classmates.
In general terms, they're the same thing!
Are not!
It's two guys and two girls, which you think
would be the ideal roommate setup, and yet...
They are!
I want mine back!
Too bad!
I heard the whole argument!
Tsurayuki, seriously,
eating someone else's food
is the one of the worst
things a roommate can do!
What's wrong? Why'd everyone go so quiet?
Uh, well, Nanako... Your clothes...
My clothes?
Quit looking!
I forgot I was in the middle of changing!
Hell of a puncher, isn't she?
For whatever reason, I ended up traveling
ten years into the past
with my memories intact.
Do not eat other people's food!
It's what you might call a "time leap."
My second attempt attempt
at college has so far been colored
with instant ramen's flavor and
painful hits to the solar plexus,
along with hope and anxiety.
It won't be long before
we start creating for real.
I can't help but wonder what awaits us.
Comprehensive Exercise
Direction
Technicals
Performance
Production
When it comes to filmmaking,
these four areas are going to be crucial.
I want you to form groups of four,
with each person handling one area.
The project is to be three minutes long.
And I mean that seriously,
because once you've all turned
in your shorts, we'll be screening them.
Everyone's gonna see?
Better make sure it turns out good!
Finally, regarding the theme of the
short films I want you all to make...
"Time" is kinda broad as far as themes go.
So broad it's hard to know
where to drill down.
Yeah.
And there's a three-minute
limit on our runtime, too.
That teacher isn't trying to make this easy!
It's a good thing we were able to
pick out our team so quickly, though.
Team Kitayama, featuring the roommates
from Share House Kitayama...
Kinda on the nose, huh?
You're directing. Shinoaki's handling
the technical side.
Nanako's performing, and I'm production...
Well, I wanna do the script, but don't care
about the performance side of things.
I'm counting on you, Kyoya!
I didn't think we'd end up
at the same part time job, too.
Tell me about it.
The manager gave me a funny look
when he noticed we had the same
address on our applications.
What do you mean?
Forget about it.
Here, hand that over. I'll put it on this shelf.
Say, Nanako...
Why'd you enroll in art school?
Is there something you want to do?
There wasn't any real reason.
Maybe because I was sick of Lake Biwa?
The big lake from where you live?
Yeah.
When I was in grade school,
I used to think it was the ocean.
L-Listen, it's seriously huge!
You would've thought it was
the ocean at that age, too!
Anyway, there's really nothing else to it...
I mean, there are towns and stores,
and you can find most things
you need there.
But I think if I had never left home,
I would've never learned
what the ocean was really like.
The idea of time just passing by
in a place like that scared me.
And before I knew it, here I was.
It's embarrassing to admit, but it's
kind of like I'm here to find myself.
I think I get what you mean.
The doors are closing. Please stand clear.
Are you here for a similar reason?
Yeah.
What is it?
Let me.
This goes up here.
Wait, Nanako...
Aw, it got caught on something.
Sorry, gimme one second...
Just one?
Uh, never mind.
Almost done...
I might be trying to act like I did
when I was younger,
but I'm still 28 mentally.
Say, Nanako...
Uh... thank you.
No sweat.
Come on. Let's finish up.
I'm sure I don't need to explain how
I was in no hurry to finish up.
Get those hands moving, Kyoya.
Application
Team Name: Team Kitayama
Members
Direction: Tsurayuki Rokuonji
Production: Hashiba Kyoya
Technicals: Shino Aki
Performance: Nanako
Description:
You're going to fill this in, later, then?
Right. We're still not sure
what we're doing.
There's no telling when inspiration
will strike, after all.
Make sure to keep your antennae up.
Right...
Has anything interesting happened
lately that you could use?
Lately?
Well, it sure looks like something has.
You have no idea.
Uh, no, nothing really!
I-If you'll excuse me!
We'd better figure this out soon.
I'm home...
Shinoaki, you'll catch a cold.
Can't eat another bite...
Come on. Time to finish eating.
Important
Part
Good morning, Kyoya-kun.
That was a real nice dream.
I had a bunch of Itoshima oysters to eat.
Sorry to interrupt your meal.
Come to think of it, Shinoaki,
why'd you enroll in art school?
I can't do anything,
so I wanted to find something I could do.
That's how I ended up here.
That's why you choose art school?
Yeah.
I've never been real good at studying,
even in elementary school.
I'd even miss the train a lot.
I can imagine that.
Since it was in the country, missing the
train meant waiting for a whole half hour.
The folks from the station
even got to know me.
What's wrong?
I think I have an idea
that goes with our theme!
I'm thinking of having the short
take place at a train station.
Why a train station?
Since it's the type of place
everyone is familiar with,
there's a lot of obvious shorthand
that'll help people understand the setting.
And I think it'd be well-suited to a story
that wraps up in three minutes.
You've got a point!
Everybody uses the train.
Station
And since stations tend to stay intact
for long periods of time,
they work well for depicting
the passage of time.
My idea is to use that to depict
the life of one woman
over the course of three minutes.
And I thought it might be good to have her
life progress in tune with the time of day.
What do you think?
Sounds interesting! I think it'll work.
I like it, too.
I can't wait to see it screened!
What do you think, Tsurayuki?
Can I get a half-hour?
I wonder what that's about.
I dunno.
What's this?
I wrote up a plot for the
setup you described.
I figured it was what you were after.
Wow! This is exactly what I meant!
You're really something, Tsurayuki-kun!
You were able to come up
with something so quick!
That's better than
I figured you could manage!
Well, I didn't come up with the idea myself,
so I figured I should do this much.
That settles it, then!
No objections!
Yeah, I'm looking forward to the script—
Kyoya...
You got a second?
What is it, Tsurayuki?
What's this?
Something from my idea notebook.
Isn't this—
It's the exact same thing.
Your idea, and what I had
written down in my notes.
I swear, I didn't see—
Yeah, I know.
I actually had it locked up.
You couldn't possibly have seen it.
But you still managed to come up
with the same idea,
like you read my mind.
It honestly felt like you took
something right out of my head.
Which is why I rushed
to write down the outline.
I didn't mean to.
It was scary, man, if I'm being honest.
Come to think of it, how exactly
did I come up with that idea?
I remember now... It was from
a collection of short stories.
A story about a woman's life, depicted against
the background of a train station.
I think the impression it left me with
is what had me imagine something similar.
And I didn't read that book
until some point in the future.
Does that mean I essentially stole the idea
from Tsurayuki's future self?
Kyoya, is it just a coincidence?
Or is there something else going on here?
Well, Kyoya? Which one is it?
Yeah, it couldn't be...
Sorry about that.
It has to be a coincidence.
It's not out of the question
for different people to have the same idea.
You've got a point.
I've gotta be honest, I was kind of glad.
Why?
A train station makes for an easy setting,
both in terms of the possibility space
for characters' behavior,
and the things that can happen to them.
That's something that you pick up
from learning about screenwriting.
But if anybody here at school
realized that, I sure didn't notice.
Which is why I was thinking about just
doing the bare minimum for the project,
and focusing on my individual studies.
But I get the feeling we could make
something good together, Kyoya.
Let's give the teachers
a real shock with our project!
Yeah!
The girl_
What do you mean, you want to make some cuts?!
As things stand, we're going to
end up going over three  minutes,
so I was hoping you could
rewrite the script.
I submitted the script we have
after already rewriting it a bunch,
because I thought it was
the best version of that story!
There's nothing in it
that can be cut for time!
Still...
Shinoaki, you can adjust the storyboards
to make sure everything fits, right?
Let me think...
It should be doable, but...
And if we pick up the pace with your lines,
we can cram them in within
the time limit, right?
Can we, though?
I mean, I'd have to try...
That's what I'm talking about!
We should at least try first!
Right?
There's a hard time limit
on this assignment.
No matter how good the short turns out,
if we go past that limit,
we'll be worse off for it.
But is that good enough a reason
to convince Tsurayuki?
Right now, this is probably
the best I can do.
It's an assignment, after all, so we need
to follow the rules if we want the credit.
So...
Okay. Fine. I'll make the cuts.
Tsurayuki...
Is this your approach when it comes
to making something good, Kyoya?
Talk about lame.
Tsurayuki is such a perfectionist!
If it's running long, we should
just make the cuts!
Don't let it bug you too much.
You there, the young lady stepping on me...
I'm going to refrain from the impulse
to savor this sensation,
and ask for your help instead.
If you have any sympathy for your senpai,
who's run out of money from home,
and is slowly starving to death...
Fine Art Study Group
Is this the place?
Y-Yes, thank you.
This is a huge relief.
It looks like I was able to make it back,
thanks to the three of you.
And now, freshmen—
You're ours!
Nice one, Prez!
Looks like we can avert
a third year of budget cuts!
We'll be able to survive another year!
I am seriously so sorry!
Sorry about the whole snare.
It's not a big deal, so please, stop bowing!
So, you're going to join the club, right?!
That is a different matter altogether.
It's no use after all.
Please! We're going to be
in real trouble without new members.
Could we at least get permission
to use your name?
Please, Hashy?!
Please don't come up
with weird nicknames for me!
I don't really have time
for a circle, anyway.
I'm thinking about joining.
Yeah, me too, as long as it's
for a trial period.
Seriously?
Hooray! Hooray!
Hooray!
I...
Fine Art Study Group
Now Recruiting Members
I'm Kiryu Takashi, in my fifth year
of the photography program.
If you have any questions
about taking pictures, I'm your man.
I'll make time.
Location Release Form
Hashiba Kyoya...
Oh, chief...
Er, Kawasegawa-san.
Is your team going to be filming
at the station, too?
Oh... yeah. Yours, too?
You're not going to outdo us.
No matter what
you're putting together,
my team intends to get
the highest marks.
O...kay.
Don't think we're competing
at the same level.
Because we're not.
We're trying to make something good—
Then let me ask you...
What's the concept of your short?
What's the most important element of it?
How are you going to use
the three-minute runtime?
You're handling production,
so you should have some idea, right?
Well...
Don't underestimate filmmaking.
Here's the location release form.
Have a seat, and I'll see about
getting that stamped for you.
Let's see...
Sorry about—
Production's always got something
to worry about, huh?
I heard your group's got
some creative differences.
Well, uh... Yes.
What's this?
The script of a movie
that came out the other day.
It's had great reception, and seems likely
to win a few some awards.
But no one seems to like the actual movie.
The director and cast probably
did whatever they wanted.
The runtime ended up too long,
ruining the tempo,
and wasting the strengths of the story.
This really is hard, isn't it?
A script isn't a finished product.
If the point was to just have
people read something, and that's all,
it'd be better done as prose.
At the script stage,
it can still go either way.
What you're doing isn't just
a matter of subtraction.
If the production side stops trying,
then that means the whole project is doomed.
That's how important it is.
You're handling production,
so you should have some idea, right?
Don't underestimate filmmaking.
I've got one piece of advice for you.
Everyone involved in the
filmmaking process is a creator.
And no one outranks anyone else.
Thank you so much!
Whether it's ten years in the past
or the future, time is limited either way.
Why didn't I realize that sooner?
I have to make sure I have no regrets,
or nothing will change at all!
Tsurayuki! Tsurayuki!
What? What is it?
I'm sorry, Tsurayuki!
What brought this on?!
What? What's up?
What's going on?
I want to talk this over again!
So please, can we make some time for it?
It's already decided. Just do what you want.
That's not true! We haven't
even gotten started yet!
You're right, Tsurayuki!
We haven't filmed anything,
or started an edit yet,
so it's too soon to give up!
Kyoya...
I want to talk this through as much
as we can, until the last minute,
so we can decide what we can do
that'll have the best result!
We'll worry about time later!
If you insist... I'm in, then.
Yeah! Let's do this!
Great weather today.
We picked a day where it was
supposed to be clear.
There was planning involved.
It was hard work getting everything
to fit into three minutes too, y'know?
Thank you.
Let's make this good.
Yeah!
Oh... This is...
What is it?
The camera that Tsurayuki-kun
borrowed isn't a video camera.
No, that can't be...
O Digital Single Lens Reflex Camera
Digital Video Camera
I marked the wrong one.
Why not just go get the right one?
We can't. It'd take too long.
Oh, no...
I'm sorry... I can't believe
it turned out like this...
Hey, everyone makes mistakes.
Not much we can do.
Yeah. There's nothing we can do.
Is there... nothing?
If there's no camera, then we can't film.
If there's no actors, we can't record a performance.
If there's no key art, we don't need to draw anything.
If the writer is missing, we shouldn't bother writing anything.
If there's not enough budget, we'll throw something together.
It is what it is. Nothing we can do about it.
It can't be helped.
Didn't I spend my life ten years in the future
repeating that excuse,
and regretting it every time?
And now, when I've got
the chance to do it all over...
Am I going to just do it again?
Make excuses... and kick it all down the road,
without actually achieving anything?
Put a hold on everything for ten years,
and see how that turns out?
No!
We are not out of options!
We're going to figure something out, damn it!