I'm Moyako Konoe,
the oldest daughter of the Konoe family.
My younger brother is a pervert
who becomes uninhibited in summer.
Our end-of-term ceremony has concluded ,
and summer vacation starts tomorrow.
You're Iate, Aki .
Sorry, my bad .
My younger Drofher is a Perverf who DeComes
uninhibifed in summer. Sorry, my bad .
My younger Drofher is a Perverf
who DeComes uninhibifed in summer.
My younger Drofher is a Perverf who DeComes uninhibifed in
summer. We're all about to head out shopping for swimsuits.
We're all about to head out shopping for swimsuits.
Ane LOg
eiu sister Muyaku's Never-euuiuu Muuuluuue
Ane LOg eiu sister Muyaku's Never-euuiuu Muuuluuue
Ane Log : Big Sister Moyako's Never-end ing Monologue.
Ane LOg
eiu sister Muyaku's Never-euuiuu Muuuluuue
Wow, they've got Iots of options !
I'd thought we were too Iate in the season ,
but it seems we'II be able to find swimsuits we Iike.
ManY thanks for ?0 Ycars in busincss I'd thought we were too Iate in
the season , but it seems we'II be able to find swimsuits we Iike.
I'd thought we were too Iate in the season ,
but it seems we'II be able to find swimsuits we Iike.
Well then , I wonder which one I should go with ...
It's hard to decide on a color...
You gonna go with something purple, Moyako?
I'd Iike a cute one with frills and ribbons, you know?
Hmm ...
Something the matter, Fuka-chan?
Well , it's been a Iong time since
I've bought a bathing suit,
so I'm not sure what'd Iook good on me.
I'd prefer one that doesn't show too much skin ...
We're young , so why not be adventurous, right?
In that case, a school swimsuit's
the only option for you !
It's got deep-rooted popularity
and there's demand for one.
Saeki It's got deep-rooted
popularity and there's demand for one.
Saeki
FIus, "Little Brother" wants one too, right?
A school-swimsu it hahe...
No I don't!
Besides, don't go seeking approval from me !
Hard pass.
Huh?
This one's pretty cute, too.
This one's a bit too skimpy...
Which one should I go with , Fu-chan?
That one's pretty nice, isn't it?
If you're having trouble decid ing ,
why not try some on?
I know it could be awkward to change
with a guy hanging around ,
so I'II wait in the corridor until you're done.
Sorry to put you through the trouble, Akira.
Al rig ht, you go try one on first, Moyako.
Show us too once you've got it on , okay?
What? You want to see it?
That's the whole point of trying it on .
You wanna see Moyako-senpai
in her swimsuit too, don't ya, Fuka?
U h , yeah , I guess...
I-it's a d irty trick to use one of the younger girls
on me Iike that, Kasumi.
Rlease make free use
Of the fitting rOOm
rlease make free use Of the fitting rOOm Well
, I guess now that Akira has stepped away
Well , I guess now that Akira has stepped away
it's just us girls here shopping .
So I suppose showing oft my bathing suit
once I've got it on is no big de-
Don't Iet your guard down , Moyako !
A new-swimsu it fashion show
put on by an older sister!
There's no way a guy who
crushes on his sister Iike Akira
would n't jump at the chance
to see such a big event!
Akira is planning to leer at me in my swimsu it!
He said he was Ieaving so that I'd Iet my guard down ,
but he must actually be hid ing somewhere in the store.
And the second I open that cu rtain ...
I just can't get enough of Moya in that swimsuit...
Jeez, my younger brother's a stealth master!
I've gotta contact Kasumi outside
and ask for her help ASAF !
Hm? It's from Moyako.
Huh? She texted you from the fitting room . . .?
Sender: Moyako suuject: Help!! MaoosqDio from usbiou' Akira witb stsaltb swimsDit' olusr sistsr io a ssrioDs uiou'
so immsuiatslv aftsr oussrviog tbat it's oscsssarv to captDrs Akira' arrsst bim' aou latsr iotsrrogats wssurftg
sender: Moyako suuject: Help!! MaoosqDio from usbiou' Akira witb stsaltb swimsDit' olusr sistsr io a ssrioDs uiou' so immsuiatslv
aftsr oussrviog tbat it's oscsssarv to captDrs Akira' arrsst bim' aou latsr iotsrrogats wssurftg Manneq uin from behind ,
Sender: Moyako Suuject: Help!! MaoosqDio from usbiou' Akira witb stsaltb swimsDit' olusr sistsr io a ssrioDs uiou' so immsuiatslv
aftsr oussrviog tbat it's oscsssarv to captDrs Akira' arrsst bim' aou latsr iotsrrogats wssurftg Akira with stealth swimsu it,
Sender: Moyako SuUject: Help!! MaoosqDio from usbiou' Akira witb stsaltb swimsDit' olusr sistsr io a ssrioDs uiou' so immsuiatslv
aftsr oussrviog tbat it's oscsssarv to captDrs Akira' arrsst bim' aou latsr iotsrrogats wssurftg older sister in a serious bind ...
older sister in a serious bind ...
What the hell is this?
A secret code. . .?
Mysterious...
Aki !
I don't really know what's going on ,
but it seems your sister's in a real fix.
What? !
Kasumi, please come q uick!
Moya, what's wrong?
Aig Sie ie the Ueet
aig Sie ie the Ueet
WHAT? !
Aig Sie ie the Ueet
He plans to openly savor the sight
from the front row? !
Hm?
The true aim of my perverted Iittle brother
wasn't to Ieer at me but to grope me !
I-it was an accident! I swear!
Ah , here we go again .
You're so bold , Akira.
Well , that was enlightening .
Summer vacation , in which the mind , body, and desires
become more uninhibited , got underway.
WalCOma hOma, MaStar.
WalCOma hOma, MaStar. I'm Moyako Konoe,
the oldest daughter of the Konoe family.
I'm Moyako Konoe,
A eoothing epace Precioue cafe cheerful maide will eerve you delicioue food and alcohol.
come join ue on the eecond floor! I'm Moyako Konoe, the oldest daughter of the Konoe family.
A eoothing epace Precioue cafe cheerful maide will eerve you
delicioue food and alcohol. come join ue on the eecond floor!
A eoothing epace Precioue cafe cheerful maide will eerve you delicioue food and alcohol. come
join ue on the eecond floor! My Iittle brother is a pervert who has a fond ness for maids.
Having been encouraged by Brisa,
I'm currently working part-time at a maid cafe.
There's no way I can Iet Akira
see me d ressed Iike this.
Welcome home !
Welcome ho-
Hey there, Moyako ! You working hard?
K-Kasumi? !
And Akira, too? What're you doing here? !
Pantaey space
I found out thanks to a text from Bri-boo.
She said you were working here.
I'm embarrassed about it,
so I'd been keeping it a secret...
I'm gonna give Brisa a talking-to
once she gets back from buying supplies.
You really Iook the part in that uniform !
Right, Aki?
Yeah , it Iooks good on you .
R-really?
Wi]d Fantasy Begins
A hrother whose heart is set aflutter
by the sight of his older sister in a maid outfit!
I'm no fool !
I know that maids ad mirably serve the master
of the house in a submissive and courteous manner!
When it comes to maids,
who're the ideal image of a woman
but who've Iong d ied out in modern society,
the men of the world are simply infatuated !
And sister-loving Akira was certainly no exception !
That tablo's opon .
Lot's go sit down .
And sister-loving Akira was certainly no exception !
To Akira, my appeal is doubly strong .
It's Iike giving an oni an iron club
or giving a tiger wings.
Boy, it suro is hot out today. It's Iike giving
an oni an iron club or giving a tiger wings.
Boy, it suro is hot out today.
Right?
Hey, maid !
Get your head outta the clouds
and come take our order.
Huh?
Ah , yes, of cou rse.
Calm down , Moyako.
Don't forget you're on the clock.
No matter what desires Akira may have,
I must carry out my work d uties.
Hmm , well , I'II have the Heartfelt Curry, ple-
Er, why's it named something
so embarrassing to say? !
Well , uh , I'II have this one.
"Fure Love Omurice."
You will be having the Pure Love Omurice, correct?
Wh-why'd you have to say
the d ish's name twice Iike that? !
Is this revenge for us stopping by unannounced?
FIease enjoy your meal .
Make yourselves at home.
Wait a sec.
Customers here can have a maid write
something in ketchup on their omurice, right?
Oh , that's right!
U h , I don't need you to do all that.
That won't do !
I must properly carry out my d uties.
So, any req uest for what you'd Iike me to write on-
MADły lN ł0VE WlfH DIG SISfER
By tlTTtE BR0IHER
Ab . . . !
Does he intend to declare
his Iove for me in ketchup writing? !
I-I see now...
Akira must've wanted to profess
his feelings for me in a trendy way,
so he ordered Fure Love Omurice since it includes
the option of having the maid write on it!
I wasn't able to see through his plan !
Though it only applies inside the cafe,
the master-servant relationship is absolute.
In the name of your master, I command you
to write a declaration of Iove on the omurice !
There is no way I can d isobey him !
Hey, Moya, er. . . M-Maid !
Ugh , it's d renched in ketchup...
I-I can't even see the omelet part...
S-sorry, er, I mean , my deepest apologies !
I will bring you a new one right away.
Don't worry about it. It's okay.
I can eat it just fine. See? !
Whoa, guess you're up for the challenge !
Moya, this is your first job, right?
That's why we came today
to ofter you encouragement.
I'm relieved to see it Iooks Iike
you're doing your best.
Akira...
Besides, making such a blunder is the
kinda thing a clumsy maid would do. It's cute.
It's one of those "aww, so cute" things, right?
Hey now! Don't tease your big sister.
What? !
He says his big sister is cute as a clumsy maid? !
Tee-hee, now I've gone and done it.
What is Akira doing hitting on me so casually? !
CIumsy-Moya, can I get a refill on my water?
Don't Iaugh at other people's blunders !
You're making that arg ument only now? !
A m inute ago, you were laug hing , too !
I'm back!
What?
WalCOma hOma, MaStar.
WalCOma hOma, MaStar. Moyako worked hard at her
service-oriented part-time job at the maid cafe.
Moyako worked hard at her service-oriented
part-time job at the maid cafe.
I'm Moyako Konoe,
the oldest daughter of the Konoe family.
My younger brother is a p-pervert
who is super into his big sister.
It's embarrassing to say,
but right now I'm feeling the call of nature.
I-I want to go use the bathroom ,
but I can't bring myself to...
Why can't I , you ask?
Because of a certain incident
that took place two hours ago.
TwD hDurs agD
CURSE Tv
TwD hDurs agD CURSE
Tv Do you get it now?
CURSE Tv
Do you get it now?
Outside the window...
the woman's ghost...
Stop freaking out so much , Moya.
They're obviously just using CG eftects.
I can't believe he's playing it so cool .
The present
Akira's favorite trick of showing
his big sister a ghost TV show,
getting her scared ,
and Iucking into a Iewd situation .
To think his Iittle scheme resulted in
this kind of secondary eftect...
Ghosts and such ...
There's no way that supernatural stuft really exists !
Al rig ht, I'm going to the hathroom !
Akira
Akira You know, back when we were Iittle kids it was
Akira who was more afraid of those kinda TV shows...
Moya, will you walk me to the bathroom?
Thinking about how he used to
say that so helplessly
and come begging to me in tears
Iate at night really takes me back.
Th-that scared the crap outta me.
Did Akira wake up to use the bathroom , too?
C-could this be...
I can't hold it.
Commence "Operation Walk Me
to the Bathroom , Sister" !
The very moment I'm reminiscing
he does something so daring .
Is Akira some kind of ESFer who can
read his big sister's mind?
I never imagined that affer
nearly ten years have gone by
he'd again attempt "Operation Walk Me
to the Bathroom , Sister" !
I-I see now!
He d id n't have me watch that
ghost TV show in order to frighten me.
Saying that the truth is
deep down he was scared too,
Akira's true ohjective was to create a pretext
Go Go Go
Go Go Go for carrying out his "Operation
Walk Me to the Bathroom , Sister" !
Go Go Go Walk mo to tho bathroom . for carrying out
his "Operation Walk Me to the Bathroom , Sister" !
Go Go Go for carrying out his "Operation
Walk Me to the Bathroom , Sister" !
What preparation !
What a schemer he is !
Boy, am I thirsty.
Hm?
It came out!
Akira's scream? ! "Came out"? !
What came out? ! Some kinda ghost? !
Or do you mean that in a bod ily-function way? !
What? Huh?
What? !
Affer watching a TV special ahout g hosts,
Iate that night the Konoe siblings freaked out in unity.
Ane
LOg
I'm Moyako Konoe,
the oldest daughter of the Konoe family.
My Iittle brother is a pervert
who romps about the beach .
Today, we've all come to take a d ip in the ocean .
Wow, seeing the ocean up close Iike this
is getting me hyped up !
Yay! The swimsuit episode is finally here !
Whew, it sure is hot.
I'II go set up our spot on the beach ,
so you girls go ahead and get changed .
Really? Well , thanks.
M uch appreciated .
Wow!
Sorry to keep you waiting , Akira.
5wimsnit Appreciation Time
End
So, what do you think, Akira?
How do we Iook in our cute bathing suits?
Well , uh . . . I suppose you Iook good in them .
Trying to play it cool , huh , M r. Low-key Ferv?
Al rig ht, Aki ! Let's go take a d ip !
Yeah , Iet's do it!
Yes !
Hey now! Akira! Kasumi !
Do some warming-up exercises
before you head out swimming !
Come on , don't be so strait-Iaced , Moya.
Yeah , seriously, we're not Iittle kids, okay?
Whoa, it's freezing .
Aw, it feels g reat!
Good grief...
Let's at Ieast do some warm-ups
ourselves, Fuka-chan .
Al rig ht, su re.
Still , you are a bit of a worrier,
huh , Moyako-senpai?
That just shows how much you
care for your brother, I guess...
I mean , it'd be just horrible
if he were to d rown , right?
Especially in summer,
water-related accidents really scare m-
Wi]d Fantasy Begins
Mouth-to-mouth !
Could it be that Akira's goal is
to purposely nearly d rown
and have his big sister resuscitate him
with artificial respiration?
A. check for conecioueneee
Artificial respiration .
When it comes to the good deed of saving a Iife,
A. check for conecioueneee
one cannot allow a sense of guilty pleasure,
a. open the airway
a. open the airway a sense of shame,
or their moral values to get in the way.
A sense of shame,
C. Provide artificial reepiration a sense of
shame, or their moral values to get in the way.
Conseq uently, without any hesitation
or concern of subseq uent hard feelings,
he could thoroughly enjoy a k-k-kiss !
I can't believe he wants to
steal a kiss from his sister so bad
Holp. I can't believe he wants to
I can't believe he wants to
steal a kiss from his sister so bad
he's willing to put his Iife on the Iine !
Moyako-senpai, your face is beet red !
You suftering from heatstroke?
Here we go, Bri-boo !
Okey-dokey, Kasumin !
German-Suplex Toss !
Ah !
Akira's d rowning? !
Oh no !
I'II save him before he ever needs
to be resuscitated !
She's fast!
That came as a surprise.
Al rig ht, you're getting a Frankensteiner next!
Don't be rid iculous !
Akira!
Moya?
A hu man torpedo? !
I'm not about to Iet you d rown !
There's no way I'm giving you
mouth-to-mouth , okay? !
Whoa, whoa, whoa! You're actually suftocating him !
FIease take care to avoid
water-related accidents in the summer.
This message is brought to you by Moyako Konoe.
Summer really has a way of emboldening people.
What fun , what fun ...
swim niogs opso for
BDsiosss Parasols ovoza
swim niogs opso for BDsiosss
Parasols ovoza I sure am hungry...
Oh?
Welcome !
Oh , it's you , Konoe !
And Saeki , too? !
So you're working here part-time, huh , Fukuyama?
Lucky you two, out enjoying Iife !
Er, why do you still have
your hood ie on anyway, Saeki?
I'd sure Iike to see ya in a swimsuit! Oh , yes !
Huh? Not a chance.
Oh?
I'm sorry...
Aah , he got you pretty good .
I'II wash it for ya when I go on break.
Give it here, please.
Guess I don't have much choice...
Al rig hty! What a feast for the eyes !
Can it!
Why only me? !
Al rig ht then , let's have some dessert!
I borrowed a stick from Fukuyama, so Iet's do
a watermelon-splitting game before we eat it!
How marvelous !
Moya, it's time to train your mind's eye !
The watermelon is five minutes' walk
from the nearest station .
Hey now, stop fooling around .
Jeez, will you please just
guide me to the watermelon .
Okay, Iet's not tease her too much .
Moya! Make a half turn and head right.
Akira's voice !
I hear every single day, so his voice is
the easiest for me to make out clearly.
Go for it!
Make your way north-north west!
Take three more steps forward !
Moya, go west!
No, the other way! You're headed for the ocean .
That's the way.
Okay, now rotate 46 degrees to the Ieff.
Al l I need to do is fol low Akira's instructions.
Yoah , that's it. You'ro doing good , Moya.
I trust you , Akira!
Oh , you're getting real close !
Yeah , rig ht there !
Now just give it a good hard swing !
Okay, got it!
Wi]d Fantasy Begins
A sister led arou nd hy the cu nning navigation
of her younger brother!
Right now, I'm just Iike Akira's puppet on a string !
Isn't it the case that with his navigation Akira
is only pretend ing to guide me to the watermelon
and is actually spewing BS
and Iuring me d irectly to him instead? !
Bingo !
He's attempting to trigger an
unavoidable incident that results in
him getting to enjoy an "accidental" Iewd situation
where his sister ends up in his arms...
N-now I get it.
That's why Akira suggested we play the
watermelon-splitting game in the first place !
I can't believe how smooth of a talker my brother is
and how good he is at manipulating people !
Now's your chance ! Swing !
Chance? ! For an accidental Iewd situation? !
Moya. . .?
Huh?
Stop trying to sed uce me already!
Moyako's gono crazy!
Just settle down , Moya!
It's in bite-sized pieces now.
Calm down !
That was skillfully done.
Yikes, that was close !
Japanese fireworks are beautiful !
Sure are, right?
Hey, be careful !
That's not the kind you hold in your hand !
Oh , the cand Ie went out.
Where d id we set down the Iighter again?
Without a flame, we can't Iight the fireworks.
Moya, will you Iet me use the sparks from yours?
Yeah , sure.
It's still not Iighting ...
You've gotta stick them closer together.
That's it. Stick the tip closer toget. . .her...
Wi]d Fantasy Begins
A you nger hrother who desires his sister's spark!
Something about it. . . is incred ibly obscene !
The act of sticking the tips of two fireworks
together to catch the unlit one on fire...
At a g lance, it seems to he nothing more
than a common , everyday experience
when using fireworks...
But when it's my perverted Iittle brother doing it,
it's a d ifterent story!
To Akira, it's a form of contact that's
on the same Ievel as an ind irect kiss !
I got my paws on my sister's flame !
I see now!
He purposely put out the cand Ie
because this is what he had in mind all along !
I could n't see through his ruse !
Al rig ht, it final ly l it!
Think again !
Why'd you do that? !
I won't Iet you have your big sister's flame !
Hard to beat sparklers to close things out, huh?
I can really feel the Japanese wabi-sabi.
There's just something about sparklers
I Iike, you know?
Can't say that surprises me, Fuka.
Here, I'II share mine with you .
Ah , it's dou hle the size now.
We can't be getting outdone by Saeki.
Let's unite our sparklers, too !
Okay!
We d id it! Ours also doubled in si-
Wi]d Fantasy Begins
U niting with big sister's sparkler!
U niting with big sister? !
Oh , it fell .
Aww, you've gotta hold onto it tig htly.
Moya?
Stop using fireworks as a pretext
to unleash your desires !
Why're you giving me
a Cobra Twist all of a sudden? !
Cool it, Moyako !
Ah , it fel l .
Now that we've arrived at the
unexpected twist, Iet's head home.
A su m mer evening hreeze and the chatter
of young ones having a good time.
It's all rather pleasant.
My Iittle brother is a pervert
That brother of mine Ioves his big sister
(Busteu , busteu , busteu , busteu , busteu , whoo!)
(Busteu , busteu , busteu , busteu , yay)
Hiuuen gazes, outrageous thoughts
That's right, he always has uesigns on his big sister
(Busteu , busteu , busteu , busteu , busteu , whoo!)
(Busteu , busteu , busteu , busteu , yay)
Passionate but immoraI
AII the more passion beCause of the impropriety
Day after uay, the Konoe householu is ChaotiC
wooing , Courtship, mauly in Iove with Big Sister
A young man who Crushes on his big sister
anu Can't stop suuuenly
Turning a blinu eye to Civil Iaw
Love you, Big Sis, oh Jesus
wooing , Courtship, a sister Complex towaru Big Sis
A supremely unhingeu young man
who Crushes on his big sister
Give Common sense the boot
Neeu you, Big Sis, oh my girI
Nevertheless, I will rehabilitate him
BeCause beyonu the IanusCape
where the haze has CIeareu
Surely a sparkling future is waiting
Moya is so darn cute in her maid outfit...
I'm so sleepy.
Fuka.
Hey, Fuka, I'm talking to you .
What is it, Kasumi-senpai?
Look at that. Straight in front.
"In front"?
Aah ...
Right?
It's a heartwarming sight, isn't it?
They sure are close, those Konoe siblings.
Moya. . . what's for d inner tonight?
Akira, stop crushing on you r hig sister...
Moyako and friends made great summer memories
on their trip to go swimming in the sea.