I'm Moyako Konoe,
the oldest daughter of the Konoe family.
My Iittle brother is a pervert
who Iikes his bath at 41 OC.
Hey, Moya!
Huh?
Is that brother of mine
calling me from inside the bath?
My younger Drofher is so
MuCh of a Perverf lf's Laughable.
Ane LOg
eiu sister Muyaku's Never-euuiuu Muuuluuue
Ane LOg eiu sister Muyaku's Never-euuiuu Muuuluuue
Ane Log : Big Sister Moyako's Never-end ing Monologue.
The shampoo's all out. Do we have a refill?
I do recall seeing one around ...
I'II bring it to you now!
B-behind his door...
Wilct Fantasy Begins
Akira m ig ht he stand ing huck naked
with his Iegs spread ...
I'm no fool !
I know there are people in this world who derive
sexual excitement from exposing themselves !
What a pervert!
Isn't Akira just using the shampoo being all out
as an excuse to Iure me to him ...
with the intention of doing some in-home streaking? !
If it's done inside his home in front of a family member,
then would it not count as public indecency? !
You've come to use Ioopholes in the Iaw
to commit your perverted acts, Akira!
I brought it. Come and get it.
What? Can't you put it down
inside the shower room?
Hmm ...
Akira is inside the hath ,
so the area around the sink should be safe.
Beyond this door, Akira's stark naked
and waiting for his chance...
Just open the door and set the shampoo down .
He's enticing me...
Wilct Fantasy Begins
He's undoubted Iy positioned himself in the bath
in some rid iculous way
to put his foolery on full d isplay!
Think again , Akira.
Big sisters are q uick stud ies, you know!
So Iong as I don't catch sight of you doing it,
it's no big thing !
I-I'm coming in .
Huh?
Th-that was a blind spot in my plan .
I can't see Akira's naked body,
but I can't see anything else either!
H-hey, wh-what're you . . .? ! Moya? !
That was a shock!
Wet and See-Tbrougb
My shirt's soaked and see-through !
So seeing me with a wet shirt sticking to my skin
was your true aim , you perverted schemer!
Those charges won't stick!
Once again today Moyako was at the mercy of
her Iittle brother until the very end of the day.
I'm Moyako Konoe,
the oldest daughter of the Konoe family.
My Iittle brother is a pervert who crushes on
his sister from breakfast to bedtime.
I'm so sleepy...
Come on , sit up straight!
Yeah , yeah .
Ah , dam m it!
Oh , for God's sake !
Here, I'II wipe it up for y-
Wilct Fantasy Begins
Right on his groin !
C-could it be that Akira
pretended to be half asleep
and purposely d umped his coftee on himself
to get me to fond Ie his crotch? !
He thinks up perverted stunts that put his body
on the Iine starting first thing in the morning !
What's done is done...
Words once spoken can't be taken back...
I already told him , "I'II wipe it up for you" !
Taking it back now would reflect poorly
on my honor as an older sister...
Wilct Fantasy Begins
M-my only choice is to wipe it up !
Huh?
I-I can wipe it up myself!
Just hand me the d ishrag .
Oh?
Rather than make me do it,
he's wiping up around his groin himself?
Did I misunderstand and there was
never a plot to begin with?
R-right, of course.
I'm not thinking straight this morning .
This isn't working !
Wiping isn't gonna be enough to get my pants d ry.
Wha-? !
Wh-wh-what're you . . .? !
Why are you taking your pants oft? !
What? I'm gonna change into
another pair, of course.
I've gotta change into a new shirt, anyhow.
Ah , makes sense.
It's true that might be a good id-
Wilct Fantasy Begins
Akira's heart-pou nd ing chang ing session is...
Say, Moya. . .
Say, Moya...
about. . . to. . . begin !
I-I get it now.
His aim was to make a show
as he changed in front of me,
so he spilled his coftee on purpose
and manufactured an excuse to change !
Look! Como on , Iook!
I wasn't able to see through his ploy.
Yikes, even my underwear's wet.
He's gonna take oft not just his pants
but his underwear, too? !
Akira! Don't get carried away now, you hastard !
Not on my watch !
Wh-what exactly are you doing?
You can't tell?
I'm blowing on your uniform to d ry it.
How many hours do you think that'II take? !
We'II be Iate to school !
In the end , Akira went into the bathroom
to change his clothes.
Good morning !
I'm Fuka Saeki.
I don't really have anything else to say.
Saeki ! What's with the way you're d ressed? !
Time and time again ,
you d isplay a shameful Iack of d iscipline !
Saeki-san got caught by
the guidance counselor again .
Let's get outta here before he zeros in on us, too.
Scold ing a 1 st-year girl as a warning to others, huh?
Jeez, what a pain ...
I guess that means I'm subject to
punishment too, then .
Strictly speaking , my card igan
isn't approved by the school either,
so if you're going to reprimand that student,
go ahead and do the same to me.
Aw, that's ou r Konoe-san !
She stepped in to help !
Damn she's cool !
W-well , you're an excellent student, though , Konoe...
Is student guidance
something you change the standards for
depend ing on the particular student in front of you?
Well , I , uh ...
That was q uite the d isaster, huh?
I'm Moyako Konoe, a 2nd-year.
I-I'm Saeki. Fuka Saeki, a 1 st-year student.
Thanks for what you d id back there.
How one d resses is a matter of ind ivid uality.
Feople should respect that.
Moyako Konoe-san ...
She's so pretty...
That said , there are also perverts who
abuse that ind ivid uality for their Iewd urges.
What? "Ferverts"?
There's one over there ! That male student!
Konoe. . .?
He's my younger brother.
Why do you think he always has his
top button undone Iike that?
U-uh , 'cause he doesn't Iike
being all stift and formal?
That's not it. The reason is...
Wilct Fantasy Begins
Hey! Do up that button .
It's so that he can smell his
big sister's hair from super up close...
that he keeps it undone Iike that!
What? !
Your brother snifts you?
Why the hell would he do somethin' Iike that?
Because that brother of mine is the type of guy
who's in Iove with his big sister
and crushes on her.
Huh?
Without exception , all Iittle brothers have
impure feelings toward their big sisters, you see.
I'm the source for that info !
Now, don't you forget that fact, Fuka-chan .
Th-that's absurd ...
B-but, well ...
someone as respectable as her is stating it
to be fact with such confidence.
Her claim could be correct...
It might be...
the truth .
Homeroom Teacher Nagiea Nanami
Hey,
what's it Iike waking up in the morning
and having your big sister there with you?
What?
Don't you get aroused?
Like hell I do, d umbass !
I don't even see her as a girl
in the first place, you know?
Ah , there it is !
You g uys with older sisters
are always saying that same thing !
And now I het you're gonna tel l me,
"Try thinking about how you'd feel
in the case of your own mother?"
I'm tired of hearing from guys
who don't know how to d ream !
That's my seat, you know.
M-M iss Saeki, I was simply
keeping your seat warm for you .
Gross. Why don't you go back to your own seat?
Catch you Iater, Konoe.
Y-yeah ...
G-good morning , Saeki.
My brother's the type of guy who is
in Iove with his big sister and crushes on her.
What is it?
U h , well , I was just thinking everyone's got their
own inclinations and ways of d ressing ...
What are you talking about?
Fuka moved her desk slightly farther away
from Akira to the tune of a few centimeters.
Ane
Log
Konnichi-hello !
My name is Brisa U mehira!
I'm a high school girl who Ioves the manga, anime,
and games of Japan , my dad's home country!
Which is why I splurge on that stuft
and I'm flat broke now!
What the heck are you doing , Bri-boo?
Oh , Kasumin and "Big Sis" Moya.
Ah , I see you r l ittle hrother too, Moya!
Hey, check out Aki's face !
It's obvious he was sleeping d uring class
with his face down on his desk.
You're wrong , Kasumi .
That's from rubbing his cheek on something .
Rubbing his cheek?
Wilct Fantasy Begins
Akira must have put a photo of me,
his older sister, on his desk,
and rubbed his cheek against it all class Iong !
Not a chance !
No, there is a chance.
Huh?
That said , Moya, here's what I think.
Was rubbing his cheek all he d id?
Hm?
Having put a picture of the sister
he Ioves in front of him ,
he was unsatisfied with just
rubbing his cheek against it...
and he smoochy-smooch kissed it
and Iickity-Iick ran his tongue all over it...
That's what I think!
Even Iess of a chance !
That is an intriguing idea, Brisa.
Hey, don't praise her! Come on !
However, doing that would end up
getting his precious picture all wet.
And if the photo came from a regu lar printer,
then the ink would end up getting all over his Iips.
The way I see it, even if he d id nuzzle the photo,
he d id not Iickity-Iick and smoochy-smooch it.
B-but, but. . . !
What if he put it inside a plastic sleeve first?
If there was a cover over it, would n't his Ionging
for his big sister be slightly d iminished?
Then , is it possible he made it
his smartphone wallpaper
and Iickity-Iicked and smoochy-smooched that.
There'd be a high risk of him
inadvertently tapping on something .
Rubbing his cheek on the photo's
the best bet, affer all .
That's the odds-on favorite !
Th-these two are on the same wavelength
in a weird kinda way...
Hey, Kasumi !
Oh , and Brisa and Moya, too.
So, was it nuzzling?
Lickity-Iick and smoochy-smooch?
Which was it? !
What Ianguage are you speaking? !
Speaking in the Ianguage of wild fantasies,
Moyako and Brisa found kind red spirits in each other.
I'm Moyako Konoe,
the oldest daughter of the Konoe family.
My Iittle brother is a pervert
who has a fond ness for sweets.
Wow, you d id a great job baking those, Konoe-san .
They Iook so delicious !
Thanks.
So, what're you planning to do with these cookies?
Gonna give them to someone?
Yes, and I've decided on who.
Who are you going to give them to?
Well ...
Oh? Cookies from cooking class?
Would n't it be better to just
give them to me back home?
They're best freshly-baked , right?
Share some with your friends, too.
It figures you chose your younger brother
without giving it a second thought, Moyako.
So she gave the cookies she made in
cooking class to her brother, huh?
Girls Iike her are everyone's idea
of a perfect big sister...
In that case, I'II accept them with thanks, Moya.
Wilct Fantasy Begins
Come to think it, inside that bag
some of the cookies are heart-shaped ,
a symbol of maiden in Iove !
A heart sym hol izes love !
It's totally gonna Iook Iike
I'm making advances on my Iittle brother!
Akira, actual ly, g ive that hack!
U h-oh ...
They're all broken apart now...
Y-you shoved me so suddenly...
Well , I am glad I succeeded in
hid ing the heart shapes...
but it's a shame since they'd
turned out so well ...
Gimme that, Moya.
Ah , tastes g reat!
Broken or not, they're still plenty good .
I-I see...
It all worked out, huh , Moyako?
Saeki?
You Konoe siblings...
There's something I Iike about ya.
Akira ate the hroken cookies his sister
had made for him with delight.
I'm Moyako Konoe,
the oldest daughter of the Konoe family.
My Iittle brother is a pervert
who isn't a member of any school club.
Moya! Kasumin !
Let's do club-activity stuft!
What's this all about, Bri-boo?
Accord ing to my info,
these days with school-setting stuft
it's standard for the story to start
with the found ing of a club.
Despite not having a slogan
or taking part in competitions,
Iet's make a uniq ue club
where we just Iazily hang out
that for some reason still d raws in
d roves of the big guns at school !
Think we'd get approval for
a joke of a club Iike that? !
Besides, I've got housework to do,
so I don't have time for a club anyway.
You mean taking care of your brother?
Oh , I know!
How about we have him join the club, too?
If he's passionate about the club,
then maybe his cruel Iibido that's
fixated on you will d iminish some, Moya.
Ah , I get it...
It is true that club activities make for a precious
community for getting to know Iike-minded people.
By cultivating friendships with fellow members
whose ambitions are aligned ,
surely his abnormal obsession
with his big sister will subside.
Meeting Iike-minded people? !
Wilct Fantasy Begins
A...
Big Sis CIub
A Big Sis Clu h is gonna get formed !
CrH$hírtg art sí$ter Big si5 rlHb A
Big Sis Clu h is gonna get formed !
CrH$bírtg art
sí$ter Big si5 rlHb
Big Sistor, Big Sistor, Big Sistor, Big Sistor...
The Big Sis CIub is an sister-infatuated army corps formed for
the purpose of Big Sistor, Big Sistor, Big Sistor, Big Sistor...
dearly Ioving big sisters above all else and spread ing their influence
around the world ! Big Sistor, Big Sistor, Big Sistor, Big Sistor...
dearly Ioving big sisters above all else
and spread ing their influence around the world !
If a major force that holds that kind of
unbend ing intent were to advance on me...
I'm not confident I'd be any match for them !
In that case, why don't I form a Little Brother
Rejection CIub to oppose the Big Sis CIub?
Littte Brotber Reiectiort ctHb In that case, why don't I form
a Little Brother Rejection CIub to oppose the Big Sis CIub?
Littte Brotber Reiectiort ctHb No, that
would end up developing into a blood feud !
The Big Sis CIub is formidable !
"Big Sis CIub"?
What's that?
From this casual girl talk,
Moyako had a club-formation flag set oft.
Sorry to keep you waiting .
Is somethin' the matter?
N-no...
Let's head on home.
The soccer game's gonna start!
FIease come on in .
Thanks for having us !
Today, Kasumi, Brisa, and Fuka
are over at our house,
and all five us are going to cheer on
Japan in their soccer game.
Wo'vo got a must-win gamo...
The current Japan national team
has some real talent in the midfield .
We've got a Iot of players
who can compete in the vital area.
And in today's gamo...
A 4-2-8-1 with an offensive m idfielder
has become the team's go-to formation ,
but I wonder if we'II try going with three defenders.
Like a 3-4-3 or 3-6-2 formation?
We've got a must-win game on our hands here !
This room is so clean ...
Seems care's taken to keep it spick and span .
Ideal big sisters Iike that
are a d ifterent breed , affer all .
Let me help ya.
Nah , don't worry about it.
Go on and talk soccer with everybody.
I myself don't really understand
all this soccer talk...
Wilct Fantasy Begins
Are they real ly tal king ahout soccer?
Could they be making me believe
they're d iscussing soccer
but actually be talking about
something else entirely?
COde WO rd
COde WO rd I'm no fool ! I know full
well about the existence of code words !
COde WO rd
Isn't it Iikely those four were just now using code words
to have a conversation I can't understand? !
Yeah , that's it.
In the first place, just Iisting oft
sets of numbers Iike 4-2-3-1 and 3-6-2
should n't be enough to have
an actual conversation !
Ah , the crosshar!
Their player touched it, d id n't he? !
Corner! Corner-kick time !
He d id a great job breaking free
from the other team's pressing .
Low-key miracles sometimes do happen ,
so they're Ioci of change !
Hey, Fu-chan , you start cheering , too ! Come on !
By "Fu-chan ," do you mean me?
Wow, up into outer space !
What a time to send it way too high !
I'm the only one unable to understand
and I was just stand ing here smiling .
How Iaughable and humiliating !
Thank you , Moya.
Thanks !
But, just what kind of conversation were
those four having using those code words?
Goal !
We got one !
Our oft-the-ball movement
was superb on that score !
That movement really broke down
the other team's defensive Iine !
"Oft the ball"?
Off tha bal l
M ust be another code word .
Well then , I'II use that word to decipher
what it is they're actually talking about.
Off tha bal l
Oft the ball ...
Tha bal l is off. . .
The ball is oft...
Tha bal l is not thara. . .
The ball is not there...
Thara ara no bal-
There are no bal-
Oh my God !
They're definitely talking about
Iewd stuft, aren't they? !
At this point, I can't hel p hut see
all the countless words they've used
as all being highly suspicious.
PreSSing
"Fressing"...
Fress? Exert pressure?
PreSSing
Does it mean to forcefully push someone down? !
Vital area
"Vital area"...
An essential reg ion . . . An im portant spot...
Vital area
In other words, it means inside of a girl's skirt? !
Additional time
"Add itional time"...
What kind of time is that? !
Additional time I don't really get it, but
I'm sure it must be some kind of Iewd time !
I don't really get it, but I'm sure
it must be some kind of Iewd time !
Ah , I see !
Those Iists of numbers represent the female form !
What complex code words !
It's really q uite astonishing !
U h . . . What's wrong?
Whoa, she's shaking Iike crazy!
Trembling with excitement?
It's 'cause we all got so fired up and Ieff her out...
Did you get sulky?
Sorry, Moyako.
I'II fill you in on the all the details, okay?
Do they intend to Iure me into
their Iewd and shameless world?
Hup !
Defend at all cost! Save this one goal !
The goalkeeper stopped it!
Nice save !
The goalkeeper Kokubunji
saved Japan from d isaster!
Screw that.
Aw, don't say that.
We want you to have fun , too.
Don't bring up d irty talk around me !
But we're talking about soccer? !
The five of them Iivelily cheered on
Japan's national soccer team .
Watashi no otouto wa hentai ueaaru
Sou otouto wa ane ni koishiteirunua
(Kanpa kanpa kanpa kanpa kanpa fuu !)
(Kanpa kanpa kanpa kanpa yay)
Inbi na shisen furaChi na shisou
Sou itsuuatte ane o neratteiruunua
(Kanpa kanpa kanpa kanpa kanpa fuu !)
(Kanpa kanpa kanpa kanpa yay)
Jounetsuteki uakeuo haitokuteki
Fuuoutoku uakarakoso no netsujou
Kyou mo kyou tote Konoe-ke wa tenyawanya
Kyuuai kyuukon ane ni zokkon
Kyuu ni wa tomarenu ane-moe uanshi
M inpou nante miteminufurishite
Ane ni Iove you, oh Jesus
Kyuuai kyuukon ane ni sisCon
Kyuukyoku ni yabai ane-moe uanshi
Joushiki nante kettobashite
Ane ni neeu you, oh my girI
Soreuemo watashi wa kouseisasetemiseru
Moya no hareta keshiki no saki ni
Kitto kagayaku mirai ga matteru kara