I'm Moyako Konoe,
the oldest daughter of the Konoe family.
Good morning , Big Sis Moya.
Good morning , Akira.
And my you nger hrother...
...is a pervert.
My Younger Brother
is a pervert.
Ane Log
eiu sister Muyaku's Never-euuiuu Muuuluuue
Ane LOg eiu sister Muyaku's Never-euuiuu Muuuluuue
Ane Log : Big Sister Moyako's Never-end ing Monologue.
Without any explanation ,
I bet you're wondering ,
"What's this high school girl talking about?"
My apologies.
His name is Akira Konoe,
and he's my Iittle brother.
And , as his sister, I know...
That Akira. . . That my Iittle brother...
possesses a grossly immoral sexual pred ilection .
This brother of mine...
is a mega perv who seeks the hand of
his own sister in marriage
and who is attempting to get us
to exchange vows of Iove.
It all started 1 0 years ago...
Hey, Moyako !
Hm? What is it, Akira?
One day when we're older,
I'm gonna marry you !
I'm gonna take you as my wife !
Huh?
What a perv! What a freaking pervert!
I can't believe he had such a Iewd d isposition
from the time he was a young kid !
Seems that brother of mine
has got q uite the crush on his sister.
Wilct Fantasy Begins
compenctinm of caws
compenctinm of caws To begin with , my brother
and I are relatives in the second degree,
compenctinm of caws
and in Article 734 of Japan's Civil Code...
it is stipulated by Iaw that "blood relatives up to
the third degree of relationship cannot marry."
Yeah , you bet I researched it!
Affer al l , I can't fu l ly d isregard
the possibility of "if by any chance. . ."
No matter the feelings
the two of us share for each other,
what kind of happiness could be found in
a marriage the state will not sanction?
That's why he must fully give up on pursuing me
and get back on the right path ...
Wait! What do I mean
"the two of us share for each other"? !
I want no such thing !
M-Moya? ! What's wrong? !
I-it's nothing .
Anyway, Akira, what do you want
for breakfast this morning?
Well , I'm good with anything .
"Anything"...
"Anything"? !
What gives?
That sounds Iike something a
domineering husband would say to his wife !
Why would you utter such a stereotypical phrase
a man must never say to his wife now of all times?
Besides, saying it to me, your own sister...
Wh-what are you trying to do?
D-don't tell me...
you're trying to outflank me? !
Gah!
By naturally playing the part of a husband ,
are you aiming to grad ually build up our image
as a pseudo-married-couple? !
By getting the neighbors to think, "Boy, those
Konoe siblings are just Iike husband and wife,"
you're trying to establish a relationship
between us that transcends even civil Iaw? !
What a schemer you are !
You act Iike a tactician who could've
ruled the world if only times had n't changed !
Were you Komei in your previous Iife?
Were you? !
What? !
Ko. . .me. . .?
Ah , then something with o-kome, rice.
Wow, Iooks tasty!
Make sure to wash your hands.
Your miso soup is hard to beat.
Its flavor is so soothing , ya know?
Complimenting me Iike that
won't get you anything .
By that, do you mean ,
"AIways keep on making miso soup for me"? !
The message behind that is. . . Fut simply...
It means. . . !
What's the matter, Moya? Your face is all red ...
Don't you go proposing to me
first thing in the morning !
Huh?
What're you even talking about? !
It was another peaceful morning
at the Konoe household .
Koten Private Academy
Koten Private Academy My Iittle brother is a
pervert who has a thing for his own sister.
However, Ieaving that aside,
I'm a 2nd-year high school student,
and Akira is a 1 st-year at the same school .
Oh , that Akira...
Iusting affer me and trying to woo me again today-
he's really made things hard for me.
You a d ummy?
What do you mean by that, Kasumi? !
That's too short and simple a response !
You should be happy I gave you
even a three-word reply!
Dummy-Moyako !
Oh , good grief...
Ah , thank you , Moyako.
That girl is Kasumi Kurose.
I've know her since we were Iittle kids,
and she's one of my best friends.
But, you know, Moyako...
Think about how I feel affer all these years of Iistening
to these odd and reckless ramblings of yours.
There's bound to come a day
when I'm unable to make a good q uip, right?
Well , that's a rude thing to say.
I'm speaking on the basis of reality
and things I've experienced firsthand , you know?
Yeah , sure, sure.
This morning he was half asleep
and almost ended up using my toothbrush !
But. . . he was half asleep?
Obviously, he was faking it!
Akira was...
My brother was...
M-my sister's toothbrush ...
I just know it!
I'm half sure he was trying to thoroughly enjoy
that toothbrush that'd been
inside my mouth countless times !
J-just calm down , Moyako.
Feople who are still groggy from waking up
use toiletries all the time, right?
You're overthinking it.
This whole Akira Iusting affer you thing
is all in your imagination , Moyako.
Kasumi sure stands up for Akira an awful Iot...
Has Kasumi already been ...
won over by Akira? !
Wilct Fantasy Begins
Kasumi and I are child hood friends...
Which means that she and Akira are, too.
Moyako?
For Akira, she'd be the easiest person to win over...
I slipped up !
To think that Kasumi got caught in
Akira's clutches without me even noticing !
But how come?
Why d id he d irect his attack
on Kasumi and not me. . .?
Hoy, Moyako.
Is his game plan to first get rid of any obstacles? !
It's no uso. It sooms my voico is no Iongor roaching hor.
It's no uso. It sooms my voico
is no Iongor roaching hor.
Is his strategy to first ensnare
all of those around me,
surround me on all sides
and d rive me into a corner,
and grad ually wear me down
so that I raise the flag of surrender? !
It is my sister's stronghold that we are affer!
Forward march !
Crushlng an slster l Iave
slster Forward march !
Crushlng an slster
l Iave slster Sister!
His methods are Iike those of a
Warring States-period military commander!
Does he intend to conq uer me Iike one would
gain supremacy over a country?
Oh , Iittle brother!
Brotber sister Brotber
U h , Moyako? !
What the. . .? What's up with you?
... Never.
Huh? Come again?
I'II never Iet him capture my castle !
How in the hell d id that come about? !
Moyako Konoe spent yet another
enjoyable day at school .
Ane
Log
My brother is a student in a Iower grade
as well as a pervert.
And together with that hrother of m ine,
the three of us child hood friends
are going to spend Iunchtime in the courtyard .
So you're eating with us today, huh , Akira?
Not offen that happens.
I invited him to join us.
Told him it's nice to hang out
just us child hood friends once in a while !
You've been strong-arming me
into stuft for years, Kasumi.
What? What? You've been strong-arming
me into stuft for years, Kasumi.
What do wo havo horo? You've been
strong-arming me into stuft for years, Kasumi.
What do wo havo horo?
Come on , Iet's go.
Sure enough , having Iunch in the courtyard together
with two older girls is no walk in the park...
What're you so embarrassed about, Aki?
It's not that I'm embarrassed !
Your face is beet red .
Wilct Fantasy Begins
A you ng g igolo who has
two older girls wait on him !
Right now. . . doesn't Akira Iook Iike that
kind of stylish guy to all the onlookers? !
Ah , it's just as I thoug ht...
I can sense the sheer number of
curious glances we're getting ...
To the other students who know
nothing of our relation to each other,
Akira's su re to look l ike a guy who's got
two of the older girls at school
waiting on him hand and foot!
What a player he is, that brother of mine !
A knig ht in shining armor!
Sophisticatect anct styłish
Sophisticatect
anct styłish
I get the feeling she's caught up
in some unsavory thoughts...
Huh?
Kasumi's kind gesture of inviting Akira to Iunch
has resulted in an unforeseen misunderstand ing ...
and given rise to rumors.
Can I have a piece of fried chicken?
Nope.
M ine now!
Hoy, cut it out!
Kasumi is already acting carelessly...
Wait, could this all be part of Akira's plot?
He won Kasumi over for the very purpose of
creating this kind of gigolo-esq ue situation ,
and then he made her falsely testify
that she actually invited him?
I invited him .
But, to what end . . .?
Oh? Moya, you haven't even
opened your Iunchbox.
Lunch break'II be over soon .
G-good point. I'II open it up right n-
Ab . . . !
My Iunch is exactly the same as Akira's !
We're family, so that's only natural ...
I prepare them myself every morning ,
so it's only natural ...
But even so, as I mentioned earlier,
the typical student around here is
unaware of our relationship to each other...
And what'd happen if I was to open the l id of
an identical Iunch under those circumstances?
It goes without saying ...
Darling !
Right, we'd be mistaken for a Iovey-dovey
"darling and honey" kinda couple !
I'm getting the sense she's Iost
in depraved thoughts...
Y-yes, that's it...
Eok! Look how Iovoy-dovoy thoy aro !
Eok! Look how Iovoy-dovoy thoy aro ! Akira cooked u p a scheme to
ensu re everyone'd catch sight of the three of us eating together...
Akira cooked u p a scheme to ensu re everyone'd
catch sight of the three of us eating together...
I can't do it. I can't open this Iunchbox!
B-but, I am hungry...
Wh-what can I do? !
Gimme one more piece of fried chicken .
Not a chance !
Hmm , bread alone just isn't cutting it for me...
Why not have Moya give you some of her Iunch?
I mean , she's got the same stuft in hers, anyway.
Oh , that so?
Now they're trying to force it open !
Well , now that it's come to this...
Moyako, can you share a bit of your Iunch with-
M uncb
Munch
That really hit the spot.
In a single mouthful . . .? !
The three child hood friends had
a very Iively Iunchtime together.
My brother is a pervert who tails his big sister.
And , rig ht now, that perv is wal king
a few meters behind me.
Oh , you head ing home now, Moya?
Yeah . Why not head home
alongside each other for a change?
What? "AIongside each other"?
Side by side, huh?
My brother claims he would be
embarrassed to have
a classmate see him walking home
alongside his sister.
And that feel ing of his has resu lted in him keeping
six-person's-worth of d istance between us.
Jeez, he's such a Iittle kid , that Akira...
Wilct Fantasy Begins
Could it be that. . . he's perving on me?
Like Iooking me over head to toe...
Is Akira's true aim to get his fill
of ogling me from behind? !
Fositively speaking , he could be thought of
as a boy who's in Iove.
Negatively speaking , he could be thought of
as a stalker who has a twisted pred ilection .
His strategy is to unassumingly follow behind me
by oftering the reasonable excuse that it's
embarrassing to walk home alongside his sister.
I can't believe I was unable
to see through his ruse !
I'm an older sister who's fallen into
her brother's trap and Ieff her butt exposed !
How shameful ! How humiliating !
It's become hard to take another step
now that I've realized he's Ieering at me.
Huh? How do I normally walk again?
Moya, why are you trembling Iike that?
Hyaa!
That was close !
Fervert!
Oh my, a pervert?
Look, a pervert.
Wow, a real pervert!
M-mind your own business !
I-I'm her brother, okay? !
Are you feel ing u nwel l or something?
If that's it, I'II carry your bag for you .
Well then , Iet's head on home.
Weren't you embarrassed to
walk home side by side with me?
Huh?
Yeah , well ...
But it's a d ifterent matter if you're feeling sick.
FIus, I'm worried about you . . .
as your brother.
W-well , if you insist...
Sure, I don't mind head ing home together with you .
Er, weren't you the one who first suggested
we head home together?
Well , whatever.
Let's just get going .
If someone sees me carrying two bags,
people'II start saying that my sister
wears the pants in the relationship.
His sister wears the pants in the relationship...
Sister's pants !
So Akira is crazy about my butt, affer all? !
You alrig ht, Moya?
Want me to Iend you my shoulder?
Don't stand there.
Huh?
Don't you dare stand behind me !
Wh-who are you? !
Somehow or other, the Konoe siblings
managed to harmoniously return home from school .
Well then , I better start getting d inner ready.
Oh?
This milk is about to expire.
Better d rink it while I can .
I'II give you a hand with that. Gimme a glass.
Really? That'II be a big help, Akira.
Thank you , Moya.
He's d rinking cow milk his big sister poured for him .
Sister's cow milk...
M ilk...
Sister's milk...
Sister...
milk...
DreBm of tbe FBrm
Wilct Fantasy Begins
A l ittle hrother who d rinks his sister's m il k? !
Talk about Iiving on the edge !
No mooooo-re of this !
Well , that really hit the spot!
A sing le g lass of m il k sent Moyako's
power of imagination oft the charts.
My brother is a pervert who espouses
crushing on one's sister.
Akira, the hath is ready!
Say what? The bath?
There's no good place to stop
in my game right now,
so you go ahead and take a bath first.
That so?
Al rig ht, I'l l head in first, then .
My brother is mad Iy in Iove with me
to the point he's thinking about
asking for my hand in marriage.
He's the type who has the hots for
his sister and takes it too far.
As his sister,
I must seek to straighten out that kind of outrageous
and unworthy younger brother of mine.
I spend my days with that thought in mind .
And here I was letting him
use the freshly-d rawn bath first...
Oh , that Akira...
W-wait a minute,
Wilct Fantasy Begins
Wilct Fantasy Begins could it be Akira Iet
me go first because he intends to peep on me?
Could it be Akira Iet me go first
because he intends to peep on me?
He says there's no good place
to stop playing his game?
Al l he needs to do is put the system
in sleep mode, right?
It's all just an excuse to
put oft his bath until Iater on .
Komei Type
For a Komei type of guy Iike Akira,
devising a strategy of this sort
is just a matter of course.
That was a close call . I got complacent.
Got you . Can't fool me.
Don't underestimate your big sis, Little Brother!
The water feels great.
That Akira...
He sure has a roundabout way of doing things.
I mean , until starting midd Ie school
we took baths together, right?
If he simply said he wanted to take baths
together again , I would be happy to...
I-i-it's not Iike that!
It's not Iike I actually wanna
take a bath with him or anything ...
No. . . I jumped to the wrong conclusion .
Akira isn't trying to peep on me.
He never intended to peep !
The water his sister bathed in ...
That's what he's really affer!
Wilct Fantasy Begins
Feeping?
Such a thing is trifling ...
That was just a false objective
he assumed I'd be able to detect.
Akira's true goal is to get his hands on
the bath water I've bathed in !
What a fiend ish boy...
Futting aside us being siblings,
just as a human being
I take exception with such a deed !
Wh-wh-what should I do?
Just d rain all the water?
No, that would be so wasteful ...
sense ofwastefnłness
sense ofwastefnłness Being mindful of wastefulness is a virtue
that Japan can hold up to the world as a point of pride.
Sense ofwastefnłness
That's how I feel about it, anyway.
0ne honr Iater
I mulled it over for too Iong and now I feel d izzy...
You must find a way, Moyako !
It need not be zero-one-hund red ...
Find a way where both
my brother and me can be happy
and split the Ievel of satisfaction fiffy-fiffy.
Wait, how safe is this water from
a sanitary stand point anyway?
Though we d id just refinish the tub,
there must still be a Ieast some germs in there.
If he d rinks many gallons of that kinda water,
he's gonna have major bowel trouble...
And su pposing that does happen ,
there's a chance he has a foolhardy proclivity
such that it Ieaves him feeling very satisfied ...
Zero, 60, 1 00...
No, 200 !
I can Iet him have up to 200 ml !
Moya, you took forever in th-
What's with that getup? !
Wh-what's with that glass?
This is sister juice.
Here, d rink it all up !
What the hell are you on about? !
It was once again a Iively night
at the Konoe household .
My Iittle brother is a pervert
That brother of mine Ioves his big sister
(Busteu , busteu , busteu , busteu , busteu , whoo!)
(Busteu , busteu , busteu , busteu , yay)
Hiuuen gazes, outrageous thoughts
That's right, he always has uesigns on his big sister
(Busteu , busteu , busteu , busteu , busteu , whoo!)
(Busteu , busteu , busteu , busteu , yay)
Passionate but immoraI
AII the more passion beCause of the impropriety
Day after uay, the Konoe householu is ChaotiC
wooing , Courtship, mauly in Iove with Big Sister
A young man who Crushes on his big sister
anu Can't stop suuuenly
Turning a blinu eye to Civil Iaw
Love you, Big Sis, oh Jesus
wooing , Courtship, a sister Complex towaru Big Sis
A supremely unhingeu young man
who Crushes on his big sister
Give Common sense the boot
Neeu you, Big Sis, oh my girI
Nevertheless, I will rehabilitate him
BeCause beyonu the IanusCape
where the haze has CIeareu
Surely a sparkling future is waiting
I'm Moyako Konoe,
the oldest daughter of the Konoe family.
My younger brother is a pervert
who seeks his sister's hand in marriage.
Akira
Akira And now, yet another day with
that brother of mine is about to begin .
And now, yet another day with that
brother of mine is about to begin .
Akira! It's morning ! Get u p !
Akira!