Îmi cer scuze pentru așteptare.
Kei!
Minghua...
Te-au rănit cumva?
Ești bine?
Am auzit că voiau să te interogheze, deci începusem să-mi fac griji.
Sunt bine. Nu s-a întâmplat nimic.
Știu că a fost o neînțelegere, dar încă
îmi pare rău că am fost duri cu tine.
N-Nu, eu îmi cer scuze că am provocat zarvă.
Ne vedem mâine, atunci.
Te vom aștepta.
Am înțeles.
Baza Forțelor Aeriene Komatsu
Îmi cer scuze.
Pentru chestiile spuse.
I was only thinking about myself.
I wasn't thinking about
how you felt, Minghua.
No, I'm sorry.
I think I went too far.
Anyway, what was that about?
When he said, "See you tomorrow."
I'm going to be working part-time
at the base starting tomorrow.
Working?
Barbie 01, cleared for take off!
Barbie 01, gata de decolare!
souten akogareta
Admirând cerul albastru,
kurenai no inochi
sufletul stacojiu
kodou shinkoro sase
își liniștește bătăile inimii
saa tobitate Hero Girl Azure Sky
Haide, zboară, eroino Cer Albastru
zetsubou no spiral
Spirala disperării
zankyou no refrain
și refrenul ecoului
hikari to kage no hazama
Între lumină și umbră
mezameta kibou no shikisai
s-a trezit culoarea speranței
ten to ten tsunagiawase
Unind cerurile
mukau
Înaintează
kasokudo agete
Mărește viteza
tsubasa narabeta Fighter
Întinde-ți aripile, luptătoareo
hitosuji no omoi kate ni
tsukuridase (don't be afraid)
ne vom face (nu-ți fie teamă)
arata na memory
noi amintiri
uchi otoshite ike Shooter
akumu kechirashi tachikire
kachidorou
Haide să învingem
ima koso Break the Blue!!
A venit clipa să străpungem cerul albastru!
It's late.
Let's talk more tomorrow.
You'll be rewarded for your cooperation.
Dosar pentru Academia Forțelor Aeriene
Come back tomorrow. Tell your friend
you're working here part-time.
Help her fly...
Întâlnirea din Komatsu
I don't know what that means,
but if I can help defeat the Xi,
I'll do whatever he wants me to.
A teenager in civilian clothes
stands out pretty bad here.
But the inside of this base is pretty nice.
It's like a university campus.
Hello.
I came to get you.
Where's Y-Yashirodoori?
Not here.
Out.
So I'll work with you today.
Let's go.
W-Wait!
You're the one who shot down the Xi
off the coast of Shanghai, right?
Do you remember me?
Um... when you crashed...
No.
I was so focused on what I was doing then
that I don't remember when I
crashed or when I was recovered.
Sorry.
I s-see.
I'm told you saved me.
Thanks.
Tea and food. I'll go get them.
Food?
I haven't eaten breakfast yet.
The tea is for you.
A secret weapon that eats?
I'm back.
Where's my tea?
Don't you need a spoon and some chopsticks?
I'm back.
Listen, are you...
A scatterbrain?
I am not!
You are very wrong!
You don't seem like a weapon at all.
You keep forgetting stuff,
you talk kind of funny...
It's kind of like...
One more word and I'll get mad.
I'm a little nervous.
I've never talked to anyone from outside.
Is that right?
So I'm just a little nervous.
Narutani Kei.
That's my name.
We haven't introduced ourselves yet, right?
Kei?
So your name's Kei...
What should I call you?
Gripen.
That's the name of an aircraft, right?
JAS39 Gripen.
That's who I am. Nothing else.
Just as humans make no distinction between
their brain and the rest of their body,
an Anima and a Daughter are
identical and inseparable.
I'm just a weapon.
So call me Gripen.
Got it. Gripen, right?
So, Gripen, what do we do after this?
What's next on the schedule after breakfast?
You don't have a plan?
What do you want to do, Kei?
I'm not sure how to answer that.
Um... What is it that you usually do?
Here at the base.
Walk.
I wander around.
Also, go on adventures here and there.
You're a free-spirited weapon, huh?
Also, nap.
Are you really that plane I saw?
What's with these people?
Oh, sorry.
That's H3.
H3?
Hangar 3.
The place you were held when
you were abducted yesterday.
Next to it is H2.
Next to that, H1.
There are also smaller hangars:
H4, H5, and H6.
This place is pretty big.
This is the only base near the
Sea of Japan that has any fighter jets.
If the continental coast falls to the Xi,
Komatsu will be a front line base.
Taiwan and the peninsula are still fighting,
so it's peaceful here now.
But when they fall...
There's one runway.
It's alternately referred to
as Runway 06 and Runway 24,
depending on the direction
of takeoff and landing.
One runway?
But don't civilian planes land here?
They use it as well.
What if you need to do an emergency takeoff?
We share.
What's this?
An old bunker. It's not used now.
I like this place.
I feel like a princess here.
I see.
For an airplane, this is like a
fancy bed with a canopy, huh?
Yes.
My secret base.
But is that okay?
This is a JSDF base, right?
If you try to make it into your own room,
won't they get mad if they find out?
Haruka said that if you do something bad
and nobody finds out, it's not bad.
Haruka?
Yashirodoori Haruka.
The director.
Yeah, that sounds like something he'd say.
Come sit.
Sure.
Fui ao jardim da Celeste,
giroflé, giroflá.
giroflé, flé, flá.
What language is that?
I don't know.
It was in the default training images.
You were saying something off the
coast of Shanghai too, right?
Um, Nova Elu... Nove Ere?
Nova Era.
Yeah. That's right.
I don't remember doing that,
but I know what it means.
"A new era."
Was that in your training images, too?
No, it was there from the start.
The start?
I don't know where I learned it, but...
From the start.
Yes? Roger.
I'm sorry. It's time for checkups.
Checkups?
I need to go back.
I'll walk you to the gate.
See you tomorrow.
Is she really that plane?
Hey, Kei, do you have plans tomorrow?
Yeah, I've got my job at the base.
Two days in a row?
Well, fine.
I'm going to Kanazawa.
Kanazawa?
I passed the review for
my refugee application.
I was hoping you could come with
me if you were free, but...
Sorry.
Your grandparents are leaving
tomorrow morning, too.
Don't bring any girls home!
I won't!
Coming, coming, coming, coming!
Hello, who's there?
Gripen?
Hello, Kei.
What are you doing here?
Narutani
Someone from TRDI brought me here.
TRDI?
The Technical Research
and Development Institute.
So, um... why are you here?
Haruka told me to do whatever
you told me to do.
Whatever I told you to do?
He said to let you have your way with me.
Don't resist, no matter what you do.
You're a young man, and some
things are understandable.
Let's have some fun!
Oh no!
Don't resist?
Kids these days.
Kei?
Just get inside!
Barley tea's fine, right?
Is that you?
Yeah.
This is a photo of me and my mom
when we went flying in China.
I think I was about ten?
She let me take over a little.
You flew?
Through the sky? Yourself?
I've got over a hundred hours
of flight time, you know.
Wow.
Wow?
You've flown a lot more than me, right?
No...
I can't fly.
You can't?
During tests and during combat,
I always lose control in the middle of
the flight and am sent back to base.
I'm useless. Defective.
They don't know why?
They keep giving me exams
and finding nothing.
But...
But?
It feels to me like I'm missing something.
Like what?
I don't know.
But that's how it feels.
How do you fly, Kei?
What can I do to fly right?
Um...
Well, let me think.
When I flew with my mom, she told me that
planes are built to fly, so if
I was worried about what to do,
I should just do whatever came to mind.
Without worrying about it?
Once you start thinking
about it, you freeze up.
First, try to fly. Enjoy doing
whatever you want to try.
Maybe that's what she meant.
Then if I fly with your mom,
maybe I'll get better.
If she can fly with me and help me,
like she did with you,
I can feel safer when I'm in the air.
Can you ask her?
No.
Why?
My mom's gone.
She was doing stunts at an airshow when
her plane was shot down by the Xi.
N-No, it's nothing you need to worry about.
Though I guess I'd be lying if
I said I was totally over it.
So, um... I'm counting on you!
Get better soon and beat those Xi!
So we can fly again.
So I can avenge my mom!
Okay. I'll do my best.
So... what am I doing my best at?
What is this?
When you're in trouble,
you ask for divine help, I guess.
Altarul Uhashi
Divine help?
Yeah. You pray you'll be able to fly better.
I pray I'll be able to fly better.
You don't need to actually say it.
What did you pray for?
That the Xi will be gone soon.
You don't like the Xi, Kei?
Of course not.
You were made to fight them, weren't you?
Yes, but...
I've lost so many things because of them.
If it weren't for them...
I'll never forgive the Xi.
I pray that the Xi will be gone soon.
Altarul Uhashi
You've never really left the base, right?
Yes.
This is all new to me.
At times like these,
if you just take it easy,
everything will sometimes just work out.
I see.
That's good to know.
Oh, right. What do you want for lunch?
The daily lunch B set!
It comes with one more
side dish than the A set.
And a deep-fried dish, too, so it's better.
Is that the meal at the JSDF cafeteria?
Yes.
Sorry, but there is no B set in this city!
What about the C set?
No C set, either!
My dreams are crushed.
Don't worry.
I'll give you something even better.
Here you go!
Let's eat.
Okay, let's dig in.
Okay.
It's good.
I'm glad.
You've got soup on your face.
What's this?
Gyoza.
Dip it in the sauce before you eat it.
Hot!
You're not supposed to eat it so fast.
But it's good!
You two are close, huh?
Your sister?
Yes, I guess.
Kei is my teacher.
He teaches me lots of things
about the outside world.
That's a good brother to have, huh?
As the Chinese civil war escalates,
what should Japan's response be?
Well, I think it's important
to understand just what
it is these militants called the Xi want,
and be prepared to sit
down and talk with them.
Sit down and talk with the Xi?
Is all Japanese media like this?
The Xi, was it?
The weekly magazines talk about them
like they're some kind of alien invaders.
I wonder if they're going to attack Komatsu.
Don't worry.
If they do, I'll protect the city.
Welcome!
Keep your mouth shut, dummy.
But it's important.
I was made to protect humanity.
Even if I'm unstable during flight,
I need to fight until the very end
and shoot down the enemy.
I see.
She's trying her best to protect humanity,
in her own way.
Kei...
I want more gyoza.
The Gripen is an extremely unstable weapon.
The slightest thing causes it to lose
function and go out of control.
My bosses are telling me they
don't want to waste any more money
on a prototype without obvious potential.
But as a scientist, I want to keep
struggling until the very end.
Will you help me?
Help her fly again.
Here.
I didn't know what you liked...
So I just bought something at random.
If you don't like it, you can have this one.
No, yogurt drinks are a favorite.
But I remembered something
slightly unpleasant.
Unpleasant?
Someone once told me that my body
wasn't developing properly,
and I should drink lots of dairy products.
If I liked sweets,
then I should drink yogurt.
It would make my breasts bigger.
It was very rude.
Y-Yeah.
It's good.
Oh, I'm glad you like it.
This may be the first time
I've ever drank yogurt.
What?
I thought you said it was a favorite.
Hey, Gripen!
What's wrong?
Are you okay?
Don't worry.
She's asleep, that's all.
Yashirodoori...
"Yashirodoori-san" to you, Prince Charming.
I'm older than you, you know.
What are you doing?
Don't worry. They work for me.
What is the point of all this?
Just leaving the two of us
together with no explanation...
Three hours.
That's how often Gripen
is awake, on average.
That's usually how long it
takes before she passes out...
Regardless of whether she's
in the middle of the air or not.
But today...
That's right. She was up and
about for over ten hours.
I'm surprised.
And all she did was go on a
child's idea of a date with you.
You were watching?
We have no idea what it
is that wakes her up.
I'd like to develop a hypothesis and
investigate, but we don't have a lot of time.
The date of her test
flight has been decided.
Her test flight?
Exactly one week from today.
If she can't fly right then,
she'll be scrapped this time.
Scrapped?
I did everything I could.
Well, just take it as a sign that
Anima cost a lot more than you think.
There's no denying the fact
that they're inefficient.
But the other Anima keep adding to
their flight hours with no problems.
It makes sense to just scrap a plane with
no future and move on to the next one.
But...
If it weren't for her, we'd be dead.
Then it's time pay her back.
Stop whining and help us, Prince Charming.
I've been wondering...
Why do you keep calling me that?
Because in the fairy tales,
it's always Prince Charming's
kiss that wakes up the princess.
Even if it's the princess
who goes in for the kiss first.
Dara viitoare în Girly Air Force...
ALT 03: "Nucleul Anima."
Nucleul Anima
Barbie 01, gata de decolare!
Narutani