Ei-kun! Ei-kun! Open up!
Can you hear me, Eita-kun?
Hime?!
Eita...
What's going on?!
Y-You're naked!
It was predetermined in ages long past
that the reincarnation of the holy dragon,
descended from the heavens, should be—
I don't care! Why are you naked?!
It... was my first time.
Could I get a real answer, please?!
The world needed more love. Sufficient?
Completely insufficient!
Then hold me.
Hey!
Why is the door locked?!
Open this door!
This is bad!
Don't worry, Eita.
That is most likely the sound of poltergeists.
Low-level spirits, controlled by the Wyverns.
You can banish them by chanting
"I love you, Hime-chan, with all my heart," 100 times.
In a loud, clear voice, now.
Or you could help me escape in that time!
Harusaki-san, why don't we just break the door down?
Sounds good to me! We'll just blame Ei-kun for it!
I shall deceive the lowly spirits.
With my holy aura, it will be but child's play.
No! Not while looking like that!
Now, Eita-kun. Get on your knees and start apologizing.
Ei-kun! Pork bowl, beef steak, and a hamburger!
Ei-kun! Pork bowl, beef steak, and a ha—
Huh? Only you, Himecchi?
Akishino-san, where is Eita-kun?
Unknown.
I don't believe that for a second.
He said he was going to rest in the nurse's office
because he wasn't feeling well during class.
I'm certain I heard both of your voices coming from this room.
The wind was quite loud until a moment ago.
It must have been the wind.
The wind?
A wind that blew something bad into this town.
You could call it a challenge from the underworld.
Yes, I see. The wind.
Just out of curiosity, Akishino-san,
why aren't you wearing any clothes?
It... was my first time.
Hey!
Your first time doing what?
Locking my lover from my past life in loving emb—
M-My first time receiving a challenge from the underworld.
You're sweating.
Th-These are merely the tears of my weeping soul.
Natsukawa?
Hime! Do something!
No! You mustn't, Shadow!
If you use your second transformation here...
No! Calm yourself, my right arm.
Damn it, Hime!
You!
What do you think you're doing here?!
isse-no
One, two, three
okaeri
Welcome back
saa dekakeyou
Now, let's go out
nukegake rendezvous
I'm stealing you for a rendezvous
kizuna ga daiji
Friends are important
koibito ga daiichi
But a girlfriend is the most
Girlish Lover
My
Girlfriend
And
Childhood Friend
Fight
Too
Much
kono itami kimi no sei
This pain I feel is your fault
mune no tokimeki uso no tsumori
This feeling in my chest is supposed to be a lie
ima made no position wo
What would happen if tomorrow
koeta ashita wa dou naru no
I tried being more than what I am to you now?
nee motto issho shiyou
Hey, let's spend more time together
dame
Can't we?
dame watashi dake
You can't, he's mine
yudan mo suki mo nai
You can never be too careful with me
kimi to no border koetai
I want to jump the border between us
sou motto
Now, I'll be
daitan de chotto gouin
A bit bolder, maybe even aggressive
suki wo misetai
I want to show you my love
yasashii kimi mo
I want you when you're nice
ijiwaru na kimi mo
I want you when you're mean
hitorijime
You're all mine
kitsui tte
Too much for you?
yappa yamete
You really want to stop?
urahara fall in love
It's the wrong way to fall in love
tomodachi ijou
I'm more than just your friend,
honmono miman no
But less than a real
Girlish Lover
My
Girlfriend
And
Childhood Friend
Fight
Too
Much
My
Girlfriend
And
Childhood Friend
Fight
Too
Much
My
Girlfriend
And
Childhood Friend
Fight
Too
Much
My
Girlfriend
And
Childhood Friend
Fight
Too
Much
My
Girlfriend
And
Childhood Friend
Fight
Too
Much
My
Girlfriend
And
Childhood Friend
Fight
Too
Much
My
Girlfriend
And
Childhood Friend
Fight
Too
Much
My
Girlfriend
And
Childhood Friend
Fight
Too
Much
My
Girlfriend
And
Childhood Friend
Fight
Too
Much
My
Girlfriend
And
Childhood Friend
Fight
Too
Much
My
Girlfriend
And
Childhood Friend
Fight
Too
Much
My
Girlfriend
And
Childhood Friend
Fight
Too
Much
My
Girlfriend
And
Childhood Friend
Fight
Too
Much
My
Girlfriend
And
Childhood Friend
Fight
Too
Much
My
Girlfriend
And
Childhood Friend
Fight
Too
Much
My
Girlfriend
And
Childhood Friend
Fight
Too
Much
My
Girlfriend
And
Childhood Friend
Fight
Too
Much
My
Girlfriend
And
Childhood Friend
Fight
Too
Much
Do you even have an ounce of common sense?
Summer School Turns Into a War Zone
The nurse's office is not a playground!
You bunch of samefags!
Samefags?
You're horrible!
I poured my heart and soul into creating that club name!
How could you abbreviate it like that!
Look who's talking.
You're the horrible ones.
Akishino-san used to be a model student, but now look at her.
I'm so happy, Eita.
You've finally remembered our connection from our past lives.
Yay! We'll never be separated again!
Well, it is hot today.
As I told you yesterday, it's been decided that your club will be shut down.
Get that through your thick skulls and disband.
Yeah, yeah, sure!
That didn't sound very sincere to me!
Woof!
What's with your attitude?
I get it.
You're just jealous.
Excuse me?
You're jealous of us because we're trying to become popular.
What?
I bet you don't even get a chance to talk to guys since all the hall monitors are girls.
You know you'll never find a boyfriend.
You're jealous, so you want to get rid of the Society.
Is that true?
Don't make fun of me!
I totally have a boyfriend!
Idiot!
Is your boyfriend a student at this school?
L-Like I'd ever be interested in a guy my own age.
H-He's a college student. At one of the best schools in Tokyo.
He's also the heir to a certain financial group.
It's a long distance relationship, so we don't see each other often,
but he texts me every day!
And he's really kind too.
How lovely! I'm so jealous.
I hope you die.
May I ask his name?
M-Michel? Murata Michel Daigorou!
His mother's American!
Pretty cool, huh?
Impressive, right?
Let's go.
We're leaving, Himecchi. Get dressed.
Okay.
Hold it.
Something else?
I-Is Kidou-kun with you today?
It seems he left early today.
Oh.
What do you want from Ei-kun?
N-Nothing!
What makes you think I need something from him?
Out of my way!
What the hell?!
She's so irritating!
Let's go.
Remember this, Eita.
HALL MONITOR
LINE DO NOT
CROSS
HALL MONITOR
LINE DO NOT
CROSS
HALL MONITOR
LINE DO NOT
CROSS
HALL MONITOR
LINE DO NOT
CROSS
HALL MONITOR
LINE DO NOT
CROSS
HALL MONITOR
LINE DO NOT
CROSS
HALL MONITOR
LINE DO NOT
CROSS
HALL MONITOR
LINE DO NOT
CROSS
HALL MONITOR
LINE DO NOT
CROSS
HALL MONITOR
LINE DO NOT
CROSS
HALL MONITOR
LINE DO NOT
CROSS
HALL MONITOR
LINE DO NOT
CROSS
HALL MONITOR
LINE DO NOT
CROSS
HALL MONITOR
LINE DO NOT
CROSS
HALL MONITOR
LINE DO NOT
CROSS
HALL MONITOR
LINE DO NOT
CROSS
HALL MONITOR
LINE DO NOT
CROSS
HALL MONITOR
LINE DO NOT
CROSS
HALL MONITOR
LINE DO NOT
CROSS
Fuyuumi Ai forced SAMEFAG to shut down.
HALL MONITOR
LINE DO NOT
CROSS
HALL MONITOR
LINE DO NOT
CROSS
HALL MONITOR
LINE DO NOT
CROSS
HALL MONITOR
LINE DO NOT
CROSS
HALL MONITOR
LINE DO NOT
CROSS
HALL MONITOR
LINE DO NOT
CROSS
HALL MONITOR
LINE DO NOT
CROSS
HALL MONITOR
LINE DO NOT
CROSS
HALL MONITOR
LINE DO NOT
CROSS
HALL MONITOR
LINE DO NOT
CROSS
HALL MONITOR
LINE DO NOT
CROSS
HALL MONITOR
LINE DO NOT
CROSS
HALL MONITOR
LINE DO NOT
CROSS
HALL MONITOR
LINE DO NOT
CROSS
HALL MONITOR
LINE DO NOT
CROSS
HALL MONITOR
LINE DO NOT
CROSS
HALL MONITOR
LINE DO NOT
CROSS
HALL MONITOR
LINE DO NOT
CROSS
HALL MONITOR
LINE DO NOT
CROSS
HALL MONITOR
LINE DO NOT
CROSS
HALL MONITOR
LINE DO NOT
CROSS
HALL MONITOR
LINE DO NOT
CROSS
HALL MONITOR
LINE DO NOT
CROSS
HALL MONITOR
LINE DO NOT
CROSS
HALL MONITOR
LINE DO NOT
CROSS
HALL MONITOR
LINE DO NOT
CROSS
HALL MONITOR
LINE DO NOT
CROSS
HALL MONITOR
LINE DO NOT
CROSS
HALL MONITOR
LINE DO NOT
CROSS
HALL MONITOR
LINE DO NOT
CROSS
HALL MONITOR
LINE DO NOT
CROSS
HALL MONITOR
LINE DO NOT
CROSS
HALL MONITOR
LINE DO NOT
CROSS
HALL MONITOR
LINE DO NOT
CROSS
HALL MONITOR
LINE DO NOT
CROSS
HALL MONITOR
LINE DO NOT
CROSS
HALL MONITOR
LINE DO NOT
CROSS
HALL MONITOR
LINE DO NOT
CROSS
HALL MONITOR
LINE DO NOT
CROSS
HALL MONITOR
LINE DO NOT
CROSS
HALL MONITOR
LINE DO NOT
CROSS
HALL MONITOR
LINE DO NOT
CROSS
HALL MONITOR
LINE DO NOT
CROSS
HALL MONITOR
LINE DO NOT
CROSS
HALL MONITOR
LINE DO NOT
CROSS
HALL MONITOR
LINE DO NOT
CROSS
HALL MONITOR
LINE DO NOT
CROSS
HALL MONITOR
LINE DO NOT
CROSS
HALL MONITOR
LINE DO NOT
CROSS
HALL MONITOR
LINE DO NOT
CROSS
HALL MONITOR
LINE DO NOT
CROSS
HALL MONITOR
LINE DO NOT
CROSS
HALL MONITOR
LINE DO NOT
CROSS
HALL MONITOR
LINE DO NOT
CROSS
HALL MONITOR
LINE DO NOT
CROSS
HALL MONITOR
LINE DO NOT
CROSS
HALL MONITOR
LINE DO NOT
CROSS
HALL MONITOR
LINE DO NOT
CROSS
HALL MONITOR
LINE DO NOT
CROSS
HALL MONITOR
LINE DO NOT
CROSS
HALL MONITOR
LINE DO NOT
CROSS
HALL MONITOR
LINE DO NOT
CROSS
HALL MONITOR
LINE DO NOT
CROSS
HALL MONITOR
LINE DO NOT
CROSS
HALL MONITOR
LINE DO NOT
CROSS
HALL MONITOR
LINE DO NOT
CROSS
HALL MONITOR
LINE DO NOT
CROSS
HALL MONITOR
LINE DO NOT
CROSS
HALL MONITOR
LINE DO NOT
CROSS
HALL MONITOR
LINE DO NOT
CROSS
HALL MONITOR
LINE DO NOT
CROSS
HALL MONITOR
LINE DO NOT
CROSS
HALL MONITOR
LINE DO NOT
CROSS
HALL MONITOR
LINE DO NOT
CROSS
HALL MONITOR
LINE DO NOT
CROSS
HALL MONITOR
LINE DO NOT
CROSS
HALL MONITOR
LINE DO NOT
CROSS
HALL MONITOR
LINE DO NOT
CROSS
HALL MONITOR
LINE DO NOT
CROSS
HALL MONITOR
LINE DO NOT
CROSS
HALL MONITOR
LINE DO NOT
CROSS
HALL MONITOR
LINE DO NOT
CROSS
HALL MONITOR
LINE DO NOT
CROSS
HALL MONITOR
LINE DO NOT
CROSS
HALL MONITOR
LINE DO NOT
CROSS
HALL MONITOR
LINE DO NOT
CROSS
HALL MONITOR
LINE DO NOT
CROSS
HALL MONITOR
LINE DO NOT
CROSS
HALL MONITOR
LINE DO NOT
CROSS
HALL MONITOR
LINE DO NOT
CROSS
HALL MONITOR
LINE DO NOT
CROSS
HALL MONITOR
LINE DO NOT
CROSS
HALL MONITOR
LINE DO NOT
CROSS
HALL MONITOR
LINE DO NOT
CROSS
And so, our club meetings over summer vacation were canceled.
But the club being shut down is a blessing for me!
My daily supplemental summer classes start today!
To earn the school's recommendation...
Farewell, SAMEFAG!
Farewell, war zones!
Wh-Why are you here?
Why? I came here for summer school.
Wh-What class are you in?!
Class Z.
This is freakin' awesome! Ai-chan, epic win!
What?
You did not just hear that!
You heard nothing!
Wh-Why are you in the same class as me?
You're so shameless.
Don't ask me.
But if you're in class Z, does that mean you're shooting for a top-tier college too?
I haven't decided yet.
I just want to be prepared for any eventuality.
Good thinking.
It's always better to have more options.
I could apply myself after I've figured out what I want to do,
but I don't want to start panicking when I'm a third-year.
And the prep courses here—
You idiot!
The hell?
Why are you trying to be all buddy-buddy with me?
We're supposed to be enemies!
Enemies?
Don't play dumb.
You and your samefagging club.
Oh, that.
You'll infect me with your samefag if I keep talking to you.
Excuse me.
It's not infectious.
Morning, Eita.
Oh, morning.
You were just talking to A-chan, weren't you?
A-chan?
You mean Fuyuumi?
Yeah.
She and I were in the same class back in elementary school.
Oh, really?
I never imagined A-chan would take one of these courses.
Hm, I see. What a coincidence.
So Kaoru knows Fuyuumi, huh?
It just melts in my mouth.
Eat the vegetables too, damn it.
I could be with you every day if I went to those classes too.
Speaking of which, she's taking them too.
Fuyuumi Ai, I mean.
What? Are you serious?
How does she have time to study when she has a boyfriend?
Is there bad blood between you two or something?
Like there wouldn't be!
I got called to the faculty room because I was fighting with Fuyuumi.
It's like she's got a grudge against me or something.
Hey, Ei-kun, did anyone ever ask you out before Natsukawa?
Nope.
Wait... I take that back.
Once, during kindergarten.
Oh, one of those.
Doing anything on August 4th this year?
What's happening then?
The Hane River fireworks show.
Oh, it's that time of year again, huh?
I couldn't go last year.
Wanna go with me this year?
Come on, Ei-kun!
I'll pass.
I want to focus on studying.
Come on, can't you take a break for once?
No.
I've decided to spend all my time studying this summer.
Why do you have to be so freaking serious all the time?
Received Message
Natsukawa Masuzu
I have your notebook.
If you want it back, come alone to the cafe near the station by 8 pm.
If you don't, your dark, dark, dark past in your note, note, notebook
will be leak, leak, leaked to the world! Your dark, dark, dark past in your note, note, notebook...
I forgot...
The club might be gone,
but my girlfriend isn't!
You're late, Eita.
It took you 11 minutes and 38.39 seconds
to get here after replying to my text.
You knew it'd take me at least ten minutes running!
You're such a useless man.
Can't you travel through Dark Space?
Well, excuse me for not being a Stand user.
You really are useless.
That wasn't very clever.
And what's this all about?
Why are you talking to me like that?
When I decided to stay here, I realized something.
There's no reason to pretend that we're dating when it's just the two of us,
so I'm going to be the twisted bitch I am.
I see.
Anyway, it seems you've been getting chummy with Fuyuumi Ai at your summer school.
How do you know about that?
I want you to dig up some dirty laundry on her.
What? On Fuyuumi?
Why?
So I can get the Society up and running again.
It's the only way we can prevent the hall monitors from interfering.
Dirty laundry, huh?
I discovered a valuable piece of information from Fuyuumi Ai's classmates.
No one's ever heard of this Daigorou.
Huh?
You remember how she was bragging about her boyfriend, don't you?
No. When was this?
She shared all of those details with us, her arch-nemeses,
but she kept it a secret from her classmates.
There's only one way to explain this:
Daigorou doesn't exist.
Fuyuumi Ai just made him up.
I want you to find evidence that Daigorou is a fabrication.
Easily said, but...
how do I do that?
A-chan was amazing back there, wasn't she?
Yeah, that quadratic was pretty long.
I'm not talking about that.
Remember how all the guys surrounded her during the break?
Oh, yeah.
She looked kind of ticked off.
Maybe she really does have a boyfriend.
A-chan's cute and smart.
It's no surprise that she'd be popular.
She's a good cook too.
Don't you think A-chan's cute too?
Do you like Fuyuumi or something?
Why would you think that?!
Have you been listening to me at all?
Besides, A-chan has someone she likes.
For crying out... I'll be right back.
Come on, A-chan. Say hi.
Say hi!
You're stupid!
That's no way to greet someone, now is it?
It's fine. Relax.
I heard you went to the same elementary school as Kaoru.
That's right. Got a problem with that?
No. Not at all.
A-chan and I were in the same class from first to fourth grade.
Wow, so you guys go way back.
She moved away in fifth grade, so we went to different middle schools.
But she came back to town this spring.
So that makes you and Fuyuumi childhood friends, doesn't it?
Why are you glaring at me?
No reason!
A-chan...
I'll stop helping you.
I'm sorry.
Good. Now, why don't you give it to him?
K-Kidou-kun!
Help yourself...
Help yourself!
Huh? What?
Eat some, Eita.
She wouldn't have much left for herself...
I'll share my jam roll with A-chan later.
Maybe just a bite, then.
Oh, this is good.
This is really good.
I'm gonna go run a bit.
Huh?
I'm gonna go run a bit!
Hey!
What's gotten into her?
She's happy that you complimented her cooking.
Really?
Hey, Eita.
Yeah?
A-chan can act kind of defensive sometimes,
but there's a reason for that.
So could you give some thought to why she acts the way she does?
Why are you telling me that?
She has a boyfriend, doesn't she?
What?! A-chan has a boyfriend?!
Wait, where'd you hear that?!
She said she had a boyfriend named Michel...
Huh?
Pass in One Shot!
Hanenoyama Seminar
Eita.
Got any plans for the rest of the day?
Chiwa's having dinner with her parents tonight, so I'm eating out alone.
Oh, that sounds nice.
Mind if we tagged along?
Sure, I don't mind.
Huh? Why?
Weren't we going to grab a bite on the way home too?
When did we decide to do that?
Can't you see that this is a golden opportunity?
Maybe you'd like to cooperate for it?
Oh, I see!
Very well! We'll have dinner with you!
Right. Thanks.
Fuyuumi, I noticed you always go out in your uniform.
Of course I do. It's a school rule.
You have to wear your uniform if you're going out.
You're a real stickler for the rules, aren't you?
Do you wear your uniform on dates too?
About that, Eita...
Come on, A-chan.
Um... About Michel...
Actually... he... well...
Actually, he...
Actually, he what?
Chiwa? What are you doing here?
We were on our way to the steakhouse, but then I spotted you in here.
So, what were you about to say?
That you were lying about having a boyfriend?
I...
Cut it out.
Fuyuumi wouldn't lie about having a boyfriend.
I mean, just look at her.
She wears her uniform during summer vacation because it's a rule.
You think someone who follows the rules to the letter would lie?
You actually believe her, Ei-kun?
Our Society got shut down because of her.
She was putting on a front because Natsukawa and me were pushing her.
Only people who don't have anything to be proud of put on fronts.
Fuyuumi gets good grades and takes her hall monitor duties seriously.
She's got no reason to lie.
Right, Fuyuumi?
That's right.
I'm ranked third in our grade, a hall monitor, and honest to a fault.
I wouldn't get worked up enough to do something so incredibly stupid and lie about it!
Hey...
I don't want to lose to her!
Michel and I are head over heels for each other.
And we've got plenty of dates planned over the break.
Please, tell me more.
You're here too, Hime?!
I was investigating Point CPS,
when I felt a strong Dragonic aura.
CPS? What's CPS?
And then Eita was there.
I want to hear more about Michel.
What?
I still have much to learn about the ways of the present world.
CPS... CPS...
Central Police Station?
The best way of doing so would be to absorb information
Oh, wait!
The prep school? College Prep School!
from a knowledgeable present-day individual.
The president said it would be best for me to ask Fuyuumi Ai.
That explains things. Another of Masuzu's plots.
Please, Master.
Master?!
I wanna hear more too!
Very well!
I'll tell you!
A-chan?
I usually wear a white one-piece when we go on dates.
He seems to be fond of clothes that give a "pure" feeling.
Guys like it when you wear clothes that give the impression that you're trying too hard.
That said, they'll laugh at you for wearing accessories that make you look kiddy, like ribbons.
This is very useful. I want to hear more.
Sure! Ask me anything!
How long have you been dating Michel?
Two years... No, half a year? About a year, maybe.
How did you two meet?
I think he tutored me during middle school—
No, I mean, I'm certain he did.
I was surprised when he asked me out,
but I wasn't dating anyone at the time.
Wait, does that mean you dated someone before him?
Michel's probably my third boyfriend.
They all asked me out!
I'm actually way more popular than Natsukawa Masuzu!
You're so cool.
Let me call you "Love Master" from now on.
Be my guest! Call me whatever you'd like!
Women are such a pain.
Well, my house is this way. See you.
All right. Talk to you later.
Kidou-kun.
Um...
What did you think when you heard I had a boyfriend?
Why do you ask?
No, sorry, it's nothing. Forget it.
Have a good night.
Yeah, you too.
See you tomorrow.
Yeah...
See you... tomorrow.
mirai he to futari no Wonder tale
Unfolding into the future, a wonderful tale about us
senaka ni sasayakitai no
I want to whisper to you,
mune no naka sotto misete
Secretly show me what's in your heart
hontou wa ienai kikenai kara
But because I can't say it, I can't ask you,
ijiwaru shitakunaru
I just have to pick on you
konna hazu ja nai
It wasn't supposed to be this way,
watashi no kokoro ga
But my heart just can't help but sing,
shiranai tokimeki mo utaidasu
Skipping beats that it never knew could be,
girigiri no atsusa de
With a passion, about to explode
mirai he to futari no Wonder tale
Unfolding into the future, a wonderful tale about us
hajimari ga kowai no ni tomaranai
I'm afraid that it might start, but I can't stop it
kimi no hitomi ga watashi no tame ni
I wonder why I want your eyes
kagayaite hoshii no wa naze kashira
To start shining for me
koi na no oshiete yo
Is this love? Can't you tell me?
Next Episode
The popucute item for next week is...
a movie ticket.
If you use this piece of paper at Point TMT,
A Double Date at the Movie Theater Turns Into a War Zone
you can experience a surge of pathos.
Let the show playing on the silver screen that sunders darkness take away your body and soul.