Why am I on the floor?
Let's Start Our Quiet Life Together
Morning.
Sleep well?
Not really.
Maybe I'm not used to that bed.
I got it for next to nothing, so I'm not surprised.
But that's not really why I had trouble sleeping.
Thanks for the food!
It's delicious!
Eat up.
We have a busy day ahead.
Okay!
After buying my new bed,
I'll head home and bring back a few paintings
that'll suit the store.
Paintings?
The impact of artwork is nothing to sneeze at.
Placing the right piece of art in a good spot
is sure to boost sales.
Really?
I never heard of that.
We also have to go ask the Zoltan Council
to approve your new pain killer.
It'll probably take some negotiating.
Leave the negotiating to me.
About my salary...
How about one and a half payril a day,
for a total of thirty a month?
That's a pretty reasonable salary for live-in help.
For Rit, though, it seems low.
But what if she says she doesn't need a salary?
I'd probably insist on a higher amount
more suited to her standing.
Okay, let's go with that.
Great!
Wait a second.
Did she say she wanted to live here
so I wouldn't worry about her salary?
Don't tell me she had it all planned out?
Thanks, Rit.
Huh?
Oh, sure, my pleasure?
Zoltan is far removed
from the threat of the Demon Lord's army
and doesn't send troops to the front.
It's a land with no need for the Hero.
A land with no need for the Hero?
Sometimes I used to feel like something was missing.
Oh?
I didn't stay with you all in the Hero's party.
Although if I had,
I might have found a life adventuring
with you and the others satisfying, but...
being here with you now is what I'd rather have.
We have left the blood-soaked path of the Hero.
We now walk the land of Zoltan
simply as Red and Rit.
Stormy, you there?
If it isn't, Lady Rit!
Thank you for choosing to shop at my—
What's Red doing here?
Well, it's a long story.
I decided to move in with Red.
So I'm here to buy a bed.
Congratulations!
Red, you lucky dog, you!
Nudge, nudge, wink, wink.
Wait.
I think you've got the wrong idea.
Hey, Storm.
You weren't nearly this nice to me
when I shopped here.
Of course! Customers who haggle
for 30 minutes over a cheapo bed
don't get treated like those
who pay full price for a quality product!
Good point.
This walnut double bed is perfect!
Make it a single!
Friggin wuss...
Tsk!
Say that again!
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Wanna
piece
of me?
Coward...
The bed won't fit in my item box,
so please deliver it to the shop.
Okay, you got it.
Thanks for your business!
There's lots of good stuff at Stormy's shop.
Stormthunder has the Craftsman Blessing
and he's leveled it way up.
Wow, Red.
You can tell how high a Blessing's level is!
Truth is, I found out after helping him hunt monsters
in lieu of paying for a purchase.
I see.
The Almighty deity Demis grants a Divine Blessing
to all living things at birth.
Lineage and education
have no impact on the Blessing granted.
Orphans from the slums have been granted
the Strategist and General Blessings.
Strategist
Thief
General
And those of royal birth
have been granted the Thief Blessing.
General
Thief
Their success depends on whether
they can level up their Blessing.
So then the question is, how does one level up?
There's but one way.
You must battle and slay someone who has a Blessing.
It's the same with all Blessings,
whether they're battle-related or not.
People kill each other to level up their Blessings.
This world is ripe with violence.
Tanta!
You okay?
You son of a...!
Is that a skill?
Hey, stop it!
That's enough!
Butt out!
At your level, you should be
fighting monsters with the adults.
You talk tough,
but all you got is that crappy bronze sword!
Tanta, you okay?
Y-Yeah.
You okay, too?
Y-Yeah, but...
His name's Red.
He's my friend.
He's also an apothecary and adventurer.
Wow, really?
That's why he's so strong.
This is my friend, Al.
Al, it looks like your knee's hurt.
Huh?
We gotta patch you up.
Miss Rit.
Wait. What are you doing with Red?
Well, he and I are very close friends.
I even moved in with him yesterday.
What?!
Is Red really dependable enough
for something like that?
I worry about that a bit as well.
That should do it.
It'll feel better in a few days.
Thank you.
Why were you fighting?
It was the other guy's fault.
We were playing, but he told us to scram
'cause we were in his way.
He's already developing his Blessing.
That was a pretty good attack for a kid.
Ademi wasn't always so violent.
But he's been a real hothead lately.
He must've connected with his Blessing.
Does connecting affect everyone like that?
Well, Divine Blessings
also influence a person's personality.
What do you mean?
For example, with the Craftsman Blessing,
you'll start to like making things.
And with the Mage Blessing,
your thirst for knowledge will grow.
So what's Ademi's Blessing?
He probably has the Tavern Brawler Blessing.
Tavern Brawler?
It's a Blessing focused on fighting
with whatever's at hand.
They'll use anything they have as a weapon,
like rocks or booze jugs.
They have skills for knocking people over
or through the air and so on.
The problem is, Ademi has
a really high affinity for his Blessing.
An affinity?
If one's body and soul are well suited for their Blessing,
they give one an affinity for its skills.
So Ademi is a natural-born brawler.
A natural-born brawler?
What a crappy Blessing.
Yeah, you hit the nail on the head.
It would be great if all Blessings
were socially acceptable.
But some aren't
and they can steer people toward evil.
Ademi's Blessing inclines him toward
resorting to violence when he encounters obstacles.
I see.
You needn't worry about it.
His Blessing had a powerful—
I don't want a Blessing.
Don't say that!
The Church elders won't like it if they hear you!
Have you discovered what your Blessing is yet?
Yes.
I have the Weapon Master Blessing.
Wow, I'm impressed!
That's a fighter-type Blessing
which enables you to master a weapon.
But if it means I'm gonna be like Ademi...
Al, I know exactly how you feel.
It's a scary thing to come to terms
with your Blessing.
After all, it's almost like your life
is completely decided by it.
Rit has the Spirit Scout Blessing.
That means she is a scout for forest dwellers.
Maybe one reason Rit couldn't live quietly in the castle
Spirit Scout
was because her Blessing naturally craves freedom.
But no matter what Blessing you have,
you'll always be who you are.
Really?
Blessings are only one part of you.
For example, a normally gentle mother
may sometimes raise holy hell when angry.
I see.
There are lots of different parts
of who we are as a whole—
one's Blessing is one of them.
You're not a slave to your Blessing.
It's only a part of you and can be controlled.
Do that and your Blessing
will prove quite useful in the future.
Really?
Yeah.
The Weapon Master Blessing
gives you lots of skills for overcoming
fear and confusion as long as
you have your weapon in hand.
Um, I'm kinda afraid of the dark.
Will it help me get over that?
Sure!
You won't be afraid, no matter how dark it is.
That's a relief!
Thanks, Mr. Red!
Al, let's get going.
All right.
Come by our shop any time
you're feeling anxious about something.
That's if you don't mind advice
from a D-rank adventurer.
Thanks!
Can I come over to visit... even if I don't need advice?
Sure.
I'll even make you something to eat.
Hurray!
Bye-bye!
Well, we should get going, too.
We gotta go get Red and Rit's Apothecary's
future hit product approved!
You sure about this?
Once we change the shop's name,
I won't let you off so easy if you want to quit.
Are you saying you want me to stay here forever?
I said no!
Absolutely not!
B-But...
This mixture is less addictive than—
I'm a busy man.
Now get that out of my face and scram!
We've no choice but to go over his head!
It's worth a shot.
Aye-aye, Captain!
You always worked solo, Miss Rit.
I never expected you to team up with someone.
This should be interesting.
So, what can I do for you?
Well...
I see.
I must apologize for that,
but your timing couldn't have been worse.
Has something happened?
We discovered that
a remedy we approved about a month ago
is being misused as an illegal narcotic.
It's spreading on the black market
to everyone from townsfolk to nobles.
It was only approved a month ago?
The new remedy
was mass-produced outside of town,
and once it was approved, it flooded the market.
Its maker was clearly targeting
illicit use from the start.
This fiasco has done great harm to our reputation.
Dan, who is in charge of the new remedy,
has been dealing with angry townsfolk non-stop.
I see.
But since this request is from you,
Miss Rit, I'll personally approve it.
You'd really do that?
Thank you!
Sorry for making you do all the heavy lifting.
No need to apologize.
Yeah, but I did say,
"Leave the negotiating to me," like an idiot.
I'm just happy that I can help you.
And I wanna keep doing so.
I'd do anything for you!
Thank you, Rit. I, um...
I'll be counting on you.
I know!
Well, it's good the new medicine was approved,
but it'll be a while before
word spreads about its effectiveness.
Yeah, the shop needs a hit remedy
that is fast-acting in the sales department.
A hit remedy?
Any revolutionary ideas for something
customers will want to buy at all costs?
Let's eat while we think it over.
Great idea!
You really are a good cook, Red!
How about serving food alongside your medicines?
Don't be silly.
My Cooking skill is really low.
I can't compete with a professional chef.
Plus, I've never heard of an apothecary that serves...
An apothecary that serves food?
What is it?
There's something I want to try here...
What's that?
A nutritional supplement.
It helps prevent colds and other illnesses,
and recover from exhaustion...
But it's difficult to take because it's so bitter.
Apple jam?
I'm using my Cooking skill to make the bitterness
accentuate the jam's sweetness.
And my Elementary Preparation skill lets me bake them
without destroying their nutritional value.
I get it. It's medicine in cookie form.
Now for the final test.
So tasty!
This just might work!
Definitely!
Get your free samples
from Red and Rit's Apothecary right here!
It can help prevent colds!
Medicine without the bitterness!
Would you like to try one?
They're also good for post-battle exhaustion.
Get your free samples here!
Would you like to try one?
Cookies?
No thanks.
Welcome.
Our daughter caught a cold and now has a fever.
I heard you sell medicinal cookies.
We sure do.
Would you like to try one?
They contain that bitter medicine, don't they?
It's delicious!
My daughter won't mind eating this!
I'd like one, too!
My pleasure!
We sold 'em all.
Yeah.
Yay!
It's all thanks to you, Rit!
Y-You really think so?
You just made my day.
Without you,
I'd probably still be twiddling my thumbs
without a customer in sight.
Rit!
Thank you for being there for me!
S-Sure.
I'm so happy I can be here with you, Red.
I'll never forget each and every word you just said!
I'm sick of this!
Do you even realize how much time
we've wasted in this desert?!
The desert dwellers are useless,
and we haven't a single lead
for the weapon we're after.
And now you want to go back to resupply again?!
It can't be helped, now can it?
The previous Demon Lord's weapon
isn't going to be easy to find.
I did my best trying to negotiate
with the desert dwellers,
but they are a lowly people
who won't even obey the king of this land.
The state of supplies and negotiations
was never this bad when Gideon was here.
Are you saying I'm less useful than him?
I'm a Sage, all he has are just common skills!
Enough is enough!
I'm gonna go find Gideon!
You can't do that.
Please, wait!
I only joined this party because it seemed like
the most direct route to defeating the Demon Lord.
If that's no longer true,
there's no point in me being here.
Banishing Gideon from the party
was a fatal mistake, Ares.
He left of his own free will.
Danan, you're going to look for my brother?
M-Milady!
We need Gideon in our party.
Surely even you...
Even I, what?
N-no, nothing...
I'll allow it.
Now go.
Danan.
Find my brother.
We will continue our journey.
Ruti...
So, what will you do?
I've no choice but to go.
Say, you don't also think Ares might've killed Gideon
because he was in his way, do you?
Are you referring to Yaradrala's suspicions?
She was in tears.
She likely recognized Sir Gideon's abilities.
He was truly skilled in battle.
I was always amazed he could fight at the level he did
with nothing more than common skills.
He was a tactician worthy of respect.
Yet you never failed to criticize his combat blunders.
Th-That's just the kind of man I am.
Mistakes are bound to repeat
unless they're called out.
But I can swear on my Divine Blessing,
I never once thought Gideon
was a liability to our party or hindering us in any way.
Then maybe you should have actually let him know that.
We both know Sir Gideon is a worthy fighter.
That means a lot coming from you,
the greatest martial artist of our times,
and me, acting master
of the Temple Knight's style of spear fighting.
No matter how skilled a mage Ares is,
he'd be hard-pressed to slay a knight
revered by two skilled combatants such as us.
You're absolutely right.
Gideon must still be alive!
I'm off to find him!