Where are all the customers?
My medicinal herbs and concoctions will expire
if no one buys them.
But with this rain, the Zoltanites
will probably just stay home.
Welcome!
Gideon.
It really is you.
Rit.
It's been ages, Gideon.
The Princess Who Did (Not) Join the Hero’s Party
Actually, I go by "Red" here.
So it seems.
I heard at the guild.
I never expected to see you in Zoltan.
She is a B-rank adventurer here in Zoltan.
Her full name is Rizlet of Loggervia,
the second princess of the Duchy of Loggervia,
a major military power.
What about you?
Why's a princess of Loggervia
working as a B-rank adventurer in the boonies?
Some were favoring me for the throne
over my younger brother, the crown prince.
So I left before it tore our family apart.
I'm enjoying my freedom till things settle down.
I see.
By the way, what's with the name?
Rit and Red have a similar sort of ring to them.
Well, I couldn't think of anything else,
so I sorta based it off yours.
That makes me happy to hear.
I see you actually remembered me.
Of course I remember.
We were comrades, even if it wasn't for too long.
A comrade, eh?
So you're still calling me that...
So, Gide—no, I mean, it's Red here...
What are you doing here?
Well...
What the hell?!
You've gotta be kidding me!
You adventured together for so long!
Regardless, it is true that I was a liability.
That's totally not true!
You did your best to ensure
the party always succeeded!
You worked so hard!
Don't get so mad.
Staying meant putting
the lives of my comrades in danger,
so it was probably for the best that I retired
before anything horrible happened.
But are you sure Ruti and the rest of the party
are okay without you?
They defeated Gandor,
one of the Four Heavenly Kings
in the Demon Lord's army.
They're doing fine.
Your tea's grown cold.
I'll go make some more.
No, this is fine.
I haven't seen you in so long.
The least I could do
is serve a decent cup of tea.
I left the Hero's party.
There's nothing more I can do for Ruti.
That's so good...
It's even better than the tea back at court.
That's laying it on thick!
I'm just a novice chef.
I can't compete with the Chef's Divine Blessing.
Then maybe it tastes so good
because you made it just for me.
We met several years ago.
Several years ago
Duchy of Loggervia
Alonor
Several years ago
Duchy of Loggervia
Alonor
Several years ago
Duchy of Loggervia
Alonor
Almost all the orc sightings
have been concentrated in the west.
So then we go defeat them.
They might be scouts.
Most likely.
Hey, sweet maid.
Let's enjoy a drink together.
Hey, don't ignore me.
The name's Dir.
You must've heard of me.
Ow, that hurt.
Wh-What the hell, you bitch!
You've picked the wrong person to hit on.
M-My bad!
I'll be on my way!
Wait!
You haven't paid yet!
Did you think I needed your help?
The Duchy of Loggervia doesn't need the Hero
to crush the Demon Lord's army!
Hmph.
Smug
Pay her no mind, Ruti.
I know.
That little lady's got spunk.
Who do you suppose she is?
That was the Champion Rit,
the most formidable adventurer of all!
Never been defeated in the arena!
She's our pride and joy!
You weren't honest with yourself back then.
You were really prickly.
W-Was I?
Yep... despite defeating countless foes together,
you were always complaining.
But I could be honest with myself at times.
Like when?
Like that time we were
scouting out the mountain village...
Made any progress?
Nope, nothing to speak of.
Looks like the Hero's party isn't very impressive
when it comes to gathering intel.
You're probably right.
We don't have anyone with a Blessing like that.
Well, our investigation
has been making great progress.
Wanna hear about it?
Yeah, let's have it.
All right.
If you say, "Princess Rit,
please share your knowledge with this fool."
I'll be happy to tell you all about it.
Princess Rit,
please share your knowledge with this fool.
Swallowing my pride
is a small price to pay to save Loggervia.
Now I feel bad.
Really?
What's that mean?
Nothing much—I was not expecting
an actual, honest apology from you.
Why you...!
Now I'm not gonna tell you!
Sorry about that.
So, what have you managed to learn?
I found strange tracks around the village.
They indicate recent and frequent
back-and-forth travel from the north.
From the north, eh?
I seem to recall a mountain cabin
used by loggers up there...
That's true, but all the logging
is happening in the northeast right now.
It's strange how the logging continues
even though no wood is being delivered.
Then there are those strange tracks.
Where'd the missing wood go?
I don't know.
There's no sign of it being moved.
Most likely magic, then.
Probably.
Any ideas why the villagers
aren't complaining about this?
Hostages, I bet.
There are almost no kids or old folks left.
So it's a group organized enough
to hold hostages?
Yeah.
That eliminates brigands and goblins.
So it has to be...
The Demon Lord's army.
Hey, Rit, maybe we should
work together on this one.
Huh?
With you and your party?
Don't make me laugh.
I've already beaten back
the Demon Lord's army twice!
Loggervia doesn't need some outsider Hero!
But it wasn't the enemy's main force.
What's your point?
Loggervia has never lost land to invaders.
We win battles, plain and simple!
When that huge force of goblins attacked,
your forebears requested Central's help.
I don't think ignoring obvious means
of boosting its chances for victory
is a point of pride for Loggervia.
No.
I'll take care of this myself.
Then Father won't have to cede command
of any of my master's forces to the Hero.
The entire royal guard will remain his.
Okay.
I won't twist your arm, so...
Here.
What's that for?!
You've been on limited rations too, right?
This better not taste gross!
Well?
Not bad.
Where'd you buy them?
I made them.
You did?
Why?
Aren't you also
sick of eating salt-cured foods everyday?
So I learned to cook for long trips.
I completely agree with you there.
See? I was being honest with myself there.
Were you really?
What about when we joined forces?
You're not half bad,
but don't let it go to your head.
I'm only admitting you're barely capable.
Okay, okay, enough already!
Rit wasn't truly honest with herself
till our showdown with Shisandan.
The outcome of that battle
was nothing to celebrate about.
The Duchy of Loggervia
The enemy offensive has halted for now.
But the Demon Lord's army
will resume its invasion before long.
We must do something now!
With food and fuel running low,
we'll be annihilated if the war continues much longer!
The enemy's in the same boat.
I discovered a mountain fortress
where they've been storing food.
We should strike there.
While our main force distracts the enemy,
I'll lead a party of adventurers
in a raid on the fortress.
We can't risk having a princess
enter enemy territory!
If our foe is also wearing thin—
we can hole up against a siege.
Lord Gaius?
I like the princess's plan.
Master!
The royal guard and I will serve as a decoy.
We'll help as well.
That is most welcome.
I'll entrust the castle's defense to the Hero's party.
But the plan failed.
Master?!
What are you doing here?
Who are you?
Where's my master?!
I am Shisandan.
I devoured your master.
I needed his memories after all,
"my beloved disciple".
Your people love you as their hero.
If I use your appearance,
conquering your country will be far easier.
What do you think?
What are you doing here?!
Something didn't feel right
about being left at the castle.
Don't cry, Rit.
If you number among the Hero's comrades,
vengeance won't come through tears...
only through cold steel!
Right!
Ruti will be here shortly.
We must hold out till then!
Got it!
The Hero!
You didn't attend the war council again today.
They decided to keep holing up for a siege.
May I sit?
Rit.
If you really don't want to fight,
I won't try to make you.
But I think you do want to.
At the moment, though,
you are weighed down heavily by sorrow.
You're probably right, but it's no use.
I'm scared.
I'm scared of losing someone else.
I'm scared, really scared.
My Master, the royal guard,
and all those adventurers...
I know each and every one of the fallen.
I know what they were like,
how they lived their lives,
and even why they fought alongside me!
But they're all gone.
They're dead because of me.
I'll never see them again.
We're going to break through the siege lines
and summon reinforcements.
We're going through the Bewitching Woods.
It's usually impassable,
but a former comrade of mine
by the name of Yarandrala lives nearby.
With her Blessing...
I'll leave it in your hands.
Rit.
I'll fight if the reinforcements arrive.
That's not what matters here.
What matters is whether Loggervia
has the will and pride to keep fighting.
You must join us in requesting reinforcements
and help us battle the Demon Lord.
If you don't, the people of Loggervia
will only remember today
as the day they lost
the great captain of the royal guard.
Even if the Demon Lord is vanquished,
that bitter memory will remain
an unhealed scar in the duchy's heart.
You are my comrade
and one of the Hero's comrades.
However,
this war isn't the Hero's to win.
It should be won by Loggervia's will to fight.
Otherwise, you won't prevail
if the Demon Lord returns after the Hero is gone.
So we have to claim victory ourselves...
That's right.
Rit regained her will to fight,
and the Demon Lord's army was vanquished.
Hey, you hungry?
I'm starving!
I haven't gone shopping today,
but I can throw something together.
Say, Red...
Could I work here with you?
Huh?!
Red and Rit's Apothecary.
It has a nice ring to it, don't you think?
Wh-Whoa, slow down.
You're only one of two B-rank adventurers in town.
I'll just retire.
No, no, wait.
I just opened up shop, and business is really slow.
I can't afford to hire anyone.
Someone has to look after the shop
when you're out gathering herbs, though.
It would be a total waste to close each time.
That's true, but it's not like I have many customers.
Your business will grow.
Don't you have any concoctions
that can only be found here?
Oh, well...
I have two original creations.
This is my "Multiplying Potion".
Mix it with a magic potion,
and you can increase its volume
by a factor of five.
That's a bad idea.
Huh?
Why?
Potion prices will crash if you start selling this.
It'll never fly with the guilds.
But we're talking potions here,
not magic items worth over 10,000 payrils.
What was that just now?
Potions form the basis of the economy,
they're inexpensive and you don't need special skills to use them.
Imagine the damage you'd do
if you made prices crash.
Y-You have a point there.
S-Sorry about that.
But I'm actually relieved.
Relieved?
I thought you were this amazing person.
You're multitalented and always calm,
so I felt this vast distance between us.
You're over-exaggerating...
No, Red, I'm not.
But I never imagined
there'd be things you didn't know,
or that you'd have a birdbrained side.
Did I disillusion you?
Not at all.
It makes me want to be with you even more.
This is the other one.
It's a new pain killer
that is just as effective as current ones,
but far less addictive.
Now that sounds good.
But pain killers require
the Zoltan Council's approval,
even if they're less addictive.
Oh, right.
Well...
whenever you have time is fine.
And I can't pay you that much, but...
it'd be great if you could help out.
Sure!
But don't say, "Whenever you have time."
We'll never be apart!
This looks so good!
It is good!
Glad you like it.
Now I'll be able to enjoy your cooking every day.
You will?
Looks like cooking will be more fun now.
What time is breakfast?
Around half past seven, I'd say.
Then I'll have to get up early.
I'll do my best!
She's coming for breakfast, too?
I know!
Let's build a bathtub. I'll pay for it.
A bathtub?
I can't have you spend that much on me.
No, I don't mind.
After all, I'll use it, too.
Come again?
She's planning to bathe here, too?
You only have one single bed?
Y-Yeah.
Okay, I'll buy another tomorrow.
My belongings are in my item box,
so I won't need any furniture.
You make it sound like you're going to live here.
That's because I am.
Wasn't it clear that I'm moving in?
What?!
Forgive the wait.
This is Tisse.
I've asked her to join our party in Gideon's stead.
She has the Divine Blessing of the Assassin
and is a rare talent,
even among the Assassin's Guild elite.
She'll be far more useful than Gideon was.
Thank you for this opportunity.
This is my partner, Mister Jumpyjitters.
I had to scour the various guilds
before I found one of her caliber.
Because of Gideon,
I've had to work my fingers to the—
The name's Danan.
I have the Martial Artist's Blessing.
I'm Theodora, and my Blessing is the Crusader.
Is anyone listening to me?!
It's the Hero.
I'm Ruti.
I'm Tisse Garland.
Despite the fact that Ares hired you,
you'll be under my command.
Is that clear?
Y-Yes.
I will obey your every command.
Good.
We're going to hunt for a weapon
the previous Demon Lord left behind.
We set out next morning at dawn.
Understood.