Nu știu cum să mă întorc.
Ce ar trebui să fac?
Și nu am deloc semnal la telefon.
O casă în stil occidental la marginea pădurii.
O fată care apare când se lasă noaptea.
Înfățișarea ei rămâne neschimbată, indiferent câți ani trec.
O teorie spune că este o păpușă cu suflet.
O fată-păpușă?
Cuvântul "păpușă" i-a atras atenția!
Mai este o poveste și despre o
fată care se plimbă prin pădure
și una despre o fată care plutește pe cer.
Cercetezi aceste lucruri pentru clubul ocult?
Da.
Uau, o fată-păpușă!
E-Este doar o legendă urbană!
Privește.
Am venit aici sperând s-o întâlnesc pe acea fată
dacă aș găsi acest loc, dar...
E-Este cumva un animal?
Sau...
O fată?
Este așa de drăguță...
Dar ce face în mijlocul pădurii?
Nu-ți fie teamă.
Sunt doar un vampir obșinut în trecere.
Nu sunt o persoană dubioasă.
Ești complet dubioasă.
E-Ei bine, m-am pierdut.
Și ai venit până aici?
Nu prea vezi asta.
Nu am știut încotro s-o iau!
În regulă, atunci, prinde-te de mine.
Vezi? Dacă mergi pe sus, nu te poți pierde.
Uau, chiar ești un vampir!
Sărut, sărut, sărut!
Te voi mușca
Exact cum credeam
Sărut, sărut, sărut!
Viața de noapte
Este cea mai grozavă
Sărut, sărut, sărut!
Nu ai vrea să dansăm împreună?
Ba da!!
Chiar dacă am avut o întâlnire puțin ciudată
Ar trebui s-o prețuim
Luna este sus pe cerul întunecat
Ceva grozav este pe cale să înceapă
Sentimentele tale adevărate nu pot fi reflectate într-o oglindă
Poate este un pic bizar, dar să accepți asta face parte din iubire
Deci am putea la fel de bine să iubim neobișnuitul
Noi suntem domnișoarele super drăguțe
Cât de minunat
Tot ce se află sub cerul înstelat este sala noastră de dans
Domnișoare super drăguțe îmbrăcate doar în pijamale
Până vine dimineața, acesta este timpul nostru liber
Hei, suntem prietene, nu-i așa?
Noi suntem fetele super drăguțe
Sărut, sărut, sărut!
Te voi mușca
Exact cum credeam
Sărut, sărut, sărut!
Viața de noapte
Este cea mai grozavă
Sărut, sărut, sărut!
Nu ai vrea să dansăm împreună?
Ba da!!
Episodul 1
Locuitoarea obișnuită a întunericului
Deci, ce faci în acest loc pustiu?
Ei bine...
Există acest loc numit "Casa Păpușii".
Îl căutam.
O, aia este casa mea.
Serios?!
Totuși, este mai aproape de oraș.
Dar zvonurile spun că este lângă pădure.
O, așa este.
O tânără domnișoară ca tine ar trebui
să umble noaptea de una singură!
Familia Mori locuiește lângă mine.
Este o familie a cărei nume înseamnă "pădure"?!
Dacă ești curioasă, poți arunca o privire.
Serios?
Vampirii nu îmbrătrânesc, deci dacă trăiesc într-un singur loc o perioadă lungă,
încep să apară zvonuri ciudate.
Înțeleg. Asta este cam nasol.
Nu prea mă interesează zvonurile.
Marea problemă este...
Care este?
...că doamna Mori continuă să îmi aducă mâncare.
Trebuie să mănânci dacă vrei
să crești mare și puternică.
Nu mănânc altceva în afară de sânge.
Aceste diete ciudate nu sunt bune.
Trebuie să mănânci și carne, și legume!
Nu vreau ca mâncarea să fie irosită,
dar nu pare să înțeleagă când îi explic.
Asta chiar pare problematic.
Am ajuns.
Arată exact ca în poza pe
care mi-a dat-o Sakuya!
Poți intra dacă vrei.
Bine!
Îți mulțumesc că m-ai pri—
Uimitor!
Este așa de vampiric!
Mă bucur să aud asta.
Deci ai auzit zvonurile și ai venit
aici ca să-ți testezi curajul sau ceva?
Nu. Am venit aici...
ca s-o prind pe fata-păpușă!
Ești mai agresivă decât pari.
Deci, cum te cheamă?
Eu sunt Amano Akari.
Eu sunt Sophie Twilight.
Înțeleg. Deci, tu ești Sophie.
Știi, eu iubesc păpușile.
M-am gândit că ar fi foarte grozav dacă ar exista cu adevărat o păpușă care vie.
Îmi pare rău, nu sunt o păpușă.
Totuși, privindu-te, arăți exact ca păpușa mea ideală.
Piele ca de porțelan...
Păr ca de mătase...
Gambe subțiri!
Chiar arăți ca o păpușă vie!
Hei, ești în regulă?
Hei, Sophie, pot să te mângâi pe cap?
Vreau
Te pot lua acasă?
Vreau să-ți pieptăn părul și să-ți schimb hainele!
Vreau
Hei... Stai departe. Mă sperii.
Șoc
Sunt un om normal, iar un vampir se teme de mine!
Hei, Sophie... Este foarte târziu.
Te deranjează dacă stau peste noapte?
Nu.
Nu-ți este teamă să rămâi la un vampir acasă?
Este în regulă!
Dacă este vorba de tine, chiar și
sugerea sângelui ar fi o plăcere!
Nu va încerca să facă ceva
ciudat cât timp stă aici, nu-i așa?
Nu prea mai sunt sigură de asta.
A-Atunci, ar trebui să luăm cina?
C-Cina?
C-Cred că n-am de ales.
Doar puțin, bine?
Nu beau direct din oameni vii. Este înfricoșător.
Nu sunt o ciudată.
ȘOC
Am speriat un vampir din nou!
Se întâmplă să am niște mâncare
primită de la doamna Mori.
Miroase bine!
Bei sânge dintr-o ceașcă de ceai, nu-i așa?
Cât de elegant!
Așa este.
O, încălzești sângele la microunde.
600 de wați, pentru cincizeci
de secunde sau pe acolo.
Serios?
Uau... Este un vampir, dar se comportă ca o persoană complet normală.
Ne vedem săptămâna viitoare!
Ca o persoană nocturnă, nu pot să nu mă uit la desene până târziu.
Forum pentru
desene
Comentarii (192)
Pariez că toți cei care scriu recenzii
la ora asta sunt și ei vampiri.
Nu prea cred...
Când spui "nocturnă",
vrei să spui că vamprii
chiar nu ies în timpul zilei?
Așa este.
I don't handle the sunlight well,
so I don't go out during the day
unless it's really important.
Înțeleg!
Oh, there's an autograph
session with the author.
De la ora 13:00 la 15:00.
Sesiunea de autografe cu artistul
Surume este în sfârșit duminica asta!
Imouto to kaachan no ... wa ...
În regulă!
Duminica viitoare voi ieși afară!
Wait, that's something "really important"?
Hey, don't they also say
that vampires can't enter
a place unless someone invites them in?
That's right. We can't.
So is it like, they're repelled by some
kind of barrier that keeps them out,
or they can enter, but it does some
kind of damage that hurts them?
Actually, we can still physically enter
a place, even without an invitation.
But if we do...
What happens?
The people who lived there would
think we were completely rude.
We'd be consumed by guilt.
That's such a normal reason!
So this is your room!
You really do sleep in a coffin, huh?
I wonder what it's like inside.
Huh?
I probably shouldn't have looked
in there without permission.
Bye-bye, Sophie-chan!
Bye.
See you next time!
Did she say "next time"?
After that, this human started
to visit me every day.
Glom Glom
Honestly, it's a little annoying.
Poate
este
un vampir!!!
Poate
este
un vampir!!!
Poate
este
un vampir!!!
Wow, really?
Hey, vampires are stronger
than humans, right?
Yes.
I know! Maybe if I shock her
by showing her my power,
I'll get my peace back.
I can pick up a road roller just like that!
She ran away in such a panic.
Maybe I scared her too much.
But at least now I can go
back to my quiet life.
Hey, hey, Sophie-chan!
I didn't think I'd miss
someone that annoying,
but when I think she's never coming
back, I actually feel sad...
Sophie-chan!
Human? I thought you fled in terror...
These are all the jars and things
that I couldn't open myself.
I thought, with your strength...
So I hurried and grabbed
them all from my house!
I thought she feared me, but she
was just finding a way to use me.
I'm not like humans.
Aren't you even a little scared of me?
Not a bit!
You helped me out the first time we met, too.
You can do so many amazing
things that I can't do.
So please, can I keep coming here?
You're a really strange human.
My name isn't "human." It's Akari.
Do as you like...
Akari.
Did you just say I can do whatever I like?!
Then I want to brush your hair
and put it into pigtails
and pet it, and then I want
to take a bath together!
Never mind, go home!
So now I'm going every day to visit
my new friend who I met in the woods.
Every day?
Yeah!
Wouldn't it be easier if you
just moved in with her?
M-Move in with her?!
You want her to move in
with a complete stranger?
I was joking.
I... I knew that!
So is your friend a boy or a girl?
A b-boy?!
I-I'm not so sure that's a g-good thing!
Good morning!
I came to see you, Sophie-chan!
You're here early on your day off.
I figured if I came early,
you'd still be awake.
Thank you for having me!
Uh-huh...
Sophie-chan, it's a waste that you have
your curtains drawn all the time.
The weather is nice today, so the
morning sun is really beautiful!
See?
Indeed.
Dying basked in light
like this isn't so bad.
Oh, sorry!
You can't handle sunlight!
So how come you brought
all these bags today?
Well, I just had a thought...
You live in this big house all alone, right?
So I was thinking I'd like to move in with you!
But that's so sudden.
Is that a no?
But I brought all my stuff.
You're getting too far ahead.
And what is all this stuff, anyway?
Well...
I brought some clothes,
and my pajamas, and my toothbrush and towel.
Also...
I brought my dolls,
and clothes and hats for my dolls.
So most of it is doll stuff?
Hmm... It's true that there are
some extra rooms here, but...
It won't be a problem for me at all!
This is also a lot closer to my school.
Your parents are okay with this?
Wouldn't they be worried if you
said you were living with a vampire?
I guess I'll ask them.
What?
You're going to live with your friend?
And their family is all right with that?
They live all alone?
Who is this friend?
They turn into ash in the sunlight?
Oh, yeah! I love the sun!
What? A vampire?!
She looks like she's around thirteen,
and she's a beautiful girl with silver hair!
Well, then, I'm all for it!
Invite her over to our house sometime.
Apel de intrare
Mama
So that's that!
Now it's all up to you.
Let me guess. Your entire family
is just like you, aren't they?
Why would you want to live
with a vampire, anyway?
It's dark all day, and it's
not exactly comfortable.
I want to because you're here!
You said vampires don't age, right?
Right.
A girl who never ages is
basically like a living doll!
You're too close.
If I live here, I can admire
you every day, plus...
you won't be so lonely either, right?
It's not like I was lonely before.
Is there anything inconvenient
about living alone as a vampire?
Since you can't stand the sun, you can't
go shopping during the day, right?
Sure, there are some inconvenient things.
I don't like running water,
so washing dishes was a problem.
If I'm living here, you can leave
all the shopping and dishes to me!
No, I mean, it was a problem in the past,
but now I have convenience
stores and Amason.
I also bought a dishwasher, so I'm fine.
These are convenient times.
I hate you, technological advances!
Okay, then...
If you let me live with you,
you can suck my blood whenever you like!
The blood of a young maiden!
Come, try it!
Stay away! I don't want any!
I've always got plenty
of blood in the fridge.
Gustos
Rich AB
Mellow O
Simplu
I would never suck your blood, of all people.
"Of all people"? What's
that supposed to mean?!
Ta-da! I can also cook!
Like meat and potato stew!
Huh, that's impressive.
I don't eat human food, though.
Oh, that's right...
Ouch!
Be careful.
Don't waste it.
Just one second, Sophie-chan.
I'll get you more.
No, stop.
For someone who only drinks blood,
you sure have a lot of china and cutlery.
I use different ones each
time I won't get bored.
When I have it hot, I'll drink it like soup,
or like tea, or like coffee.
Cold, I drink it from a stein or a bottle.
I see.
In summer, I freeze it
and eat it like a popsicle.
In winter, I warm it in a sake
bottle and enjoy it like hot sake.
Wow, how elegant!
Looks like I don't have
a lot of type O left.
I'm going to go buy some.
Go... buy some?
Like hunting?!
Vânătoare
I've been wondering where she
gets all that blood from.
Since it's Sophie-can, I can't imagine
she's harming anyone, but...
There.
I got express delivery,
so it should be here tomorrow.
You buy it online?!
Okay, I'm going to clean now!
Dust dust dust!
Wipe wipe wipe!
Sweep sweep sweep!
She's really going at it today.
Dust dust dust!
Oh, you were watching me?
She's already so loud by default.
I wish she could just act normal.
Still, with Akari around,
it feels like the house has brightened up.
You won't be so lonely either, right?
I guess she may be right.
Hey, Sophie-chan.
The light bulbs seemed really dim,
so I switched them to brighter ones.
Don't just change those!
I picked them to make it more
habitable for vampires!
I guess I shouldn't have done that.
I wonder what I can do
to get her to accept me.
Akari,
I'm going to sleep now, so go home.
I'm so sorry.
I know it's right before your
bedtime and I'm just in the way.
It didn't work out.
Go home and properly pack your things.
I'll carry the heavy stuff once it's dark.
Really?!
I never said no.
Then I'll gather up the fifty-five
dolls that didn't fit into my bag!
You're bringing more dolls over?
Woohoo!
We'll be together every day now!
But how come?
I couldn't do anything useful for you.
I never asked you to be useful to me.
There were empty rooms here, anyway.
Besides, it might be kind of fun...
if you move in here.
Sophie-chan!
That means our love is mutual!
So we're going to get married...
That's way too big a leap!
I don't have much to offer,
but please be kind to me!
I just agreed to this, but I'm
already questioning my decision.
See you later!
Good morning, Sophie-chan!
Good morning.
I'm going to school now!
Okay.
Aw, I wish I could be with you at school, too.
School, huh?
I did try to go to high
school for a little bit.
Really?
I didn't want the people in the
neighborhood to think I'm a NEET.
There was a big window that got a lot of sun.
Hey, Twilight, you can't
wear a cloak in class!
And put that parasol away!
So many unreasonable rules.
No flying in the hallways!
Violence in the guise of kindness.
What, you're only drinking juice for lunch?
That's not enough. You need to eat.
I'll give you some of my lunch.
Here, have a potsticker.
Miros de usturoi
And spaghetti aglio e olio.
It was truly terrifying.
I lasted three days.
I see.
Cred că nu este ușor să fii vampir.
Hinata!
Bună dimineața!
O, Akari?
Ce faci aici?
Păi, vezi tu...
Cred că voi merge la culcare.