Hei, ai vrea să ne sărutăm?
Nu era o ofertă serioasă.
Era clar că mă tachina.
Stai, cine era acea fată?
29 mai
"Sincer, știu că următoarea poveste va fi greu de crezut.
Dar este complet adevărată, deci citește-o până la final.
Neapărat."
Ce este asta?
6 mai
Am dat peste o fată iepure în sălbăticie.
Era elevă la Liceul Minehahara
Celebritatea, Sakurajima Mai.
Am mers la Biblioteca Fujisawa și acolo
"6 mai.
Am dat peste o fată iepure în sălbăticie."
Because of you, because of you, it's because of you
That I've turned into this pathetic coward
It's all your fault
Teenage Pig Doesn't Dream of Bunny Girls
I can't see your eyes
Hidden beneath your bangs
What are you looking at? Get over here
If you want to drive me crazy for you
There's nothing stopping you
Not a single thing
As we stand on the station platform, engulfed in twilight
I silently take it all in, including the sound of the waves
Don't you laugh like you see right through me
Because of you, because of you, it's because of you
That I've turned into this pathetic coward
This wasn't how it was supposed to go
Because of you, because of you, it's because of you
That I grow to hate a certain someone
On nights like these, I'm filled with unease
I draw my machine gun
Stare you down as you play it cool
And shoot you right through the heart
Episodul 1: Colega mea mai mare este o fată iepure
6 mai
Ce naiba?
Șșș!
Sunt uimită. Tu încă mă poți vedea?
Ei bine, pa.
Hei...
Tu ești Sakurajima din anul 3, nu-i așa?
Din moment ce ai spus asta, să înțeleg că și tu mergi la Liceul Minegahara?
Eu sunt Azusagawa Sakuta din clasa 2-1.
Azusagawa de la "Lanțul de Magazine Azusagawa" și Sakuta de la "Hanasaku Tarou".
Eu sunt Sakurajima Mai.
Sakurajima de la "Sakurajima Mai" și Mai de la "Sakurajima Mai".
Știu. Ești celebră.
Uite o avertizare:
uită ceea ce ai văzut astăzi.
Și stai cât mai departe de mine.
Ai înțeles? Da sau nu.
Cum ar trebui să uit aia?
Este dimineață, Kaede. Trezește-te.
Îmi este frig, frățioare!
Hei, ești grea!
Deoarece jumătate din mine este plină cu iubirea mea pentru tine!
Asta este o trăsătură de
caracter destul de jalnică.
Ești o adolescentă acum. A venit moment să
renunți în a mai te strecura noaptea în patul meu.
Te excită prea tare când vine dimineața?
Cine, sănătos la cap,
ar fi excitat de sora lui mai mică?
Hei, Kunimi, îți plac fetele iepure?
Nu, nu chiar.
Vrei să spui că le iubești?
Exact.
Să spunem că ai da peste o fată iepure foarte bună la bibliotecă. Ce ai face?
M-aș freca la ochi.
Nu-i așa?
Și apoi, m-aș holba la ea.
Nu-i așa?!
Liceul Minegahara, Prefectura Kanagawa
Hei, Kunimi.
O poți vedea pe Sakurajima din anul 3?
Clar ca lumina zilei.
Oare ce fel de persoană este?
Hmm... Ei bine, este o celebritate.
Asta așa este.
Deși a luat o pauză, nu ai cum
să nu o asociezi cu televiziunea.
Ai dreptate.
Am fost foarte surprins să aflu că merge la aceeași școală ca și noi.
Mă bucur să văd că ești interesat și de o
altă fată în afară de Makinohara Shouko,
dar ea nu este de nasul tău.
Nu am spui niciodată că vreau să ies cu ea sau măcar că-mi place de ea.
Atunci, care e treaba?
Mă gândeam doar că nu o vezi
niciodată cu cineva la școală.
Este mereu singură.
'Neața, Yuuma.
Hei, Kamisato.
Pe mai târziu, Sakuta.
Am auzit de la un coleg
mai mare din echipa mea
că Sakurajima nu a venit deloc la școală la începutul primului an.
De ce?
Munca.
A anunțat că va intra în pauză
imediat cum termină gimnaziul,
dar după asta, a fost ocupată cu
îndeplinirea unor obligații anterioare.
Se pare că începuse să vină la școală în
mod constant doar după vacanța de vară.
Asta trebuie să fie nasol.
Nu-i așa?
Sakurajima-senpai, a celebrity who
showed up partway through first year,
was a total outsider.
Once a class's social structure takes shape,
it's not easy to change.
If you stand out too much,
people are sure to badmouth you.
Things will never be the same again,
and everyone knows that.
That's what the society known as school is like.
Nobody can bring themselves to talk to Sakurajima-senpai.
They don't want to stick out like a sore thumb.
That's why Sakurajima-senpai's going
with the flow and acting invisible, I bet.
Hey, we need to talk.
I'll get straight to the point. Stop talking to Yuuma.
It's not like I'm standing in the way of you two lovebirds and your relationship.
That's not the point.
Everyone knows what you did in the hospitalization incident.
Oh, the hospitalization incident, huh?
It'd hurt Yuuma's reputation to be seen with you, the class outcast.
I feel bad for him.
But you're okay with ruining
your reputation by talking to me?
You picking a fight?
No, just fighting back.
Why so mad? That time of the month?
Drop dead, you creep!
I can't believe you!
Ultimately,
even though they whine every day about how boring their lives are
and how they wish something fun would happen,
nobody actually wants any real change.
That's gotta be Sakurajima Mai, right?
Really?
Look! It's totally her!
I should take a pic.
What?
Come on, look this way.
Wh-What's with you?
Hello, I'm a person. Are you a visitor from the planet Creepshot?
Dude, what the hell?
Forget it. Let's go.
Tch!
What's his problem? It's just one pic!
Thanks.
Did you think I'd get mad and tell you
to mind your own business?
Yeah.
I'll make do with just thinking it.
Then I wish you hadn't said that out loud either.
I'm used to that stuff, you know.
Even if you are, I'm sure it slowly wears away at you.
Wears away, huh? You're right.
Manager
Mobil
Mesaj
Send to Voicemail
Notify Later
Manager
Cellphone
Message
Send to Voicemail
Notify Later
Manager
Cellphone
Message
Send to Voicemail
Notify Later
Manager
Cellphone
Message
Send to Voicemail
Notify Later
Aren't you going to answer that?
The train's here.
Besides, I know what she wants.
About yesterday...
Didn't I tell you to forget about that?
I couldn't. Your bunny-girl look was too hot.
H-Hey! I hope you didn't do anything weird
while thinking about me!
Not that it'd bother me if a younger boy
had sexual fantasies about me.
Hey, Azusagawa-kun.
You remembered my name?
I saw the rumors about you.
Acel tip Azusagawa Sakuta (lol)
Site-ul Liceului Minegahara
Licee din Kanagawa
Ultimul topic
Liceul Minegahara * Partea 12
Liceul Minegahara * Partea 11
They say you got into a fight and sent three classmates to the hospital.
1. Anonim
Azusagawa Sakuta
Tipul și-a băgat 3 colegi în spital
după un incident violent în gimnaziu.
S-a mutat din Yokohama.
Unde s-o fi dus?
2. Anonim
Care e treaba cu acest incident...
3. Anonim
înfricoșător... lol
I'm honored that you took such an interest in me.
It's crazy that one's private life can be exposed this way.
I had no idea they were posting all these things about me.
You don't namesearch?
Well, I don't have a phone.
Really?
I used to have one, but I got mad and threw it into the ocean.
Ever heard of trash cans?
You don't have any friends, do you?
I have lots. Two, even.
I'm not sure two counts as "lots."
I believe two friends is plenty.
I can just be friends with them for life.
So, what'd you make of the hospitalization rumors?
It's pretty obvious when you think about it.
There's no way anyone who did that
could go to school with no repercussions.
I wish you'd tell my classmates that.
If the rumors are false, just tell them yourself.
Rumors are part of the flow, you know?
Modern society desperately
wants you to go with the flow.
And if you don't, you're treated like trash.
Nobody creating that flow has any awareness that they're doing it,
so it'd be entirely pointless to fight it.
So instead of clearing the air,
you're just giving up before you even try?
It's your turn to spill the beans.
What were you doing yesterday?
I made my showbiz debut when I was six.
After being picked to play the lead role in a morning soap,
I was all over TV, movies, and commercials.
I've lived most of my life in the public eye.
Not a day would go by when I wouldn't see Sakurajima Mai on TV.
It was fun at first, but things gradually got worse and worse.
Everywhere I went, I attracted attention as "the" Sakurajima Mai.
At some point, I started wishing I could go
to a world where nobody knew me.
I first noticed that some people couldn't see me on the first day of Golden Week.
I'd gone to the aquarium on a whim.
Alone?
Got a problem with that?
Or so I heard.
What? No way!
It's true!
Initially, I thought I was imagining it.
Maybe they were too focused on the fish.
But on the way home, I stopped by a café.
Excuse me.
Hello?
Welcome.
Had you done something to get banned from that café before?
Of course not.
Senpai, your foot.
What about my foot?
Nothing. I feel very fortunate to have you step on me.
Anyway, I practically ran home from that café.
But once I got to Fujisawa,
everyone could see me as usual.
So I've been going around places
to see if the same thing happens there.
That's why you dress up as a bunny girl?
Anyone would stare if they saw a girl wearing this, right?
Were you planning to play a bunny girl in the wild somewhere again today?
Exactly. So don't get in my way.
I'll have a cream bun, please.
Excuse me. I'll have a cream bun, please.
Excuse me. I'll have a cream bun.
Sure. Just one?
Yeah, just one.
Deep down, don't you find this a little troubling?
I guess. I don't want to miss out
on these cream buns.
Anyway, do you seriously believe this crazy story of mine?
Well, I know exactly what this stuff is called.
Puberty Syndrome, right?
Teenage Pig Doesn't
Dream of Bunny Girls
Puberty Syndrome, huh?
Cases where someone started hearing people's thoughts,
saw into people's futures,
or where two people swapped bodies...
Nobody knows who first started it, but it came to be known as "Puberty Syndrome."
That's just an urban legend.
Huh? Why are we stopping here?
This is my apartment building.
I won't do anything, I promise.
In order to make you believe that I believe you,
there's something I want to show you.
Your room's surprisingly clean.
Senpai—
Stop calling me that.
I never interacted with you in school.
Sakurajima-san?
A real mouthful, don't you think?
Mai, then?
You're forgetting something.
Mai-san, then.
Calling you Azusagawa doesn't feel right,
so I'll be going with Sakuta-kun.
Wh-Why are you stripping?
You promised not to do anything!
You perverted monster! Exhibitionist!
Is that real?
What kind of moron would do this with makeup?
May I touch?
Go ahead.
Quit moaning.
It's sensitive. Please be gentle.
Like so?
That feels really good!
Ow! Let me go!
Why do I get the feeling you're enjoying it?
Well? How'd you get these scars?
I'm not sure, actually.
That's Kaede, my little sister.
She wasn't beaten up or anything.
It was caused by cyberbullying.
I'm not sure I follow.
Because she left a message on read, or something,
she got on the bad side
of the most popular girl in class
and was bashed on the
community message board.
mă ignori din nou, azusagawa?
sper să mori, kaede
nu mai veni la școală
And one day...
Welcome home.
Nii-chan...
Hmm? What's up?
That's the reason I believe Puberty Syndrome is real.
Is that when you got those wounds?
I have no idea what caused it.
I woke up covered in blood
and was rushed to the hospital.
That's the truth behind the hospitalization incident?
Yeah. I was the one hospitalized.
Onii-chan, are you in?
I-I'm so sorry!
You should've told me you had a call girl over!
Kaede, you're making a huge misunderstanding.
Are you being scammed, then?
I'm not.
Forced to buy English textbooks?
That's not it either. Relax.
She's my senior from school.
I'm Sakurajima Mai. Nice to meet you.
Nice... too. Azu... de.
Uh, "Nice to meet you too.
I'm Azusagawa Kaede," she says.
Th... is... no.
"And this is Nasuno."
Thanks for telling me, Kaede-chan.
Sorry about that. She's super timid around strangers.
Now, she's a truant who loves
staying at home a little too much.
She doesn't know who I am, huh?
Well, she doesn't watch too much TV.
In Kaede's case, staying away from anything related to the internet
alleviated her Puberty Syndrome symptoms.
That's why I dumped my phone in the ocean, too.
And you mean to say my case is similar?
I mean, you act completely invisible at school.
So to prevent this from getting any worse,
I think you should go back to showbiz.
Where did that come from?
If you're all over TV, people won't ignore you
even when you act invisible.
And it looks like you want to go back, anyway.
When did I ever say that?
You didn't, but you were staring a hole through that movie poster on the train.
I think you should do what you want to do.
You've got the ability and track record,
and even your manager wants you back.
Leave her out of this.
I didn't ask for your opinion.
Cauți baia?
Plec!
Așteaptă, ai uitat asta.
Keep it!
After that day,
Mai-san stopped coming to school.
It seems I touched a really bad nerve.
Sakurajima Mai hiatus reason
A topic she didn't want touched.
Related:
Sakurajima Mai   însărcinată        Sakurajima Mai   mamă curvă
Sakurajima Mai   sinucidere         Sakurajima Mai   fleeing overseas
Sakurajima Mai   debut porno       Sakurajima Mai   elevă prostituată
Hey, Kunimi.
Do you know why Sakurajima Mai went on hiatus?
Publicly, I think it was to focus on her studies.
Azusagawa, that news anchor is here again.
Long time no see.
I don't believe we've been introduced.
Oh, so that's your game?
Pleased to meet you, then.
• Prezentatoare
Nanjou Fumika
Here's my card.
• Prezentatoare
Nanjou Fumika
What do you want today?
I was in the area for a story on whitebait,
and I'm free this evening,
so I came to see your pretty face.
What would you like to order?
One Sakuta-kun to go.
You seem to have hit your head.
I'll put your order down as one ambulance, okay?
Still not willing to talk about the incident?
I never will be.
I'd be happy with a photo of your scars too, you know.
Over my dead body.
Nanjou-san, would you happen to know why Sakurajima Mai went on hiatus?
At the very least, I do have information not available to the public.
I hear you're quite taken with Sakurajima-senpai lately.
Are you over Makinohara Shouko now?
Why is that the first thing both you and Kunimi can think of?
Feel free to add the sugar yourself.
Is this even safe?
The contents are probably sugar. It's white.
So, what did you want to ask?
Say, Futaba. Do you think it's possible that people can suddenly stop seeing others?
Worried about your vision? Go see an ophthalmologist.
That's not what I'm talking about.
I mean not seeing somebody who's right there, like an invisible person.
Are you trying to sneak into the girls' toilet?
I should've expected no less from a horny pig like you.
Sorry, but I'm not into scat.
If you're talking about Puberty Syndrome,
I'm pretty sure I already told you.
I'm firmly against the concept.
I know. You don't find it logical, right?
That's why I'm here. I want a logical explanation.
Consider me sitting here in front of you. Would you ever be unable to see me?
Is that possible in theory?
Yes, if I were engrossed in something,
or just spacing out.
The human brain can filter out things you don't want to see.
True, but that's not what I'm looking for.
There's also the observation theory.
"Observation theory"?
It says all things and states are only determined to exist when they're observed.
I'm sure even you've heard of the
"cat in the box," right?
Oh, yeah. What was it called...
Schrödinger's cat.
When Sakurajima Mai was in showbiz, she certainly did exist,
and she was observed by one and all.
I'll have a cream bun, please.
Sure. Cream bun, coming right up.
Um... Do you know who Sakurajima Mai is?
Who?
Sakurajima Mai, the girl who got her big break as a child actress in a morning soap.
Sakurajima?
Was there an actress named that?
When one stops being observed,
not only do they become invisible,
it also means their very existence...
katarenai nemurenai traumerei
I can't talk about it or sleep, so I daydream
You're finally back.
anata no miteru shoutai
These are my true colors, as you see
Did you want to see me that badly?
dare mo yomenai karte
Nobody can read my medical chart
Man, I'm so hungry.
You're a jerk.
I'm more or less aware.
fukashigi shiritai dake
So puzzling, I just want to know what it means
When did you start a new career as a starving girl?
kyou mo hitorigoto
I mumble to myself again today
I can't buy anything.
Over the past two weeks, I've become invisible to more and more people.
Nobody around Fujisawa Station can see me anymore.
nani mo muri wo shinai de
Feeling too lazy to push myself
For starters, would you like to eat this?
aisaretai
I want to be loved for free
uyamuya sayonara karui memai
Left dizzy with things still up in the air as we say goodbye
"May 6th.
I ran into a bunny girl in the wild.
anata no inai genshoukai
I enter a world without you by my side
6 mai
Am dat peste o fată iepure în sălbăticie.
Era elevă la Liceul Minehahara
Celebritatea, Sakurajima Mai.
Am mers la Biblioteca Fujisawa și acolo
That was our first meeting, and the start of everything.
dare mo yomenai karte
Nobody can read my medical chart
I could never forget it.
Azusagawa
Even if I do, you'd better remember it.
jiishiki afuredashite
So self-conscious, what's wrong with me?
I'm counting on you,
my future self."
Acesta este Sakuta al meu. Un adevărat porc.
Data viitoare
#2: Primele întâlniri sunt mereu haotice