„Să te îndoieşti de tot sau să crezi totul sunt două soluţii la fel de convenabile; amândouă înlătură necesitatea cugetării.”
Henri Poincare, „Știință și ipoteză”
În ultimii doi ani, am fost foarte mândru și recunoscător
să conduc colectivul elevilor în postura de președinte al consiliului elevilor.
Deși este simplist,
discursul meu se încheie aici.
Vă mulțumesc.
Înainte, Horikita ar fi fost
imposibil de consolat.
Îți mulțumim pentru toată munca depusă, președinte Horikita.
Acum, vom asculta câteva cuvinte de la noul președinte al consiliului elevilor.
Eu sunt noul vostru președinte
al consiliului elevilor,
Nagumo Miyabi din clasa 2-A.
Voi trece direct la subiect:
Vreau să transform această școală într-o meritocrație.
Elevii capabili se vor afla în vârf,
pe când ceilalți vor fi la urmă.
Așa ar trebui să fie lucrurile.
Prestația ta de la festivalul
sportiv chiar m-a impresionat.
Katsuragi.
Te rog s-o avertizezi pe
Horikita să aibă grijă la Ryuen.
Nu ai colaborat cu el în trecut?
Spre rușinea mea, da.
Nu ar fi trebuit niciodată
să am de a face cu el.
Ryuen e inamicul nostru comun.
Am înțeles.
O voi avertiza.
Mersi.
Se pare că ambele părți își
fac griji în legătură cu el.
Hei...
Ei bine...
Ai câteva minute?
Vreau să te întreb ceva.
Classroom of
the Elite
Asta ar putea suna puțin ciudat...
Dar...
Te vezi cu cineva în acest moment?
Ei bine...
Ce vrei să spui prin asta?
La ce crezi că mă refer?!
Te întreb dacă ai prietenă!
Deci?
Nu.
Oh... serios?
Putem avea o relație platonică și toate cele...
Deci mi-ar plăcea să facem schimb de numerele de telefon.
Bănuiesc că e în regulă.
Dar de ce eu?
Cursa de la festivalul sportiv.
Ai fost incredibil acolo...
Nu mi-am dat seama niciodată de cât de grozav... matur și drăguț ești...
O-Oricum, asta e tot ce voiam!
Văd destul de multe fețe serioase...
Vă voi arăta acum rezultatele la testele de la jumătatea semestrului.
Pe bune?
2nd Term Midterm Test
Chemistry
Koenji Rokusuke 95
Horikita Suzune 93
Hirata Yosuke 93
Yukimura Teruhiko 90
Kushida Kikyo 85
Ijuin Wataru 80
Matsushita Chiaki 80
Wang Mei-Yu 80
Mori Nene 78
Miyake Akito 78
Hasebe Haruka 77
Hondo Ryotaro 73
Ayanokoji Kiyotaka 65
Miyamoto Soshi 65
Ike Kanji 63
Onodera Kayano 62
Sotomura Hideo 60
Horikita Suzune
Yukimura Teruhiko
Koenji Rokusuke
Wang Mei-Yu
Ijuin Wataru
Kushida Kikyo
Hirata Yosuke
Miyamoto Soshi
Matsushita Chiaki
Hasebe Haruka
Miyake Akito
Hondo Ryotaro
Ayanokoji Kiyotaka
Mori Nene
Shinohara Satsuki
Onodera Kayano
Karuizawa Kei
Vai, a fost cât pe ce!
Hei! Priviți punctajul lui Ken!
Sakura Airi 55
Sato Maya 53
Sudo Ken 52
Onodera Kayano 50
Okitani Kyosuke 50
Inogashira Kokoro 50
Hondo Ryotaro 50
Ike Kanji 48
Sotomura Hideo 45
Yamauchi Haruki 43
Sudo       Ken                                 52
Grozav!
Nu e un rezultat pentru
care să faci atâta zarvă.
D-Da...
Parcă ar fi cățelușul ei.
După cum puteți vedea, nimeni nu va fi exmatriculat de această dată.
În cei trei ani de când îndrum clasa D,
nu am avut nicio perioadă atât de lungă fără ca nicio persoană să nu fie nevoită să renunțe.
V-ați descurcat bine.
E asta prima oară când a
spus ceva bun despre noi?
Bănuiesc că merităm să fim
lăudați din când în când!
Da!
Totuși, parcă ne laudă doar
de dragul de a o face...
Dar e prea devreme să răsuflați ușurați.
Va trebui să dați tot ce puteți la următorul examen special,
care va servi drept
examenul vostru final.
Cunoscut ca Amestecarea Lucrărilor.
Amestecarea Lucrărilor?
La acest examen, toți elevii vor participa în grupuri de două persoane.
Adică în perechi, nu?
Eu vreau să fiu în echipă cu Kikyo!
În echipe de câte doi...
Karuizawa, tu vei fi cu Hirata, nu?
C-Ce?
Dar... ne putem alege noi echipele?
Cum sunt alese echipele, mai exact?
Nu te grăbi așa.
Modul de formare al echipelor va fi anunțat după micuțul test de săptămâna viitoare.
Alt test?!
Scopul lui va fi de a vă determina nivelul academic, curent.
Nu veți fi penalizați pentru punctaje mici,
nici măcar dacă luați zero puncte.
Ce ușurare!
Dar rezultatul la acel test va fi crucial pentru Amestecarea Lucrărilor.
Dacă, la următorul examen special,
punctajul total al echipei
este sub șaizeci de puncte,
ambii elevi vor fi exmatriculați.
Spre exemplu, dacă Ike și
Hirata sunt în aceeași echipă,
iar Ike ia 0 puncte, cât timp Hirata ia peste 60 de puncte,
niciunul nu va fi exmatriculat.
Există, de asemenea, un punctaj minim ce trebuie obținut adunând rezultatele la toate materiile.
Vă voi da numărul exact mai târziu,
dar, în general, e în jur de 700 de puncte la toate cele opt materii.
Ceea ce înseamnă că fiecare trebuie să ia în jur de 44 de puncte pe materie.
Încă un lucru.
Întrebările de la lucrări vor fi făcute de voi.
Ce?!
Iar la întrebările făcute de fiecare clasă,
va răspunde una dintre celelalte trei clase.
Puteți, de asemenea, să alegeți ce clasă sperați să vă primească întrebările.
În cazul în care două clase vor cere aceeași clasă, se va trage la sorți.
Și clasa care va lua mai multe
puncte dintre cele două,
va fura 50 de puncte clasă de la cealaltă.
Ca un atac direct.
Dar dacă vor exista întrebări
la care nu există răspuns?
Mi-ar plăcea să văd asemenea întrebări!
Nu aveți de ce să vă faceți griji.
Ceilalți profesori și cu mine
vom verifica întrebările ca să ne asigurăm că asta nu se va întâmpla.
Evident, dacă trișați veți fi picați imediat
și apoi, ambii membri exmatriculați.
La Amestecarea Lucrărilor, una sau două echipe sunt exmatriculate în fiecare an.
Țineți minte asta.
Next exam: Paper Shuffle
• Pairs determined by the mini test
• Pair's combined score bar
• Bar for total score as well
• Questions crafted by the students
• Generated questions solved by another class
• Classes pitted directly against one another
• Two or three pairs expelled each year
• The system for determining the pairs is key
Vă voi trimite un e-mail cu regulile în detaliu în privința alcătuirii întrebărilor.
Voi lăsa restul în seama voastră.
Ce părere ai de următorul examen?
Știu cum să câștigăm.
Explicația profesoarei noastre ne-a dat toate indiciile de care avem nevoie.
Serios?
Cheamă-i pe Hirata și ceilalți.
Vreau să ținem o întâlnire strategică.
Am înțeles.
Vreau să te întreb ceva.
(No Subject)
Got a question for you.
Sato ți-a cerut să fiți împreună, nu?
(No Subject)
Sato-san asked you out, right?
You Have a New Message
Cine ți-a dat această informație?
(Fără subiect)
Sato mi-a spus, evident!
Câteva fete, printre care și eu, știam că-ți va cere să fiți împreună.
(No Subject)
Sato-san herself, of course!
A whole bunch of girls, including me, knew she was gonna ask you out today.
Ei bine, nu e ca și cum știe cum funcționează lumea fetelor.
(No Subject)
So you were watching me behind the gym?
M-a văzut?
Darn it! Sometimes he's so dense,
and sometimes he's so sharp!
Karuizawa-san!
Horikita-san wanted to
discuss the upcoming exam.
S-Sure! Got it.
The selected email has been deleted
I'd like to begin the
strategy meeting promptly.
What, here?
Big no to that!
Why not a café or something?
Right, Yosuke... kun?
Very well.
Pallet, then.
Excuse me.
Do you think I could join in?
Or would you rather I not?
I'd love to have you!
You know so much about what's
going on in the class.
Of course, Kushida-san.
I'd planned on talking to you
sooner or later regardless.
Thanks!
Could the rest of you go on ahead?
We need to fetch my bag first.
We'll save you a seat!
Is it all right to let
Kushida in on our planning?
It would look suspicious if I
turned her down in that context.
And I'm sure there's a reason
you sent them on ahead.
I don't care for airing a
person's dirty laundry...
But I feel I should tell you...
about Kushida-san's past.
Classroom of
the Elite
Kushida-san and I...
We attended the same middle school.
The school was well attended,
and we were never in the same class,
so it took me some time to remember her.
One day, as our middle school
graduation drew near,
an incident occurred
that tore one of the classes apart.
And the rumor spread...
that the one who started it all
was a single female student.
And you believe it was Kushida?
It's all rumors, of course.
I don't know exactly what happened,
but the class remained in
turmoil until graduation.
But how could a single person
destroy an entire class?
I can think of a few ways.
Listen, Horikita...
Do you know what the strongest
weapon in this world is?
I'm not sure.
Violence, I suppose.
Nobody can stop violence
occurring in front of their eyes.
That's not Kushida's style.
If Kushida wields a power of
equal potency to violence...
One way or another,
Kushida-san sees me as an obstacle.
Even though I have no idea
what even happened...
I'm sure she doesn't believe that's true.
Direct action might be preferable
over trying to convince her.
Get Kushida-san expelled, you mean?
A strong offense is frequently
the most effective defense.
You're the one who admonished me for
considering cutting Sudo-kun loose.
Kushida will continue to plague
us until you're expelled.
Things have only gotten this bad, in part,
because I've refused to confront her.
And Kushida-san is quite talented.
She could be a considerable asset to Class D.
You think you can bring her to our side?
Yes.
I'm going to keep talking to her.
And I will make her understand.
Very well.
If you're that determined,
I'll watch from afar.
"Watch from afar"?
But I'll ask you to refrain from
protecting me the way you
did at the sports festival.
You knew about that?
I had an idea.
I was annoyed that you took action
on the assumption that I'd fail,
but I won't argue,
given how things turned out.
Sorry about that.
However...
If not for you, right now, I'd...
Thank you.
An extremely roundabout
expression of gratitude.
Seems to me there's been too much
that's off in these recent exams.
Too much to be a coincidence.
The mastermind pulling Class D's strings...
And the spy helping them out...
I know it's one of you.
You can't be serious!
All right, you lot.
Do you know what the strongest
power in this world is?
It's unrestrained violence.
I'll give you one last chance.
Come clean, and I'll let your betrayal slide.
Do exactly as I say, and I'll protect you.
But if you play dumb with me...
What's the matter?
Can't even look me in the eye,
Manabe?
You're the traitor, aren't you?
You think I didn't know the whole time?!
I... I'm sorry...
Don't sweat it. I forgive you.
Just tell me one thing...
Who's the mastermind behind it all?
I see.
Bullying can be a very amusing pastime.
How stupid can you get?
Just for that, you sold us
out to their ringleader?
Go easy on them, Ibuki.
I've already said I forgive them.
And you claim Yukimura and Ayanokoji
were the only witnesses?
In other words, the mastermind
is one of those two?
Hang on a minute.
I've had a few interactions with Ayanokoji,
and he didn't seem like
that kind of person to me!
Ayanokoji...
It seems almost too obvious
to be plausible...
Maybe I'll use her.
Hey, over here!
Hey, took you long enough!
What've you been up to?
We'll start at once.
Total brush-off, huh?
Typical, I guess...
We're talking about Paper Shuffle, right?
No.
The matter of immediate concern
is next week's mini test.
But that don't got squat
to do with our grades!
Perhaps I'll see how
Horikita does on her own.
If it doesn't influence
our academic standing,
then there can be only one reason for it:
The mini test's results will determine
the Paper Shuffle pairings.
Remember what our teacher said.
The Paper Shuffle sees a pair
or two expelled every year.
Doesn't that number seem a bit low?
If all the poorest-performing
students are grouped together,
Are you following this, Sudo?
you'd surely see a dozen or more failures.
Y-Yeah, you bet.
That's right!
Good point!
You think the pairs are designed
to create balanced scores?
Yes.
I believe the highest- and lowest-ranking
students will be paired together
so that all pairs have roughly
the same average score.
I get it!
Which means our goal should be
to precisely pair up those with the
highest and lowest academic performance.
We'll divide all members of Class D
into four blocks based on their
current academic standing.
Those in the lowest block will
leave their test sheets blank.
Oh, I get it!
Then they'll definitely get
paired with the highest scorers!
Yes.
Similarly, those in the
second-lowest block
will attempt to get only one question right.
I see. That'll reduce accidentally
disadvantageous pairings.
Are you keeping up with this, Sudo?
I'm pretty damn clueless.
Just keeping quiet so I don't get in the way.
Hey, you finally get how it works?
Shaddap! Nobody asked you!
This concludes my proposal.
The remaining question is: which class
should we request to receive our questions?
Classes A and B are full of students
with high academic performance.
So it sounds like...
Yes. Class C is our best bet.
Call Incoming
I told you to limit our contact.
What's the big deal?
I just wanna know what you told Sato-san!
This again?
What does it matter to you what I told her?
It matters a ton!
You threatened me and made
me do a bunch of stuff!
So... if Sato-san finds out about that,
it'll lead to some weird rumors about me.
Okay.
I see what you're getting at.
You're worried that if
I grow close with Sato,
I'll neglect my promise to protect you.
Why is that your first thought?!
Am I wrong?
Not entirely, but...
I promise, you have nothing to worry about.
So you're going out with her?
I didn't say that.
You basically did!
I'm getting your true colors
loud and clear here.
You think this is your big chance
to do some dirty stuff with someone.
Why would you assume that?
It's a tremendous leap in logic.
You think?
You leaped right to making
me do that weird stuff...
I beg your pardon.
If every interaction I have
with a woman is suspect,
what does that mean for Horikita?
I know Horikita-san's not that kind of girl!
She didn't actually ask me out yet, anyway.
Huh?
She said she wanted to keep things platonic,
and requested an exchange
of contact information.
Oh... Did she?
So there was nothing to agree to.
But I still bet you hope you
get paired up with her, huh?
Certainly not.
Well, I'll let you off the hook for now!
How inexplicably condescending of you.
Not how I meant it!
Anyway, that's all I wanted to know.
See ya!
Wait a minute.
I want to check something.
What is it?
Manabe and the others haven't
gone after you since then?
No... Not yet.
If anything does happen, tell me right away.
No matter what happens,
I swear I'll resolve it.
You'd better.
I mean... that was our agreement and all.
And make sure you delete the record—
...of this call, right? I know.
In Call
Perfect. See you later.
Apel terminat
The next day, Horikita explained
her plan to the class.
They seemed convinced by her explanation,
and agreed to play along.
A Swiss zoologist,
Alfred Portmann, once said
that all humans are born premature.
A newborn human can't even walk on its own.
Horikita is the same way.
But that same underdeveloped nature
is an indication of the capacity
for infinite potential.
Ziua micuțului test
An unprecedented sense of unity.
It's best when I don't have to get involved.
Următoarea zi
I will now announce the
pairs for Paper Shuffle.
Announcement of Mini Test Results
Heck yeah!
Paper Shuffle Pairs
Name | Test Result | Name | Test Result
1 | Horikita Suzune | 100 | Sudo Ken | 0
2 | Yukimura Teruhiko | 100 | Inogashira Kokoro | 0
3 | Koenji Rokusuke | 93 | Okitani Kyosuke | 0
4 | Hirata Yosuke | 90 | Yamauchi Haruki | 0
5 | Kushida Kikyo | 87 | Ike Kanji |
6 | Ijuin Wataru | 85 | Sotomura Hideo |
9 | Mori Nene | 75 |
10 | Matsushita Chiaki | 75 | Hondo Ryotaro | 1
11 | Ayanokoji Kiyotaka | 70 | Sato Maya | 1
12 | Onodera Kayano | 70 | Sakura Airi | 1
Incredible, in the worst possible way...