„Materialul trebuie creat.”
F. Nightingale - „Subsidiary notes as to the introduction of female nursing into military hospitals in peace and war”
Ce vrei să spui?
Numele grupurilor erau indiciile...
sau cumva soluția la acest test?
Tocmai ce ți-am explicat.
Gata, gata.
Ordinea planetelor în sistemul solar
și numele elevilor din fiecare grup...
Asta era cheia pentru a-ți da seama care e VIP-ul.
Are mai mult sens acum?
Marte e a patra planetă din sistemul solar.
Dacă ordonăm alfabetic, în baza alfabetului japonez, elevii din grupul Marte,
Ayanokoji
Kiyotaka
Ichinose Honami
Ibuki
Rei
Karuizawa Kei
Sotomura Hideo
Takemoto Shigeru
Hamagumo Tetsuya
Beppu Ryota
Mamoda Koji
Manabe Shiho
Morishige Takuro
Yabu Nanami
Yamashita Saki
Yukimura Teruhiko
ei vor fi aceștia: Ayanokoji, Ichinose, Ibuki și apoi Karuizawa.
Ayanokoji
Kiyotaka
Ichinose Honami
Ibuki
Rei
Karuizawa Kei
De asta am fost eu aleasă ca VIP?
Și a treia persoană din grupul Pământ, Kushida, a aleasă ca VIP.
Dar nu este acest sistem puțin cam...
Simplu.
Da, acesta e cuvântului!
E simplu odată ce ți-ai dat seama de regulă.
Dar să-ți dai seama de asta în timpul testului nu este.
E imposibil să confirmi regula știind doar VIP-urile din clasa ta.
Așa este.
Dar se pare că nu a fost pentru Ryuen.
S-a prins destul de repede de regulă.
Dar a făcut o greșeală.
Poate a uitat că nu este un monolit clasa C.
Vrei să spui că Ryuen nu are control total asupra clasei C?
A dictatorship frequently fosters a
populace unhappy with its oppressor.
The error could have come from
a student not under his control.
I wonder about that.
Perhaps maintaining leadership
is a difficult thing.
Maybe so.
Still, I'm glad you came to
us with this, Horikita-san.
What choice did I have?
There may be tests coming up
that I can't pass on my own.
Very probable!
As long as that's the case,
it'll be important to have
some quantity of connections.
Yes.
There are limits to how
hard one can fight alone.
Classroom of the Elite
The second term starts today.
From the month of September
through early October,
we'll have more gym classes than usual,
in preparation for the
upcoming sports festival.
I've given you your new schedules and
the sports festival documentation.
You can find the same information
on the school home page.
Regarding Sports Festival and Competition Points
Point Distributions
Rules and Teams for Sports Festival
The sports festival format will involve splitting the entire school into Red and White teams.
This year, the teams will consist of:
"Red Team" Class A and Class D; "White Team" Class B and Class C
Point Distribution for Mandatory Events (individual)
1st Place receives 15 points; 2nd place 12 points; 3rd place 10 points; 4th place 8 points.
Positions 5th place and below each receive one fewer point than the next position up.
For group competitions, the winning team receives 500 points.
Point Distribution for Voluntary Events
1st Place receives 50 points; 2nd place 30 points; 3rd place 15 points; 4th place 10 points.
Positions 5th place and below each receive two fewer points than the next position up. (Triple point values are awarded for the final relay race.)
Effect of "Red vs. White" Competition Results
Classes in all years of the team that receives fewer overall points will lose 100 CPt.
Effect of Rankings Per Class Year
In each class year, the class that receives the most total points will receive 50 CPt.
Compare them if you must.
Ma'am!
Is the sports festival
one of our special tests?
You can interpret it that way if you wish.
Though whatever you call it, it will
have a major influence on your class.
Cruelty unchained!
Heck yeah!
Time for me to shine!
Sports festival...
For this year's sports festival,
the entire school will compete
as Team Red and Team White.
You of Class D along with
Class A will be Team Red.
We're teamed up with Class A?
Along with second- and third-years...
Seems annoying.
I'm gonna carry Team Red to the win!
Let's raise hands to speak, everyone.
Keep it down, guys!
Are you thinking about how you'll
finally get a chance to see him?
Don't talk about that here.
I won't tell you a second time.
Right.
First, read through your materials.
Events consist of mandatory
and voluntary events.
Generally speaking, voluntary events
grant more points than mandatory ones.
It's important to give all
you have to every event.
The student who places last in individual events loses 1,000 PPt.
(If private points are currently below 1,000, penalty will be applied to written exams)
Piggyback Joust
The Piggyback Joust will consist of groups of four.
The penalty for losing is severe.
Ma'am.
What's this about bonuses
for the top three placers?
What's this about adding
points to written exams?
It's exactly what it sounds like.
By placing in the top,
you'll receive bonus points you
can add to your next written exam.
It can be very helpful for your tests.
For real?!
Heck yeah!
Wait, what?
Really?
That's amazing!
If it sounds too good to
be true, it usually is.
Crazy!
Could we use it to prevent failing?
lowest ten placers receive a penalty
A truly desirous result!
The lowest ten placers receive a penalty.
Come on, guys, keep it down!
Ma'am, what's this...
What's this penalty?
The bottom ten first-year placers will lose
ten points on their next written exam.
Say what?!
So we can lose points on our exams, too?!
I knew it!
That's so bad...
Might be hard not to fail...
What? What?
Seems pretty bad.
The materials I handed out also provide
a list of each sports festival event.
Yeah, pretty bad...
I had a feeling it might be so...
Keep it down, guys!
Event List
Mandatory Events
1. 100 Meter Dash
2. Hurdles
3. Topple the Pole (Boys Only)
4. Ball Toss (Girls Only)
5. Tug-of-War (Gender Segregated)
6. Obstacle Course
7. Three-Legged Race
8. Piggyback Joust
9. 200 Meter Dash
Voluntary Events
10. Scavenger Hunt
11. Four-Way Tug-of-War
12. Co-Ed Three-Legged Race
13. Combined Class Year 1200 Meter Relay
Thirteen events in all.
This is pretty hardcore...
We can't cover all this in one day!
We can.
There's no cheerleading or
dance competition, after all.
It will be purely a test
of stamina and athleticism.
Decide for yourselves who will
participate and in what order.
Fill in the participant
sheet and submit it to me.
How much are we allowed to decide on our own?
Everything.
You can decide everything about the
events, including who's in which heat.
The island and cruise ship tests
had infinite possibilities.
I've realized that's the case now.
So this time, as well—
What do you think
makes this test significantly different
from the previous special tests?
It seems like another special test to me.
The structure and effect on points seems
identical to previous special tests.
That is true.
On paper, it's the same.
But in practice, it's different.
For instance, the written exam.
Although there was the hidden trick
regarding buying things with points,
fundamentally, it was still
a test of academic ability.
You think the sports
festival is the same way?
We should assume that stamina and athletic
ability are the order of the day.
Sneaky tricks won't have much
bearing on the results.
The most important thing here is
strict preparation before the event.
That's all.
Preparation is just what I'm talking about.
You're looking for quick fixes, loopholes.
Like having someone be absent
before the competition,
or forcing them drop out partway.
I wasn't—
In other words, you want a surefire method.
Are you suggesting we have to fight
and win through orthodox means?
It's up to you how you take it.
C'mon, we gotta do it based on skill!
I know myself best of all.
If I win, the class wins!
That's best for everyone!
You think so?
Probability-wise, maybe...
If you want to take on all the
voluntary events, I'm okay with that.
Then it's settled!
I'll take part in all the voluntary events!
If everyone agrees with the skill method,
then the voluntary events—
How to decide on voluntary event participation?
Skill Method
Give priority placements to the skilled
Positive: Gives a high chance of winning
Negative: Gives others (less strong) little chance of winning;
ignores the will of other classmates
Voluntary Method
Choose placements based on what each person wants
Positive: Gives people the order they want; lets everyone enjoy themselves
Negative: Not everyone will get what they want; potential inconsistency of results
Wait.
I have a supplementary proposal.
Between the two options, I have
no objection to the skill method.
But there's no guarantee that we can beat
the other classes through that alone.
That's true.
While it's a given that we should put
our most athletic members in the
voluntary events where they specialize,
we can also best bring out
our maximum potential in the mandatory
events through optimized combinations.
For instance,
rather than putting two fast people
in a race together, eliminating one,
we should pair each with a slow person
to guarantee higher placements.
Wait a minute.
Doesn't that plan reduce the chances of
non-athletic people winning anything?
And we'll lose our chances
of getting the bonus...
What a disappointment 'twould be!
I understand the desire to
not lose private points, too.
An ultimate class victory will benefit
the individuals in the long run.
Why is this an issue?
B-But high placements get us
big bonuses on our next exam!
Besides, isn't quitting unfair?
I understand why you feel that way.
In that case—
But your priorities are misplaced.
Just focus on your studies to the point
where you don't have to rely on bonuses.
The bonuses are only given to
the top three placers, anyway,
so it's not that much of a problem, is it?
Is there an event you believe you
can place third or higher in?
Well...
May I?
Horikita-san's suggestion...
Sorry, but it doesn't work for me.
Classroom of the Elite
That's a very vague objection.
Well, I'm not as smart as you, Horikita-san.
I thought it was an entirely
reasonable proposal.
I just don't get it!
What exactly don't you "get"?
All of it?
Why don't you explain it so
even an idiot can understand?
Oh, right. You don't deal with idiots.
I didn't say that.
Did so!
Like Shinohara-san said, how can you
want to see the other students fail?
They'll be rewarded in the long run.
And you blamed people too stupid
to pass a test on their own?
How do you expect our class
to unite with that attitude?
That was the point of my suggestion.
Well, that's Horikita-san's idea.
What do you think, Kushida-san?
Huh? Me?!
Yeah.
It's tricky, isn't it?
I feel like I understand both sides!
Ideally, I think you'd combine both ideas.
So that the people taking first
and last both feel okay about it.
True.
That'd be for the best.
I've thought of that, of course.
A way for both sides to be satisfied.
Have students who don't need
test points take the top places,
then average out the private points
they gain with the ones the students
in the bottom ranks lose.
We'll share gains and losses among the class.
Hey, great idea!
But that's just for the points.
It also lowers our chances of winning.
What do you guys think?
If Karuizawa-san's against it, I am, too.
So am I.
Yeah! I agree with Karuizawa-san!
Are you people stupid?
You're against it because she is?
That's not logical!
The other classes can't possibly
have members as stupid as you all.
How do you know?
Point is, I'm against it.
And plenty of others are
clearly against it, too.
Horikita-san, you're just cruel.
She is.
Yeah.
I thought you were nicer than this...
Calm down, both of you.
If we can't agree,
we can settle this with a vote.
If Yosuke-kun says it, I'm in!
Horikita-san's idea is to
focus entirely on skill,
while Karuizawa-san's is to allow
personal opinion into discussion.
Let's have a show of hands.
First, who agrees with Horikita-san's idea?
Looks like ten votes.
Hey, Ayanokoji-kun!
Don't worry. I'm abstaining.
Next, Karuizawa-san's combined plan.
Who agrees with that?
Thank you.
The result of the vote is...
Ten votes for Horikita-san's idea.
Eight votes for Karuizawa-san's idea.
The rest abstained, I guess.
Heck yeah!
Now, regarding participation for each event,
let's take some dedicated time to discuss it.
Okay!
I'm in for all the events!
Sudo-dono is so quick to act!
Just leave it all to me!
Isn't this one cute?
Yeah, totally cute!
Right?
Excuse me!
That email you sent me.
Mind telling me what it was all about?
The bonuses are only given to
the top three placers, anyway,
so it's not that much of a problem, is it?
Închide
Ai primit un nou mesaj
De la: A
Deschide
Is there an event you believe you
can place third or higher in?
From: A
To: Karuizawa Kei
Subject: None
Find a way to oppose Horikita's suggestion.
When you do, ask for Kushida's opinion, too.
Well...
You cooked up a good argument on the spot.
I actually agreed with
Horikita-san's opinion, though...
And I don't understand why you wanted
me to get Kushida-san's opinion.
What was the point of the order?
If you need to understand the
reasoning behind everything I do,
we'll never get anywhere.
Besides, I won't always tell you.
Then tell me one other thing.
What is it you want?
To bring Class D to Class A.
I'm sure Horikita believes that.
That's not what I mean!
I want to know what you're after.
Oh, that?
I'm happy to make my current class
one capable of rising to Class A.
That's how I've begun to feel.
What in the world?
You think you're that much better than us?
You wouldn't believe me if I told you now.
And I can't prove it to you.
So I'm going to create a framework
to allow you to believe me.
During this sports festival, Class D...
will produce a traitor.
The traitor will likely spill all of
Class D's internal information to others.
Wait—
What?!
G-Give me something more concrete than that!
I will, when the time comes.
A t-traitor?
Isn't that dangerous?
The groundwork has been laid.
Now, go. We'll attract
too much attention here.
Alegerea participanților la evenimente
Be amazed!
Testele de aptitudini
That's amazing!
Awesome!
How's that?
11.5, looks like!
I pulled 82.4!
How dang strong are you?!
Over 80!
I've been workin' out.
Obviously.
You do it, too, Koenji.
I'd prefer not.
Here, Ayanokoji.
Yeah! Hope I get a good result!
What's wrong?
Show me your grip strength, Ike-dono!
What's the boys' average grip strength?
About 60, maybe?
Sixty?
Grip strength isn't necessarily proportional
to the thickness of one's arms.
What matters is the muscles
in the forearm called
the brachioradialis and
flexor carpi radialis.
Working these out will
increase grip strength.
In other words,
as long as you have
sufficient muscle mass,
you can train it to surpass 100 kilograms.
That should be acceptable.
It won't go any further.
What's your score?
60.6.
Wow.
You're strong, Ayanokoji-kun.
No, I think that's about average...
The average would be lower than that.
It's around 45, or maybe 50.
Take that!
It's a 42.6.
Couldn't you nudge me up to a 50?!
Ike-kun scores 42.6.
Oh, so 60 is on the higher side.
All done!
Let's see. I got...
Heck yeah!
I'm in for all the voluntary events!
The information we just
agreed on is very important,
Just watch, you guys!
How excited he is!
so write down only your own roles.
Sure, okay.
Don't take pictures or
leave any other record.
You gotta go harder than that!
Keep your hips low!
L-Like this?!
Really put your back into it!
I'm your leader, so you gotta keep up!
We're winnin' this, guys!
Y-Yeah...
I can't hear you!
Horikita-san, you're running too fast.
It's true that our rhythm is off,
but only because you're too slow.
Shouldn't the slower person try
to match the rhythm of the faster?
Who wants to compromise to
make their own times slower?
Can we talk?
About what?
I think you need to learn
to compromise a little more.
I'm only being stubborn because I want
to get us the best possible time.
In the three-legged race,
it's logical that the relatively slower
people should be made to pace up.
You're inflexible on this point?
Yes.
That will lower the number of people
willing to practice with you.
I can't match my rhythm to those
who refuse to work from the start.
Give me your leg.
Why?
Run a race with me.
Why should I?
There's a co-ed three-legged race.
We should try to assess our suitability
as partners, shouldn't we?
You think you can keep up with me?
You'll just slow me down.
Logically speaking,
speed shouldn't matter, should it?
Very well.
I'll tie us together.
Let's begin.
H-Hey!
It shouldn't be hard to match my rhythm.
I know that!
It's not about individual speed.
The problem is that you
won't look at your partner.
Looking at your partner and giving them a
degree of initiative is what's important.
Horikita.
Come out with me a while tomorrow.
What?
Tu, eu și încă o persoană,
will embark on Team White reconnaissance.
Da, asta ar putea funcționa!
Încă o persoană?
Kushida.
De ce ea?
Trădătorul din grupul Pământ de la testul de pe vasul de croazieră...
You're so reliable!
a fost ea.
I appreciate you helping
everyone, too, Kushida-san.
Oh, nu spune asta!