Știu că am venit aici
ca să investigăm, dar...
Nu a mai rămas nimic
din țara mea natală.
Asta a fost țara ta natală?
Aici fusese un mare oraș când eu încă eram micuță și drăguță.
Cred că erau niște ruine aici...
Unele care aveau legătură cu Lordul Demon?
Așa este.
Sunt ruinele unde mi-am
obținut armele legendare.
Biblioteca Raiului...
Știi...
S-a întâmplat ceva?
Nu, doar am fost cuprinsă de nostalgie.
Detecting a large-scale
energy signal from above.
Could it be the same as before?
Connect to Superbia Archive!
Execute Thema!
Meteo Dragonar!
Această putere...
Arata!
Filmul
Biblioteca Raiului și Lord Demon Stacojiu
Totul e în regulă acum, Lilith.
Ce? Tu ești... Akio, nu-i așa?
Am devenit puțin prea serioasă.
Sunt micuță și drăguță, nu-i așa?
Da.
Deci unde suntem?
În Biblioteca Raiului.
Exista în ceruri încă de
la începuturile timpului.
It has watched over the
world and all that it is,
and contains all its wisdom.
Mai important...
eu trebuia doar să vă fiu ghid.
Dar simt că tocmai am fost implicată în ceva ce nu-mi doresc.
Serios?
Bănuiesc că nu mai contează.
Asta e șansa mea.
E timpul să vă întorc favoarea.
Oh? Deci plănuiai să
ne trădezi până la urmă.
Nu am intenționat niciodată
să fiu de partea voastră!
Well, I did plan for just such an occasion.
I'm here just in case you tried
to play any tricks, Lugh.
E așa de strâns...
The demon lord candidate is
going to have his way with me,
and then the only purpose I'll
have left is to service him...
Deci asta îți trec prin minte.
Ei bine, dacă nu vrei să se întâmple ceea ce tocmai ai spus, ai face bine să-mi urmezi ordinele!
B-Bine...
Așa voi face.
Talk about despicable.
That's Arata-kun for you.
Doamne, Arata...
Bun, e de ajuns, Liese.
Bine!
You fell for it again!
Akio.
Mă ocup!
T-Timeout... I call timeout...
Ce se petrece?
It feels like...
Stăpâne, ai grijă! Ceva
periculos se îndreaptă spre noi!
Numele meu e Trinitatea Abisului.
Eu sunt Lordul Demon Stacojiu și stăpânul Archivei Luxuria.
Are aceeași față ca stăpânul meu.
Deci avem de a face cu un
Lord Demon dintr-o altă lume?
Sistemul de securitate al
Bibliotecii Raiului l-a adus aici.
It's just part of the alternate
world Demon Lord's power.
Sistemul de securitate?
Când un candidat la poziția
de Lord Demon vine aici,
e forțat să înfrunte un Lord Demon dintr-o lume alternativă.
Așa este, fetiță Spriggan.
Iar el e cel care mi-a distrus țara natală.
Se pare că orașul de dedesubt a fost distrus când îmi testam puterile.
Amintirea e destul de vagă,
dar cred că am făcut-o...
deoarece mă plictiseam.
Dintr-un... asemenea motiv...
Sunt aici ca să-l distrug
pe acel Lord Demon.
Chiar credeai că abilitățile tale
vor funcționa asupra mea?
Akio!
Te voi lăsa pe tine să te ocupi de el,
candidatul la poziția de Lord
Demon din această lume.
Arata!
Lugh!
Arma lui Virtus: Lancea Străpungătoare de Lumină, Brionac!
Se pare că datoria ta față
de mine tocmai a crescut.
Mersi, Lugh!
Frate Lord Demon,
ar trebui să știi că nici eu nu
voi fi doborât atât de ușor.
Atunci, arată-mi de ce
ești în stare, „frate mai mic”.
Ține asta! Meteo Dragonar!
Asta e tot ce poți?
Cu o singură mână?!
Acum e momentul să-ți
arăt eu de ce sunt în stare.
Teza mea e Vanitas.
Reprezintă conceptul
morții și distrugerii,
care reduce totul la nimic.
Asta e de rău!
Trebuie să pleci de acolo!
I'll intercept!
I see... This is the moment...
Ce?
Schimbare de planuri.
With you, I'll be able to regain
the power of the demon lord!
Lilith!
Îți mulțumesc, candidat
al poziției de Lord Demon.
Ai făcut o treabă bună
aducându-mi această fată.
El...
To show my gratitude,
I shall wipe you from existence
instantly, sparing you from pain.
Master, he's serious business!
Please run!
Dar a luat-o pe Lilith!
It can't be done...
Lugh, please help us out!
Foarte bine.
Datoria ta față de mine
va crește și mai mult.
Fugiți dacă credeți că puteți...
scăpa de o lovitură directă
de la un Lord Demon!
Lilith!
Atât de multă magie impură...
As my prophecy foretold, it seems the
Crimson Demon Lord has awakened,
and the demon lord
candidate has fought him.
And Lugh-chan seems to have just
barely managed to save them.
Why did he take Lilith-sensei?
Well, it may be that
Lilith-sensei has a secret.
The problem is that
Arata-san would have been
wiped out by that demon lord
if left to his own devices.
We have to accept this fact.
That's true,
and we also have to get
Lilith-chan back somehow.
And that means...
It's our turn now, I imagine.
Yep.
I was thinking of asking the remaining
Trinity Seven here to retrieve Lilith-chan.
Hijiri, you should guide the demon lord
candidate to the ultimate demon lord weapon.
The ultimate demon lord weapon...
Judecca.
That being said,
I'm not sure if he'll be able to stay
in his right mind once he obtains it.
Lilith!
Unfortunately, he successfully
took our teacher away from us.
I see...
Where are we?
In one of my dreams.
You fainted and accidentally ended up here.
Really?
Sorry about that.
Didn't mean to intrude.
It's fine.
Your magic will recover faster
if you sleep a bit, anyway.
Makes sense...
That demon lord was pretty powerful, though.
Sorry, I didn't mean to complain.
Don't worry. No one else is around to know.
This is your hometown, right?
Why was everything destroyed?
That demon lord we fought destroyed it all.
Abyss Trinity...
My mom protected me with her Mantra Enchant.
I see.
Your mom did a good job protecting you.
Y-Yeah.
Then I need to do the same.
I can't let him get to you now.
You...
I have to get Lilith back, too.
So I'll have to be even more powerful,
even more like God,
in order to protect all of you.
Where am I?
It seems you've awakened.
Why did you take me?
It's no surprise you don't
know about yourself.
You are not of this world.
What are you talking about?
Lilith Azazel.
You exist to return my power to me.
How dare you—
What about Arata? What happened to Arata?
Arata?
Oh, you mean that demon lord candidate?
It seems he got away.
I believe he's resting
somewhere in this castle.
I see...
You'd rather worry about him
than about yourself, huh?
Don't worry.
There's nothing I need from you until
I'm finished preparing for the spell.
I won't do as you wish!
I'm not so sure about that.
You cannot defy me.
No matter what.
How can you be so sure?!
You still don't get it?
This is...
The light of a Luxuria demon lord element.
An element of my power
that sleeps within you!
Your demon lord element is within me?
That's correct.
It is because you are my daughter,
Lilith Azazel!
I don't have any parents.
But the resonance of the demon lord
element is proof in and of itself!
Now obey me, as my daughter.
If you do, I'll give you enormous power!
I won't...
Such a stubborn girl.
I can't believe I'm the
daughter of someone like you!
It doesn't matter if you believe it or not.
I will use your power
to reclaim my power as demon lord.
And when that happens, this world, as well,
will be destroyed by my demon lord power!
I won't let you destroy our world!
Realize: Buster Mode!
I see. You wish to get a
bit closer to your father.
Disintegrate into light, Helmick Buster!
You do possess strong magic.
You can use Outer Alchemic
and bring forth impressive magical power.
It's no match for that of
your demon lord father,
but I am truly pleased with your growth!
Excuse me.
Secret Technique: Avidya Slash!
So a mage has infiltrated us, eh?
Finding any escape routes or
hidden paths is a ninja's job.
Levi-san!
We're here, too!
We've come to save you, Lilith-sensei!
Dreamy Faerie Serenade!
Soil!
A distraction, huh?
Magic as impure as yours
will disappear before
my justice, my Justitia!
White Universe!
Using attack magic to create
a distraction and flee...
Those mages showed impressive judgment.
Now, I guess I'll enjoy a game
of father-daughter tag.
The central part of the castle is that way.
The only exit is there.
I'm pretty sure our demon lord
is around there somewhere.
Hey, to be perfectly honest,
we can't beat that demon lord
as we are now, can we?
Yeah, probably not.
The difference in our
magic level is too great.
Isn't there anything we can do?
There is.
Hijiri!
I've come to save you, Arata-san.
Something we can do...
Could it be treasure?
Well, it is a type of treasure,
but I don't think anyone
but Arata-san can use it.
Isn't that right, Akio-san?
Are you talking about what
I think you are, Hijiri?
What's that?
The demon lord weapon, Judecca.
It's a forbidden weapon that only
a demon lord can use, and it
allows them to destroy the world.
The only problem is whether or
not my current master can use it.
Even if he could use it,
I'm not sure he'd be able to go back
to being a normal mage afterward...
A normal mage...
Not that you were ever a normal mage.
I know I'd never lose to a normal mage.
It's because you're a demon lord.
Yeah. All right.
Can you lead me to that
demon lord weapon, then?
Sure!
This...
wasn't here the last time I was here.
Yeah, that's right.
Akio-san, a Spriggan and
protector of the ruins,
must have caused a secret door to open when
she brought a demon lord candidate here.
Oh, I see. So we'll find the
demon lord weapon if we go on?
But...
It seems Heaven's Library won't
let us get there so easily.
That thing's huge!
It's a Guardian Golem.
Watch out!
Protect yourself!
Conception!
Ow... Damn, it's powerful!
Don't let your guard down!
Black Azazel!
It didn't do anything?
Anti-demon lord types are really strong.
Do you have to hate demon lords so much?
It's gotten even more powerful.
This isn't good.
You help, too!
Oh, no!
Are you okay?
Y-Yeah.
Good...
We don't have time to fool around right now.
Let's get going.
Is this it?
Yes.
This is the demon lord weapon of Control,
the Impel Arm, that sleeps
in Heaven's Library...
The Black Imperial Sword, Judecca.
The Black Imperial Sword, Judecca?
Hey there.
Arata-san!
A bunch of the other
Guardian Crystals are here now!
We don't have much time, Arata-kun!
Let's get what we need.
And if you think I can use it,
give it to me when we're done.
Well, I'm not sure if I can do this or not,
but I guess I'll try to get this thing.
Demon lord element confirmed.
Judecca will now activate.
O-Okay.
Be careful, Master.
I know.
Judecca, lend me your power.
Confirmed Archive: Superbia and Thema: Impel.
Analysis complete.
Luxuria, Outer Alchemic.
Gula, Mantra Enchant.
The specified demon lord
has not reached Trinity.
Entering forced start-up sequence.
Initiating Rampage in target demon lord.
This isn't good!
It's gonna make Arata-san's
magic go out of control
and destroy the world!
What?!
This isn't good!
Hey!
Let go of Judecca!
Akio-san!
We only have one shot now.
Akio, put all your magic
into the camera shutter!
G-Got it!
Chrono Calculation!
Where am I?
Whew.
Looks like I made it in time.
Liese!
Where am I?
You're within my frozen world.
In simpler terms,
we're inside Selina's camera.
You stopped it for me?
Thanks.
Well, more accurately,
it's still moving, albeit slowly.
It'll only buy you some time.
Well, that makes sense...
Wait a—
Hey, it could've been really dangerous
to just pull that thing out, Master!
Yeah, you really frightened me!
Oh, sorry.
I couldn't move easily with it
on me, so I wasn't thinking.
Sorry about that, Liese.
You had to save me again.
It's fine.
I like you quite a bit, anyway.
Anyway, Sora-chan, why couldn't
Arata-kun use that demon lord weapon?
It seems like he's short one last Archive.
You can only use Lilith
and Akio's magic, right?
I knew it...
In that case, I'm going to have
you steal my magic right now.
And since the mood's right...
I'm going to get very hands-on teaching
you everything you need to know.
I appreciate it.
You mustn't be perverted!
Well, we'll help you out, too.
Yeah, thanks.
So what am I supposed to do?
You know I can copy other
people's magic, too, right?
So I'm going to try getting
a taste of you one more time
and analyzing you.
Are you sure you're not just planning on
eating Arata-san's demon lord
element just to get out of here?
Well, I could do that, too.
You don't have to believe me, Arata-kun.
I'm a bad mage.
Of course I believe you.
Huh?
You might be a bad mage,
but you're my friend, too.
It's okay for someone to be
bad if they're a friend?
It doesn't matter if you're good or bad.
You're Liese.
The bad parts of you, the part of you
that loves your little sister, Selina...
And the part of you that's
just so damn sexy.
I like you because you're you.
What's wrong with that?
Oh...
Thank you, Arata-kun.
All right!
That's enough lovey stuff.
O-Okay.
Now, then, Arata-kun...
I'm going to take a bit of your magic.
I, uh...
I'm ready.
Y-You mustn't be perverted, okay?
But you know what's best...
Wh-Wh...
Wh-Wh-Wh-Wh-Wh-Wh...
Wh-Wh-Wh-Wha?!
Direct bodily contact, huh?
That's the best way to
improve magical sensitivity.
Right?
So I'm going to make use of my
whole body to take all of him.
Your whole body? For real?
Look, you're all nervous.
Anyway, Sora-chan, Ilia-chan,
I'll be counting on you.
Sure.
Fine.
Get this over with, and
then stay away from him.
What's going on here?
Am I about to become a man?!
You're going to learn the conditions
and method for copying one's magic.
We can become adults together
once we're back home.
Not even then! I won't let you!
Well, you can have fun fooling around
until this dirty girl and I finish our analysis.
Oh, sure. I could go for this anytime.
Time to analyze.
Or maybe this works better?
The first condition, Form, has been analyzed.
To understand the governing principles
and concepts of a magic...
In other words, to learn its name and
execution, you must use your eyes and ears.
Well, yeah, I've seen
Lilith and Akio's magic.
The second condition, Understanding,
has been completed.
That means understanding
the evolutionary tree that
forms from the very substrate of magic,
the progenitors of which
are still known by name
to the mages of this day.
Progenitor mages?
I think Akio's was Saekino Mao...
I think I've heard Lilith's, too.
I've also executed Logos Art.
And during the Last Crest ordeal, I told
you the progenitor mage was Pythagoras.
The third condition, Reason—
Liese!
She was fine before since she
had the demon lord element...
But Liese-san is just a normal mage now.
When she eats your magic, she's being
eaten from the inside out by it instead.
No!
Liese!
The third is...
A breakdown and analysis of the fundamentals
of the magic you wish to copy.
You get to its nature.
A breakdown and analysis of the
fundamentals of that magic?
That makes sense!
It's the magic you're best at, Master.
The magic I'm best at? You don't mean...
My "turning people naked" magic?!
I'm not sure why you'd call it that...
You're breaking down their Magus mode
and analyzing their magic.
In short...
Why not try it on the lady there?
Can you do it, Arata-kun?
Of course!
I can't leave you hurting like this.
Could the two of you help me?
Sure.
Leave it to us!
I trust you, Arata-kun.
Yeah, leave it to me.
I promised you I'd get you back home.
Give me your magic and your power,
Liese!
Okay, Arata-kun...
Here I go!
Impel Magista!
He did it!
He made it through Process #3!
Arata!
All right...
Time to fight back.
Arata-san!
Chrono Calculation...
I see...
So you've gotten Logos Art.
Yeah.
Take care of Liese for me, Akio.
Come, Judecca.
Luxuria, Outer Alchemic.
Gula, Mantra Enchant.
Acedia, Logos Art.
Trinity confirmed.
Good morning, demon lord.
Y-Yeah.
Um...
Can you get rid of him?
There is a 100% chance of submission.
No problem.
I see. In that case...
Arata-san's magic dropped to zero?
Is this his...
Yes, this magic...
At last...
Did he...
My husband...
Oh?
That demon lord candidate...
Really?!
You got us all excited, and now
you're not going to defeat him?
Huh? Oh, that's already been done.
I think I really understand how to
use magic now, thanks to this thing.
You made him instantaneously explode after
lowering your magical power to zero...
Only a paladin could pull that off.
So, um... Could I try touching the sword?
Well, sure, if you want to,
but I wouldn't recommend it.
Extracting magical energy from target mage.
Wait, not that! That's really not...
Are you okay?
I don't think I'll ever be able to
marry anyone but you now...
Uh... Well, I'm all for that,
but I'm not seeing the logic here.
Well, if I marry you,
then all of your treasure
becomes mine, as well.
You never change, do you?
Anyway, Lugh was a nice distraction,
but we should head toward Lilith's magic.
Lilith-sensei, you shouldn't
push yourself so hard.
That feeling just now...
Did something happen to Arata?
No, I should have faith...
that he's still himself.
Yeah, you're right.
Looks like he's caught up to us.
It seems that demon lord candidate
has obtained the demon lord weapon
and started down the same path
as demon lord that I have.
Arata's becoming a demon lord...
As time was running out,
he obtained the Trinity,
and he now controls the demon lord weapon.
He's pretty good for a kid.
Those who awaken as demon lords have
no one who can stand against them,
who even compares to them,
because of their enormous power.
In the end, all you have
is absolute isolation.
Your mind loses its
human consciousness and,
finally, you become a
full-fledged demon lord.
A-Arata won't lose his heart that easily!
Oh?
No matter the situation he's in,
he's audacious, impudent, clueless,
perverted, and timid.
When he first became a mage,
during any breakdown phenomenon,
and even when his own life is in danger,
he was and still is our unchanging Arata.
And there's no way he'll change just
because he's a demon lord now.
How amusing.
And yet you're the daughter
of a demon lord...
Or perhaps it's because you are one.
What are you saying?
The world is nothing but a
cycle of beginnings and ends.
The demon lord is part of that system,
and the demon lord is
always born as a human.
I was born as a mage,
and it seems this world's demon lord
candidate was raised as a normal human.
But without exception, the demon lord will encounter
that world's top mages,
the Trinity Seven,
and begin his transformation.
And because that concept is furthest
from the concept of Luxuria, lust,
when I became a demon lord,
I decided to defy that system
before my world was destroyed.
That meant having a child.
I mated with someone from my world,
and you were born.
And by sending you to a different world,
I succeeded in sending my
demon lord element to another world.
You mean... you sent me
here to destroy his world?
That's correct, daughter of mine.
Lilith-sensei!
Now, with the power that lies within you,
the Last Key, which will unlock the world...
I will regain my true power as Demon Lord!
Arin-chan, let's go!
Yeah.
If you overstimulate it,
the demon lord element within
my daughter will go berserk,
and her body will be torn apart.
Now, demon lord element that
lies within my daughter,
appear before me!
Arata...
I think you've taken this
a bit too far, old man.
Judecca!
My dragon, Mushussu!
Akio!
Right!
Ninja, Yui, Arin!
Okay!
Right!
Got it!
Take that!
And that!
Don't get cocky, kid!
Realize!
Reboot!
Are you okay, Lilith?
Arata...
Uh... S-Sorry I was a bit late!
It's okay.
You're still you.
Huh?
Well, of course I am.
Sorry. Were you scared
while I wasn't here?
Yes, I was.
I thought you might change.
Me? Why would you think that?
I thought that the closer you got
to becoming a demon lord,
the more you'd lose your humanity.
That's what you were worried about?
I won't change.
If I did, Mira would slap me.
So if you don't like what I'm doing,
just give me a good slap across the face.
Are you sure?
Of course.
If you're not going to get mad, I won't
hesitate to fondle those boobs!
Is this really any time
for you to be such a perv?
Okay, Lilith, hang on for just a second.
You're much stronger now that you've
gotten your demon lord weapon, kid.
The Brilliant Imperial Sword, Caina...
That's what destroyed my world...
That's his demon lord weapon?
I knew there had to be more to your power.
I see...
As you approach my class, you can
gauge my ability that much better.
Let's go, old man!
Come forth, kid.
Arata-san...
This isn't good, husband...
Hijiri-chan, Arin-chan...
Any more, and...
Husband, you mustn't fight him any more!
Do the two of you know something?
They're about equal... No...
His power's just slightly greater.
Brilliant Imperial Sword, Caina!
Execute Thema: Fall.
It looks like he's put some high-level
destruction magic into his sword.
Yeah. Guess I'll have a go at it.
You two, analyze and come
up with a way to handle it.
Got it!
Leave it to us!
You're going to leave the
magic to your grimoires
and come at me with your own strength, huh?
Interesting!
We've analyzed the Thema Fall.
It erases the existence of that which
it touches, including any magic in it.
That's what's imbued in that sword.
Judecca, we're going to use Akio's power.
Conception!
Roger that, Master.
Executing Archive: Gula, Thema: Fides.
What?!
The feelings of all those people
in the city you destroyed...
Akio's mom's feelings...
You're going to be hit with all of them!
Caina's magical signature has disappeared?!
He erased his opponent's magic...
So he directly hit his opponent with the
Mantra Enchant he put into the sword?
Just how much of that power does
Arata-san have hidden within him?
A demon lord candidate who has
obtained both the Trinity
and the demon lord weapon...
I suppose one who only has
a portion of that power
is at a disadvantage.
I'd like you to surrender and agree
to be sealed away, if possible.
However, the time has come.
Lilith, run away!
Huh?
Wh-What's going on?
Lilith!
This elevation in magical power...
It's like what happened to Hijiri-chan...
She's becoming a demon.
The manifested attire
of the Luxuria Archive...
Aeshma...
So you're finally here, my daughter.
The Last Key that surpasses the world itself.
Now, open for me, my world.
My power is coming forth!
The true power of a demon lord!
I shall show you the power
of a true demon lord.
The essence of my magic...
The darkness that is Vanitas.
A void that consumes all.
The nature of this world,
the truth of this world...
I, Abyss, shall overwrite
all that is in this world
with the Law that is Nihilism!
Furthest Argol!
I can't negate this?
He's overwriting the very laws of nature.
This magic surpasses magic itself!
Run, Arata-san!
Chrono Calculation!
The power of a demon lord
cannot be measured!
Arata-san!
My Furthest Argol will continue
to devour everything
until it reaches the ends of the earth.
It is the essence of Vanitas.
All Archives fall before the
power that is my Vanitas,
and are erased.
It is a natural law created by a demon lord—
true magic, kid.
It's coming here, too...
This magic is really scary!
So this is the power of the demon
lord who will destroy the world...
My body...
My magic is fading...
At this rate, we'll just
get caught up in it, too.
Looks like Arata-kun's in trouble.
Are you planning on
going to that monster?
Yeah, I guess so.
Yeah.
Is it because that man is
your demon lord candidate?
Huh? That's not it at all.
We fell in love with him!
I see.
Anyway, we'll be back!
I might not make it out of this.
Currently, the chance that
you will survive is less than 1%.
The cold truth, huh?
Hello, Arata-kun!
How are you doing?
It looks like you're having a
harder time than I expected.
Y-You guys...
I'd like to tell you to leave
because it's dangerous, but...
I guess you're already here, anyway.
We won't be able to win head-on like this.
That demon lord is using a magic
that makes use of the total Trinity.
So he's using them all and
putting it into his Vanitas, huh?
I kind of feel sad for him.
He managed to make it to our world,
and all he could do was
use his daughter as a tool.
All right, I've decided!
In any event, I guess I'll
just have to punch him!
I need to show him that his style
of demon lord is out of date!
Good plan. Sounds like something you'd do.
Yeah.
You should just keep trying to be you.
All right...
Give me a hand, you two.
Okay!
Reconnect to Superbia Archive!
Reconnect to Gula Archive!
Reconnect to Acedia Archive!
Execute Thema!
Oh?
You're going to control three of the Archives
to fight against the power of the Trinity, eh?
Not a bad idea.
However, kid, I am already above that.
I am this world's demon lord!
You shall fade into nothingness
along with your friends!
I didn't set up this spell to fight
back against that, old man!
I'm borrowing the power of my
friends in order to surpass you!
Impel Magista!
I'm sorry, Lilith.
You keep having to go through
all this scary stuff.
I know now.
Thanks to that demon lord, I know now.
To save Hijiri, I just kept learning magic,
went through so much, and had
so much help from all of you.
But Hijiri wasn't the only important one.
You're important to me, too, Lilith.
Yui, Levi, Arin, Akio, Mira, everyone...
And Liese's important, too.
I want to exist in a world
where all of you are.
And to make that happen,
I want you to come with me.
I want you to come into my Trinity Seven.
Arata...
I will.
I will always be with you.
Reconnect to Luxuria Archive.
The true attire of a demon lord...
The Trinity Form...
Impossible...
You can surpass even the Trinity?
This is the fourth Archive.
Arata-san.
It's finally time.
Gula. The Thema is "faith,"
Fides.
Acedia. The Thema is "stagnation,"
Stagna.
Luxuria. The Thema is "life,"
Abies.
Three Archives, three Themas.
And I have my own Thema:
Superbia, "control."
I command with Impel!
I am the Black Imperial Sword, Judecca,
the embodiment of the Fourth Gate.
Mira, Arin, Yui, Levi, lend me your power!
Very well.
Let's go, everyone!
We'll help you, too!
I will support you, Arata-san!
This is our world's demon lord.
This is how I do it, old man!
I will fight with everyone's help.
If it is fate that the
world will be destroyed,
then I'll just take control
of that destruction!
That's my magic!
You naïve demon lord!
The magic of the Void will
devour any magic you have!
Hey, I think mages with bad
habits should watch out.
What?
I like taking the best moments
for my future husband.
Old man...
The reason you lost...
is because you never made
any important friends!
Le Ciel Cocytus!
I see...
Am I in Akio's dream?
Nope.
This is reality.
There's nothing here, as always.
It's my homeland.
I see.
So we're finally back.
Is everyone asleep?
Yeah.
I was pretty tired myself,
but I wanted to be up first.
That's why I willed myself awake.
Thank you.
I should be thanking you.
Now I can get you and
the others back safely.
Your mom won't get angry with me, after all.
Where are we?
My hometown...
Mom!
Yeah.
Thank you.
Well, anyway...
Now I'm back to normal.
Thanks, Arata.
Yeah, you should rest.
Oh, yeah, what happened to Judecca?
Master, I'm right here.
Oh, you have a compact form?
Yes, I can take any form you wish.
What would you look like as a human girl?
Rather... busty.
Seriously?!
Show me sometime!
If that is what you wish.
I wanna see busty!
I was just thinking of commending
you on all you've done...
I can't believe you'd sexually harass a sword!
W-Wait, Lilith!
My ideal amount of bustiness is
exactly your amount of bustiness!
So don't worry, okay?
Arata, you...
Ajutor!
Oprește-te!
That was pretty good.
Da.
I'm talking about you.
Ce?
I was watching, too.
What?!
I witnessed it, as well.
Really?!
I want to hug my husband, too.
We have to be at least somewhat proper.
That's not easy.
Și eu vreau să-l îmbrățisez!
Arata, stai! Nu mai fugi!
Ei bine, e distractiv să fii prin preajma lui.
Sunt de acord.
Arata!
Îți strig numele
Kurui sou na karada wo ugokashite yuku
Te rog să rămâi așa cum ești
(Nu te schimba!)
Kono mune ga shimesu no wa utsuro na akai yami
Namida no fuchi ga kioku tadoru you ni nagareta
Shukumei kara nukedashitai to sakende ah
Chikara wo te ni shita shounen ga kare no michi wo aruku
Jiyuu ni miete kowai wa
Shounen ga hate ni miru kodoku wo daku tame ni
Watashi wa iru
Anata no namae wo yonde
Kurui sou na karada wo ugokashite yuku
Kyomu no housoku wo midashite
Watashi wa anata to ikite yuku
Watashi-tachi wa tomo ni aragau
Anata no sekai wo shinjite iru
"Kitai" ga itai "kakugo" mo kurai
Asobi ni you douke
Naze sonna ni mo tsuyoi no?
Sakanade suru you ni tawamurete
Șapte păsări își iau zborul
Aishite aisare sore ga
Dore dake no yuuki ni naru ka tte koto yo
Hashiri nuketeku kaze mitai na
Anata to te wo tsunaideru
Watashi-tachi wa yami ni sakarau
Anata no sekai wo mite mitai no
Sukoshi zutsu mirai ga ugoku
Sukoshi dake shikai ga yureta
Anata wa doko?
"Zettai ni mukae ni iku"
Anata no koe wa kikoeteru no ni
Aitai aitai no ni
Shin'en kara nukedashitai to sakenda ah
Anata no namae wo yonde
Kurui sou na karada wo ugokashite yuku
Kyomu no housoku wo midashite
Voi supraviețui alături de tine
Watashi-tachi wa tomo ni aragau
Mă voi încrede în lumea ta