Catch (ooishi) the rabbit, Kanoyama!
The rabbit's "yummy (oishi)"?
No! It's about the thrill of the hunt.
Although, they are yummy, huh?
So we are talking about eating.
Don't eat the rabbit this time!
I don't think she'd taste good!
But let's hunt her down!
Yeah!
Please! Please don't shoot me!
No! Please don't do it!
Please don't shoot me!
No, don't do it!
I promise I won't shoot till you tell me why.
Which means I'll shoot you if you don't.
I'll die.
Well, yes.
I will die...
Stop being so formal!
Did the player just switch?
This is the real me.
And if you shoot me, I'll die.
I'll die!
You mean in the game?
No, not in the game!
What do you mean?
If I die in SJ, the real me will die, too!
This isn't Sword Art Online.
M, what was written in that letter?
If you try anything funny, I'll shoot.
Okay.
"Yoo-hoo, M. Are you in a tough battle?
I told you to read this after an hour,
so if you ripped it up, I'll kill you."
You're participating in my place, so have a blast!
It's a game, so it's just for fun!
If you die a cowardly death,
I'll slaughter you, okay?
But if you two actually survive for an hour,
I'll be so impressed!
I'll pat you on the head and praise you.
If you die after that, though,
I'll kill you, okay?
And no suicide.
Whatever happens, you have to survive.
Without tension in the battle,
it wouldn't be fun, you know?
Now, then. Enjoy yourself! Feel life!
That's all.
I don't really need to ask,
but Pito wrote this, right?
That's right.
I can picture her writing this,
but she means "kill you" in the game, right?
You don't understand anything!
You have no idea how crazy Pitohui is!
Pitohui will kill me.
If she says she will, she really will!
"In the game?"
It's not that trivial!
I know she'll murder me in reality!
That woman knew that,
which is why she wrote me the letter!
She says to have a blast,
and now this?
She yearns for a "death game!"
That woman is still obsessed with it!
She's insane!
This is just like her!
So if you die in battle in SJ,
the real Pitohui will murder the real you.
That's what I've been saying!
Thank you very much.
So why did I need to die?
If you died, I'd become the leader.
And then?
I could surrender.
You took me lightly, huh?
I should've kept quiet
and thrown a grenade instead.
Okay, moving on...
15:15...
The scan finished a while ago.
They could be close.
Well, whatever.
M, don't worry about it.
From now on, I'll fight alone.
You can hide somewhere.
If I die, then you can surrender.
Thanks for everything! Bye!
How can I maximize my advantage?
That's... That's obvious.
All right! I'll run!
It's not my fault. It's better this way.
Nobody knows how scary that woman is.
So they can say whatever they want.
I'm not in the wrong here.
What's bad about being afraid to die?
I'm gonna go wild!
The last battle! I'm gonna see it through!
Well, as far as I can, anyway.
You're mine!
Enemy locat—
She dodged?
One enemy! Armed with a P90!
She's fast as hell!
I did—
No!
How dare you?
Die.
Dammit!
How many times today does this make it?
Leave the Last Battle to Me
I'll avenge you.
You or Sophie take this.
I hope you have a chance to use it.
Roger.
I'll take the kill shot.
HP at 70%. Six magazines left.
Two plasma grenades.
A knife.
I might need it to commit suicide.
That was far. About 200 meters away.
LLENN, no matter how bad your situation is,
or how scared you are, never fire randomly.
It's like a drug that lets you forget your anxiety,
at least while you're shooting,
but it wastes bullets and in addition to giving away
your location to the enemy, it tells them "I'm scared!"
As a plan, it's the worst of the worst.
Can I still win this?
I'll kill them all and claim victory!
Imagine the look on M and Pito's faces
when I get an easy win!
She has the luck of the devil.
I missed my shot.
She's retreating to the south.
Begin pursuit. Stay on guard.
Roger!
I'll finish her off.
I-I was shot by a sniper.
I didn't hear anything coming.
It was a trap.
They intentionally gave away their position
to draw me out.
Of course a team that's survived this long
wouldn't have done something so stupid.
B-But...
I can still move. I-I'm still lucky.
Found her! Directly under the sun!
About 100!
That boulder?
Да!
(Yes!)
Lend me your shoulder!
Die!
No!
Not good! It's not good!
I'm a goner! I'm definitely a goner!
If I move from here, I'll get shot.
If I stay, they'll throw a grenade at me!
Will it work? Well, it's the only way!
One...
Two...
Three!
She used the explosion as cover!
She's moving farther west!
There's more rock formations over there!
Roger!
She's... good.
No kidding. The best was saved for last.
It worked! It worked! It worked! It worked!
All right!
I'll keep running and running... and running.
What should I do?
Running, and then what?
How have I survived up to now?
How have I won?
I got close.
When I took down my opponents,
I was up close.
I can't run away.
That's right, LLENN!
You finally figured it out, huh?
So stop running away.
Go after the enemy.
I-I can hear...
Make use of your speed and agility
to fight in a style all your own.
...a voice.
I'm with you!
No, no, no, no, no!
Live or die, we'll be together!
This can't be happening!
Where are you? Come out! Come out!
Boss!
Looking for me?
Yeah!
Here I go!
You little...
- She's tiny!
- Run!
P-chan?
You did well, munchkin.
Now, die already!
The grenade?
A sniper?
M!
Are you joining now?
Yeah.
For the last battle, anyway.
Sorry. I failed to take them out.
Don't worry about it.
Don't underestimate me!
This is the end.
Wh-Why won't you die?
Ow...
Are you immortal?
The scan terminal! An Immortal Object!
In that case...
Empty!
D-Doesn't that hurt?
It's easy to forget that
when you're excited, huh?
Then you should remember!
But I feel too weak.
You seem strong enough to me!
What's your name, munchkin?
LLENN. What's yours?
Eva. But everyone calls me "Boss."
You're out of ammo, aren't you?
So are you.
Boss!
Sophie!
Shoot us both!
But...
Just shoot!
Boss! Use this!
No way.
Don't give up!
I'll protect you, LLENN!
How's that?
How dare you?
How dare you shoot P-chan?
You used your gun as a shield?
Think you can escape?
You cut me!
I win.
She let go of it right before...
I-I did it!
Get down!
Over here!
You've got guts!
M!
Congratulations!
The winner is LM!
M!
M—
His head's twisted completely around!
- A ghost!
- What are you talking about?
Oh, come on. Don't scare me like that!
After all, I... absolutely don't want to die.
Squad Jam, game over!
The winner is Team LM!
The game lasted one hour and 28 minutes.
During the event...
a total of 49,810 shots were fired!
U-Um, sorry to randomly bother you, but...
w-we're always passing you, right?
Y-Yeah.
Did you get a haircut?
Yeah, I got it cut short yesterday.
It looks good. You look cool!
R-Really?
Every time we walk by you, we talk about
how tall and stylish you are, like a model.
I mean, we're all short...
I liked how you looked with long hair,
but this looks even better on you!
Th-Thanks.
I wish I were taller.
I've always hated being tall,
but, well, the day before yesterday
it just stopped mattering to me,
so I got a haircut.
How did you get over your complex?
Th-That's...
...because I repeatedly fought for my life.
I realized that if I didn't give up,
I'd survive somehow.
Th-That's amazing!
Good for you, Boss!
You finally got to talk to her.
Boss?
It's a weird nickname, isn't it?
I'm Saki Nitobe. I'm a second-year
at the affiliated high school.
I'm the captain of the Rhythmic Gymnastics Club,
and these are its members.
Hello. I'm Karen Kohiruimaki,
a first-year university student.
That's a pretty name.
Thank you. Nice to meet you, Saki.
If I see you again, is it okay if I talk to you?
Of course.
Thank you very much!
- Well, see you!
- See you!
Yep.
It couldn't be, could it?
Um...
Ms. Karen.
One last thing. Can I shake your hand?
Of course.
Congratulations on your victory.
But next time I'm gonna win, munchkin.
Bring it on anytime, Amazon.
- In GGO!
Next time: Refrain.