Long ago, when the Earth was young,
Demonkind ruled the planet.
Over time, the surface of the Earth
was overrun by a new dominant race.
The former masters of Earth hid
in the uncharted recesses of the planet.
However, demons are capable of living
for tens of thousands of years...
They have begun to scour the planet,
taking it back for their own.
We now embrace our life with fear,
day by day, crawling toward oblivion.
The mic is ready!
2 minutes before we're on the air!
Today, all of us are truly in your debt.
Not at all. Honestly...
It is I who should thank you.
Signs: TAKE BACK JAPAN
KILL EVERY DEVILMAN
How cute, nice and ripe!
It's been a long time since
I've tasted human flesh...
You can't eat just one!
You're a Devilman?!
Well, how do you like my venom?
Good job, Yumi!
Exactly as planned.
But it's getting more and more dangerous.
Right. Demons are taking on
human form more often every day.
It's almost like something big is about to—
Miko-san!
You jerk! Let her—
Who the hell are you?
Mother fu—
Can you stand up?
I think so...
And you Yumi?
I'm all right...
Good.
Hey, wait!
I'm not a demon...
Hey, jackass!
You know how to drive or what?
What the hell's wrong with you?!
Sir, please calm down.
Shaddap'!
I bet you're a demon, too.
I most certainly am not...
Sir, stop! Leave me alone!
You lying demon bitch!
I'll kill you!
I'm home!
Welcome back!
Hey Tare-chan, has Akira-kun called?
Nope.
Oh...
It's been 3 days now.
What could be keeping him?
You must miss your lover boy.
Dummy.
So where's Dad, and everybody else?
He said they went demon hunting...
Satou-san, over in Sanchou-me.
I said I wouldn't go.
But you have to go!
If you don't, they'll say we're traitors.
It was about that time I found my father's notes...
Ryou?
From them, I learned the awful truth about demons...
And even the supposed 'Devilman'.
What you are about to see is shocking
footage given to us by Asuka Ryou.
This is Fudou Akira.
He was my best friend.
Brother Akira, he...
Brother Akira...
Sister, sister!
Sister, this is bad!
Brother Akira's in trouble!
Sister, sister!
Sis—
Tare-chan?
Tare-chan...
Dad? Mum?
Tare... chan!
We must unite to find these demons now!
They are clever and transform, taking the shapes of others.
There are likely demons among you
and you don't even realise it.
How do I know you're really human?
That stupid TV broadcast, it's making everyone riot!
Miko.
Sir?
I'm worried about Makimura Miki and her family.
I'll meet up with you two later.
Rendezvous with the Devilman Army.
Yes sir!
We got that witch!
Hurry up, we're gonna' be late!
Miki-chan, wait up!
Let's go!
Akira-sama!
What is it?
The Devilman Army scout troops are
combating a squadron of demons!
The one named Selos seems to be their leader.
Selos...
Understood. Let's hurry!
Yes sir!
Please, wait a minute! Akira-sama,
are you sure you're up for this?
What are you saying?
I'm fine!
Now...
They followed Yumi!
Devilman, Fudou Akira.
If you pledge your loyalty to my own
Demon Army, I'll spare your life.
What'll it be, Fudou Akira?
Fudou Akira, huh...?
Satan-sama,
your plan is working marvellously!
Yes.
As I knew it would.
Everything...
Everything begins, here and now.
Yes, lord.
Akira...
What's all this?
Is that...?
Couldn't be!
Is it really him?
Demonkind's greatest hero...
Amon!
I'm gonna' slaughter that creepy son of a bitch!
Wait, I'll destroy him!
Allow me!
Whoa... he's strong!
We can't beat this guy!
Fuck! FUCK!
Selos-sama! Amon—
You ran from an enemy!
Totally unforgivable.
So that'd make us enemies?
I've got just one question...
Where is Satan?
Amon... I'd love to fight with you.
You're known as the ultimate hero of all Demonkind.
At last, the time has come
to defeat you with my own hands!
It'll mean so much more...
Now that you've taken your body
back from that human Fudou Akira!
Where, is, Satan?
Whatever.
I'll find him after I've dealt with your sorry ass.
Bring it. I'll kill you.
Damn them...
What the hell?!
So that's what he's like...
You're a hero all right, Amon.
Looks like there's still some fight in you after all!
It's time to win this.
What?!
Been a long time, Satan!
I was trapped, you know.
Inside that wretched human,
Fudou Akira, to fight for Mankind.
You used me, hiding me inside that worthless human's body!
All my shame, and my fury...
Have a taste of it yourself!
Amon, you mean you don't know yet?
No, I suppose you couldn't...
Fudou Akira isn't dead, not yet.
Akira...
AWAKEN, AKIRA!
Akira-kun?
Why are you so spaced out?
You're weird, Akira-kun...
Miki...
Were you thinking about that story I told you earlier?
So, what do you think I should do?
I know, Miki-chan is such a pain.
But I'm still worried...
So, what do you think?
Um... what were we talking about?
You really weren't listening! Pfft...
Miki, wait!
Miki-chan! Miki I—
This is where...
You shouldn't underestimate me!
Miki, it's dangerous!
MIKI!
Why can't you just leave me be?
Because we're not through yet.
Take a look.
Been looking for this?
Why show this to me?
I want you to fight me.
This time, winner controls all!
If a fight is all you want, you're gonna' fucking get it!
Am I... going to die?
Miki...
Miki.
I've done nothing but make Makimura Miki suffer...
It's my fault you're dead.
I... killed you!
Miki, I...
Miki!
Are you... crying?
Over a woman?!
Do you even have the strength to stand up?
I'd thought...
I could never be human again...
But I never let go of my human heart!
You could never understand how I feel.
I can't be defeated by you!
Is this a joke?
Time for the final blow!
The hell?
What the...?
But why?