Nimeni nu știe
când această lume a devenit astfel.
Infectarea a început dintr-odată, într-o zi,
iar oamenii au pierdut abilitatea de a se conecta cu orașul.
Imediat după asta, orașul a
început să se extindă de unul singur,
iar oamenii erau văzuți
ca niște rezidenți ilegali
și exterminați.
Totul s-a întâmplat...
cu mult înainte să mă nasc.
Așteptați.
Pe aici.
Ai grijă.
Ai dreptate. Îmi pare rău.
Ești prea incordată.
Te vor auzi.
Încă suntem în regulă în zona asta.
Poate doar am avut
noroc până acum.
Nu-ți lăsa garda jos.
Dar...
Zuru are dreptate.
Chiar mă întreb dacă
acesta e drumul bun.
Este puțin diferit față
de cum era pe hartă.
E o hartă veche. Constructorii
trebuie să fi reconstruit zona.
Chiar credeți că vom fi în regulă pe cont propriu?
Haideți să ne întoarcem.
De ce ne-am întoarce când am ajuns așa de departe?
Ar trebui să fie imediat
după acest pasaj.
Cred.
Zuru, acolo sus.
Ieșirea.
Avertizare de
posibil impact
la coborâre
Avertizare de
posibil impact
la coborâre
Tae!
Ești bine? Tae?
Mersi, Fusata.
Ești bine, Tae?
Îmi pare rău, Zuru. Bateria de rezervă...
O să fim luați la rost când ne vom întoarce.
E doar o baterie.
Toată lumea va fi încântată dacă ne vom întoarce cu niște nămol. Haideți.
Zuru.
Zuru, ce tot faci? Grăbește-te.
Un Constructor!
Nu vă faceți griji.
Chestiile astea nu dau atenție oamenilor.
Bun, să mergem. Aproape am ajuns.
Continuă să scoată sunete ciudate.
Să mergem, Tae.
Uau, ăsta e...
Nu am mai văzut niciodată un spațiu atât de mare.
Pericol
Un turn de veghe!
De asta ne-au avertizat adulții să nu venim aici.
Bun, asta e. Să ne întoarcem.
Aveți grijă să nu vă vadă turnul.
Cum ar trebui să ajungem
pe terenurile de vânătoare în timp ce evităm chestia aia?
Haideți să urmăm alt drum.
Vom merge pe aici.
E un ocol destul de mare.
Și ne vor aștepta tone de obstacole.
Păi, nu prea avem de ales. Să mergem.
Dacă vor veni Gardienii aici...
We've been trained as
Electro-Fishers, too, you know.
Sutezo said that Zuru's already
as skilled as a
full-fledged Electro-Fisher.
Dar nu am primit permisiunea ca să luăm aceste echipamente.
Pop is definitely gonna be mad.
Zuru, îmi pare rău.
Ce? Tae?
Ai spus că e pentru binele surorii mele, nu?
Să mergem astfel la vânătoare.
Nu doar pentru Ito.
After all, there's almost nothing
left to eat in the village.
Mersi, Zuru.
Am reușit.
Priviți! Acolo!
Ce de gândaci!
Sunt conducte de nămol!
Așteptați!
Nu e de bine.
Sunt complet uscate.
Dar sunt așa de groase.
Zuru.
Turnul de veghe?
Gardenii!
Exterminatori!
Yaichi! Deasupra ta!
Retragerea!
Fugiți!
Everyone, stay calm!
Remember our training, lure them in
then shoot!
Ai auzit asta, Shizu?
Ademenește-i!
Nu pot scăpa de ei!
Shizu!
La naiba!
Shiro! Lume!
Tae!
Zuru!
More!
Ești bine?
Zuru!
Yeah, this is no...
Stai, Fusata.
S-a oprit.
Take off your headgear.
Vreau să-ți văd ochii.
Hei.
Zuru.
Zuru!
Încă suntem în aria vizuală a turnului!
NET TERMINAL GENE
NON-CARRIER
De ce?
The watchtower didn't react
even when she took her
helmettals off?
Hei! Tae!
NET TERMINAL GENE
NON-CARRIER
Are there
any humans here with
the Net Terminal Gene?
Net Termi...?
Ce?
Ne-ai salvat...
deci ne-ar plăcea să te ajutăm,
dar nu știm despre ce vorbești.
Stai. Unul dintre adulți ar trebui să știe ceva.
Dar, înainte de asta,
spune-ne, te rog.
Ce ești?
Eu sunt Killy.
Un om.
Our village is inside
the perimeter up ahead.
We'll be fine once we get back there.
Perimeter.
That's the one place
the Safeguard can't enter.
We don't know why, though.
Semnal blocat
Amenințare: scăzută
See, that's the perimeter up ahead.
Stai! Zuru, îndepărtează-te de lângă el!
Sutezo, așteaptă!
Why are you all showing your faces?
You'll be spotted by the watchtower!
That's because
when we're with him, it's okay.
Cine e tipul ăsta?
Killy ne-a salvat.
E un om!
Om?
Nu se poate.
Om, nu?
Ești sigură că nu e un Gardian?
Am auzit că există Gardieni care arată exact ca oamenii.
Da, tată.
Doar voi trei, nu?
Îmi pare rău. Exterminatorii...
De asta te-am avertizat, Zuru, nu puteți merge pe cont propriu!
But then you went and took that gear
without our permission anyway.
At any rate,
it's dangerous to stay out here.
Hurry and get inside the perimeter.
Pop!
Deci nu e un Gardian.
Da.
Ești un călător?
De unde vii?
NET TERMINAL GENE
NON-CARRIER
De jos...
Am urcat...
șase mii de etaje.
Șase mii de etaje?
Nu se poate.
Vom vorbi mai multe înăuntru.
Come on.
Tată!
Ăsta e satul nostru.
At the most, there were about
400 people living here.
Dar acum am mai rămas doar 150.
Dacă ești un călător,
ești bine venit aici.
Asta e tradiția noastră.
Deși tu ești primul din generația noastră.
Prima persoană din afara satului căreia i-am urat bun-venit.
Noi, Pescarii, suntem descendenți ai Cultivatorilor,
care se pare că umblau liberi prin oraș, exact ca tine.
Se spune că au descoperit acest loc acum 300 de ani.
So, we've lived inside the perimeter
ever since.
So, it's rare for us
to meet any strangers.
In the city,
there must be other humans
managing to survive.
But we have no idea
how many there are
or where to find them.
Nu știm nimic.
So, any stories we could hear
from a traveler would be precious.
Pop, have you ever met a human?
No. I've only found the remains
of places where humans lived.
Pop.
Pop and the others are back!
Hey! The kids are with him!
Hei! Copiii s-au întors!
What's that?
Pop and Sutezo
brought the kids back!
Câți sunt? Sunt toți?
Nu, nu sunt toți.
Și au adus și un ciudat cu ei.
Ce vrei să spui prin asta?
Ei bine...
Welcome back, Pop.
Pop.
Just you guys?
Unde sunt ceilalți trei?
And their gear? Did you leave that, too?
What about the helmettals? Weren't you at
least able to bring the helmettals back?
Damn it.
You know we don't have the tech
to make that stuff anymore.
Cum rămâne cu mâncare?
Era complet secată.
It's enough that
three of them came back alive.
Oh, well, in another month,
we'll all starve anyway.
Hey, Pop.
Who's that?
E un călător?
Un călător?
So, there really are
other humans out there.
Putem avea încredere în el?
Dacă este un călător,
îi vom ura bun-venit.
But we don't have
anything to feed him.
Nu este un Gardian, nu-i așa?
Un Gardian nu ar putea ajunge aici.
Nu te apropia de el.
NET TERMINAL
GENE NON-CARRIER
MALNOURISHED
Nu!
E ceva desenat pe ea.
O găleată cu apă?
This is pretty good.
It must be really nutritious.
Vreau și eu.
Hei, lasă și mie.
Asta e grozav!
Îți va da energie.
Pop, Sutezo.
Pop.
Tae.
Poftim.
This much?
There's some for your sister.
Mersi.
Zuru, Fusata.
Mă bucur că v-ați întors.
Dar să nu mai faceți așa ceva, bine?
Îmi pare rău.
Sunt sigur că știi asta deja,
dar oamenii au căutat terenuri noi de vânătoare și înainte
și au fost omorâți de Gardieni.
Grupul care a mers spre est a fost eliminat complet.
That's why these guys
thought they had
to do something for the village.
Zuru.
When you've put the equipment back,
come to my room.
Okay.
- Sutezo, let's go.
- Right.
You come, too, please.
I'd like to speak with you.
Your name was Killy, right?
Thanks for sharing your food with us.
Normally we'd be the ones
feeding you...
but as you can see,
we're nearly out of food.
Hey.
Where did you get that thing?
Two hundred levels
-below.
- Two hundred?
So, we can't go get more.
This place is protected
by the perimeter,
but there's nowhere inside
where we can get food.
So, we Electro-Fishers go out
and get sludge to bring back.
I'm the leader of the Electra-Fishers.
But the hunting grounds near here
have all dried up
and we have to go out farther.
Each time,
friends of ours get killed
leaving us with
fewer and fewer Fishers.
So, even the children...
Here. Come in.
That food is amazing.
- Wonder where he got something like that.
- Yeah.
And that weapon. To think it could
cut through even an Exterminator's body.
Six thousand levels below.
I wonder if he came all that way
all alone.
Who knows.
I wonder how many more
humans there are.
Maybe there are other villages
like this one.
There might be.
I can't even imagine it.
How far do you think
this city stretches?
Why does the Safeguard
exterminate humans?
I've never even thought about that.
We really don't know anything.
Amenințare
So, according to Zuru, you took out
four Exterminators at once.
It would really help to have
someone skilled like you around.
Would you consider staying here
for a while to help us hunt?
I'm... looking for humans with
the Net Terminal Gene.
Net Termi--?
What's that?
All humans had it
before the contagion.
Before the contagion.
You're talking about a time
when the city belonged to humans.
It's said the Builders
and the Safeguard followed
the humans' orders back then.
Such an ancient legend.
What's that supposed to mean?
The city belonging to humans.
Are you saying that if we had
that Net Terminal Gene thing
we could stop the Safeguard?
Not only that,
we could give orders to the Builders
and make them stop building
on their own.
We could stop the expansion of the city.
But there's no way
there's anything like that here.
Well...
I've actually heard of it before.
That Net Terminal thing.
I'd long since forgotten about it,
but hearing him speak of it
reminded me.
I know I've heard that phrase before,
a long time ago.
But where?
Right below this village.
A place inside the perimeter,
but we've been told for generations
not to go near it.
You don't mean...
the Rotting Shrine?
My Gran always told me
never to go near it
because there's a ghost there
scarier than the Safeguard.
Sutezo. Do you really believe that?
Hey,you!
Right below...
the village.
He's planning to go there.
Sutezo, follow him.
- Tell him to wait. I'll show him the way.
- Right.
I'm going, too!
Hurry.
Gran said...
that if you go near
the Rotting Shrine
a stranger interrupts
your communications
and their voice can control you
like a puppet.
Quit telling stories.
My own great-grandfather
fell to his death because of that...
according to Gran.
Over there.
- What's that?
- Look!
Net
terminal
connection.
Eu sunt...
Cibo.
Come out.
Is someone there?
I've waited for so long.
It talked.
I've been calling for help all this time,
but no one came.
It was so long, until you came.
I waited for 17 million
526 thousand hours.
What's your name?
Killy.
Eu sunt Cibo.
Un cercetător.
Mă bucur să te cunosc, Killy.
So, a scientist
really did survive.
That's a Gravitational
Beam Emitter, right?
Ai o armă foarte impresionantă.
That's the one technology
that even we couldn't re-create.
Where did you find it?
I don't know about the gun.
NET TERMINAL GENE
NON-CARRIER
There are vestiges of the contagion
in your irises.
You... don't have
the Net Terminal Gene.
What sort of stupid thing is that to say?
Of course I don't.
Do you know
any humans who have
the Net Terminal Gene?
If there were any humans like that
then this city would have been
made functional again ages ago.
But I've got something good.
Killy, take me to the automated factory.
Automated factory?
What's that?
Who knows.
If you take me to the automated factory
I'll make you a synthetic terminal
that has the same effect
as the Net Terminal Gene.
You don't believe me, do you?
But it's true.
That thing there,
that's actually the wreckage
of a synthetic terminal that I made.
There's a connection port beneath it.
When we found a connection port
to the NetSphere here
we surrounded the area with an electric
barrier to keep the Safeguard
from invading,
and started experiments.
To keep the Safeguard from invading?
The experiments were successful.
We got all the way
to the entrance to the Authority.
But then we were found by their
defense mechanisms,
and you can see what happened.
Did you...
communicate with the Authority?
No, we couldn't.
But we analyzed information
coming through the counter-current
and found a channel we can use to get in.
So, given another chance,
I can definitely succeed.
I have no idea
what she's talking about.
Hey,you!
Yes?
Just now
you said you did something to keep
the Safeguard from invading, right?
Does that mean
you set up this perimeter?
That's right.
How exactly did you do a thing like that?
Killy, move that rubble out of the way.
That's an electric barrier generator
I made.
Thanks to that, we ran our experiments
without interruptions by the Safeguard.
Connect?
If you can do that
you can give orders to the city?
That's right.
Long ago, all humans had
the Net Terminal Gene
and they could all do it.
I can't believe it.
How could humans
do a thing like that?
But it's true, they really could.
We tried to re-create that ability
artificially using machines.
To stop the city running wild.
If we go to the automated factory
I can make another terminal.
Come on, Killy.
Your goal is the same as mine,
isn't it?
You want to bring the city back
under human control, right?
Yes.
Then it's decided.
Let's go right away!
Hey, wait.
Where is this
automated factory thing?
In a section far east of here.
About 15 blocks away.
Fifteen blocks.
That'd take two or three days.
Could we help as well?
- Pop.
- Sutezo.
What these people are trying to do
might end up saving our village.
Did you really believe all of that?
Either way, things are growing worse
in the village.
It won't be long before
we make a decision
to leave the perimeter
or stay inside and starve.
So... don't you think it's worth
taking a chance?
That may be so,
but if we go east for 15 blocks
the batteries in our equipment probably
won't even last long enough,
and we can't get that far without
being caught by the Safeguard.
All the more reason.
No matter how strong this man is,
there's no guarantee that even he
could reach that far alone.
But if we can help him, even a little...
True. It might be better
to have more people with us.
But we'll need to take food
along for the trip
and there's already so little left.
At the automated factory
we can make anything.
If we get there
I'll make you anything you want.
Anything?
Yes, even food, anything you like.
Really?
Killy.
To be honest,
we don't even understand
half of what she's saying.
But...
we'd like to take a chance
with you, and her.
- Hurry!
- Aren't there any more spare batteries?
- Take as many spears as you can!
- We need one more person!
- Leave some to defend the village.
- Do we have enough helmettals?
Stop stalling, all of you.
Hey, Zuru!
We'll be fine
as long as we're with Killy.
Let's go. Follow me.
Yes, sir.
What is that?
I heard they found it
at the Rotting Shrine.
Is that thing really alive?
Yes, I'm alive.
Hey, Sutezo. Is it true?
Will she really make us food
if we take her to this
automated factory place?
I told you, don't ask me.
It's true.
I can make thousands
of the portable rations
like the kind Killy had.
Thousands?
How wonderful if that's true.
Pop, is it really safe
to believe what this thing says?
If you have a problem with my decision
then go back right now.
I don't have a problem.
Right?
I never had a problem to begin with.
Shut up and walk.
Pair up and get in a circular formation.
Don't leave much space between you.
Yes, sir.
There was no need for you
to come along, Tae.
My sister's doing better
thanks to the food that Killy gave us.
I need to repay him.
And also, wherever Zuru goes
I go with her.
Tae.
Things must be desperate for us
to be bringing these children along.
To be honest,
there aren't many of us left
who can use the Electro-Fisher gear.
A watchtower!
Hey.
Is that what's doing it?
What is this place?
Hey, Killy.
You're not going to just leave me
somewhere on the way, are you?
Killy.
Killy's metabolism is different
from normal humans'.
He very rarely needs to eat.
Well, what about you?
I'll pass.
But I appreciate the thought.
Were you scared?
Yeah. But I'm fine.
When those Safeguards come
the air around them stinks of ions.
It's like, you know,
your nose kind of stings.
Did you smell it?
I was so frantic
I don't really remember.
Actually, I think I kind of did.
Now that you mention it,
there was a weird smell.
I see.
That's the type of thing
you have to experience to understand.
Yeah.
Remember this.
When Electro-Fishers camp
we always light a fire like this
and sleep beside it.
It's the way we've always done it.
Why?
Because
we're on edge all day
when we're out hunting.
It's said that
the sight of fire
is soothing to humans.
I'm sure that's been true
since long ago.
Since long before the city
came to this state.
At the end of the day
people would watch the fire
to put themselves at ease.
I've waited for so long.
There were others with me before
but they all passed away.
No one knows how long
the city has been like this.
One day the contagion
just suddenly started
and humans lost the power
to connect with the city.
After that, the city started to expand
at random
and the Safeguard regarded humans
as illegal residents
and began to exterminate us.
I was the chief scientist of Kaito,
a district far away from here.
In that district
we'd excavated some information
from the remains of the city
and managed to use it
to preserve human life.
But we knew
it couldn't last for long.
My group of scientists
found a way to simulate
the Ne!' Terminal Gene.
My coworkers and I
set out in search of another place
with a connection port.
And that's where we found it.
Along our journey
one, then another of us died.
Even the ones who managed to reach
there, during the experiment they all...
I'm sure Kaito is gone now, too.
The automated factory is through here.
Pop.
Yeah.
No one who's gone this way
has ever come back.
They must have been caught
by the defense net.
But with me and Killy here
you'll be okay.
You heard her.
Let's go.
Yes, sir.
This is the entrance
of the automated factory.
There are still automated factories
like this here and there around the city.
This is the closest one to your village.
It opened!
You were able to connect?
You don't need to be able to connect to
the NetSphere for something like this.
What are those?
So, this is what they call a factory.
What are these pool things?
Killy, put me on that console.
INITIATE
Look!
Yes!
Now we'll never have to worry
about food again!
Yeah!
Zuru, look! It's amazing.
Yeah.
STAND BY
Killy, can you hear me?
I'm having a little trouble.
Take that synthetic terminal
and get ready to escape.
I still can't move yet.
Be careful.
I dug in pretty deep. Last time
this happened things went very badly.
Is that one of those synthetic terminals
you told us about, Cibo?
With that, we can stop the city, right?
Hey, you.
Pop!
Retreat in two groups.
The cargo team goes first.
Fighters, draw them in
and take them out.
Yes, sir. Cargo team, hurry!
Tae!
Hurry!
Exterminators! So many.
Tae!
Forget your pack, just come!
But...
Tae!
Zuru!
Hurry!
Here they come.
Lure them in first.
Right.
Cibo!
Retreat!
Incredible.
We're going!
Hurry!
Tae! Can you hear me? Tae!
Tae! Where are you?
Damn it!
- Atsuji! Are you okay?
- My leg.
Where's Tae?
Where?!
Up there.
She was crushed by an Exterminator.
Zuru!
Zuru! No!
Zuru! Zuru!
Tae!Tae!
Tae.
Thank goodness.
Zuru.
I'm sorry, I'm okay now.
Tae, are you okay?
Yeah.
Tae!
Thank goodness.
Man, you're so reckless.
Sorry.
Are you all okay? You're not hurt?
Tae's arm is broken.
Tae, can you move?
- All right, let's go.
- Yes, sir.
Where's Cibo?
She was crushed.
Safeguard!
They're still crawling around.
They keep coming!
Hey,you!
Fire that weapon from before!
What's wrong with you?
Why don't you shoot?
Sorry I'm late.
I've come to rescue you, Killy.
Who?
Cibo?
That barrier coating
only lasts 30 seconds.
Run.
Hurry!
I'm done for.
You go on.
What are you saying, Atsuji? Run!
Get in this car.
Hurry!
It's not broken?
I'm making it work now.
- Can't we go yet?
- Just a moment.
There we go.
Here we go.
It moved!
All right.
I'm out of spears.
I've got two left.
I have one more.
I have two.
Don't give up!
Killy, we'd finally gotten
the synthetic terminal and everything.
It's a shame.
INTERIOR POWER
GENERATION ACCELERANT
DANGER
Killy.
Killy!
Why is this guy so heavy?
POWER SETTING
- ENERGY SAVING MODE
- We're almost at the village.
- Yeah.
Does it hurt?
I'm fine.
Tae.
They're back! Pop and the others!
Hey, bring out the crane.
Time to unload!
Welcome back.
Welcome back, Pop.
- How did it go?
- Did you find the food?
Hey, take that down below.
Yes, Pop.
Don't worry, I'll take her.
- Okay.
- They're injured.
Get the molecular tape!
She's an awfully big girl.
Is that the person
who looked like a corpse before?
Is he dead?
I don't know.
Bring it around slowly.
It's pretty heavy.
This girl sure is strong.
Killy's fine. He's just sleeping.
Take him inside.
Right.
With all this, we should be fine
for four or five months.
So, it was worth gathering
all the equipment.
We can finally eat till we're full!
How many died altogether?
So, two more good workers died.
Finally!
Real food and drink at last!
Bring down the lights.
For everyone we've lost
over the last two years...
a moment of silence.
Pop.
Thanks.
Give me another one, too.
You're drinking too much.
I wanna drink.
We finally get to mourn properly.
Yeah.
For a while there we couldn't even
afford to do that.
But now we've got food,
the village is saved.
But at a high cost.
We lost a lot of skilled
Electro-Fishers
and equipment as well.
Can't we just go back to that
automated factory place?
You can make anything there, right?
No.
No, we can't go back there again.
It's crawling with Exterminators.
I see.
So... we have to see how long
this food lasts.
Killy.
They say the village is saved.
Everyone's really happy.
If Cibo's experiment is successful...
will you still
continue your journey, Killy?
Hey, Killy.
Do you think maybe...
you could stay?
Cibo.
Killy.
POWER SETTING
The synthetic terminal.
I'm going to connect it now.
There's something I'd like your help with.
Wait.
What are we gonna do now, Pop?
Now we just pray
that Cibo's experiment works.
If it does, we won't have to live in fear
of the Safeguard anymore.
I really can't wrap my head around it.
Around what?
The idea of humans
connecting to machines.
I mean, it's like...
They say the Builders and the Safeguard
will do what the humans say.
That's a good thing, right?
But why did people
want to do that in the first place?
I don't want to live long enough
to find out.
You sure eat a lot.
Well, you earned it.
No, it's not for me.
I thought I'd take some to Tae.
Zuru.
I won't be able to move
while I'm connected.
I want you to protect me, then.
Oh, Sutezo.
Zuru, looks like he woke up.
You were with Killy, right, Zuru?
Did you talk with him?
No.
Hey.
Zuru!
Oh, Pop.
You're here to help?
I had a bit too much to drink.
I'll take this on the way back
to my room.
Zuru.
Wait, Zuru.
How'd it go?
Tae was pleased, wasn't she?
She's not in her room.
Tae?
- What is it?
- Tae!
It looks like the shock-absorbing
equipment has been destroyed.
Tae!
What's wrong with you?
Tae.
Wait! Don't go near!
- Tae.
- Hey!
Tae.
Pop!
Fusata! Hang in there!
Tae.Tae!
Tae!Tae!
No! Wake up!
BEGINNING DUPLICATION
Tae!
I am Sanakan.
Representative construct
of the Safeguard.
We, the Safeguard, will eliminate
all illegal residents lacking
the Net Terminal Gene.
- Tae! What's wrong with you?!
- Fusata!
The Safeguard?
Tae!
Fusata! Come on!
OUTPUT POWER SETTING
Watch out!
Fusata!
Zuru, don't!
What's going on?
An explosion!
What's happening?
What happened?
ILLEGAL RESIDENTS
What is going on?
Successful infiltration of illegal
residents' unauthorized compound.
Barrier generator destroyed.
Total extermination in progress.
Successful infiltration
of illegal residents'...
That's...
Posing as a human
to get through the barrier.
DANGER LEVEL
That's a high-level Safeguard, Killy.
It looks like we should hurry.
IMPOSSIBLE TO AIM
AT A SINGLE TARGET
Killy!
Fusata!
Fusata, this way!
Tae.
Taefiae.
In accordance with
Elimination Ordinance 5
beginning auxiliary elimination.
Damn it! Our village.
Pop!
Don't worry about me.
Go on ahead.
Pop.
Listen, Sutezo.
Gather everyone together
and go up the tower.
Shoot back from the top of the tower.
Right.
- Take care of Pop.
- I will.
Hurry up!
I'm going first!
You guys, hurry Up!
Fusata! Put on your gear!
There aren't any more helmettals!
We don't have enough!
Zuru... here.
But...
Sutezo.
- Over there, don't let them in!
- Damn it, they just keep coming!
SIGNAL BLOCKED
Amenințare: mare
Arată bine.
Ce se petrece?
Zuru?
Unde e Tae?
A fost înlocuită de un gardian.
There's no way she's alive anymore.
Nu.
Tae.
Nu se poate ca Tae să fi murit!
Fusata!
I'm going on ahead.
Zuru.
How's that?
Damn it!
I'll blast you from up close!
Damn it! Are they monsters?
MEGASTRUCTURE
Killy!
Zuru! Hey, Zuru!
Hurry, up here!
Everyone, get up here quickly!
Hurry!
In accordance with
Elimination Ordinance 3, Clause 2,
Elimination Level has risen by three.
Requesting authorization to use
Gravitational Beam Emitter.
APPLICATION FOR USE
GRAVITATIONAL BEAM EMITTER
PERMISSION GRANTED
You are a body that was
stolen from us, the Safeguard.
A body.
Do you intend to return?
Answer immediately.
In accordance with the Ordinance
I will destroy you here.
Unauthorized connection
to the NetSphere detected.
UNAUTHORIZED CONNECTION
DETECTED
Elimination Level has risen by two.
I won't let you!
DEVICE DESTRUCTION
Sutezo!
Killy!
POWER SUPPLY LOW
POWER SUPPLY CONVERTED
TO HIGH ACCELERATED CHARGE
- DANGER
RELEASE DANGER
Aim carefully! Lure them in and shoot!
We did it! That was the last one!
Tae.
It can't be.
The Authority!
This is...
inside the NetSphere, right?
This is one of the reserve
electronic worlds that connects
the NetSphere to base reality.
Reserve.
Please, let me connect
to the NetSphere.
The net terminal you used
has just now lost its effectiveness.
No.
The connection to your brain
in base reality
will also be cut
in just a few nanoseconds.
But you still have time.
Here in the reserve world,
time is sped up
so from your relative point of view,
time seems extended.
Please, at least stop
the Safeguard's attack on that village.
Without an order from someone
with the Net Terminal Gene
we, the Authority,
cannot take any such action.
You're right.
However, as much as is allowed
within this reserve electronic world
I can tell you the coordinates
of abandoned levels
that the Safeguard
are not currently monitoring.
What's this?
It stores a map of the levels near here.
We cannot take this information
out into base reality...
but we do not have any orders
to stop you from connecting to it.
Take the injured over there!
Someone help carry them!
Hurry, over here.
Bring the molecular tape!
Fusata.
Shall I wrap it?
Yeah.
Killy.
We were saved thanks to you.
Zuru, what happened to Cibo?
I don't know.
I see.
It's all over.
It's too early to give up.
Wait!
NET TERMINAL GENE
NON-CARRIER
Cibo.
Cibo!
My brain is in my arm.
This place has been found out
by the Safeguard.
Sooner or later
the Exterminators will be back.
Then what should we do?
There's an abandoned level
between this one
and the one below it.
There's a descending track to it
to the north of here.
An abandoned level.
It's a place that's been disconnected
from the NetSphere.
The Safeguards and Builders
won't interfere.
What should we do?
Can we believe her?
If we stay here we'll just be killed
by Exterminators.
Pop.
Everyone, get ready to leave.
Let's go, Killy.
Killy.
Come on, let's go back home.
It's scary out here.
We're not going back there again.
The Safeguard found us there.
Pop, I'm sorry.
Eu...
It's my fault for
taking everyone out hunting.
No.
It's all thanks to you.
Wow, Cibo,
you can call the railway car!
You shouldn't try to copy me.
MOVEMENT DETECTED
- ILLEGAL INHABITANT
CONNECTED TO AUTHORITY
Okay, everyone get in.
Can we really get
to an abandoned level?
- Here, get in.
- Okay.
Be careful.
Acest miros.
- They're here!
- Hurry, everyone!
Killy, what are you doing?
Hurry and get in!
Killy!
You can't be serious.
Ce este în neregulă, Killy?
Killy.
Nu te voi mai revedea?
Eu... caut
the Net Terminal Gene.
Voi închide ușa acum.
Aceea a fost ultima oară când l-au văzut.
Apoi, bunica mea, Zuru,
ne-a dus într-un loc nou.
Ce mare te-ai făcut.
Bunica mea
mi-a povestit mereu
despre Killy când eram mică.
A trecut mult timp, dar...
Nu se observă niciun semn că orașul și-ar reveni la normal.
I suppose no one has been found yet
with the Net Terminal Gene.
Dar eu continui să cred.
Știu că undeva,
în acest oraș nesfârșit,
el își continuă căutările.
Just feel sad history
I feel pain
No one knows it
Hear me? Hear me?
Echoing in
The abyss
Fear
Long time like this
I feel lonely
So far away
I'm crying
Hear me?
Many
Tears
Unde este?
Unde este parola?
E cumva aici?
Stau singură aici
și nu știu de ce
Calling you
Just feel eternity
Do you feel anything?
If you remember
That day of the beginning
Near here?
How far?
Where is the same world?
Near here?
Can't you hear me?
Drift in this world
Calling you
I'm standing alone
I don't know why
Calling you
Unde este?
Unde este parola?
E cumva aici?