You're about to see my guts .
I'm going to...
...​beat this bastard!
If I were the rain...
...​that binds to­gether the earth and the sky,
who in all eter­nity will never mingle...
...​would I be able to bind the hearts of peo­ple together?
Six years ago June 17th
It was rain­ing that day.
Like the day be­fore... and the day be­fore that.
The river was swollen from the rain.
Still, that girl was stand­ing shak­ily on the riverbank...
...​looking like she might jump in any second.
Wow, you're good!
One day, I'm gonna be­come the fe­male Vale Tudo cham­pion.
Note: "Vale Tudo" is a form of fight­ing where the out­come of the fight is de­cided by knock out or submission.
What about you, Orihime?
Did you do the art as­sign­ment? "The Fu­ture Me"?
Won­der­ful of you to ask.
Ac­tu­ally, I'm se­cretly quite proud of it.
Wow, what is it of?
The Fu­ture Me
Top speed of 380kph, from the mouth 20,000 C flames, from the eyes spe­cial de­struc­tion lasers...
That's not it, Orihime!
You wanna get de­ten­tion again?
Good morn­ing, Kurosaki-kun!
Oh, morn­ing, Inoue.
What's with Kurosaki-kun?
He's in such a good mood today.
I won­der why he's so tense.
What?
Even though he's all smiles?
Oh...
What?
Ori­hime, if you have any­thing im­por­tant to talk to Ichigo about, do it by the end of the day.
Tat­suki-chan...
He's gonna be ab­sent tomorrow.
This hill is re­ally steep.
Re­ally?
I'm fine.
But if you talk like that...
Give it your all, Yuzu!
Don't give up, Yuzu!
Dad's right be­hind you!
See?
Ig­nore him, Yuzu.
If you re­spond to peo­ple like that, they'll be on your back forever.
How naive.
Even if you don't re­spond to me, I'll be on your back any­way!
Run!
Deadly Dad Sliding!
Polka dots.
Get lost to the ends of the earth!
Come on, let's go be­fore he comes back.
You too, Ichi.
Yeah.
Who's that?
An ac­quain­tance of yours, Bro?
I dunno her!
I dunno her at all!
I dunno her the tini­est lit­tle shred at all.
Some­how, I think I've seen her before...
Oh, I remember!
She's my class­mate from ju­nior high!
I to­tally re­mem­ber now!
No way! It's soooo nos­tal­gic that I just gotta talk alone with her right this minute!
Okay, so I'm just gonna go talk with that girl!
You two go ahead to Mom's grave!
Bro!
What're you chuck­ling for?!
It might be about time for you to let go of your brother.
Noooo!
I first met him when I was four.
At the dou­jou I was going to,
a boy came with un­be­liev­ably bright-col­ored hair,
led by his un­be­liev­ably beau­ti­ful mom,
and smil­ing un­be­liev­ably wide.
He was so skinny and goofy,
and he looked sooo weak.
One hit up high.
Didn't even take ten seconds.
But you know,
even though he was al­ways crying,
when he saw his Mom's face when she'd come to pick him up,
he'd turn all smiles right away .
I just hated that.
"A boy shouldn't lose and be happy," I thought.
But he looked sooo happy.
He smiled so hap­pily.
Dammit, why're you fol­low­ing me?
Fool.
If I'm not by your side, what will you do when a Hol­low appears?
That doesn't mean you-
I mean, if you're gonna fol­low me, do it more secretly.
Sorry about that.
I didn't realize.
Why're you angry?
I'm not angry.
Last night, you said... she was killed...
...​your mother.
I didn't say that.
Who killed her?
For­get about it.
You said you could see ghosts ever since you could re­mem­ber, right?
Then an­swer me one thing.
Wasn't the one who killed your mother... a Hollow?
That is a pos­si­bil­ity.
If your spirit abil­ity was high enough that you could see spir­its ever since you could remember,
a Hol­low who was after you could have killed your mother by mis­take.
I can't take this...
I CAN'T TAKE THIS!
Ac­cord­ing to you, every damn thing is the work of Hol­lows, isn't it?
You force me to van­quish mon­sters , and if that wasn't bad enough...
I won't let you blame this on those mon­sters, too.
It wasn't a damn Hollow.
Bet­ter luck next time.
His mom died... when he was nine.
He was still a goofy, clingy mama's boy.
But she died.
He wouldn't come to school.
I went look­ing for him and what d'you think he was doing?
He was on the river­bank where his mom died,
still with his school bag on his back, wan­der­ing back and forth, back and forth...
When he got tired, he'd squat down.
Then after awhile, he'd stand up again.
Day after day, from morn­ing 'til night, it was like he was search­ing for her.
I couldn't stand watch­ing Ichigo back then.
It's the same... as if I... had killed her.
Mommy...
Kurosaki
It's been a long time, Mom.
Have you been well?
I guess you can't be well being dead.
All of us, Yuzu and Ichi and me, are all healthy.
Ex­cept...
Okay, okay, okay!
It's time again for this year's "Omigosh, Kurosaki fam­ily-mem­bers-only grave­stone domino tour­na­ment!"
For two hours and 30 min­utes, we'll dev­il­ishly de­mol­ish grave­stones as we go a-
In this game full of nip­ple peeks, the win­ner gets to boss around the loser for one wee-
To be hon­est, that beard guy is so healthy he's ag­gra­vat­ing.
SHUT THE HELL UP!
Geez, you gotta stop cry­ing every sin­gle year.
We turn eleven this year.
That's grown up al­ready.
Yeah, I get it.
I get it, but...
Hey.
I'm such a fool...
It's near.
But where...
Dammit...
Hey!
What's that?!
What?
Is there some­thing there?
Karin-chan?
Yuzu!
Stay away!
Karin-chan!
No, stay away...
Karin-chan, what's wrong?!
Yuzu!
What is this?!
Stop!
Ground Fisher?!
So you know me.
You're a Death god, is that it?
What is Ichigo doing ...
If you mean your friend, he can't come.
I adored my mom.
I've never once seen my mom cry or get angry.
So...
...​no mat­ter what bad stuff might happen,
I could for­get it when I was near her.
It wasn't just me.
Yuzu, Karin, and Pops, we all adored Mom.
I don't know how it hap­pened.
But it was ob­vi­ous it hap­pened when she was try­ing to save me.
In other words,
I took Mom away from our whole family.
I did it...
That pisses me off...
...​seriously.
I don't know who you think you are,
but you don't know how it feels...
...​SO DON'T FREAKIN' USE MY MOM AS A TOY!!!
You're that...
I was so close...
What?!
Too weak.
And you call your­self a Death god?
You do look delicious.
You enjoy con­sum­ing women THAT much?!
Ichigo...
Stop!
Rukia!
Ichigo!
So you de­ceived me.
I'd never have thought you were a Death god.
And what do you think you're doing?
Take care of Karin and Yuzu.
Where's your lit­tle friend?
I've got ques­tions to ask.
You mean this?
What the hell are you things?!
This kid was on the river­bank that day.
It was six years ago.
How come you're with a Hollow?
How come you looked like my mo-
You're so annoying.
In that case,
I shall tell you.
Well?
Do you com­pre­hend, boy?
A Ground Fisher...
That's it's codename.
It hides it­self,
machi­nates the ap­pendage grow­ing out of its head to re­sem­ble a human form, and ma­nip­u­lates it.
Then it at­tacks hu­mans with souls pos­sess­ing high spirit abil­ity who are lured by that thing.
It uses that method often .
This time, it tried to slow you down by show­ing you your mother so it could eat your sisters.
Be­cause the par­tic­u­larly nasty thing about it is its fa­vorite food is women.
Then my mom...
Ichigo, don't be­come emotional!
That's prob­a­bly im­pos­si­ble, though...
That Hol­low has evaded us Death gods for over fifty long years.
Calm your-
How can...
How can I stay calm?!
You're being care­less, you fool!
So like an am­a­teur, boy.
Ichigo!
Dis­in­te­grate, Black Dog of Ron­danini!
Look upon your­self and burn, tear away your own throa-
STOP, RUKIA!
This time, you mind your own business.
I'll do this alone!
Don't be ridicu­lous!
That thing is strong.
Didn't I just ex­plain that?!
Shutup!
Please...
Don't interfere.
This is...
...​MY fight!
Huh?
Nee-san?
Take these two some­where safe.
What about you, Nee-san?
I'm count­ing on you.
Too slow, boy.
If you just keep run­ning like that,
you'll never be able to in­jure me!
With your abil­i­ties, I'm sur­prised you had the guts to tell me to stay away from your friends, boy.
You're about to see my guts .
After mom died,
I can't imag­ine how sad Yuzu and Karin felt...
I de­cided I would pro­tect them.
I'm going to...
...​beat this bastard!
So careless...
...​to rush into your enemy's range like that with­out a plan.
Here.
And what of pride?
Cap­tain Ukitake!
If you go to his aid now, his life will be saved.
But that...
...​would end up killing his pride for all eternity.
What mat­ters of pride?!
Re­mem­ber this well.
There are two kinds of fights.
As long as we place our­selves in bat­tle, we must al­ways know the difference.
Fights to de­fend life...
...​and fights to de­fend pride...
That's right...
This is a fight to de­fend pride.
Don't interfere...
Don't die, Ichigo!
So impulsive...
You send away your com­rade based on fleet­ing emotion,
and on fleet­ing emo­tion, you lunge at your enemy.
There­fore, you will per­form for me like this...
...​and die with­out in­flict­ing a sin­gle wound on me.
Don't make me laugh.
I'm gonna beat you.
Even if my arm gets severed...
Even if my leg gets tossed...
I'll beat you no mat­ter what!
That is why you will die.
You are young...
...​so you anger easily.
Be­cause you anger, your heart is in chaos.
And be­cause your heart is in chaos, your blade is dulled.
Ichigo...
What's wrong?
Are you al­ready frozen just from hear­ing your name called?
You bastard...
Do you have any idea what you're doing?
Don't freakin' bring out my mom's image in a place like this!
Don't, Ichigo.
Put your sword away.
Don't kill Mommy.
Please...
It is over, boy!
Of all the Death gods I've en­coun­tered, you were the youngest, the most impulsive,
and by far, the WEAK­EST!
I've fi­nally caught you.
"Anger dulls the blade "?
You might be right.
But...
...​didn't I tell you?
No mat­ter what hap­pens to me, I'm gonna take you down!
It's over, Fisher!
Of all the Hol­lows I've en­coun­tered, you are the most over-the-hill, the most cowardly,
and by far, THE BIGGEST ASS­HOLE... OF THEM ALL!!!
I un­der­es­ti­mated you.
But you still weren't able to cut your mother.
Fool­ish Death god.
We shall meet again!
Wait!
Ichigo!
Stop.
That's enough!
Wait...
Stop now.
Nei­ther you nor it can fight any longer.
The fight is over!
Not yet...
It's not dead yet...
I-I'm still...
Ichigo!
I can't be­lieve he isn't dead from these wounds.
This fool's power is impressive...
I'm glad you're still alive... Ichigo.
Sorry.
I wasn't able to avenge you, Mom.
Yo.
Pop...
Here's an umbrella.
It stopped already.
Hey, I went to the trou­ble of bring­ing it.
Come on, use it.
C'mon, c'mon.
That hurt!
The years go by so fast...
Wow, ten years al­ready since Mom died...
It's SIX years!
So close.
That ain't close at all, geez...
A dif­fer­ence of four years would turn a grade-schooler into a high-schooler!
Hey, that's clever of you.
Don't be admiring!
I mean, at least re­mem­ber the year your own wife died right!
Aahh, geez, talkin' to you an­noys the hell outta me!
Well, as long as you show her you're full o' en­ergy like that, Mom can rest as­sured on the other side.
I thought you quit.
She com­pli­mented me on it when we first started dating.
"Your hand looks cool when you're smok­ing," she said.
Think­ing about it now, that was the first and the last time she com­pli­mented me on my looks.
So I smoke just this one day every year.
Here in front of her.
Don't look so depressed!
I just got through telling you to be lively.
How come...
How come you can smile?
Why isn't any­one blam­ing me?!
I couldn't do anything.
I couldn't!
When Mom died...
...​even now...
This is too hard!
If you'd just tear into me, it'd be eas­ier...
Why...
Why should I blame you?
I don't know what's weighin' on you,
but if I blamed you for Masaki's death, she'd get angry at me.
It wasn't any­one's fault that Masaki died.
It's just that...
...​the woman I fell in love with was a woman who didn't mind dying to pro­tect her kid.
And don't for­get,
you're the man who the woman I fell in love with lost her life to protect.
Pop...
Owww...
Live to the fullest, Ichigo.
Live to the fullest,
age to the fullest,
go bald to the fullest,
and die long after I do.
And if pos­si­ble, die with a smile.
I'll be wait­ing down below.
You lis­ten­ing, Rukia?
Let me... be a Death god for a lit­tle longer.
I wanna get stronger.
More...
Stronger so I can pro­tect them from Hollows...
...​protect the peo­ple being tar­geted.
I'm going to get stronger and beat him!
Oth­er­wise,
I won't be able to face my mom!
Ichigo.
I found you~
6th Squad Lieutenant,
Abarai Renji... has arrived!
Abarai
Renji
Howl, Zabimaru!
Ke~n-cha~n!
Gonna kill the enemy?
Kusajishi Yachiru
Yeah, it's a ryoka!
It's the guy who fought with Ichi­maru and survived.
I wanna cut 'im.
Zaraki Kenpachi
Oh, man.
It seems this has got­ten out of hand.
Well then, I guess I'll have to take your life.
Ky­ouraku Shunsui
*^s^z^x^m^ %^&^*^
e^s^z^x^m^ %^&^*^
e^s^z^x^m^ *^&^*^
e^s^z^x^m^ %^&^*^e
Ya­mada
Hanatarou
Take one pill and what do you know,
Up we go.
Hi­namori Momo
o
May I please speak with you for a lit­tle bit?
WAS IT YOU?!
Hit­sug­aya
Tou­shi­rou
Hey, I'm a cap­tain, too, you know.
If you made Hi­namori spill blood,
I would kill you!
It seems the alarm sounds quite con­ve­niently these days.
Ichi­maru Gin
I ain't sure I understand...
...​what you're tryin' to say.
You had best not un­der­es­ti­mate me.
Aizen Sousuke
Then I have no choice.
I shall kill you.
Uk­i­take Juushirou
o
Kuchiki Byakuya
I thought I told you not to speak so im­pu­dently, boy.
Set upon the Frosted Heav­ens, Hyourinmaru!
Death Lance, Shinsou!
Scat­ter, Senbonzakura.
Zangetsu!
Damn...
I lose?
Hold on, Rukia.
Bye bye!
Too slow, boy.
If you just keep run­ning like that,
you'll never be able to in­jure me!
With your abil­i­ties, I'm sur­prised you had the guts to tell me to stay away from your friends, boy.