Digital Devil Monogatari Megami Tensei
Juusei Academy
I have a new classmate to introduce to you all today.
My name is Yumiko Shirasagi.
Nice to meet you all.
Ms. Shirasagi transferred from Yuai High School in Sapporo.
I'm Kanehito Muraki.
I'm Somu Takaichi.
Good morning.
Well, Hirayuki Kondo and Kyoko Takamizawa will temporary not be attending due to illnesses.
Also...
Ah, good morning, Nakajima-kun.
Okay, Shirasagi-san, try your best.
A-All right!
Stand!
Bow!
Obara-sensei...
I'll see you after class, just like we planned.
Y-Yeah...
In the computer room, right?
Hey, your name's Nakajima-kun, right?
We've met somewhere, haven't we?
Did you live in Sapporo?
Or maybe in Nara when you were a little kid?
I just transferred here today, my name's...
Yumiko.
I knew it!
Hey, where did we meet then?
Yumiko
I'll warn you now, transfer student, you shouldn't get too involved with me.
I've come to an awful school,
especially that Nakajima kid.
But where did I meet him?
Oh, I can't figure it out!
Obara-sensei...
DO NOT OPEN
Computer Room
The Moon and Mars are in opposition.
The Sun and Pluto are in opposition.
In the celestial sphere lies a single Grand Cross.
There's no better day for this.
Let's get started right away, Obara-sensei.
I'll begin calling him immediately.
Please relax.
There's nothing to be afraid of, sensei.
With your body, you're sure to satisfy Loki.
Electronic Beast Cerberus.
Protect this holy ceremony!
We're ready.
Take some deep breaths.
Concentrate your mind.
I'll call him down from the world of Atziluth.
Note: Atziluth is the highest world in the Quabalistic Theology.
Sensei!
Yumiko Shirasagi, wasn't it?
What have you done to her?
Look.
A computer graphic...?
His name's Loki.
Loki?
You may not be able to believe it, but he's a demon.
A real one.
You can't mean...
That's exactly right.
She's in the middle of "having fun" with a demon.
That's impossible!
Don't worry.
A powerful demon like Loki can't be materialised with the likes of the computers at this school.
In other words, it's all happening in a world of images created by Loki.
What's wrong?
The ceremony is over.
Go home!
Just like I thought...
I haven't processed enough data to actually make Loki materialise.
What's wrong, Loki?
Make
me
an
offering
An offering?
Do you mean the next sacrifice Loki?
What
Nothing...
I just... have a bad feeling.
(Green book: Computer and Magical Theory)
The materialisation of demons.
If I could do that...
We've met somewhere, haven't we?
That's impossible...
Fumiya... I don't feel so good.
Do you know anything about Akemi Nakajima?
And he says he was doing a Demonic Ritual!
What is this?
Anyway, I need to get going.
What? Today?
Why must we hurry so much, Loki?
There
is
no
need
to
ans
wer
that.
But...
tate?
wer,
ri
gh
t?
Ah, that's...
What's wrong Kondo-kun?
You've got some guts Nakajima.
Akemi, are you okay?
Why...
What's wrong?
A bastard with an ugly face like you...
kissed Kyoko!
You know what that means!
Kondo-kun.
How about you let him off with that?
You're forgiven.
A-All right.
Stand!
Bow!
Today we're going to have our class in the computer study room.
Come on, hurry everyone.
The computer study room?
Shirasagi-san...
Let's go.
Come on, quickly.
Sure...
T-That hurts!
That hurts, Kanou-san.
Nakajima-kun...
You're the star of the show today.
I won't!
I won't listen to what you have to say!
Why are you guys listening to him?
Demons don't exist...
Sensei!
Nakajima-kun!
I can't turn back now.
Prepare the sacrifice.
What's wrong!?
Impossible!
Stop it...
STOP!
Stop it... Loki.
"Stop it," you say?
This is everything you wanted, Nakajima!
Nakajima, what are you doing?
Kill!
Kill! Kill! Kill! Kill!
Nakajima!
Stop right now, Nakajima!
W-What are you doing!?
Stop it, Nakajima!
What do you want...!?
Don't come any closer!
L-Let me go!
D-Damn it!
Let me go!
Stop it!
Let me go, Loki!
Let me go!
You're nothing but a nuisance now.
Obara, you...
No!
Stop it!
Stop it, Loki!
No, no! No!
No, no!
Yumiko!
Who?
Who are you?
Yumiko, you must not give up.
In a previous life, you were known as Izanami.
Note: Izanami is the mother of all gods in Japanese mythology.
A previous life?
Izanami of the myths,
a brilliant light is spreading
throughout this dark greed.
You must combine your powers with him and fly!
Him?
Yes!
Combine your powers with Akemi Nakajima and fly into the light.
With Nakajima-kun?
The guy who made this happen to me?
That's right.
You can do it!
I can't...
You must not run...
And neither must he.
Open your eyes and look well.
Damn you...
Fly with me!
You...
Get back, demon.
Fly!
Shirasagi, are you okay?
I'm...
going to die again...
I will die soon.
The Izanami who saved us told me so.
Izanami?
Nakajima-kun...
Take my body to the grave of Izanami.
You can see it in the distance...
A small hill...
That is the grave of Izanami...
I can revive there.
Don't talk anymore, Shirasagi!
It's okay, you won't die!
Please...
Nakajima-kun...
Just once more...
Please go...
Shirasagi!
Why?
Why do you throw me away...?
Izanagi!
Forgive me, Izanami...
Forgive me, Izanami.
Forgive me, Izanami!
Have you finished analysing the data?
Yes.
The Third Bank of Sakurai City will do, I believe.
Prepare to transport us there.
I'll directly connect to the Third Bank's network.
Sakurai City
Third Bank
That's an... 'Ishi butai'-Stone Stage.
This is Asuka!
We teleported from the school.
Third Bank
Sakurai branch
Thank you!
Kensetsu Saitou-san
Kensetsu Saitou-san?
Huh... This is...
What is this!?
Please take care of it...
Help me, Cerberus...
Loki!
Cerberus!
Thank you for coming, Nakajima.
Beyond this darkness lies the sparkling light world of you and Yumiko Shirasagi.
Now. Together, break through the darkness!
Together, break through the darkness!
Together!
Break through the darkness!
Cerberus!
Cerberus.
Loki!
Get out of the way, demon!
You think just attacking me will do?
Cerberus!
Begone, demon!
Loki-sama!
I
am
S
et
Set?
Aren't you Loki-sama?
I am Set
The
Dark
Set...
Egypt's...
Dark God...