Miyamura!
Ce este?
Lasă-mă să te tund.
Ce? De ce?
Hori, ai grijă cu foarfecele!
Miyamura, sunt sigură că-ți va sta bine cu părul scurt.
Parcă ți-am spus să nu faci asta!
De ce? Fața ta este așa de mică și ai părul așa de moale încât mă enervează rău!
Este mult prea scurt!
Vezi că mă tragi de păr!
Nu mai face atâta zarvă.
Nu!
Nu-mi place deloc asta!
Așa este. Ce vreme frumoasă este astăzi, nu?
Modul cum decurge această conversație mă înspăimântă.
Hori și Miyamura este pe cale să înceapă!
Hori și Miyamura
Asta va fi singura dată când vei apărea pe ecran.
Ce?
Doar cele mai populare personaje vor fi în centrul atenției.
Ce? Ce?!
Noul an școlar începe astăzi.
Compared to when we were just admitted,
going back as a third year student doesn't really feel special.
Now it just feels like spring break ended too soon.
Well, it's not like I really had high hopes or anything...
Dar în acest an...
'Neața.
O, 'neața, Hori.
În ce clasă ești?
I'm in Class 1. Hori, you're with me.
Really? Yay!
But I don't see Tooru's name anywhere.
Furuda Mina
Hori Kyouko
Miyamura Izumi
Mizouchi Taiki
Furuda Mina
Hori Kyouko
Miyamura Izumi
Mizouchi Taiki
It's there. I'm also in Class 1.
Furuda Mina
Hori Kyouko
Miyamura Izumi
Mizouchi Taiki
Furuda Mina
Hori Kyouko
Miyamura Izumi
Mizouchi Taiki
Furuda Mina
Hori Kyouko
Miyamura Izumi
Mizouchi Taiki
Furuda Mina
Hori Kyouko
Miyamura Izumi
Mizouchi Taiki
Furuda Mina
Hori Kyouko
Miyamura Izumi
Mizouchi Taiki
Furuda Mina
Hori Kyouko
Miyamura Izumi
Mizouchi Taiki
Furuda Mina
Hori Kyouko
Miyamura Izumi
Mizouchi Taiki
Furuda Mina
Hori Kyouko
Miyamura Izumi
Mizouchi Taiki
Furuda Mina
Hori Kyouko
Miyamura Izumi
Mizouchi Taiki
Furuda Mina
Hori Kyouko
Miyamura Izumi
Mizouchi Taiki
Furuda Mina
Hori Kyouko
Miyamura Izumi
Mizouchi Taiki
Furuda Mina
Hori Kyouko
Miyamura Izumi
Mizouchi Taiki
Furuda Mina
Hori Kyouko
Miyamura Izumi
Mizouchi Taiki
Furuda Mina
Hori Kyouko
Miyamura Izumi
Mizouchi Taiki
Furuda Mina
Hori Kyouko
Miyamura Izumi
Mizouchi Taiki
Furuda Mina
Hori Kyouko
Miyamura Izumi
Mizouchi Taiki
Furuda Mina
Hori Kyouko
Miyamura Izumi
Mizouchi Taiki
Furuda Mina
Hori Kyouko
Miyamura Izumi
Mizouchi Taiki
Furuda Mina
Hori Kyouko
Miyamura Izumi
Mizouchi Taiki
Furuda Mina
Hori Kyouko
Miyamura Izumi
Mizouchi Taiki
Furuda Mina
Hori Kyouko
Miyamura Izumi
Mizouchi Taiki
Furuda Mina
Hori Kyouko
Miyamura Izumi
Mizouchi Taiki
Furuda Mina
Hori Kyouko
Miyamura Izumi
Mizouchi Taiki
Furuda Mina
Hori Kyouko
Miyamura Izumi
Mizouchi Taiki
Furuda Mina
Hori Kyouko
Miyamura Izumi
Mizouchi Taiki
Furuda Mina
Hori Kyouko
Miyamura Izumi
Mizouchi Taiki
Furuda Mina
Hori Kyouko
Miyamura Izumi
Mizouchi Taiki
Furuda Mina
Hori Kyouko
Miyamura Izumi
Mizouchi Taiki
Furuda Mina
Hori Kyouko
Miyamura Izumi
Mizouchi Taiki
Furuda Mina
Hori Kyouko
Miyamura Izumi
Mizouchi Taiki
Furuda Mina
Hori Kyouko
Miyamura Izumi
Mizouchi Taiki
Furuda Mina
Hori Kyouko
Miyamura Izumi
Mizouchi Taiki
Furuda Mina
Hori Kyouko
Miyamura Izumi
Mizouchi Taiki
Furuda Mina
Hori Kyouko
Miyamura Izumi
Mizouchi Taiki
Furuda Mina
Hori Kyouko
Miyamura Izumi
Mizouchi Taiki
Furuda Mina
Hori Kyouko
Miyamura Izumi
Mizouchi Taiki
Furuda Mina
Hori Kyouko
Miyamura Izumi
Mizouchi Taiki
Furuda Mina
Hori Kyouko
Miyamura Izumi
Mizouchi Taiki
Furuda Mina
Hori Kyouko
Miyamura Izumi
Mizouchi Taiki
Furuda Mina
Hori Kyouko
Miyamura Izumi
Mizouchi Taiki
Furuda Mina
Hori Kyouko
Miyamura Izumi
Mizouchi Taiki
Furuda Mina
Hori Kyouko
Miyamura Izumi
Mizouchi Taiki
Furuda Mina
Hori Kyouko
Miyamura Izumi
Mizouchi Taiki
Furuda Mina
Hori Kyouko
Miyamura Izumi
Mizouchi Taiki
Furuda Mina
Hori Kyouko
Miyamura Izumi
Mizouchi Taiki
Furuda Mina
Hori Kyouko
Miyamura Izumi
Mizouchi Taiki
Furuda Mina
Hori Kyouko
Miyamura Izumi
Mizouchi Taiki
Furuda Mina
Hori Kyouko
Miyamura Izumi
Mizouchi Taiki
Furuda Mina
Hori Kyouko
Miyamura Izumi
Mizouchi Taiki
Furuda Mina
Hori Kyouko
Miyamura Izumi
Mizouchi Taiki
Furuda Mina
Hori Kyouko
Miyamura Izumi
Mizouchi Taiki
Furuda Mina
Hori Kyouko
Miyamura Izumi
Mizouchi Taiki
Furuda Mina
Hori Kyouko
Miyamura Izumi
Mizouchi Taiki
Furuda Mina
Hori Kyouko
Miyamura Izumi
Mizouchi Taiki
Furuda Mina
Hori Kyouko
Miyamura Izumi
Mizouchi Taiki
Furuda Mina
Hori Kyouko
Miyamura Izumi
Mizouchi Taiki
Furuda Mina
Hori Kyouko
Miyamura Izumi
Mizouchi Taiki
Furuda Mina
Hori Kyouko
Miyamura Izumi
Mizouchi Taiki
Furuda Mina
Hori Kyouko
Miyamura Izumi
Mizouchi Taiki
Furuda Mina
Hori Kyouko
Miyamura Izumi
Mizouchi Taiki
Furuda Mina
Hori Kyouko
Miyamura Izumi
Mizouchi Taiki
Furuda Mina
Hori Kyouko
Miyamura Izumi
Mizouchi Taiki
Furuda Mina
Hori Kyouko
Miyamura Izumi
Mizouchi Taiki
Furuda Mina
Hori Kyouko
Miyamura Izumi
Mizouchi Taiki
Furuda Mina
Hori Kyouko
Miyamura Izumi
Mizouchi Taiki
Furuda Mina
Hori Kyouko
Miyamura Izumi
Mizouchi Taiki
Furuda Mina
Hori Kyouko
Miyamura Izumi
Mizouchi Taiki
Furuda Mina
Hori Kyouko
Miyamura Izumi
Mizouchi Taiki
Furuda Mina
Hori Kyouko
Miyamura Izumi
Mizouchi Taiki
Furuda Mina
Hori Kyouko
Miyamura Izumi
Mizouchi Taiki
Furuda Mina
Hori Kyouko
Miyamura Izumi
Mizouchi Taiki
Furuda Mina
Hori Kyouko
Miyamura Izumi
Mizouchi Taiki
Sorry.
Ah... Miyamura is in the same class as us.
He looks like an otaku as usual.
Ah, Hori-san. Good morning.
Good morning.
Good morning, Yuki.
Hey~
Hori, show me your notes again.
Hey, do them yourself.
Are the seats assigned?
N-Nice to meet you.
Yeah...
Hori~!
I'm glad my seat is close to yours.
The three of us are back together again.
I get it...
Good morning. Everyone, please take your seats.
I'm the homeroom teacher for Class 1, Terajima.
I'll also be your chemistry teacher.
Nice to meet you all.
OK, so this is the plan for today.
You forgot this.
At 9, we'll start working...
My... no, our secret...
I'm home!
Welc-
What happened to you?!
I fell.
Geez!
U-Um...
A dog startled him and he fell.
You came here just because of that?
Souta-kun is a pretty responsible kid.
He was able to properly tell me his name and address.
He must get it from you.
No... not really...
It's pretty amazing that you take care of the house all by yourself.
I'm impressed, Hori-san.
No...
Huh? It's Hori-san, right?
U-Um yeah, it's Hori, but...
Do you go to the same school?
We're in the same class. I'm Miyamura.
It's fine. I'm just going to go sit in this corner, so don't worry about it. It's fine.
Same class... That... Miyamura...
Having a different hairstyle can really change a person.
You too.
I'm sorry, but please don't change the topic to me.
"You too."
You must care a lot about your home.
S-Stop it.
I haven't even let Yuki see me without makeup.
Onii-chan, I don't understand this puzzle.
Let me see.
Where?
Here.
Ah, the piece is upside down.
Thanks for the food!
Are you sure it's OK...
It's fine, one extra person isn't going to make a difference.
Besides, I already made it.
It's good.
Thanks for the food.
You're right, it's delicious.
Isn't it?
You should always wear your hair like this.
Your glasses too.
Yeah, but my piercings stand out.
You look cuter without your makeup.
Huh?
That face.
What face?
Thanks again for the food.
Come over again, Onii-chan.
I didn't think that there'd be a next time.
S-Souta said that he wants to play with you again, so maybe next weekend...
A-Are you sure?
I'm not the one asking! Souta is.
After that, I started going to Hori-san's house on my days off.
Even now those days continue, but not every day.
Boys shouldn't cry like that, you know.
But you kicked me.
It's called playing the heel.
Why don't you ask your sister to come save you again?
That's what's called a sister complex.
Onee-
Souta!
It's time to go. We're going to go to Starbucks.
Onii-chan!
So that's why Souta was with you.
Yeah.
So where's my juice?
Here.
Thanks.
What's this?! It's just a cafe latte!
Eh? You don't like it?
Geez!
I'm gonna go check on Souta.
It's so frustrating...
I think it tastes good.
No... not the heel!
Hori-san, what should I do?
Huh, what?
Today's physical exams.
I told you yesterday.
Come here for a second.
What are we doing here?
What should I do about this?
A tattoo?
I don't know whether to think you're amazing or a complete idiot.
What are you saying, Hori-san?
Suspension... no, you'll be expelled.
I wonder what that's about.
Village of Bamboo Shoots
These "Village of Bamboo Shoots" cookies are really good!
I wonder if I can get out of the examination by yelling sexual harassment.
Miyamura.
What?
Haven't you been pretty friendly with Hori lately?
R-Really?
A-Are you going out?
No, there's no way...
I thought so. You and Hori are too different.
Yeah, we wouldn't make a good match.
W-We...
Speak clearly!
S-Sorry.
Ishikawa-kun, could it be that you like Hori-san?
So what if I do?
Really?
Natural Insensitivity
That's right. So...
Full Throttle
Natural Insensitivity
So that's why you're always staring when I talk to Hori-san...
Be quiet, idiot!
Just plain Insensitive
Oh sorry, it's a secret, huh?
I'm really sorry...
What are you guys doing?
Gym is next, right? Go get changed.
Well, we're already late as it is.
Let's go.
Whoa, you changed fast!
Hey, I've been thinking...
It's summer, so why are you wearing winter gym clothes?
I-I'm sensitive to the cold weather.
Don't tell me, you have a scar or something?
I shouldn't have asked. Sorry.
A-Ah, no it's...
I really shouldn't tell you, but underneath this jacket...
It could be a real problem if you tell anyone, OK?
Whoa, what's that? Is it real?
Yeah.
It's true that if you were wearing a white shirt then you could see through it.
If you're going to hide it, then why did you get it?
I didn't realize that until after I got it.
No way.
You're kind of interesting.
So Hori likes this kind of face, huh...
You even have piercings?
Shhh!
Hori.
Are you going home?
Yeah.
What?
I wanted to talk to you.
OK.
You're with Tooru?
Um, kind of.
You're avoiding the question.
I-I wasn't trying to...
Look me in the eyes when you talk to me.
No, that's...
What did I do?
Nothing! It's just...
I don't really get it, but take care of Souta for me. OK?
C'ya later!
Bye!
I'm gonna to confess to Hori. Is that OK with you?
Why did you check with me?
No, somehow...
Hori-san will make her choice, so...
I'm just grateful that she is nice to me.
We're really nothing more than friends.
New
Product
Fresh Pudding
yen
If those two start dating...
where will that leave me?
I'll just be in the way.
Hori Souta.
Hori Souta
I'm done, Onii-chan.
Onii-chan?
Y-Yeah... good job.
Can I eat the pudding now?
I'm home.
Onee-chan just came back!
It'll be OK, I'm used to being alone... it'll be just like before.
That's all.
We're going to eat pudding now.
OK, OK.
Welcome back.
Stop!
It's over, Hariken.
Tooru told me.
Oh?
I wonder what she's going to say.
"Give me back the key," or "You don't need to come here anymore," or maybe...
D-Did you really say that we don't match?
Huh?
Did you really say that I'm just being nice to you?
What about Ishikawa-kun?
He told me that you...
He told me...
He told you?
It's just like he said.
I'm dark and plain. I'd just cause problems for you, I think.
That's why I...
It's not how I really feel though.
I didn't want to blow your cover.
I'm sorry! Are you OK-
Why do you have to care about covering for me?
Don't say that again!
You idiot!
It's still OK if I come over?
If you stop coming, then Souta would cry!
And it'd be hard for me to carry groceries alone.
And there would be too many leftovers!
Tooru? Oh I turned him down.
I see. Even though he's a nice guy and all.
Most people like him would be shocked to see my face without makeup.
Ishikawa-kun wouldn't be shocked.
He's a good guy.
What?
Are you in love with him?
Then why don't you go out with him?
Eh?
Ishikawa-kun is so popular though. I don't think we'd be a good match.
Eww.
Ah, it's Tooru.
Good morning.
I'm heartbroken right now!
At least say good morning.
It seems like he's avoiding me today.
Isn't it painful for you to talk to him?
Why?
Not at all.
Tooru...
Seems like he doesn't have a problem with talking to me.
This morning he came up to me and said,
"Good morning, Miyamura. Did you do the homework?"
It's just like... we're friends.
Miyamura, you skipping class?
Yeah.
Me too.
I'm too tired to run anymore.
You're sweating a lot.
Is this OK?
OK, today we're going to do a report.
You'll be in groups of four.
Decide on groups amongst yourselves.
Chimie
Yoshikawa, loan me a pen.
You always have plenty, right?
Shut up.
I won't lend one to someone like you.
Stingy.
Does anyone have a blank piece of paper?
No.
I do.
Do we have enough paper?
I have a loose leaf binder with me.
Miyamura, collect all of the materials.
OK.
Hey! That's my eraser.
I'm just borrowing it.
Don't use it too much.
You two never stop.
Friends...
Is this what friends are like?
OK, let's all pair up and hold hands.
OK!
Let's do it.
OK.
Hey, hey, let's hold hands.
Has everyone found a partner?
Yes!
Miyamura, huh?
He's not a bad guy, he's just a little dark.
Miyamura's alone again.
Someone should let him in their group.
I always thought that was normal for me.
Ah, there you are, Miyamura.
What's up, Ishikawa-kun?
Fifth period got switched to political science.
I wonder if I brought the textbook.
I wish they'd stop changing things.
Anyway, Hori's the same as always.
Typically a person would become uneasy...
Well, I'm glad she's not doing that.
Does that mean she thinks nothing of me, I wonder?
Is Ishikawa-kun a friend?
Anyway...
What do you think?
Huh? About what?
Weren't you listening?
Um... what do you think about me?
When you say it like that... it sounds weird.
And it bothers me that you're friendly with Hori.
It's irritating when you don't speak clearly.
Sometimes you act weird.
Also, you're too nice and gullible. I can't leave you alone.
Without your glasses and a different hairstyle, you'd be good-looking.
It's irritating.
Making me say all this, that's what's annoying about you.
Eh?
Also, you're about the only one who calls me by my last name with -kun.
I'm the one who should be asking you about what you think of me.
T-Tooru...
Gross. If you're going to be embarrassed.
then you shouldn't force yourself to call me that.
Idiot.
Totally gross.
Eh... I was just giving it a try.
It's the first time I've called a classmate by their first name is all.
You really are weird.
Sorry.
You're weird, but I don't dislike you.
You're just a little awkward is all.
Izumi.
You two idiots were supposed to work on the report during lunch.
You're wrong. Including Yoshikawa, there are three idiots.
What was that?
Geez.
Do the report later, OK?
OK.
Next we have to go to the media room.
Let's go.
Do I need my textbook?
Don't need it.
It's OK.
Miyamura! Let's go.
It'll be OK.
OK.
Third year of high school, a new term.
Spring has just begun.