What is evil? -Whatever springs from weakness.
Dacă pot, mi-ar plăcea
să pun această întrebare:
„Sunt oamenii cu adevărat egali?”
În zilele noastre, oamenii vorbesc în
continuu despre nevoia de egalitate.
Un mare om a spus cândva: „Cerul nu creează un om mai presus sau mai prejos ca altul.”
Dar citatul nu se sfârșește aici.
El spune că suntem egali la naștere,
dar apoi, apar diferențele.
Acele diferențe sunt rezultatele eforturilor
academice ale unei persoane sau lipsa acestora.
În orice caz, oamenii pot
gândi pentru ei înșiși.
Poate că „egalitatea” e un concept fals,
dar inegalitatea noastră rămâne
un lucru greu de acceptat.
Scuză-mă... Ai putea să
cedezi locul pe care stai?
E un loc cu prioritate. Cred că ar trebui să o lași pe această doamnă în vârstă să stea acolo.
Vai, vai, ce fetiță drăguță.
Deși e un loc cu prioritate, nu există nicio lege care să-mi ceară să renunț la el.
Vrei să renunț la locul meu
doar pentru că sunt tânăr?
Asta e pur și simplu absurd.
Chiar dacă sunt tânăr, statul în picioare
consumă mai multă energie decât statul jos.
De ce ar trebui să fac ceva în defavoarea mea fără să am vreun beneficiu?
Cred că ai ajuta societatea.
Iar această doamnă nu prea pare să poată sta în picioare.
Nu am niciun interes
să ajut societatea.
Pe lângă asta...
Cum rămâne cu ceilalți care
stau pe celelalte locuri?
Diferența dintre locurile cu prioritate
și celelalte mi se pare nesemnificativă.
S-Serios, sunt în regulă.
Dar îți mulțumesc.
Scuzați-mă! Dorește careva
să renunțe la locul său?
Ei bine, îl poți avea pe al meu.
Mulțumesc foarte mult!
Disembarking
Deci asta e noua mea școală?
Liceul Metropolitan de
Cultivare Avansată din Tokyo.
O școală înființată
de guvernul japonez
ca să cultive tinerii care
vor susține țara în viitor.
Afirmă că are o rată de angajare și de intrare la colegiu de 100%,
iar prin metode de învățare
complexe și supervizate de stat,
lucrează din greu ca să atingă
viitorul dorit de națiune.
Scuză-mă.
Te uitai la mine în autobuz. De ce?
Oh. Îmi cer scuze.
O făceam deoarece, la fel ca mine, nici tu nu păreai să fii interesată să renunți la locul pe care stăteai.
Deci nici ție nu-ți place să te implici în genul acela de lucruri, nu?
Nu presupune că
sunt la fel ca tine.
Mi-am păstrat locul ca o
chestiune de convingere.
Hei, asta nu te face chiar
mai îngrozitoare decât mine?
Dacă nu ai vreo treabă
cu mine, am plecat.
Acum vom asculta câteva cuvinte din
partea președintelui consiliului elevilor.
Eu sunt președintele consiliului elevilor, Horikita Manabu.
Ca reprezentant al
claselor mai mari,
mi-ar plăcea să urez bun
venit noilor noștri elevi.
După cum deja bănuiesc că știți, școala noastră are mari reușite în toate aspectele
și o rată de angajare și
intrare la colegiu mare.
Asta este mândria școlii noastre, recunoscută prin munca grea
a celor care au absolvit, dar și a celor care încă studiază aici.
Avem aceleași așteptări de la elevii noi.
Suntem în aceeași clasă?
Totul în această școală
e decis după merit...
Înțeleg! Care este genul tău favorit?
O, gen? Ei bine... Îmi place romanța!
O, serios?
Chestii precum benzile desenate de fete...
Serios? Mie îmi plac misterele!
Misterele?!
Surprinzător, nu?
Da!
Mi se spune des!
Stau lângă ea?
O coincidență neplăcută.
Sunt de aceeași părere.
Toată lumea, mă puteți asculta o clipă?
Speram să ne prezentăm cu toții
ca să fim cu un pas mai aproape de a ne cunoaște mai bine.
Oricum, profesorul nu
pare să fi ajuns încă.
Ce spuneți?
Sunt de acord!
Pare distractiv.
Da. Nu știu numele niciunuia.
Mulțumesc. În regulă,
voi începe primul.
Eu sunt Hirata Yosuke.
Spuneți-mi doar Yosuke.
Nu este nevoie să fiți formali.
Practic tot feluri de sporturi și intenționez să mă alătur clubului de fotbal al acestei școli.
Mă bucur să vă cunosc pe toți!
Sună bine!
Pariez că va ajunge liderul clasei.
Eu urmez acum!
Numele meu este Kushida Kikyo.
Obiectivul meu este să
devin prietenă cu voi toți!
Mi-ar plăcea să-mi fac multe amintiri plăcute, deci nu ezitați să mă invitați în diferite locuri!
Abia aștept!
Ea va fi populară și
cu băieții, și cu fetele.
Eu urmez! Sunt Ike Kanji!
Are deja acea aură „pot fi
prietenă cu oricine” în jurul ei.
Îmi plac fetele și detest tipii arătoși!
Dar nu cred că e momentul potrivit să critic.
Accept mereu noi aplicații pentru postul de iubită!
Aceste prezentări vor decide
poziția fiecăruia din clasă.
Eu sunt Yamauchi Haruki.
În școala primară, am mers la
concursul național de ping-pong.
Ar trebui să încerc să fac o glumă?
In middle school, I was the baseball club's ace and cleanup hitter.
Pariez că-i pot face să
râdă dacă sunt energic.
Încă mă recuperez de la o accidentare căpătată în compețiția dintre licee.
Sau poate doar i-aș îngrozi pe toți.
O, uau! Competiția dintre licee, când încă erai în gimnaziu?
Nu este ca și cum am vreun
hobby sau vreun talent.
Sunt doar o pasăre
albă care zboară liberă.
Acum urmează... tu!
Ce? Eu?
Nu am de ales.
Aș face bine să îmi adun
puțină energie ca să mă prezint.
De dragul vieții mele de licean.
Păi...
Ei bine...
Eu sunt Ayanokoji Kiyotaka.
Abia aștept să învăț alături de voi.
Și, păi...
I'm not good at anything in particular.
Uh...
I'll work hard to get along with everyone.
I blew it.
Nice to meet you, Ayanokoji.
Let's be good friends.
She laughed at me.
Okay, next up...
Introductions? Please.
What are we, little kids?
Do that if you want, but leave us out of it.
Everyone...
Take your seats.
I'm Chabashira Sae,
the homeroom teacher for Class D.
There will be no changing of classes in this school.
I will be responsible for you for the next three years, until you graduate.
First, I'll hand out the school rule book.
Take one and pass it back.
We have special rules at this school.
First, you will live in dorms.
While at school, your ability to leave campus and contact the outside world will be limited.
But don't worry.
The school offers a variety of facilities.
Everything you need can be found here, including entertainment.
To buy things, you'll use points stored in the school's official computer system.
At this school, you can buy anything using points.
Points are allotted on the first of each month.
One point is worth one yen.
You have already been allotted 100,000 points for this month.
100,000?
Are you serious?
Are you surprised by the size of your allotment?
This school judges students based on merit.
You are attributed significant value just for being accepted here.
Thanks for your business!
It really does work like money.
Twenty-five students per class, and four classes per grade...
That makes 300 students total.
If each student gets 100,000 yen per month,
that's 360 million per year.
Strange, even if it is government-funded...
Another unpleasant coincidence.
You don't have to be so twitchy.
Well, since we sit beside each other, we should at least get along.
What's your name?
You can tell me that much, can't you?
Is it a problem if I refuse to answer?
No, but it's unsettling not to know the name of the person sitting beside me.
It's Horikita Suzune.
Horikita?
Like the student council president?
You're buying lots of cheap stuff.
You have a lot of money, though.
You could buy more expensive—
I don't need it.
But—
I don't need it, I told you.
Right.
You don't seem very good at interacting with people.
You're a lousy conversationalist.
That's true, although you don't seem much better.
True. But I, for one, feel no need to make friends.
Items on this table
FREE Up to three per month
Free?
Items on this table
FREE Up to three per month
I guess it's to help people who use up their points?
Items on this table
FREE Up to three per month
On top of 100,000 yen a month?
This school is quite indulgent.
You looking down on me? Huh?!
You're in Class 1-D, aren't you?
And what if I am?!
Now, that's no way to talk to your seniors.
Shut up!
Huh?
He's from our class, isn't he?
I don't care if you're my seniors!
You want to fight or not?!
My integrity would take a dive if I involved myself in that.
I'll take all three of you!
Bring it on!
We'll let you off easy today.
You guys are already defective losers.
If we knocked you any lower, you'd just be pathetic.
Are you running away?!
Scream all you want.
The real hell is yet to come for you people, anyway.
Hell?
Damn it!
It wasn't long before groups began to form within the class.
Kikyo, let's get lunch together!
Sorry, I've got some things to do.
'Twas a mere 80,000! We're to receive 100,000 every month, after all!
I bought tons of mobile games!
Sounds good! I'll buy some, too, and we can battle!
I saw this accessory I really liked.
Want to stop by after class?
I wanna buy clothes, too.
I failed at making friends.
You're pitiful.
You're alone, too.
Yes, because I like to be alone.
Maybe I'll hit up the cafeteria...
Um... Ayanokoji, right?
Yeah. Um...
Kushida?
Thanks!
I'm so glad you remembered my name!
Yeah... I guess.
Um... Can we talk?
Tokyo M
Tokyo Metr
Tokyo Metropoli
Tokyo Metropolitan
Tokyo Metropolitan Adv
Tokyo Metropolitan Advan
Tokyo Metropolitan Advanced N
Tokyo Metropolitan Advanced Nurt
Tokyo Metropolitan Advanced Nurturing
Tokyo Metropolitan Advanced Nurturing Hi
Tokyo Metropolitan Advanced Nurturing High Sc
Tokyo Metropolitan Advanced Nurturing High School
At this school, each student will have their own points to be used in place of
money when buying goods and services.
There is nothing, within the realm of reason, that cannot be
bought on campus using points.
Ayanokoji, you seem very close to Horikita.
No, I wouldn't say that...
But you're the only one she ever talks to.
I want to be friends with everyone in school.
So I asked Horikita for her contact information,
but she turned me down...
She said she doesn't want to be friends with anyone.
Yeah, I think that's just how she is.
But I want to be friends with Horikita, too!
Won't you help me?
Help you? I don't...
You... won't?
The head of the Yamato government was known as the "o-kimi."
He controlled the powerful families of each region using the uji-kabane system.
"Uji" referred to groups that shared the same bloodline,
while "kabane" referred to post and status.
In other words, it was a system where bloodline determined one's post and status.
That's all for today.
Please review the material thoroughly.
This school really is indulgent.
Students play around and nap in class, but the teacher never calls them out.
Is this really an advanced school run by the government?
Maybe they want to encourage student autonomy.
Perhaps.
Hey. If you're on your way out,
would you come with me?
What are you after?
Does an invitation from me suggest an ulterior motive?
If you'll tell me specifically what you want,
I'd be willing to hear you out.
You know that café in the mall, right?
The one where lots of girls hang out.
Would you go there with me?
Why me?
I'm not brave enough to go by myself.
It feels sort of "no boys allowed."
And there's no one else you can ask? No, I suppose not...
It pains me to say it, but you're right.
It's quite crowded.
So this is your first time coming here, too?
Ah, right. You're a loner.
Was that a dig? You child.
That table's free.
You know, I wonder if we look like a couple to the oth—
Yeah, probably not.
Thinking of what's about to happen is making my stomach hurt.
Ready to go?
Yeah.
Horikita!
What a coincidence!
You, too, Ayanokoji!
Do you two come here often?
Today's our first time.
I see.
I'm here alone—
I'm leaving.
Hey, we only just got here.
If Kushida is here, you don't need me, do you?
Well... Kushida and I are just classmates.
That's all you and I are, too.
Besides...
I don't like this. What are you after?
C-Come on, it was just a coincidence...
Kushida, you should have said,
"What's that supposed to mean?"
The girls who were sitting here,
and the two at the next table over,
were all students from Class D.
Coincidence?
I'm impressed you recognized them.
I didn't even notice.
We came here right after class ended,
which means they could only have been in this café for a few minutes.
Too soon for them to be leaving.
Um...
I'm sorry. We set you up.
I thought as much.
Horikita! Please be my friend!
I want you to leave me alone.
I won't trouble the class.
But you'll be lonely all by yourself...
I have never once felt lonely by myself.
You're wasting your time.
Every word that comes out of your mouth disgusts me.
Hey, are you sure about this?
If you won't be friends with anyone, you'll be alone for the next three years.
I've been alone for the last nine years, so I don't mind.
Longer, if you include kindergarten.
Sorry. I might have made Horikita hate you...
Nah, don't worry about it.
Maybe I can never be her friend...
If I can't even make friends with my own classmates,
I guess my goal is still far away.
I think Horikita's an exception, personally...
Your hair is always so silky!
Oh, it's Ichinose!
You think so?
Ichinose Honami from Class B.
We became friends yesterday.
You're even friends with students in other classes?
Yeah! There are a lot of nice people in Class B.
Hey, this school is pretty amazing, huh?
There are so many stores, and we get 100,000 yen each month...
That amount seems a bit excessive to me, though.
Yeah... You think so, too?
And calling them points makes me spend them without thinking.
It really messes with my sense of money.
Items on this table
FREE Up to three per month
I want to be really careful not to over-spend.
I'll buy the things I have to, of course.
Daily necessities like soap and detergent...
Underwear, and stuff...
Yeah, Horikita was doing the same thing.
Oh?
So you know how Horikita spends her money?
You really are close, aren't you?
I just happened to see it.
Um, she's really close...
Well, we'll just leave it at that.
It really is true, though...
100,000 per month, huh?
Most students decided to make the most of their school lives,
without thinking too deeply about anything.
Day after day, they blew through their monthly allowance of 100,000 like it was nothing.
The teacher was very lenient,
so in-class conversations, napping, tardiness, and absences became a daily occurrence.
Extravagance, debauchery, and indolence were rampant.
And then, May 1st arrived.
Huh? What's going on?
Really? You, too?
How come?
Take your seats.
Morning homeroom will now begin.
Hey, teacher, we didn't get our points!
We're supposed to get them on the first day of the month, right?
No, this month's points have already been allotted.
But...
The points have been allotted.
I can say that for certain.
There is no chance that this class has been overlooked, either.
But we didn't get any points!
Yeah!
What a bunch of idiots you are.
A combined total of 98 tardies and absences.
391 instances of talking and cell phone usage in class.
Quite a month's work.
At this school, your grades and performance evaluations
are reflected in the monthly points you're given.
My assessment of you
has resulted in the loss of all 100,000 points you were to be given.
The points you're receiving for this month...
are zero.
You mean I have to live on no money this month?
Wh-What the heck?
No one told us that...
Did you really think that mere high school students
were going to be given 100,000 yen a month to spend without a single catch?
That's absurd.
Use your common sense.
If you had doubts, why did you do nothing about them?
I told you on the first day, didn't I?
This school judges students based on merit.
Which means you're all worth nothing.
You're garbage.
Welcome to the Classroom of the Elite
The butterfly glimmered as it flew
in a dust cloud that danced across the earth
It longed to be in the sky, however far off it might be
I glare at them, but the stars won't fall
How will I go about capturing them
from where I stand now?
Beneath the fading ultramarine, equality sets a trap
A hook is cast into my room
The shade mixes with the sunlight
Entropy begins to rise
As if to ask me,
"How will you choose to live with so few restrictions on your freedom?"
Step by step, little by little,
We're going to seize the sunlight
Change isn't something to be feared—
let's achieve evolution
We'll crawl back up as many times as needed
The sky will always be waiting for us
We're travelers walking across our room that we call Earth
It is a great talent and skill to conceal one's talent and skill.
La Rochefoucauld