Toate avem peste 20 de ani!
Vom ajunge imediat în ultima stație: Tokyo.
Vă rugăm să aveți grijă la coborâre.
Aici voi locui de azi înainte.
Sper să întâlnesc niște oameni drăguți.
Episodul 1: Berea Yebisu
Deci aceasta este Stația Tokyo!
Arată exact ca la televizor!
Vai, ce de oameni.
Ei bine, deci trebuie doar să schimb trenurile la...
Track Numbers       Track Numbers      Track Numbers          Track Numbers
Aș face bine să nu iau trenul greșit.
Ce?
U-Un hoț!
Cum îndrăznești să iei lucrurile altei persoane?
Poftim. Ești bine?
O, îți mulțumesc foarte mult.
Este așa de frumoasă...
Are acel aspect metropolitan rafinat.
Așa frumoasă și grozavă și...
Ai grijă, bine?
Îți mulțumesc foarte, foarte mult!
La revedere.
Presupun că există persoane
drăguțe în Tokyo, la urma urmei.
Tată, mamă, cred că voi fi bine aici!
Vă mulțumim că ați mers cu...
Unde sunt...?
Tată, mamă, nu cred că voi fi bine aici deloc...
Am reușit!
Mă bucur că am luat trenul
shinkansen de mai devreme.
Dacă aș fi întârziat...
Femeie necioplită și nepricepută de la țară!
O, nu! O femeie demonică din Tokyo!
Mersi că m-ai așteptat.
Nu! Îmi cer scuze! Îmi cer scuze că am venit în Tokyo!
Mă aștepți de mult timp?
Ce...?
Tu ești Amatsuki Michiru, nu?
D-Da.
Eu sunt Midorikawa Kae. Am venit ca să te conduc!
Eu sunt Amatsuki! Încântată de cunoștință!
D-Deci... Așa arată o femeie din Tokyo...
Mergem?
Da!
T-Trebuie să dau tot ce pot...!
Uau!
Aceasta este Stella House Haruno.
Deci asta este noua mea casă!
Este o casă cu chirie numai pentru femei.
Suntem deja trei care locuiesc aici.
Iar tu ești a patra, Michiru-chan.
Vai, devin agitată acum.
Scuzați deranjul...
De azi înainte, asta este și casa ta, deci nu trebuie să fii timidă.
O, ai dreptate...
A-Am ajuns.
Bine ai venit!
A-Asta este foarte jenant!
Nao-chan, noua noastră colegă de cameră a ajuns!
KEEP YOUR AFTERNOON DRINKING TO A MINIMUM
Vai, nu fi așa gălăgioasă...
Haide, ridică-te.
Eu sunt Kiriyama Nao.
Mă bucur să te cunosc...
Îmi cer scuze pentru asta, Michiru-chan.
She's been drinking since noon
since she has the day off today.
New roommate?
We should celebrate!
Welcome to Stella House!
We've been looking forward to this!
Now to celebrate! By cracking open a Yebisu beer!
Sheesh, you're really going to keep drinking?
Well, duh!
We're talking about Yebisu here. Yebisu!
I was worried you'd have downed them all already.
Oh, no, I would never!
Hmm?
Okay just one.
Then why are there two missing?
I'll wash the dishes to make up for it!
Now as way of apology allow me to pour you
a fan-freaking-tastic glass of Yebisu beer!
Hold that glass for me, would ya?
L-like this?
Get ready!
Here GOES!
Relax, relax! A good pouring is key!
First we fill it up about half way and then STOP!
Now we let the fizz there settle down
and wait until it's about half foam half beer.
Next we pour very carefully making sure
to keep the foam until it's about 90% full.
Then you gotta hold back that desire
to gulp it down and just wait.
Now here's the last part!
Pour the rest in nice and slow
to bring the head to the top.
The perfect ratio is 7 to 3 and with that it's ready!
Oh my! It's like something out of a commercial!
Right?
This is the ideal way to pour
the perfect glass of Yebisu beer.
I call it the three step pour!
Now then, let's celebrate Michiru Amatsuki
moving in with us here!
Cheers!
The foam is so fluffy...!
Right? Right?
The foam is so fine and the bubbles have settled down.
That's the magic of the three step pour!
Now Michiru-chan, make sure you eat up!
Chilled tofu is the perfect match for a summer drink.
I topped it off with some plum and okra
to make it even more refreshing.
Don't mind if I do!
Oh, that plum accent really stimulates the palate!
And it looks just as wonderful as it tastes!
And nothing like some beer to wash it down!
DRINK SLOWER TO ENJOY IT MORE
How can she drink that much...?!
Here's some chopped avocado and tuna
dressed with wasabi soy sauce.
The avocado is so rich it's just perfect with a beer.
That wasabi is just the perfect dose of spicy!
Small dishes like these are what summer is all about.
The heat can drain your appetite after all!
How can she eat that much...?!
Now that you've got your chopsticks
warmed up and ready, it's time for our main dish.
Shrimp and summer veggie tempura.
Bring on the fried goodies!
Even in this heat you can't help
but crave something deep fried.
No matter how hot...
Woah, hang in there Kae!
I'll crank up the A/C!
Now nice and hot tempura is fine with salt. But here we
dig in with some grated daikon and dipping sauce.
Oh, my! How refreshing!
Glad to have you back!
Oh, that grated daikon is to die for!
And that freshly fried batter is so light and crispy...
Fried food and beer go hand in hand, but a premium
beer like this would be wasted on anything too heavy.
Good thinking...
I guess there's food to match every sort of drink.
To be honest though Yebisu beer
tastes great no matter what you eat.
How uncouth!
Hey, by the way, why did you
move out to Tokyo anyway?
For work! I'm going to be working
sales a startup company.
I'm going to stride through the crowds in my suit.
Drink a smoothie every morning.
Eat my own handmade lunch in the afternoon.
And finish off the night at a fancy restaurant with a view!
Sales sounds pretty tough, though.
Don't let your quotas drive you crazy.
Can you not crush my dreams right from the get go!
What do both of you do, though?
I work in the apparel industry.
I'm a wedding planner.
Oh, wow! Those both sounds so lovely and fun!
Okay what's with the silent treatment?!
You've still got that light of hope... huh, Michiru?
We were like that too, once upon a time.
It's true! We had hopes and dreams!
But...
before we knew it our dreams were shattered,
and the hope drained form our eyes...
Before long, all we were doing
was griping and moaning...
We want nothing but happiness,
but are not spared even the time to seek it out...
N..Nao-san?
That's life, kid!
She's seriously crying?
Then one day while I was trying
to drown my sorrows away...
Yebisu is so GOOOOD!
Grant me your attention.
Who's there?
The label on that bottle you're holding.
Yebisu-sama?!
Yebisu-sama spoke to me.
Oh, you poor soul...
And that very same bottle...
...is right here!
My lucky Yebisu!
This little bottle saved you, huh?
Don't look at me like I'm crazy!
Go ahead and compare it to this can here!
Hey! There's a fish in the basket on this one!
Exactly! It's a super rare special label!
The luckiest Yebisu around!
Nao-chan you still had that thing?
It's my most cherished possession!
And so yeah, that brought
a spark of happiness back into my life.
So you just do your best, okay Michiru?
Lucky Yebisu here, is watching over you!
I'm already quite lucky.
My first time in Tokyo and I meet such friendly people.
Everything about Tokyo is so unfamiliar, and I was
afraid to live alone so I picked this share house.
But that meant I'd have to live with people I've never
even met, so I was worried maybe we wouldn't get along.
Looks like I was worried for nothing, though.
So thank you both again!
Oh, Michiru!
No, thank you!
Welcome to the group.
Oh! She's back! My sweet sister!
Huh? Is our other roommate...
Yup! She's Nao's little sister.
I'm home.
Makoto!
Welcome home! Nghh!
Oh!
You big meanie! Why would you avoid me like that?
You reek of beer.
U-umm...
I'm Michiru Amatsuki,
the one you helped at Tokyo Station.
Oh, that was you?
Thank you so much for that!
No, no, nice to meet you for real though.
Yeah, you too!
Hey, now! Why don't you treat me like that?
Well Makoto-chan is not exactly fond of drunks.
I'm not drunk!
Michiru you and Makoto know each other?
I ran into her at Tokyo Station.
I was so lucky, she really saved me...
I hope we get along.
Nao-chan, how long are you going
to sit there zoning out?
Look, we were up so late drinking...
I hope Michiru-chan is okay.
Good morning!
I went and picked up breakfast at the convenience store!
How is she so lively...?
Are you all right? You don't feel hungover or anything?
Oh, no, I'm fine.
My parents are pretty heavy drinkers you see.
Ever since I turned 20
I've drank at home plenty with them.
I'll pick up something for us to drink
on the way home tonight.
Wait, is she a heavier drinker than us?!
This is the start of my new life in Tokyo.
I'm going to make the very best
of my work and home life!
I thought that jingle that plays
at Ebisu station sounded familiar.
Turns out it was from the Yebisu Beer commercial!
Apparently it's the theme song
from the movie "The Third Man."
Tokyo is just so stylish!
Data viitoare
SHOCHU HIGHBALL
Here's to another night! Cheers!