Hei.
The Faraway Paladin
Unde crezi că te duci?
Unde?
Să omor bestiile demonice.
De unul singur?
Da.
Mă îndoiesc că ai putea ține pasul cu mine.
De asta trebuie să-l protejez.
Nu-ți face griji. Va fi bine.
Mă voi ocupa eu de tot.
Voi omorî himera și întreaga gloată de bestii demonice.
Dacă sunt demoni care le controlează, atunci, îi voi ucide și pe ei.
Șe pare că ăsta e genul de monstru care sunt.
Tu...
Gata cu prostiile!
Revino-ți odată!
Idiotule!
Oh, deci așa vor decurge lucrurile.
Asta e tot ce poți, Meneldor?
La naiba!
Nu-l pot lăsa să mă urmărească.
Presupun că i-aș putea rupe o mână.
Găsește pe cineva să te vindece.
Nu...
Nu am terminat încă!
Oh? Te opui mai mult decât credeam.
Ce ar trebui să fac?
Oare să folosesc Cuvinte ca să-l țin pe loc?
Nu, îl voi strânge de gât și-l voi face să-și piardă cunoștin...
Gnomilor, oh, gnomilor, încleștați-vă pumnii!
Și folosiți-i ca să vă doborâți inamicul!
O incantație inutilă.
Nu! Dacă mă voi feri, vraja îl va lovi pe Menel!
What's this crap about
fixing everything alone?
Ești doar un fricos!
Chiar trebuia să mergi atât de departe?
Ce?
We were only together because
things worked out that way.
Nu ai niciun motiv să faci asta.
Da, așa este.
I have no reason to go out of my way
to stop an emotionally unstable
coward who's completely lost it
just because he got his
ass handed to him once.
În acest caz...
Dar...
Ești prietenul meu.
Iar prietenii rămân împreună.
Dacă prietenul meu o ia razna, trebuie să-l readuc cu picioarele pe pământ.
Menel...
You don't know much about your own origins,
and you're clueless about the world.
There've been times when I
thought you seemed suspicious.
But you're a nice guy.
I know you're trying to do things right,
and doing your best at everything.
You saved my life, you saved that village...
We traveled together, we fought together...
And I enjoyed spending time with you.
I'm grateful to you from the bottom of my
heart for sending off those villagers.
Will, you are my friend,
and I don't abandon my friends.
Well, you still wanna fight?
I surrender.
I'm still weaker than you now,
but just wait.
I'll catch up before you know it.
Menel...
I'll prove to you soon enough
that you're no monster.
Okay.
I'll wait. I'll be waiting for you.
Man, you're a real pain in the ass!
Sorry. I kinda lost control of myself.
Well, it happens—ow!
I'll heal that—
But a surrender's a surrender.
That means I win!
I only surrendered because
you wouldn't give it a rest!
Keep whining!
Wow...
And so we kept exchanging
dumb jokes and laughter.
What a pretty sight. The moon's
congratulating me on my victory.
What? Want me to break your other arm?
It was my first ever argument with a friend,
and I guess I lost.
Oh, you're back, eh?
Welcome back!
Will! Menel!
You jerks! You had me worried!
Sorry, Bee.
Will...
If you don't mind, would you
please tell me what happened?
Sure.
That's an illness of the strong.
The stronger you are,
the harder it hits you.
Depending on the case, it can even kill you.
I'm really sorry for
making all of you worry.
But I'm all right now.
You were just stuck in bed not long ago,
and you were off slugging it out?
We even set a trap for a surprise attack.
That chimera's got no chance!
You said it!
I've got a debt to repay to that bastard.
I won't be humiliated like that again.
You're gonna fight that thing again?
Yeah. We're going for a return match.
I refuse to just get beat
up and leave it at that.
I'll split all three of that
demon beast's heads open.
Chimeras don't occur naturally.
That thing is, without a doubt,
the product of a demonic ritual.
Let's take all of them out at once,
before they can escape.
So soon after it roughed us up that bad?
I can't just give up and leave it like this.
Let's bust 'em up good!
All right, guess we should
round up some help, huh?
It's gonna be a good, fun,
stupid-as-hell adventure!
You'll get one silver coin
for a demon beast's head,
and ten gold coins for the demon boss's!
After that, we spent a few days
getting a force together,
sent out several rounds of scouts,
and made our preparations.
We didn't arrange any special tricks.
We'd just get enough people together,
make preparations ahead,
and face our enemy head-on.
Let's set up our formation and gear here.
Anna and the other priests,
please support us from here.
Right!
When we're all ready, we'll send
our front line to the battle zone!
If we can wipe out all of those,
this whole area's gonna be
a whole lot more peaceful.
Yeah.
Let's wipe them out.
Sometimes you say the wildest
things so casually.
Here they come.
I'll back you up.
Okay. I'm counting on you, Menel.
We'll break through head-on!
By Volt's blade of lightning!
Burn bright, Blaze's flames of courage!
Whirl, send us a tailwind of good fortune!
Grant us the divine protection
of all the virtuous gods!
Shoot!
Sagitta Flammeum!
Flame Arrow
It's war!
Stand ready!
Goddess of flux, repel the
poisons that rain down upon us!
Fortis...
Strong
Vita!
Life
How could I say I'd fix all this alone?
I was never any more than
one factor in this battle.
The battlefield isn't so easy
that just one dose of penetrating
strength is enough!
By the flame of Gracefeel!
According to reports,
the campaign to eliminate the demon
beasts should be starting by now.
I wonder, will these great Wyvern Killers
succeed in a new heroic feat
for the bards to sing about?
Hmph.
The temple has bent over backwards
to facilitate that novice boy.
If he fails to succeed in this,
he will not be worthy of our backing.
By the way, Bishop,
I hear you entrusted your daughter, Anna,
and many other brilliant
priests to the paladin.
Losing valuable talent to the philanthropic
exploits of such a novice
has caused nothing but trouble for me!
What's this?
The abandoned remains of a monastery?
Looks like we're the first ones here.
Be careful. There might be traps.
Omnia...
Everything
Vanitas.
In Vain
Erasus.
Erasure
Hi there.
It was waiting in ambush with Invisibility?
Careful, Will.
This thing's pretty damn smart.
Do you think maybe it's
got some demon in it?
Are you after the High King?
Oh?
You know the High King's seal.
Are you a warrior sent by one of the gods?
That answer... I'm certain now.
Basically, this is like taking
a square on a chess board.
The city of the dead, where
the High King was sealed,
isn't yet under either side's control.
If the demons take control,
they'll undo the seal,
and disaster will ravage
the continent again.
But if the people take control,
the seal will likely become even stronger.
The demons are in a position
where they need to keep Beast Woods
permanently devastated.
They need to keep it in a state of
chaos, destitution, and lawlessness.
That's why they're commanding demon beasts
to attack villages and keep the pressure on.
They can't let mankind
advance any further south.
They can't let people head toward the south.
They can't let them think
there's hope in the south.
If you consider the existence of their king,
it's incredibly easy to figure
out what their objective is.
In the name of the goddess of flux,
I will destroy all of you.
Oh? But wait.
There seems to be some sort of mistake,
or perhaps a misunderstanding.
A misunderstanding, you say?
Yes.
In truth...
Demons like to stick to the classics
in their surprise attacks, don't they?
Menel!
Yep!
Sagitta Flammeum!
Flame Arrow
I'm not takin' that hit!
Sylphs, sylphs, maidens of wind!
Gracefeel, grant us your protection!
Don't stop it!
Divert it!
Gnomes, O gnomes, slip underfoot!
Tighten, bind, and tie it down!
It has multiple heads.
If each one takes a different
reflexive action,
they're sure to end up confused.
This demon beast is unnatural
in terms of living beings!
I don't need to score a clean
victory in one strike.
I just need to fight it the right
way and win by being better.
I don't need a flashy secret technique.
I'll just use all three of their teachings
and do what it takes to win!
That's the fighting style
that's best for me!
Maidens of wind,
bless this arrow with your kiss!
That's one down!
Although I detest this dragon power,
you leave me with no choice!
Dragon?
This one, too?
Menel.
Get back a little farther.
I'll strike it down now.
I was raised on Mary's bread,
and my arms bear Mater's stigma,
so poisons don't work on me.
I'm sure you'd like some
glory of your own, too, huh?
Gnomes, O gnomes, clench your fists!
Use them to strike the enemy!
There's nowhere to run to the left or right!
Then...
Acceleratio!
Accelerate
Gnomes, O gnomes, slip underfoot!
Tighten, bind, and tie it down!
We won!
All right!
On to the next one.
Yep.
Took you long enough.
Reystov?
I'll be taking those ten gold coins.
What?! He beat us to it?!
You're kidding! How'd you do it?!
Came around from the side.
Since you guys were taking
care of the chimera for me,
it was actually pretty easy.
That's Reystov the Penetrator for you.
He's way too good at getting
the jump on people.
You have to be, if you want to
get to the strongest opponents.
Careful! No telling what
kinda traps are in here!
Heh, we're the first ones here!
And those ten gold coins are ours!
Huh?
To our victory!
Episodul 12
Paladinul Ținutul Îndepărtat
Ce părere ai?
I'm happy, but still kinda embarrassed...
I feel like you embellished a bit too much.
This kinda thing is supposed
to be a little embellished!
Hey, someone who gets it!
I'll write a song about you next, Menel!
Huh?
Maybe I'll give you the nickname
"Meneldor the Beautiful"!
The one who walks the hero's path
along with the Faraway Paladin!
Hey, isn't that gonna make people
think I'm actually a woman?
And you can be Will's girlfriend!
Don't you dare!
Aw, it's fine!
It is not!
After his vehement objections,
Menel's nickname was revised
from "Meneldor the Beautiful"
to "Meneldor of Swift Wings."
It's so much more lively now.
And it's gonna get more and
more lively from now on.
I hope so.
What're you talking about?
Of course it will.
The threat of the demons and
demon beasts has faded.
People searching for new lands
are gonna flock to the south.
There'll probably be problems,
too, but that's how it goes.
I guess so.
Also, I'll say this since you'll
find out eventually anyway.
The villagers are building a shrine.
A shrine?
The one they talked about
back at the meeting hall.
They made an altar to hold votive candles,
and they decided to make
it a shrine to Gracefeel.
To the goddess of light?
It's the first step toward
growing her following again!
By the way, what are you gonna do next?
Next?
Well, there's still a lot of clean-up to—
I mean after that.
After that?
Gonna be the lord of a domain?
Huh? A lord? For what domain?
The villages of Beast Woods.
Who is?
You.
Oh, come on!
I am a knight, but a
single-generation one with no land.
I'm no different from an
adventurer, really...
Is that seriously what you think?
Huh?
For real? You didn't even
know what you were?
Huh?
Just so I'm clear here...
If you wanted to do business in this
forest, who would you talk to?
Tonio?
But didn't most of the funds come from you?
Well, yeah, but...
Listen to me!
First of all, you're a paladin with the
goddess of light's divine protection
and the approval of both the
country and the temple.
You have all kinds of power!
On top of that, you have the military
authority to gather all these adventurers,
and by arbitrating for the villages,
you effectively have jurisdiction over them.
So, um, you're saying...
In the process of exterminating the demons,
you took control of the flow
of goods, ruling power,
military force, jurisdiction,
and every other kind of authority.
If you say you don't wanna do all that now,
that would be the disaster.
Are you saying...
you seriously didn't realize it?
You...
I just hoped I could do
something about the demons,
and improve the impoverished conditions
in the villages a little bit...
From there, I just thought I'd make a
slick exit, like Blood and the other two.
Um... Menel?
Wh-What do I do? Should I start
by getting people together?
You've already got a merchant
and priests who know the law.
If you need more,
just have the crown prince
set you up with someone.
Cum naiba am ajuns în această situație?
Spune-mi, te rog,
zeița mea!
Then again...
That does sound like it might
be a goal worth working toward.
It's probably gonna be some
damn hard work, though.
But as long as I have all of you,
I'm sure it'll work out.
Mă vei ajuta, nu-i așa?
Of, fie.
Te voi ajuta.
Mai întâi, trebuie să aflăm ce plănuiesc demonii...
Cui îi pasă?
Just grab the bastards and crush 'em
as soon as you find 'em!
That's so violent...
Hei! Will! Menel!
Nu vă mai ascundeți în micuța voastră lume și veniți aici!
If more people come in and
everything goes well,
maybe we'll be able to return to that city.
Maybe we can make the city of the dead
a regular city where living
people can laugh together.
Up on the hill where
Mary and Blood's graves are,
the laughter of children will resound,
and the sounds of people working
to make a living will return.
Somehow, that seemed like
such a wonderful thing to me.