Stagnate is consumed by
the desire to kill me.
We're on even footing.
If I fight him now...
Nu! Templul!
Accelerare
Acceleratio!
It was all a bluff!
He was pretending to be consumed by rage,
and then he used the cloud of dust...
It's Blood and Mary that he's after!
Trebuie să ajung la timp!
Te rog!
Acceleratio!
Accelerare
Dacă pot crede ceea ce a spus Stagnate,
atunci, poate sunt o persoană cu care el consideră că trebuie să fie precaută.
Dar asta nu înseamnă nimic pentru un zeu al morților vii care poate trăi veșnic.
Prioritatea sa în acest moment e să ajungă la Blood și Mary, iar apoi la Gus.
Acum că am protecția divină a zeiței luminii și mă pot ruga pentru a primi binecuvântarea ei,
îi pot trimite pe cei trei în ciclul morții și renașterii!
La acest lucru e el precaut!
He weighed Blood and Mary's
souls against the risk I posed,
and tried to play the fool...
That's what I was trying
to do in the beginning!
The Faraway Paladin
Mary! Blood!
It's no use. I won't get to him in time.
I borrowed the strength of a goddess
and finally managed to stand
on even footing with him,
but then I fell for a trick like that...
And now it's all over?
I don't remember seeing her before... but...
And then everything was clear to me.
Mary had been forgiven all along.
She never resented Mary at all.
Mary never sought forgiveness,
nor did she expect lenient treatment.
That's why she continued to watch over
her and admonish her as she wished.
And she's kept that up for 200 years,
never revoking her divine blessing,
until Mary could forgive herself.
What mother wouldn't protect
an imperiled daughter
who's devoted her life to worshiping her?
The earth-mother Mater that Mary
reveres is truly a great goddess.
In this moment that Mater has granted me...
Gracefeel, Goddess of Light!
Grant this soul peace and guidance!
The Divine Torch guides souls into
the cycle of death and rebirth,
but it still can't completely
defeat Stagnate.
So what I need to do is...
Wha—
That's right.
Since these two aren't resisting, the Divine
Torch will guide them back to that cycle.
Which means...
You have to protect them!
Delay the cycle!
Flummox the guidance!
And in the moment when he
erases my technique...
Acceleratio!
Accelerare
Vasta—
Devastare
Tacere, Os!
Be Silent, Mouth
You'll start by learning how to use
minor magic skillfully and accurately.
An exhilarating strike like
that is far more Gus's style
than extravagant magic that
would erase his existence!
Curse you...
Curse you!
Will, child of Blood and Mary,
disciple of Gracefeel!
I will remember that name!
Until you surrender to me, your nights
will bring you no rest or repose!
That's the kind of thing a
third-rate villain would say,
God.
I swear on Gracefeel's light
that I will never become like you.
I will live right...
and then die.
Search
Quaerere,
Ambulare Alevita.
Treading Softly
Do Not Let Even a Sigh Escape
Noli Fugito,
Nor Any Sign of Trembling
Etiam Sigillum.
That was way too close.
This Overeater that Blood gave me,
Gus defeating the double of the Echo,
Mary's earth-mother Mater buying me time...
All the things that the three
of them have given me...
The sword, the magic,
and the prayer technique,
and most importantly, the part that's
essentially my core as a person...
If I'd been without any one of them,
I never would've stood a chance.
It's all thanks to the goddess's
divine protection...
and the three of them.
Will...
Will, I'm so glad you're all right.
Mary...
You did great.
Blood...
You may not share blood, but you are
still the child of Blood and Mary.
It's only natural that you
could accomplish this.
Yeah... I did it.
I did it.
I protected them. I'm here
now with the three of them.
Okay, then!
I guess this calls for a party to celebrate
this victory and Will's adulthood.
You're right. I think cleaning up
here can wait until another day.
Well, in that case, we'll have to break
out the you-know-what from 200 years ago.
You mean that stuff from the dwarfs?!
You've been hiding something
like that from us, Old Gus?
Well, it seemed a waste
to let a child drink it.
What is it? Something tasty?
So tasty that even I would love to
drink it, if I had a corporeal body.
Well, you can still fake it,
can't you? We're celebrating!
Yeah! Drink with us, Gus!
Will...
Be careful not to drink too much.
If you repeat what happened last time,
I won't show mercy again.
Y-Yes, ma'am.
That also goes for you, Blood.
S-Sure...
What on earth are you doing?
Anyway, I suppose I should go and get it.
We should go, too.
Yeah.
Huh?
Mary?
Blood?
I guess we can't after all, huh?
Yes, it seems we can't.
But that's how it goes.
We lost our attachment,
denied selling our souls
to the god of the undead,
and insisted we wanted to remain undead.
This couldn't last.
Yeah, that's for sure.
I wish we could be spared just one night,
but I guess that ain't happening.
Gracefeel has been exceedingly easy on us.
Under normal circumstances,
we might have vanished instantly.
What are you guys talking about?
Listen, Will...
This is the end for Mary and me.
Y-You're joking, right?
We're supposed to be celebrating!
That's just mean!
Will...
You are a clever boy.
I'm sure you understand.
Sorry about this.
We are sorry.
Can't anything be done?
No.
Even if something could be
done, we mustn't do it.
It's like you said. You gotta
live right, and then die.
We got lost for a couple of centuries,
but you could just call that a detour.
Besides, parents should always
die before their children.
That's the first rule of nature.
Right...
Yeah. I guess so.
But... I'm going to say something I'm
not supposed to, just this once.
I still don't want to see you two die.
I want to see you again when
I come back here someday.
I want to duel with Blood,
defeat him, and be defeated.
I want us to say silly things to each other.
I want to do chores with Mary,
and hear her say that I've gotten better.
I want you to meet my children
and grandchildren someday,
and I want you to teach
them lots of things, too!
It's just cruel to say
you're going away now!
I don't want you to!
If you two go away, I...
I don't know how I'm supposed to go on...
Don't go...
I can't take it.
Stay here, even if you
have to cheat somehow.
Don't be selfish, now.
Blood is right. Be reasonable.
First time I've felt like a dad in ages.
Will was always a good boy.
Listen, Will. Even if we go away,
humans can live just fine as
long as they eat and sleep.
You'll find something else to hold dear.
When all's said and done,
you'll go on living.
Once you leave here,
you're gonna make lots of friends,
bag yourself two or three pretty girls,
and have all kinds of fun.
Blood! Don't encourage him to be insincere!
Will, you must be sincere
in love and marriage.
Now that you've sworn your oath to the
goddess of light and killed a god,
the path you walk is sure
to be filled with troubles.
You will most likely experience setbacks
and be a target for unjustified criticism.
You may be betrayed by people you help,
your good deeds may be forgotten,
you may lose all that you had gained,
and you may end up with nothing but enemies.
Even so...
love others.
Do good things.
Do not fear loss, build rather than destroy,
forgive sins, offer hope in despair,
and be a source of joy in sad times.
And protect the weak from
violence of all kinds.
Just like the way you challenged
the undead god for our sake.
Okay.
Oh, Will... William...
Blood's and my sweet child...
May the divine protection of the spirits of courage
and the virtuous gods be with you always.
Listen. Move forward with faith
in the results you'll achieve.
Once a person makes up their
mind, they can do anything.
You might get lost in your
own thoughts sometimes,
but don't get so stressed
that you freeze in place.
I engraved the images of them and
the words they said into my heart.
I won't forget them.
Just like the light of the goddess,
I know they'll always light my path.
Uh... Ahem!
Did I get here a bit too soon?
After that, we all celebrated
my victory and my adulthood.
The first drink I had with
all four of us together
left a lasting impression with
its strong burn and rich aroma.
That day, the holy light guided my parents
back into the cycle of death and rebirth.
Yeah.
The view really is the best from right here.
Mary, Blood...
I know you're not here anymore,
but I'll still come back to let
you know how things are going.
If I make friends or start
a family, I'll bring them.
I'll become an adult who
can tell you with pride
that your child is living well.
So, for now, I'll be leaving
you for a little while.
Are you all done?
Yeah.
By the way...
Why didn't you die, too?
How cruel! You would wish
death upon an old man?!
Evil grandchild!
Aw, you're making me sad.
I was just thinking all your treasures
would be mine if you died.
You are an evil grandchild!
The evil grandchild just outed himself!
C'mon, I just meant all the money you have
no use for would finally have a use!
Right, Grandpa?
That is true. Fine, take it.
Huh?
What is all this?!
My treasure.
I'll lend it to you interest-free.
Make it grow, you hear?
Er, b-but... I-I mean...
Stagnant money that never gets
spent might as well be dead.
I don't like stagnant money.
Make good use of it.
Gus...
So this is my last gift from Gus...
Not that I'll be passing on for a
good ten more years, of course.
Huh?
Well, you know, there is still the matter
of guarding the High King's seal.
I made a little deal last
night with your goddess.
She granted me permission to
continue wandering this city
for at least ten more years, until the
god of the undead regains his power.
What?!
I have become something like
Gracefeel's errand boy, it seems.
Th-Then... what about Mary and Blood?
It seems they did not want that.
Giving them another ten years would make
them greedy and reluctant to end it.
If given ten years, they would want
another ten, then another ten,
and then to remain at
least until you pass on.
They knew they would want that,
so they chose to die.
Just like you, who tried to appear strong
when you were crying and
screaming on the inside.
Granting a position that inspires such
greed to just one old man is enough.
You really are so rock 'n roll, Gus.
What will you do with the seal in ten years?
You'll have to figure that out before then.
Huh? You're dumping it on me?!
It seems the worship of Gracefeel has
gone out of style in the world outside.
She used a great deal of strength
just intervening for us.
So the goddess of light's future
depends on your efforts, as well.
I haven't even left, and I keep picking up
more baggage, both physical and mental.
I guess this is one of the hardships
I'm destined to suffer.
In any case, you'll need money.
Take it, take it!
Yeah... It seems like I'm
gonna have a lot to do,
so I'll accept it gratefully.
Well, I'm going now.
Say, Will...
If you're going out into the world,
you'll need a last name to go by.
Those two gave you the name "William,"
so I thought I'd give you a last name.
How about it?
Okay, sure.
Then perhaps I'll hijack a custom used
by certain clans of elves and halflings.
They put their two parents' names
together to form their last names.
Maryblood.
You are William Maryblood.
Maryblood...
Take their names with you.
Thank you, Gus.
I like that name a lot!
Well, take care.
Indeed.
Oh, and I'll add "G" for my middle name!
You fool! You don't need my initial!
What did you learn in
those classes of yours?!
Well, you're Gus, after all!
"Old Man Augustus" is just
too much work to say!
Hmph. What a hopeless grandson you are.
Well, so long, William G. Maryblood!
Goodbye, Gus! I'll see you again sometime!
Hey, fortress general! Doin' good?
It's only natural
for two warriors to introduce themselves
and say a few words before facing off...
But you demons are just so damn boorish.
Being told that by the likes of you
must leave that demon at quite a loss.
What a mean thing to say.
How's it going on your end?
I performed the funeral quite easily
and stopped the transformation to undead.
Looks like Old Gus's group did just fine.
It appears so.
In any case, we've taken down the fortress.
It won't hurt anything for
Old Gus's group to retreat.
The fortress general fell
at the hands of so few.
Any more is just reckless.
Don't praise me. You'll make me blush.
I wasn't praising you.
How many days will destroying the
bridge over the Great Canyon buy us?
A few at most.
We're never gonna get anywhere
unless we take out the High King.
Gus seems to have a plan in mind.
Probably still a one-way street, though.
There won't be any way back.
You're not coming.
That's rather sudden.
I am a valuable asset in
battle, if I do say so myself.
I know. But you're still not coming.
Seeing you die would make me sick.
What?
Couldn't you, at least, add,
"because I love you," to that?
It would be pleasing, primarily to me.
L-Like hell I'm gonna say
something that irritating!
You really are hopeless, you know that?
And what if I refuse to stay behind?
I'll send you back if I have to
knock you unconscious to do it.
I even got Old Gus's permission.
I see. And I suppose it would
be pointless to resist.
Yeah. Your skills aren't bad,
but they're no match for the skills
of the great and peerless Blood.
Then, let's do this.
If you leave me behind,
I will kill myself on the spot.
Y-You—
Did you not hear me?
I said that if I can't go with you,
I will kill myself on the spot.
Now, you will take me along, yes?
Th-That's not fair! In a lot of ways!
You may be the strongest man there is,
but no man can win against a woman.
You're so damn stubborn...
Man, I landed one crazy woman.
We haven't even done anything,
and you call me your woman?
Listen, Mary...
If I make it back alive,
let's find some quiet,
peaceful place to get married.
Okay.
I would love to.
I'd like a quiet house,
maybe up on a hill with a nice view.
That sounds lovely.
I'm sure the breeze would feel nice.
We could even start a vegetable garden.
And if we ever have a kid,
we can ask Old Gus to tutor them.
Despite all that he may say,
I believe he would agree to that.
And if our kid is a boy,
I'll teach him how to fight.
Between that and Old Gus's magic,
he'll be the strongest man around,
even stronger than me!
How's that sound?
I'm terrified that he would turn out
to be a very strong, clever failure.
Harsh!
So I suppose I'll have to
teach him the smaller things.
I'm sure our child will be adorable.
Yeah.
What name should we choose?
I've already got one for a boy.
I hope it's not some weird name.
It's a perfectly good name!
Look, we're talking about our kid.
You know he's gonna have an unbending will.
So we'll call him "William,"
meaning "helmet of will."
Coiful determinării
Episodul 5
William... That's a fine name.
I like it, as well.
Will... My little boy.
Episodul 6
Arcașul din Pădurile Bestiilor