Nu arată prea bine.
Au luat toate animalele
și au distrus multe unelte care nu pot fi înlocuite.
Va trebui să mergem în Pânzele Albe ca să cumpărăm.
Cu ce bani?
Ei bine, nu vom putea înlocui totul.
Hei... ce sunt Pânzele Albe?
Serios, cine naiba ești tu?
Ai putea fi mai neștiutor de atât?
Scuze.
Deci... Pânzele Albe este...
Oh, ei bine... dacă mi-ai putea spune mai multe și despre istoria acestui loc...
Da, bine.
Știi că acesta e continentul sudic, izolat cunoscut ca Semnul Sudului, nu?
Da, știu asta.
Deci, cam acum... două sute de ani a fost?
Semnul Sudului a fost înghițit de o hoardă de demoni.
Grupul celor o sută de eroi l-a învins pe regele demonilor,
dar oamenii au abandonat acest continent,
trecând marea ca să se retragă în Ținutului Ierbii, aflat în nord.
Grupul celor o sută de eroi... Se referă la Blood și prietenii lui.
De când Regatul Fertil a unificat regiunea sud-vestică a Ținutului Ierbii,
au cultivat pământurile cu intențiale de a le recupera.
Iar Pânzele Albe e orașul port care a devenit centrul imigrărilor spre nord.
Înțeleg.
Mulți oameni cu istorie și sperând să devină eroi, merg acolo.
Și oameni care au avut parte de revelații divine.
Speri și să aduni mai mulți credincioși în această călătorie, nu?
Gracefeel obișnuia sa aibă mulți credincioși pe continentul sudic.
Mi-ai putea spune mai multe?
Cred că adepții ei au fost împrăștiați în timpul Măreței Prăbușiri...
Da, așa este.
Iar cei care au reușit să scape spre Ținutul Ierbii i-au păstrat numele viu.
Dar adepții ei tot au scăzut mult.
Demoni și bestii demonice scăpate de sub control,
sate care recurg la furturi
și credința tot mai mică a oamenilor în zeița mea...
Was doing something about all this
the mission the goddess gave me?
Oricum, de ajuns cu legendele vechi.
Trebuie să repunem satul pe picioare, mai întâi.
Da, în legătură cu asta...
Oamenii acestui sat nu au niciun ban.
Menel, vrei să explorăm niște ruine?
Vom împărți tot ce găsim în mod egal.
Ce?
The Faraway Paladin
Nu aș fi ghicit niciodată că ești bun la cotrobăit prin ruine!
Sunt obișnuit cu ele.
Serios, cine naiba ești tu?
Totuși, am reușit să facem rost de destui bani ca să reconstruim satul.
Putem chiar să cumpărăm alte animale și unelte noi.
I made up for my own expenses, too.
Abia asțept să mergem în oraș.
When we do, the first thing
we gotta do is eat.
The seafood in season right now is—
Cineva!
Ajutor!
O maimuță uriașă!
Hei! Ce tot faci?!
The two running from it are a
halfling and... is that a hawker?
Aruncă aia odată!
Dar...
No ifs, ands, or buts!
Oh, for crying out loud! Over here, you!
Vino aici!
Ce?
Cine ești?
Stai, e periculos!
Blood mi-a spus că
atunci când înfrunți un animal sălbatic,
ai pierdut imediat cum ai rupt contactul vizual.
Ei bine, haide, atacă-mă.
Ne putem tăvăli puțin.
Ce ușurare. Nu a trebuit să mă lupt cu ea.
Ești bine?
Hei, cine naiba ești tu?! Un aventurier?!
Nu mulți oameni pot opri o maimuță uriașă, agitată doar uitându-se la ea!
Ești incredibil! Incredibil!
Oh! Numele meu e Robina! Robina Om-bun!
Sunt un trubadur! Cânt, dansez și merg oriunde mă poartă vântul!
Îmi poți spune Bee!
Iar ciudatul de acolo e negustorul ambulant Antonio.
Eu îi spun Tonio!
Compania pentru care lucra a dat faliment,
deci acum se dă drept negustor ambulant pe drumurile de țară mai izolate!
Nici măcar nu am avut ocazia să spun ceva.
I'm on my way back to
Whitesails, my home base.
Pânzele Albe?
Vai, chiar ne-ai salvat pieile acolo.
Îți mulțumim.
Eu sunt Meneldor. Vânez prin zonă.
We were just heading toward the
town to do some shopping.
And that's...
William. William G. Maryblood.
I'm a priest in service to Gracefeel,
the goddess of light.
You can call me Will.
Wow, that's a totally noble-sounding name!
And Gracefeel's the one they love
in the southern continent, right?
Wow, wow! I didn't know
she still had priests!
And you're not just a priest, but a
capable warrior priest! Aren't you?
Aren't you?! Aren't you?!
Yeah, he may look pretty spacey,
but he's stupidly skilled.
I mean, I hardly ever get attacked by
any beasts when I'm walking with him.
You mean the beasts know how
strong he is and avoid him?!
What the heck?! That's so cool!
What? You usually see more?
Of course.
That's why this place
is called Beast Woods.
It feels like their eyes
are piercing me...
Anyway, is it just the two of you?
No escort? Or were they killed?
Actually, when we ran into
that giant ape back there...
I'm embarrassed to say that they ran away.
Some guys who were there for show conned
you out of their up-front pay and bolted?
You gotta get some better
judgment, peddler.
I'm so ashamed...
And they made a big ol' racket
when they ran! It was nuts!
Giant apes don't even attack people,
usually. They just look scary!
They both lost their guards?
What are you going to do now?
We could take you with us, if you want.
We'll just say you owe us one.
I'll do the deal-making, not you.
Owe you one... of what?
We want to buy some cows and
horses and such in Whitesails.
Ah, I get it.
If that's what you want, I'm glad to help.
I'll introduce you to a dealer I know.
We appreciate it. And sorry for butting in.
He doesn't know much about how
the world works, you see.
Oh, so he really was born a noble?
He has that air about him!
Like he's pure and untainted!
N-Nah...
If I told you about my origins,
I doubt you'd even believe me...
You mean you're of such noble birth that
you can't talk about your family?!
And a priest to an unsung god, no less!
Wow, that's fantastic! Fantastic!
My bardic heart is filling
with inspiration!
R-Right...
Wait... No matter what I say,
it leads to misunderstandings...
What?
Okay, that's settled. Let's get moving.
Yeah! Let's go, let's go!
Oh, this place looks perfect!
Whee! Here I am!
Bee and Tonio warmed up to me quickly.
Tonio has a gentle demeanor, and he's
good at getting close to others.
As for Bee, she doesn't seem to have
any concept of distance from people.
Okay, I guess it's time
to give you all a song!
Will, clap along for me,
and collect any donations!
Sure. You can count on me, Bee.
Listen now to these notes of gold...
It's amazing.
Every time we walk into a village,
she goes wild and gets everyone in on it.
She's always like that.
I'm impressed she doesn't get tired.
I see.
Then these items here should
fulfill your needs.
They make a good combination
for doing business.
Huh?
A lot of hawkers use high-pressure
tactics or even petty thievery.
She's hurt?
Let's see if I can get the
priest to take a look at it.
I see...
Looks like he wasn't lying
about working for a company.
Hey, Will...
there's something I'd like to ask you.
What is it?
Can the blessing you invoke
heal sickness and injury?
Yes, it can.
I see. Then I have a proposal for you.
Goddess of Light...
You're all better now.
U-Um... How much do I owe you?
Oh, don't worry about that.
You can offer your gratitude to Gracefeel.
And if Tonio has anything you like,
please buy something from him.
I'm still just in training.
Okay! Thank you so much!
We'll get something to
celebrate your recovery.
How about this hair ornament?
So Bee attracts people, Will offers
healing, and both bring him business.
That Tonio's pretty smart.
Yeah. And it'll help with the return
of the goddess of light, too.
That power of yours is pretty
damn impressive, though.
Well, the blessing is a rewrite of
reality through the power of a god.
That's how it can heal a wound
as if it had never happened.
Huh...
I'm borrowing this power from the goddess.
I have to be careful not to
mistake it for my own power.
Wh-What?
Still in training, huh?
Er... I really am still training.
Will!
Done with your free treatments?
Oh, yeah.
Then come with me!
Huh? What for?
There's a party to celebrate
everyone's recovery!
Right now?!
If they're at the party,
she can sing again,
and he can sell more goods.
He really is a good salesman.
We continued to pass through several
villages, earning money in the same way,
as we made our way north
for a couple of weeks.
Then we emerged onto Wheat Road.
Let's sleep over there tonight.
Man, you guys went too
crazy. It's already dark.
Sorry about that.
I'm in a good mood today!
I'll give you a free performance!
Wow, how generous of you.
Hee hee! Now, what should I sing, I wonder?
"Reystov the Penetrator" is
too common these days...
I know! How about the epic of the Three Heroes from The Killing of the High King,
The Wandering Sage, The War Ogre,
and The Beloved Daughter of Mater?
Ah, that sounds great.
It's a fitting subject.
I guess I haven't performed it for a while.
Hey, what's wrong, Will?
Oh, it's nothing.
Go ahead and sing it. I'd love to hear it.
Oh, I like that! You latched right on!
Okay, let's get started!
Time passes by... no, perhaps
it is us who pass by.
Be it the strong warrior, the brilliant sage,
or the holy woman,
with the turning of the moons, naught but
their ashes and their names remain.
Their names really are remembered...
This is precisely why their
song must be lifted up high,
with a prayer that their
deeds live forever,
that their heroic names resound
throughout the world.
I sing this night of the Wyvern Killer,
one of the many heroic exploits
of the Three Heroes.
Episode 8
Songs of Heroism
Keep quiet, now, and listen, all of you...
The demonblade forged by the stars...
Jeez, Blood...
You never talked about yourself at all.
So this is what you did in your past.
Casting aside any praise
He kept his true name
concealed to the world
Though time has passed,
his name is yet unknown
So I guess no one knows
Augustus's real name...
She was as beautiful as a
princess from a faraway land
When asked about her lineage,
the healer would just gently smile
Mary's refined manner definitely gave
the impression of noble origins,
but I'd believe it if someone told me
she came from a poor village, too.
These days are now long in the past.
O countless wishes now
left with no way home,
I can but play your melody loudly,
to be carried on the passing winds.
The story takes place before
they were known as heroes,
when the three of them
were traveling together.
A certain remote village that they visited
was attacked by a wyvern,
and a beautiful half-elf was chosen
as a sacrifice to appease it.
Upon hearing of this,
Mary said they should save her,
but Blood asked where they
could possibly get the money,
and Gus said nothing.
Their personalities in the
song are a bit off, I think.
But still, it brings their voices, words,
and expressions clearly to my mind.
Who are you?
You think we're gonna take
on a wyvern for that?
Ah, what fine money. Look how it shines.
If we're given such fine payment...
Then we have no choice but to do the job.
Damn, you're such pushovers.
There's no profit in this.
If it's not enough, I'll pay more!
Sell me to a slave trader
or whatever you want!
You think even that would be enough?
But you do have some guts on ya.
You're small, but you're a warrior.
It's only right to help a warrior who
swallows his pride to ask for help.
Let's do it.
Yes.
Indeed.
Ligatur!
Be Tied
Nodus!
Knot
Obligatio!
Binding
So what're you gonna do now?
Neither of you can stay
in that village anymore.
We'll figure it out.
Then take this with you.
Old Gus here carved Words on it.
It'll serve you better than
some cheap good luck charm.
You can't be a warrior if you don't
have at least one dagger, after all.
Take this, as well.
Take care of yourselves, and of each other.
You will face many difficulties,
but never forget the value of perseverance.
This is more than what I paid you!
We can't accept this.
Hah! Who said we were giving it to you?
It's an investment.
We're only lending it to you.
Lending?
Listen.
You two must live the best you can,
build up savings, and make
names for yourselves.
If your names someday reach our ears,
we will come to collect what
we've lent you, plus interest.
In preparation, I will
give you my real name.
This will be our password. Listen well.
Thus the boy and girl learned the
true name of the Wandering Sage,
known to no one else in the world.
Hand in hand, the boy and girl
made their way to the city,
and the Three Heroes walked down the
road in search of a new adventure.
That's the end of the song,
but there's more to the story.
Count Dagger of the Fertile Kingdom...
His actual surname was Wizardsdagger.
To this day, an elderly half-elf
woman still waits at his mansion.
Does that mean...
She believes someone who knows the sage's
true name will come to her one day,
so that she can return what he lent to her,
along with what he lent to her husband.
She plans to offer her thanks
to him when that day comes.
That's what the story is about...
A story of three great heroes
that still echoes to this day.
Huh? Will, are you crying?
N-No, I'm not. I'm not crying.
Aw, c'mon, now!
You must've been really
moved by Bee's story, huh?
No, it's not that!
Aw, don't be shy!
There are still many people in this
world who remember you three.
There always were.
That makes me so happy.
The Fertile Kingdom, huh?
Once we cross the sea, we'll meet people who
still talk about Blood and the others.
Hi there.
You're working hard.
Tonio.
Will, you are strong.
You think so?
I can clearly see how polished
your movements are.
Then again, maybe you don't
want to hear that from a guy
who got conned by phony adventurers...
But you're obviously used to
handling that fine dwarven spear.
Anyone who can wield a dwarven masterpiece
is a masterpiece themselves.
But there's one thing I don't understand.
Something you don't understand?
What is it that you want?
What do I... Why do you ask?
Because I'm a merchant.
It's my job to move merchandise
and grant people's wishes
in exchange for fair compensation.
You are quite a mystery.
I've never met anyone like you before.
You are strong, and you have courage.
You have good manners, you are educated,
and you aren't hurting for money.
But you're not quite like a noble.
You're more like a holy knight
I've heard stories about.
Which is why I decided to ask you directly.
What is it that you,
as an individual, wish for?
Or are you strictly a representative
for your goddess?
Um... I...
I had a happy little life up until now,
but I lost it shortly before
I set out on my own.
I gained the divine protection of
the goddess of light in its place.
I still don't know anything
about this world.
So I want to start by learning about it.
I think that, among the things I learn,
I'll find what it is I want.
Oh... and friends.
I also want companions, I guess.
Is Menel not your friend?
Well, actually...
I think we get along fairly well,
but he won't acknowledge me as a friend.
He just calls me "priest,"
like he's putting me on a pedestal.
Yeah... I want friends.
I see.
Then perhaps I'll volunteer for
the third-place position.
Huh?
Menel and Robina would be angry
if I tried to get ahead of them.
That would be scary.
Well, shall we get some water
and start preparing breakfast?
Okay.
Here you go.
It's so good!
It really is. You're a great cook, Tonio.
He sure is!
To tell you the truth,
that's why I travel with him!
We're eating a lot better
now, thanks to Tonio.
Yeah, since you can't cook worth a lick.
Well, I...
Your cooking isn't so hot either, Menel!
What? All you gotta do is eat it.
And we always get bread
from Will at lunchtime.
Isn't that so cool?
He prays, and bread appears!
I'd prefer to stop as little as possible,
so I'm grateful to have
food I can eat as I walk.
Then let's get ready to leave
as soon as we're done eating.
Yeah.
You ask when we will return home,
but there is no way to know
when we will return.
By the way, what's going
on at Whitesails now?
As the rain falls, the water
in the lake stagnates,
and the two fall silent.
I've been holing up in
Beast Woods for a while,
As the rain pounds, someday,
someday... ah, someday...
so I haven't been to the port in ages.
A new ruler has taken over
the Fertile Kingdom.
the two will draw closer together.
So Egbert II is...
His posthumous name is "Egbert the Bold."
He wasn't a half-bad king.
I see... So he's dead...
Yes... but there's a bit of a problem.
His legitimate heir,
Prince Owen, succeeded him,
but he falls short of his father,
and the lords have suggested that
now is the time to advance south.
That sounds bad...
Fortunately, this hasn't had any
great effect on Southmark yet.
The king's brother, who was dispatched
to Whitesails, is a great, wise man.
The crown prince, Ethelbald Rex Fertile.
He comes from a different
mother than King Owen,
but he excels with both the pen
and the sword, like his father.
It is due to Prince Ethel's rule
that the government of
Whitesails continues to run.
Pare o situație complicată...
Will!
Haide, pe aici!
Ce mai e acum?
E prima oară când îl vezi, nu?
Privește, acolo!
Orașul...
Unul din simbolurile pentru care Blood, Mary și Gus și-au dat viața ca să-l protejeze.
Acela e orașul Pânzele Albe!
Episodul 9
Pânzele Albe