The Faraway Paladin
I must also consider the
option of killing you.
How frightening.
And how would you have me die?
I will say you were poisoned in
the battle with the wyvern,
and that treatment came too late
when you started to spit up blood.
I understand what he's saying.
A hero who can't even prove his identity
is asking him for forces to operate
in a region he doesn't even govern.
Of course he'd see it as dangerous.
I can handle those two, but there's
still the risk of projectile weapons,
and the prince is pretty skilled himself.
No, it's pointless to think about it.
In any case, I have to get
through this somehow.
I need to speak from the heart
and plead my case earnestly.
Your Highness...
What?
If all saltiness were to
disappear from the world,
what would give salt its salty flavor?
If all those who carry a flame
live only in the sunlight,
upon what do they shine their flames?
I have received a part of that flame
from Gracefeel, the goddess of light.
I believe the ones who carry that flame
are the ones who should march
first into the darkness.
They must shine the light upon
those who lament in darkness,
and light the path for
those who follow behind.
So please, I beg of you.
Can you somehow grant permission
for this undertaking of mine?
William, this path will
only lead to despair.
It won't work, and even if it does,
you will pay the price.
I have business with that
despair you speak of.
Oh? How so?
I don't like its face, so I want
to kick it as hard as I can.
Kick it in the face? I like that!
Come to think of it, you are
a high priest, aren't you?
And you have quite a good friend, too.
What, you didn't notice?
When I said I was going to kill you,
that half-elf there gave me
quite the murderous glare.
Wh-What're you talkin' about?
I was just steeling myself 'cause
I figured you'd kill me, too.
Damn it, don't look so happy!
Bishop, please stop!
His Highness is with a guest at the moment!
Please wait, Father!
Stay out of my way!
You damned fools!
Prince Ethelbald, do not act irrationally!
Oh? Whatever do you mean, Bishop Bagley?
Do not play dumb with me!
This young man is registered
with my temple!
Though it may be temporary,
he is a member of the temple!
And you beckon him here
without a word to me?
Do you mean to disregard
the temple's authority?!
Oh, I had no idea.
Is this true?
Uh, yes.
Ignorance is no excuse!
You cannot forego verification
protocol simply because I was away!
So you say, but the people from your
temple seemed happy to send him to me.
Hmph! A total lack of discipline!
I will give them a stern talking-to later!
In any case, he—
The thing is, Bishop Bagley...
He is not what you think he is.
Huh?
He came here asking me to
assemble a private army.
Says he wants to save the
poor people of Beast Woods.
What?!
Y-You—
I would be lying if I said it never
crossed my mind to kill him right here.
But he's just so frank.
Somehow, I started to
find it quite amusing.
Which is why...
I'm thinking of appointing him as a knight.
Would your temple give him its blessing?
You know, a paladin.
The temple and I will share the
responsibility and the profits equally.
What do you say?
What?!
He would, of course,
fall under our joint authority.
If it comes to it, you could always
have him excommunicated.
Th-Th-That is not the issue here!
The temple can attest to his character,
and as the Wyvern Killer, he should
have no problems with the rest.
This is proceeding too quickly!
I will return to the temple and think it over!
Is that acceptable?!
Yes.
But it would make me truly happy
to see this happen, Bagley.
I've taken a liking to this young man.
Assuming I do become his patron,
spare me your silly games!
You, novice boy! We're leaving!
R-Right.
Honestly, what a troublemaker.
Demanding a private army?
What were you thinking?
What's that old geezer's deal?
Uh, Menel, he's...
Especially you, novice!
How dare you go and take matters
into your own hands?!
So what if we did?
It's not like you're our boss or anything.
Excuse me?!
I am the head of the temple,
in case you forgot!
So what? You wanna fight over it?
How dare you speak to me
that way?! Insolence!
I'm sorry.
My father has struggled with many unresolved
issues of late, and it has him on edge.
And I'm saying it ain't your business.
We don't work for you.
No, I apologize for my friend's behavior.
Excuse me?!
Just so you know...
Just so you know, you
two came to my temple!
Anyway, um... So you're
Bishop Bagley's daughter?
I'm saying—
I'm saying, don't create problems for me!
Yes, though not by blood.
Look, first of all—
First of all, you—
He was once in charge of a temple in the
capital that had a large orphanage.
Will you quit cutting me off?!
I'm still talking!
What?! You—
And stop talking down to me!
Who do you think you are?!
Ah, I see.
When His Highness Ethelbald asked
my father to relocate here,
I am—
The head of the temple, right?
I'm telling you,
that's got nothing to do with us!
I came to this continent along
with a dozen or so others.
If you—
Ugh, I can't deal with this!
So that's what happened.
Don't you interrupt me! I'm still speaking!
He's in a position where he
can throw his weight around,
What?!
Have you no respect for your superiors?!
he has connections everywhere,
and he has loyal subordinates.
And I keep telling you, that's got
nothing to do with anything!
Bishop Bagley.
Thank you for your help.
Your intervention with the
crown prince saved us.
Hmph! I did nothing to
warrant your gratitude!
I only defended the temple's authority
from the crown prince's selfishness.
You only happened to be a part of that.
Besides, when he becomes
amused by something,
he has a habit of doing unthinkable things.
It's truly a problem.
But be that as it may,
I must respect his worldly authority.
I will be taking his proposal
into consideration.
You will remain in the chapel
after the evening prayer.
All right, I understand.
Oh, but... um...
What?
What is the "evening prayer"?
You absolute fool!
You know the prayer by the names
"vespers" and "compline"?
Those holy practices were
revised 200 years ago.
Did you serve your apprenticeship
under one of such a long-lived race?
Uh... Yes, you could say that.
Hah! So you aren't entirely ignorant, then.
Anna, fetch some books on the
revisions to the liturgy,
and find a suitable teacher
for him, as well.
Yes, Father.
This boy is a novice,
and on top of that, an ancient who's
come here from 200 years in the past.
He'll take a lot of work.
Greetings, Bishop.
Wait here a moment.
Of course.
His praying form looks almost
frighteningly masterful.
Other than Mary,
I've never seen such an expert.
Now, then...
Um...
What?
As head of the temple,
you have most certainly earned a high
level of divine protection, yes?
Equal to my own, if not even higher.
The people of the temple told me
that you don't use the blessing.
And when you pray, either you
don't let anyone watch,
or you don't apply yourself
fully when others are present.
Why is that?
Hah! Foolish novice!
What do you think the blessing is?
Divine protection bestowed by a god.
Then why did a god bestow
divine protection upon you?
To give you special treatment?
Not so, correct?
To act through you.
Understand? The god wishes to
achieve something through you.
And in order to live up
to the gods' ideals,
we must constantly be in thought
about how to use the blessing.
To use it as a tool for one's own convenience
does not contribute to the gods' glory.
It only detracts from it.
Most of those dimwits fail
to understand that,
which is why they will one
day lose the blessing.
I am the head of the temple.
This land is wild, and development
on it has barely begun.
To secure funding and rights,
I must yell and intimidate.
To lay the groundwork,
I must do favors and use bribery.
If I were to use such a high
blessing in these circumstances,
the people would question why a man
like me received divine protection.
Now, youngster,
do you think this would contribute
to the glory of Volt, my guardian deity?
No.
Precisely.
The correct course of action for blessings
and prayers is to store them inside.
I have entrusted the vice bishop with the
glorification of the gods through blessings.
He is a very capable man,
skilled at winning the hearts of the
people to the extent it is needed.
I can trust him with the bothersome,
stressful role of being the face of the temple.
Bishop Bagley really is talented.
He's rude, and he looks like a greedy
monk who's always complaining,
but he's an amazing man.
And what about you?
Making a youngster who has yet to fully
comprehend what the blessing is into a paladin?
The crown prince does so love his jokes!
Listen.
Don't do it. Nothing good will come
of a novice attempting this.
I'll go to him and refuse
for you, if you want.
Even the crown prince will surely
give up if I give a firm rejection.
What say you?
Regardless, my goddess still wishes
to achieve something through me.
You will not change your mind?
I will not.
You are a fool.
I agree.
What did you swear to the goddess of flux?
To offer her my life, banish evil,
and save the suffering.
Rejoice!
You are the most dimwitted of all
the dimwits I have seen here!
I will send a few with you.
The rest is up to you.
Thank you.
I should respect this man,
no matter what anyone else says.
Let's go!
Welcome!
You're really putting those
drinks away, mister!
Don't go for people who use
adventuring as a job.
Find people who seek adventure, for
the glory and prestige of it.
Yeah. We need real ruffians
who'll put their lives
on the line for battle and adventure.
Right, just like Blood.
Demon beast horns... and demon beast hide?
Those are their battle spoils.
It's the easiest way to
show off their strength.
C'mon, let's go.
A chestnut-haired boy with a
silver-haired elf-mix buddy...
There's no doubt.
He's been through a whole lot of training.
Hey, what's the famous Wyvern Killer
doin' in some pub in the middle of nowhere?
I'm looking for help.
Exploring Beast Woods?
Low pay... Your reward is glory and praise,
and there's no guarantee you'll survive?!
We're doin' this for a living, y'know!
We're not takin' a quest
like this! Right, guys?
Yeah! Don't be so stingy!
Shut up, you blowhards.
When you see a swordsman,
look at his fingers.
You can tell by looking at his hands
whether he'll allow any thoughts
that prevent him from drawing his weapon.
Looks to me like what you want
is a madman. Am I right?
Not a bunch of blowhards with
good manners but no skills,
who've picked up the etiquette
and patience to do any job,
but a bunch of shitheads who
know no fear or manners.
The worst kind of scumball adventurers
who'll risk their lives for
the dumbest ideals, right?
That's why we've come here.
Hey, you hear that? Just like I said!
Tch! Bunch of damn lunatics!
You oughta buy our drinks for a change!
Yeah, that's right!
What're you hoping to get out
of exploring Beast Woods?
Where we goin'? Ruins? Outdoors?
We don't bother with small fry!
The demon boss.
The leader of the demons running rampant
in the western part of Beast Woods,
whose subordinate demons are
thought to command demon beasts.
That's a big fish.
Yes.
The location is unclear.
Just finding him will be hell.
We're talkin' instant death if
we're ambushed during the search.
Most likely.
In other words,
this is gonna be a nice, fun,
stupid little jaunt.
Let me in on it.
All I need is food and a bed.
Even better if I make a
little pocket change.
Me, too!
And me!
Leave it to us!
I'm in!
Of course, I'll have those for you!
I'm William G. Maryblood.
I'm Reystov.
Whence cometh this disciple
to the lost goddess of
flux, goddess of light?
The Disciple of the Light, the Wyvern Killer,
the Peerless Powerhouse...
It's almost time for the ceremony.
I heard they wanted to make this a
happy event to give work to people
The Faraway Paladin, William G. Maryblood.
who lost their homes and jobs
in the wyvern attack, but...
Know the name of the new hero who has
appeared in the city of white sails!
Hmm... I guess that should do it.
Bee, could you not write an epic
about me right in front of me?
What? Why not?!
You actually did do all that.
What did you expect?
Look forward to hearing it!
I'm gonna make it awesome!
Hmm...
This many cows and horses will
indeed come at a hefty price.
Oh, about that...
Can you negotiate to get us the sick
and injured ones at a lower price?
What?
And then I'll heal all of them.
Oh... That makes sense.
Also, it would be a big help
if you could start trade
between Beast Woods and Whitesails.
Hmm...
How much do you need me to
give you to fund that?
Will, why don't you and I
have a serious business chat?
Now, then...
G-Go easy on me...
I say go for it.
You need to have a good understanding
of how money works.
Right.
You're gonna be negotiating with
Reystov and those other guys next.
Reystov?!
Reystov the Penetrator is here?!
Y-Yes, he is...
That's perfect! Let me interview him!
Huh?
Making a habit of flaunting your own
accomplishments leads to arrogance.
And arrogance dulls one's blade?
Exactly.
That again?!
This is why you're so useless!
I can't get any good ideas out of you!
So you two know each other?
We've talked a few times.
No matter how many times I interview
you, it's always the same!
I thought it'd be different this time!
You're just a stubborn, broody guy!
The answers don't change,
no matter how many times you ask.
All of your tales of heroism
are so ambiguous!
I was gonna make something that came
a little closer to the truth!
I can't believe how mean you're being!
Isn't reputation important
to an adventurer?!
Whether it's to make a living
or get ahead in life!
As long as you've got skills,
those things come naturally.
I know you realize that even people with
skills can be ruined by a bad reputation!
Even a warrior never knows what's
going to be his downfall!
Don't you agree, Will?
Uh...
A lot of Reystov's tales
of heroism are ambiguous?
Yeah, exactly!
This guy will accept a job
to take down a huge threat,
then he just wanders off, kills it with
one fatal stab, and wanders back!
He hardly ever works with anyone else,
and he works so fast, hardly anyone
knows what actually happened!
And he takes such a broad range of jobs!
So the stories end up more
and more embellished?
Yep!
I try to interview people, but all they
do is fill in the gaps however they can!
I do embellish them a little bit,
but I like to add a little
more truth to my tales!
No need.
That's what I'm talking about!
If only I had a little more to work with...
I know!
How about the Penetrator
versus the Paladin?
Huh?! That sorta came out of nowhere...
You're putting Reystov on
the spot, too! Right?
If I receive a challenge from a
strong opponent, I have no choice.
Reystov?!
See?! You heard him!
Well, maybe when we're
done in Beast Woods...
Yay!
That's a promise!
This is great!
I'll make this into a song that'll be sung for
centuries, millennia—until the end of time!
I, Prince Southmark,
Ethelbald Rex Southmark,
hereby declare you a knight.
May you become the protector of
your temple, of those in need,
and of all those who
believe in the virtuous gods,
who defy the evil gods and their violence.
You who strive to become a knight...
Uphold the teachings of the virtuous gods,
and protect all who suffer along
with all who work through prayer.
I pray to my guardian deity,
Enlight, the god of knowledge,
to serve as the intermediary to
this young man's guardian deity.
May Gracefeel, the goddess of light, forever shower this young man with her grace.
Uphold your oath steadfastly, honor the
teachings, and protect the weak.
Be the light of the world!
We celebrate the birth of a new knight!
Episode 10
Renowned Glory
Bring light to the farthest
reaches of the earth!
Long live the paladin!
Vice Bishop.
Thank you for blessing me.
Think nothing of it.
It was an honor to receive such an
important duty from the bishop.
Ordinarily, this would be his job, but...
I asked him, and he said he finds it
bothersome to show people his pious side.
It's too bad.
I agree.
For a man of his caliber to be
so unknown to the public...
So this is where you were!
We're having grappling matches over there!
Come join us for a round!
Uh, okay...
Come with us, Menel!
No way.
Hey, it's the paladin's servant!
Not my servant. He's my friend.
I'm not your friend!
Huh?!
Will!
We're making a fortune!
And it's all thanks to your song!
Goddess, are you watching?
I'm getting by somehow.
And I'll continue to.
And that's how I became
the Faraway Paladin.
Episode 11
Valley of Despair