Pe aici.
Putem trece pe aici?
Vom campa aici astă-seară.
Green ones, grant me shelter for the night:
a bed of grass, a roof of trees,
and tolerance for an unannounced guest.
Uimitor!
Nu e mare lucru.
Hei, am făcut ceva greșit?
Nu am fost crescut în cele mai bune circumstanțe.
I don't deal well with people who
were brought up as well as you.
Dar îmi voi plăti datoria față de tine și îmi voi face treaba.
I wasn't brought up that well.
Vom ajunge în sat în zori.
Ține minte, doar te duc acolo.
Nu te voi ajuta să lupți cu demonii sau ceva.
Știu. E în regulă.
Nu ar trebui să stea cineva de pază?
Zânele o vor face.
Vor face zgomot ca să ne trezească dacă se va întâmpla ceva.
Hei, de ce nu stăm puțin de vorbă?
Sunt obosit.
Dacă vrei să stai treaz, fă-o singur.
Oare cât timp a trecut de când am pornit în călătoria mea?
Asta e prima noapte pe care o petrec cu cineva de când am plecat.
Paladinul ținutului îndepărtat
Ruine?
Obișnuiau să fie.
Pietrele și celelalte lucruri sunt destul de utile la construcții.
Satul e drept înainte.
Sunt acolo.
Da.
Voi cerceta zona. Așteaptă aici.
Un ritual?
Da, la ruinele templului din sat.
Acei demoni nenorociți...
Care e structura templului și cum sunt organizați demonii?
Cam așa ceva.
Nu are acoperiș, iar câteva dintre ziduri s-au prăbușit.
Au creat un cerc în mijlocul templului ca să-și facă ritualul.
Sunt doi comandanți.
Au capete de șopârlă. Am uitat cum erau numiți...
Vraskus?
Da, ceva de genul.
Altceva?
Au câțiva soldați care patrulează împrejurul templului.
Și mai știu că este cel puțin o bestie demon înăuntru.
Cum arată bestia demon?
Are cap de om, corp de leu
și aripi de liliac.
O manticoră.
Știi multe despre chestiile astea, nu?
Le-am studiat o vreme.
Dar...
Mă bucur că e doar atât.
Că e doar atât?
Voi merge peste ei și-i voi elimina.
Cadere Araneum!
Cazi, pânză de păianjen
Currere!
Alergare
Oleum!
Ulei
Acceleratio!
Accelerare
Vastare!
Devastare
Credeam că nu intenționezi să lupți.
M-am băgat doar pentru că tu urma să ieși învingător.
Nu mulți oameni se pot pune cu chestiile alea de unii singuri și să iasă învingători.
Condițiile erau în favoarea mea.
Oricum ar fi, puterea ta e anormal.
Do you do some special
training or something?
Uh... I eat a lot of bread, I guess.
Humans don't get stronger just from that.
Well, anyway, I think we took care
of the bulk of their forces.
I guess all that's left is to
clean up any surviving demons.
I hope some of the villagers survived.
Yeah.
Oh, hang on a second.
Bro...ther...
Brother Menel...
The demons... attacked the village.
It was so hot...
But I stayed strong and
didn't make any noise.
Because... I had faith...
that you would come...
And you really did.
Thank you.
What... Why?
Huh? I...
H-Hey!
You did very well.
Good job.
Who are you?
I'm a friend of Brother Menel's.
I'm sorry.
He's a bit unsteady on his
feet because he's very tired.
Oh, okay.
That's it. Good boy.
Here...
Menel.
Sorry I showed up a little late.
No, it's okay.
You must be tired. Go to sleep.
You're... right.
I feel... kind of sleepy...
Dream happy dreams.
Okay.
Gracefeel, Goddess of Light,
grant him peace and guidance.
Hey...
What?
Sorry.
For what?
I didn't take you seriously.
I thought you were some rich
boy with money and muscles
who happened to earn a god's
divine protection and got cocky,
spouting nothing but useless platitudes.
So... I'm sorry.
I don't mind.
There was still a markedly
pained look on his face,
but still, Menel smiled just a little bit.
He didn't hesitate any more after that.
He held the hands of the undead
and exchanged farewells with them.
I think we've checked all
of the major locations.
I don't sense any demons.
One more place...
Hey, Old Marple! You in there?
Oh?
That voice... It's you, Menel!
This ghost appears to be
close to the highest rank!
Her soul must be extremely tough.
If she resists, my power
might not be enough...
If it comes to that, I'll have to use
a magic weapon that works on spirits.
You don't need to worry so much, young man.
I haven't gone senile yet.
Really? Well, that's good to hear.
It seems like you stayed behind because
of some lingering attachment,
but this kid here is a genuinely
virtuous high priest.
Returning lost souls like you to
the cycle of death and rebirth,
as well as treating wounded
people, are what he does best.
Oh?
We'll take care of the village.
You can just move on already.
Or is there something you
still want to say to someone?
I'll deliver the message for—
Menel!
You've been bad again!
No, I haven't...
Where'd that come from, anyway?
Maybe you really are senile?
I can read you like a book!
What do you mean?
You're lying, that's what!
I can always tell when you're lying!
You're twisted, but at your core,
you're upright and fastidious.
All this killing and stealing isn't for you.
You see that now, don't you?
Shut up.
Excuse me?
Shut up! What makes you
think you know anything?!
What was I supposed to do, then?!
You died, everyone else was starving...
What else could I have done?!
You think I should've prayed
to the gods or something?!
The gods... The gods have
never once helped me out!
Damn it! Damn it! Damn it!
Damn it! Damn it!
Damn it all...
I've had enough!
Just let me die with you!
The life of a half-elf is too long for me.
Those with elven blood live
for hundreds of years.
Amintire traumatizantă
Episodul 7
Even after they lose the
people and places they love,
it still doesn't end.
Listen to me, Menel.
Meneldor!
Despite all that, the gods have
given you a second chance.
It is your last chance.
Stop living like some useless bum.
You may hate the gods,
but the gods will never stop loving you.
Even if you don't notice it,
they will always shine down on you,
never growing bored or tired of you.
So all you need to do now is
realize that light is there.
Now, priest, if you don't mind...
Yes?
Would you mind looking after this poor fool?
He's not a bad boy at heart.
So... please treat him well, won't you?
I will.
And as for the demons and demon
beasts that attacked the village...
I'm certain they weren't just strays.
The stronghold where their boss
dwells is deep in the forest,
and he sends his demon minions
all over the place from there.
They command demon beasts, attack people...
It looks like they're routing all
their effort into some evil plot.
Um, if I may, is your
lingering attachment...
Well, I couldn't go and pass on without
making sure someone knew this!
Anyway, I appreciate the offer,
but I don't need your guidance.
You see, someone's already waiting for me.
Oh... She has someone.
So I'll be on my way now.
Menel, take care.
So many things happen in this world
that can never be taken back.
So stand up and face forward.
There are things you need to do.
Damn it, old woman, you're too selfish!
Well, so are you.
My goodness. What are we
going to do with you?
Well, I leave the rest in your hands.
Of course. You can count on me.
The present state of this world is dark.
At the very least, in this
area known as Beast Woods,
demons and demon beasts still run
rampant, never fully exterminated.
No nation's laws reach here,
so even among humans,
robbing and mugging are widespread.
Of course, as an outsider
just passing through,
I'm not obligated to do anything.
I could just walk right by it.
But...
As you travel, I pray:
bring light to the faraway darkness.
A few days later, the villagers returned.
Though they were shocked to see
the state the village was in,
they eventually gathered up
their remaining farm tools
and started digging holes to bury the dead,
and we all laid them to rest together.
So...
What will you do now?
Well, just look at this.
Just for tonight,
we're throwing a bit of a party
to mark our return to the village
and to honor our fallen.
You're the savior who got
our village back for us,
so we'd really like you to join us.
I'd be glad to.
Menel...
Hey.
It's a nice view.
Looks nice, anyway.
Those ruins are an undead nest.
Countless adventurers have gone in,
but none ever came back.
I see.
Okay, then, tomorrow I'll go there.
Huh? Were you even listening to me?
Yeah. It's an undead nest, right?
If it is, I need to go and
return them all to the cycle.
I guess that's the kind of guy you are.
Being around you throws me off my pace.
I thought I was a colder person than that.
Little late to say that after the
way you were wailing earlier.
You—
You're saying that to someone
who's already depressed?
Menel, what was Marple like?
She was a weird old woman,
like you just saw.
I was born up north in Grassland,
in the Great Forest of Erin,
where elves live.
My mother was a woman of
insatiable curiosity.
She took off somewhere outside the forest,
came back pregnant with
some stranger's child,
gave birth to me,
and died immediately after.
I grew up at a different pace
than everyone around me,
and the thing with my mother didn't help.
They said I was a disgrace,
and I didn't fit in anyway,
so I ended up fleeing the forest.
Of course, the world outside
was no paradise, either.
But luckily for me, I could use a
bow and arrow as well as knives.
And above all, I could see fairies.
When I ran into enemies
that wanted to eat me,
I had the strength to kill them instead.
If I didn't, I'd probably be whoring
myself out in some back alley.
You do have a pretty face.
Huh?!
Uh, nothing... Please go on.
Anyway, I became an adventurer
and made my way to Southmark,
where there were still a lot of old ruins...
but a member of my party betrayed me
in a fight over the loot
we found in some ruins.
He poisoned my food, and I nearly died.
I killed him with my own hands,
but all of them except me died anyway.
I didn't even know where I was wandering.
It was near that village
that I finally passed out.
Marple was the one who
found me and took me in.
At the time, she wasn't that old yet,
but she was such a weird old woman.
She lent her bed to the antisocial
kid she'd found lying on the ground,
let me eat her food,
and even lectured me about
living a decent life.
A lot of people ended up at that
village after being found by her.
What was she, exactly?
I have no idea.
Of course, she's dead now,
so we'll never know.
That happens a lot on this continent.
She did take me in and look after me.
That's when I started
pretending to be a hunter.
There are a lot of nasty creatures
and demon beasts in this area.
I was relatively useful,
I had a place to belong...
and I lost it all without any warning.
I got all the survivors together so we
could be the ones doing the stealing,
but thanks to you, we failed miserably.
It sucks having a longer life than
anyone else in a place like that.
It sucks so much,
I just want to die sometimes.
Right then.
I gotta get back on my feet soon, though.
Huh?
What? Done making all those faces at me?
Uh... wha... huh?!
There's a huge difference between your
priest self and your normal self, huh?
Wh-What?!
Will... Priest of the goddess of light...
I'm grateful to you.
You stopped me before I could
do something irreversible,
and you saved the people of the village.
So...
I ask to receive the goddess of light's
divine protection through you.
Do you accept?
I will act as the medium
for you to establish a bond with my goddess.
I will pray for you.
May the goddess of light, Gracefeel,
hereby love you, shine her light upon you,
and walk by your side in your travels.
I swear to my guardian deity
that I will atone for my sins and
live my life facing forward.
Please shine your light upon my path.
There'll be a lot of tough times,
and I might want to die now and then,
but I'm not gonna just stay down.
I'll get up and face forward,
like the old woman said.
Menel... You are strong.
It's amazing. I admire that.
C'mon, don't be gross.
You're the strong one.
Where the hell does your power come from?
W-Well... It's not that I'm strong.
I just had amazing teachers.
Well, I'm not gonna pry.
Oricum, ești gata să ne întoarcem?
Da.
Blood, Mary...
Păi, ei bine... E posibil ca...
Să fi găsit prima persoană pe care s-o numesc prieten.
Episodul recapitulativ
Drumul ales