Many things happened at a very rapid pace.
Having earned official permission from
the crown prince and the temple,
I set off with my team of rowdy adventurers
to begin the process of exterminating
the dangerous demons
and demon beasts infesting Beast Woods.
For areas that were relatively safe,
we brought human resources and supplies,
two things every poor village needs.
The village is within sight!
Yeah!
A village with access to supplies
becomes more productive.
Even if it starts out in debt,
it should eventually make a profit.
Tonio handled all that
with remarkable skill.
It was also Tonio who funded our activities
by soliciting donations and contributions.
I could go on to become the
head of a trade company.
Feel free to go big!
When I do, I'll be counting on your patronage.
Officially, this is just a lone
priest doing charitable work,
so no one gets offended.
Of course, that means I need to remain loyal
to the crown prince and the temple, though.
The Faraway Paladin
Will, you're back.
I appreciate the work all of you have done.
Bishop Bagley assigned a few
priests to me, including Anna.
They're all experienced priests
who can use the blessing,
as well as lead ceremonies
such as festivals and funerals.
Reystov's party should be
returning soon, as well.
When we got reports about demons
or demon beasts appearing,
Reystov and the other adventurers
would pursue them as a party.
Incredible... They were all killed
with a single fatal blow!
No wonder they call him the Penetrator.
Can you do this to wyverns, too?
If it's within range of my sword.
I would intervene in any
disputes between villagers
and try to help them settle
things reasonably.
I wasn't planning to do all this...
Well, once you've done it the
first time, you're kinda stuck.
Word of my interventions spread,
and I was called to intervene
in other villages' disputes.
My sudden role as an arbitrator
gave me a lot more to do.
And whenever I had to visit other
villages for friendly purposes
or had a message I wanted to get out,
Bee was a big help.
And so we traveled back and forth across
Beast Woods, time and time again.
Mom, this way!
The atmosphere has changed so much.
This area is relatively safe now,
so there's more merchant traffic.
A village that once had such
a dark cloud hanging over it
was now full of life and smiles.
Gus, I finally understand now.
Money drives this world!
With the power of money, you can
solve anything without magic!
You can buy the necessary
tools, hire people...
The ability to make a quick profit
is just as important as magic!
Everything you taught me was exactly right.
Making people smile and giving them hope
is more magical than actual magic.
And then...
Just as we were feeling the first
signs of summer approaching...
Hey.
What is it?
Pip's party went west on recon,
and they're not back yet.
How long?
They were planning to spend no
more than ten days investigating,
but it's two days past that.
So Pip and his party...
They're talented guys.
All right. We'll go and search for them.
You, Menel, and I are
definitely going, and...
Could you put together two parties of
people who excel in forest exploration?
I'll get them together right away.
There's a chance that
they didn't simply get lost,
but wound up in the demons' base.
If that's the case...
There'll be a battle.
What do you think?
Frankly, given the skills
Pip and his buddies have,
it's hard to believe they just got lost.
So you think it was demons, then?
I think there's a good chance it was.
If we beat them,
things'll settle down a bit here, too.
I just hope they're all right.
Hey...
What?
I guess I should say... thanks.
Uh... For what?
A lot of things.
If it hadn't been for you,
I would've sunk as low as I could sink.
It's thanks to you that I'm here now,
living for a respectable reason.
So... uh...
Thanks.
No, I should thank you.
I knew nothing of the world,
and you saved me.
But you know...
What?
You could look at me and say it.
Shut up!
Hey.
It's huge...
What kind of demon beast made this?
I don't know.
It's even bigger than a manticore.
A stray living in the valley... or...
Well, they died fighting a big one.
Pip, Harvey, and Brennan must
be pretty happy with that,
but pretty pissed off, too.
Yeah, like, "We didn't get to kill it!"
They died a good death,
worthy of adventurers.
G'wan, drink up.
Virtuous gods, grant their souls rest!
Gracefeel, goddess of light,
please grant them peace and guidance.
There's a head missing.
The damage is so bad,
it's hard to tell, but...
It probably got eaten.
Yeah, I'd bet on it.
No, wait.
He tossed all his gear as he ran?
Why go deeper into the valley, though?
If the path to the forest is blocked,
this valley's the only way.
He had no choice but to run deeper down.
I guess that's true...
Something's strange.
Yeah.
It's not right.
What's not right?
The footing in this valley is poor.
Even if they fled, getting this far would be...
It's a trap!
Get out!
Get back!
It's no use!
They're coming!
Stay calm! Keep your backs to the rocks!
Don't panic! Form a shield wall!
We have to break through them.
It'll be fine! We should be
able to handle these guys!
Menel!
Yeah?
I'll give us a boost with
magic and the blessing!
Goddess of flux, repel the
poisons that rain down upon us!
Fortis...
Strong
Life to
Vita ut Omnis!
All
Much appreciated!
Thanks!
Gnomes, O gnomes, guardians of treasure,
link to form a stronghold
against our enemies.
Sylphs, Sylphs, maidens of wind,
send your winds of protection
for these brave warriors.
Much obliged!
Now, let's show these beasts who
think they've trapped us...
which of us is really the prey.
Shoot!
Hang in there!
Menel, help!
Gnomes, O gnomes,
gather to us!
Build a fortress and surround with fences!
If he can just buy me time...
Don't...
Stop!
Thunder...
Tonit—
It cut my Words short!
What happened?!
He misfired?!
Why...
Everything was going so well up until now.
And yet...
Where did I...
What did I do wrong?
William!
The techniques that I had honed...
The spirit that I had refined...
The tactics that I had accumulated...
None of it was there.
All I could rely on
was blind fury and the abilities
of my demonblade as I hacked away
in an ugly, unsightly battle
that made me want to cry.
I felt I had wronged the three of them.
I felt pathetic.
Stop! That's enough!
Go heal Meneldor, quick! He's gonna die!
Menel!
Gracefeel, goddess of light...
Shine this healthy soul's light
upon these wicked wounds,
and banish these shadows!
Please...
Open your eyes!
No! Don't leave me!
My head feels fuzzy.
Because I used the demonblade's power?
But... I have to heal Menel...
Episode 11
Valley of Despair
William!
Snap out of it!
You're awake?
Where...
A village not far from that valley.
After that battle, we retreated with
you and Meneldor on our backs.
The chimera fled.
I se—
Where's Menel?!
He's still alive.
Between the magic and protection
you put on him before the fight
and Meneldor's own quick retreat,
it seems like your blessing
was just in the nick of time.
Thank goodness...
He hasn't woken up yet, though.
Then, I have to go to him!
You need to rest a bit longer.
But—
Meneldor's condition is stable.
He's had all the care he needs.
You burned up too much strength.
So rest.
Where did I screw up?
When I left Menel to handle the chimera?
No...
Given the circumstances,
I didn't have any other choice.
Then, when was it?
Was it getting caught in that
trap in the first place?
If I had been more careful
and taken the time to send out
scouts in all directions,
we wouldn't have wandered
blindly into that valley.
We had plenty of people,
we'd been successful up to that point,
and we were rattled after
seeing some of our men dead.
All of that led to a simple lack of caution.
No, I think I'm missing something...
some fatal flaw...
Anyway, they retreated, huh?
The Wyvern Killer and the Penetrator?
I heard they ran into some absurdly huge
mixed-up demon beast called a chimera.
Wonder what they're gonna do.
Also, that elf mix was hurt bad, wasn't he?
Yeah, he's really got it rough.
When you're stuck with a monster
like the Wyvern Killer,
no amount of lives is ever gonna be enough.
Yeah.
A monster?
Yeah... I guess I am.
It wasn't my battle tactics that were wrong.
It was my estimation of our strength.
I trusted Menel.
I just believed that he'd have my back,
that he could keep any
enemy in check for me.
I thought he could handle
that much... but...
I came so close to getting Menel killed.
I just one-sidedly decided he was my friend,
and in my innocent naïveté,
without even thinking,
I put him up against dangers
he wasn't ready for.
Will!
Bee... Tonio.
We got your message and rushed here.
Anna should arrive here
with the priests later.
I see.
Will, we heard you saved Menel's life!
You ran into a beast as
impossibly tough as a chimera,
but you still beat an insane
number of magic beasts
and even saved Menel's life!
You really are incredible!
I doubt Menel and the others who've
been stuck with me would agree.
Huh?
I'm going to check on Menel.
Will?
Will, shouldn't you rest a bit longer?
I'm fine.
I'm very strong, after all.
Ever since I left the city of the dead,
people have constantly told me
that in no uncertain terms.
Every time, I've just laughed
wryly and shrugged it off.
I think, subconsciously, I was
trying not to think about it.
But I can't avoid it anymore.
In this world,
my strength is beyond the pale.
This is... my sin.
Menel... I'll fix you up right now.
Gods, please take pity
on Menel and heal him.
I'm sorry, Menel.
I wanted a friend who could be my equal.
I wanted what the three of them had,
comrades who had each other's backs,
supported each other,
and respected each other.
But maybe I was forcing that on you
without even realizing it.
I didn't want to acknowledge
just how strong I was.
If I did that...
If I set myself above everyone else
and had to admit that I was different...
I'm scared.
I'm lonely.
It hurts.
I hate this.
Oh... Of course.
It was just that simple.
I was afraid to be alone.
I couldn't bear not having
someone beside me.
That's why I tried to see the people
I should have been protecting,
should have been saving, as my equals.
I was averting my eyes from the truth,
when really, I was just scared.
And for that despicable reason...
Because of that...
I almost killed you.
But I finally get it now.
I couldn't go on that way.
Oh, Goddess.
You're here because you're worried about me?
Up until now, I was foolish.
But everything is fine now.
Please rest at ease.
I'll put a stop to your sadness right away.
I'll save everything,
everything within my reach,
as your sword, and as your hand.
It's all right.
I'll solve all of this on my own.
Will...
Episode 12
The Faraway Paladin