So, it's been decided that a new cadet to the academy will join our class.
This is Lux.
Please treat him well.
Come on. Greet them.
Oh, right!
Um, I'm Lux Arcadia. It's nice to meet you all.
Okay then, take an empty seat, please.
All right.
Look, it's the guy from before.
He's pretty cute, huh?
So he's in our class now.
He defeated that Gargoyle with the princess.
He's a former prince, right?
I can't believe they're letting
a boy into this school.
Man... I wanna go home.
Huh? It's Lu.
Is that... Philuffy?
Yeah. Long time no see!
It's been seven years. How surprising.
An acquaintance of yours?
Yes.
She's an old friend.
Then how about you sit next to her, then?
Yes, thank you.
Okay, please open your textbooks to page 27.
Um... Do you mind if we share a textbook?
Huh? Philuffy?
Don't you mean Phi?
What?
I-I know that's what I used to call you,
but at our age, that's kind of...
"Phi"?
Yeah, he called her "Phi."
How cute!
Phi... Mind if we share a textbook?
Sure, Lu.
Thanks.
Fight for the sky
afuredasu kanjou mou tomaranai
I can't stop the overflowing emotions
mune ni idaitai bokura no gensou
The illusions we hold so dear
Just revolution
kienai aza ni obiete ite mo
Fear of the scar that won't disappear
toki ga mujou ni sugiteku dake
Won't stop the ruthless passage of time
susumeyo aru ga mama
Go forth, the way you are
Let's burst up!
ima koso kawaru toki
Now is the time for change
Let's boost up!
kakumei no kane no ne ga
The sound of the bell of revolution
doko made mo hibiite yuku
Resounds far and wide
To be the soldier
mou koko ni wa irarenai
We can't stay here any longer
To be the soldier
kaze wo kitte yuke ikite yuke
Cut through the wind, live your life
hiryuu no gotoku
Like a flying dragon
hajimari ga michiru mama densetsu ni nare
As the beginning draws near, become a legend
tokihanatte yuke tonde yuke
Release yourself, fly ahead
inochi wo tagirasete
Overflow with life
erabareshi mono wo matsu sekai wa owari da New age
The world that waits for a chosen one is over! New age!
episodul 02
Cel mai slab cavaler dragonic
Say, Lux.
Is it true that you usually
work as a handyman?
Uh, yeah. That's my responsibility.
Can I also request your service?
No fair! I wanna make a request too!
Okay, okay!
Write your requests for Luxy on these sheets
and put them in this box, 'kay?
Take mine, too!
I was first!
Wait, what are you organizing all of a sudden?
And who's Luxy?
H-Hey, Lux!
Miss Lisha?
I have a request, as well.
Sure! What is it?
Th-The thing is... from now on, I want you...
to be my exclusive personal assistant.
What?!
Exclusive to Miss Lisesharte?!
And what's more, she's choosing a man.
Th-That's the least you can do.
I mean, you already saw me naked.
B-But th-that was—
Phi?
You're making Lu uncomfortable,
Miss Lisesharte.
What? Aren't you the ditzy daughter of the Aingram Industrial Group?
I'll give you my snack, so please back off.
Om nom...
Gulp.
Lu is uncomfortable. Please stop, Princess.
You're still saying that?!
Sorry, can I have a moment?
Krulcifer?
If you need me, you'll have to wait.
I'm having a very important conversation right—
The Headmistress asked me to take care of something, so I'll need to borrow him for a bit.
I trust that's all right with you, Lux?
Oh, sure.
Huh? Uh...
Wait!
Um... thanks.
You said that to get me
out of that mess, right?
Correct.
Why would you do that?
Well...
Have you heard of the Black Hero?
The legendary Drag-Knight who single-handedly brought down the former empire.
The knight's identity is shrouded in mystery,
and is unknown to this day.
I have a request for you.
Find the Black Hero.
I have some business to
take care of with him.
About the human experimentation the Imperial Army has been performing...
That girl, your childhood friend,
is now on the list.
We have no choice but to kill them.
Fugil...
Even so, I...
I want to minimize the casualties.
A dream?
Ah, feels good...
This blanket is so soft.
Huh?
Hm?
Morning, Lu.
Uh, why?! How?!
Well, this is my room.
It's been a long time since we've slept together, huh?
I-I see.
But cover yourself up!
I can see everything right now!
Philuffy, just how long do you
plan to sleep on a day off?
Be more careful! You're a girl, after all!
J-Just put—
I'm coming in!
S-Sorry for interrupting!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Hey, everyone! Big news!
Ah! Wait! Wait!
I'm appalled, Brother.
You just transferred here and you already
spent a night in your childhood friend's room.
It's not like that, Airi!
What is it like, then?
I just slept in the room they told me to.
I didn't know Philuffy was my roommate.
Roommate?!
I-I consulted Headmistress Relie, too.
But it seems there are no other vacancies.
Take care of my sister, okay?
Was it approved by her sister?
Still, it's bound to cause
all kinds of misunderstandings.
There are already various rumors going around
about you. You're the talk of the school.
Really?
I'm going.
I was thinking we could
have breakfast together.
But if I stay with you any longer,
I won't be able to leave your side.
Huh?
It's a joke, Lux.
Also, I hope you'll be careful
about that matter we discussed.
Yeah, I got it.
Excuse me!
It's Lux Arcadia.
I've come to take care of the job you requested.
Miss Lisha?
Oh, Lux...
Oh, right. I put in a work request, didn't I?
Where's the manager of the workshop?
She's right in front of you.
Huh...
You're the manager?!
Look, I repaired your Wyvern for you.
You did this?
Yeah! I did it so I can have you join the school's knight squadron.
Knight squadron?
It's a special forces unit made up
of cadets who show promise.
I saw more than enough to acknowledge your skills as a Drag-Knight.
I'd like you to lend us your strength in the name of the new kingdom.
I'll do what I can.
You will be formally initiated when the
third-years return from their campaign.
Oh, also, this is a bit sudden,
but can I request another job of you?
Welcome!
It's important that we get to know each other in order
to improve our teamwork in the knight squadron.
I see.
And also, there's a good restaurant nearby.
Okay, shall we go in?
M-Miss Lisha.
This place looks very expensive.
It's fine. I am a princess,
after all. Of course I can—
Wait. Huh?
Uh, what? Huh?!
Did you forget your wallet?
Here you go.
Sorry. I really meant to treat you to lunch.
Eat it while it's still hot.
It's delicious. Thanks!
You're welcome.
What's wrong?
N-Nothing...
I'm feeling a bit fluttery here.
Are you okay?!
I-I'm fine.
I just need a little rest.
Oh, then I know just the place!
It really feels great up here.
I've done some cleaning here
before as a handyman.
I've since come to like this place.
A handyman prince, huh?
Though, you're amazing, Miss Lisha.
I can't believe you can repair
and upgrade Machine Dragons.
And you're a first-rate Drag-Knight.
You're an admirable princess, Miss Lisha.
Miss Lisha?
That's dangerous!
Hurry and get back in here!
What does it mean to be a princess?
Tell me, Lux Arcadia.
How should a princess act?
Do you remember the brand of the
former empire on my stomach?
Five years ago, I was captured
by the former empire,
as a hostage to be used against father,
who was part of the coup d'état.
But my father refused to negotiate and the coup was carried out.
I was abandoned.
This brand is the evidence that I'm
property of the former empire.
I... I wanted my father to rescue me.
I wanted him to choose me, not the country.
Pathetic, huh?
I couldn't kill myself, so I had resolved to
abandon everything and side with the empire.
I'm not fit to be a princess.
But still...
After my father's death,
as a surviving member of House Atismata,
I was named princess of the new kingdom.
The fact that I was bearing the brand of the former empire was concealed.
Lux, wasn't it difficult for you to lose
your position as prince of the empire?
I couldn't really do anything befitting a prince.
Why? Why?
Why did you kill them? All of them...
We said we'd minimize the casualties.
You were really useful.
We didn't even have to use that whistle.
If we'd summoned hoards of Abysses,
it would've been a real pain to clean up after them since they're messy eaters.
That not the plan we—
If I hadn't killed everyone, sooner or later
they would have assassinated me.
Brother...
You don't understand anything.
With that attitude, you could never be a king.
You're the weakest.
Did I fall asleep?
What's happening?
Official notice to all military cadets.
This morning, a large Abyss appeared.
It was sighted in the southwest ruins.
Presently, several Drag-Knights of the new kingdom's
security forces are headed that way to eliminate it.
We are to form a defense unit
and prepare for battle.
Stand by for further instructions.
Yes, ma'am!
Airi!
Lux?
I was wondering where everyone was.
I'll see you later, Lux.
Huh? Where are you going?
We have a mission!
Yes. In short, the military is short-handed.
As the members of the knight squadron,
we have to take the initiative and get
out there when there's an emergency.
Stay safe!
Don't worry! I'm strong, after all!
Since I'm a foreign student and you two aren't members of the knight squadron, we'll stay behind.
Is something wrong?
That Abyss the other day, and now this.
Two Abysses have appeared within
a suspiciously short period of time.
Maximum energy output!
Five, four, three, two...
Wait! What's that noise?
Philuffy?
I hear something.
I can hear the sound of a whistle.
The sound of a whistle?
Did it explode?
Is everyone okay?
Hatch now, eggs.
Gargoyles!
Who are you? The commander of
the Royal Capital's security forces?
No. I came from the Imperial Capital.
My name is Ragreed Forus, Captain of the Imperial Guard Knight Squadron of the Arcadia Empire.
This is an act of treason
against the new kingdom!
You make me out to be the villain,
but in reality, I've returned
to the path of righteousness.
Because I've obtained power!
Dammit!
What's wrong, Noct?!
Did something happen?
Yes.
This is an emergency.
Where are you going, Lux?
I'm going to help Miss Lisha.
You can't defeat an Abyss with a Wyvern.
You can't use your other sword either.
There's nothing you can do!
Don't worry, Airi.
I won't leave you alone in this world.
Please protect this place.
Thresher!
Shalice, Tillfur, is everyone safe?
I'm sorry, Princess.
We're in no condition to keep fighting.
We're retreating.
That's fine.
I'll go for their leader,
the one with that whistle.
The whistle is probably the key to controlling the Abysses.
How uncouth, Lisesharte.
It was a mistake to give the position of princess to a filthy dog who can only survive by serving men!
How pitiful a man must be to only speak his mind
once in an advantageous position.
Bark for me, dog!
Princess!
Miss Lisha!
That's...
The former empire's... rebel army?
Miss Lisha, please, hold on
for just a little longer!
It's okay, Lux.
In the end, I couldn't do
anything befitting a princess.
Pretending to be a princess has been so difficult.
But I really wanted to become one...
because I love everyone.
I wanted to prove myself this time.
Spare me the sob story, you filthy dog.
I'll remind you who your master is.
S-Stop...
Don't you remember?
I'm the one that put that
crest on your stomach!
Don't...
Don't touch me!
You bitch!
Lux!
I failed to achieve anything
when I was a prince too.
I tried to save everyone, but I failed.
And yet, I still want to save people!
Because I want to be recognized by someone fit to be a princess of the new kingdom.
I don't know who you are,
but your resistance is futile.
What can you do on
your own, you little shit?!
Manifest, O violent dragon who
feasts on the flesh and blood of gods!
Sever the black clouds of heaven,
Bahamut!
A jet-black Divine Raiment Machine Dragon?!
No way! You're him!
So you've gone and done it, Brother?
That's... the Black Hero.
The Drag-Knight who in the
coup d'état five years ago,
single-handedly destroyed 1200
of the empire's Machine Dragons.
Lux Arcadia...
You wretch! It was you,
Seventh Prince Lux Arcadia.
Why?!
You, a surviving member
of the imperial family...
You, a prince of the empire...
Why are you raising your sword against us?
Do you think you've become a hero?!
Reload on Fire.
You traitorous little...
My brother is not a hero.
He is the undefeated weakest
Drag-Knight who destroyed the empire.
kusaki mo nemuru yoru no sumi de sekai no fushi de
In the nook of night where even trees sleep, in a cranny of the world
neiki ni sotto mimi wo tatete hitomi wo tojiru
I hear the breath of someone asleep nearby,
close my eyes, and prick up my ears
kubisuji ni futto atatakana inochi no tsubu ga
A warm seed of life near my neck
koko ni iru tte sakenderun da koe naki koe de
is screaming that it's there, in a voice without voice
umarekawaretara owarinaki you ni
If we can be reborn endlessly
kimi ga nodo wo itamenakute
Let's take such forms
sumu you na sugata ni narou
that we won't need to scream so hard to be heard
sashiatatte futari tabi doko made arukeru
Now we're traveling, the two of us. How far can we go?
ikeru toko made ikou hohaba awasete
Let's go as far as we can, matching each other's pace
tsukiatatte futari tabi koko made kureba
And when we finally get to the end of the path, the two of us
kigi ni natte tachitsukusou
Let's become trees and stay there
raise ni natte mo zutto koko de nemurou
Even in the next world, let's keep sleeping there
futari nemurou towa ni
The two of us, let's sleep for eternity