Acum 5 ani - Imperiul Arcadia
Acum cinci ani...
După câteva sute de ani sub o guvernare tiranică, Imperiul Arcadia a căzut după o lovitură de stat.
Cel care a provocat asta a fost un pilot misterios într-un robot dragonic negru.
Chiar și acum, adevărata identitate a acelui cavaler a rămas necunoscută.
Din respect și teamă, oamenii spun povestea acestui cavaler dragonic, pe care-l numesc...
Eroul Negru.
Fight for the sky
Luptă pentru cer
POVESTEA NEÎNVINSULUI BAHAMUT
afuredasu kanjou mou tomaranai
Nu pot opri aceste emoții care mă copleșesc
mune ni idaitai bokura no gensou
Sunt iluziile noastre atât de dragi
Just revolution
Este o revoluție
kienai aza ni obiete ite mo
Teama de rănile care nu vor dispărea
toki ga mujou ni sugiteku dake
Nu va opri trecerea nemiloasă a timpului
susumeyo aru ga mama
Înaintează, exact așa cum ești
Let's burst up!
Aprinde-te!
ima koso kawaru toki
A venit momentul schimbării
Let's boost up!
Și avansează!
kakumei no kane no ne ga
Sunetul clopotului revoluției
doko made mo hibiite yuku
Răsună tare și clar
To be the soldier
Ca să devii acel soldat
mou koko ni wa irarenai
Nu mai putem rămâne aici
To be the soldier
Ca să devii acel soldat
kaze wo kitte yuke ikite yuke
Spintecă vântul și trăiește-ți viața
hiryuu no gotoku
Precum un dragon zburător
hajimari ga michiru mama densetsu ni nare
Începutul este aproape, așa că devino o legendă
tokihanatte yuke tonde yuke
Eliberează-te și zboară
inochi wo tagirasete
Lasă-te cuprins de viață
erabareshi mono wo matsu sekai wa owari da New age
Lumea care-l așteaptă pe cel ales a luat sfârșit! Este începutul unei noi ere!
episodul 01
Prințesa Stacojie de Război
Fostul Imperiu Arcadia
Actualul Regat Atismata
Fortăreața orașului Crossfeed
Stai, cum am ajuns aici?
Hei, perversule.
Dorești să mai spui ceva înainte să mori?
T-Trebuie să spun ceva ca să mă scot repede din situația asta!
O-Oh, știu!
Bătrânul de la ultimul meu serviciu a spus că fetelor le place să primească complimente!
Ei bine... Ești drăguță.
Ai un corp ca de copil...
De fapt, deși pari foarte
tânără, tot ai forme și...
Ești foarte atrăgătoare!
Stai. Ce?
Ce tot spun?!
Dezgustător!
S-Stai, nu trebuia să sune astfel!
Huliganule!
Vai, în ce belea am intrat.
Mai trebuia să ajung și undeva astăzi.
Hei? Cineva?
Asta este o neînțelegere!
Îmi voi cere scuze pentru
că am căzut prin acoperiș!
Ascultă-mă, te rog!
Ei bine, îți pot explica tot.
O pisică hoțomană furase
poșetuța unei fete,
iar eu alergam după ea ca s-o prind.
Am urmărit-o de pe un acoperiș pe altul,
și înainte să-mi dau seama,
am ajuns în acel loc.
Is this Sword Device yours?
Da, așa este.
It's rare to see someone
carrying around two of them.
And furthermore, this black sword...
Dacă nu este chiar Krulcifer!
Ce faci aici?
I came to see our cute
peeping Tom here, Shalice.
Oh, înțeleg.
Okay, cute deviant.
The Academy's headmaster wants to see you.
The Headmaster?
Groping girls in the bathhouse just because
the third-year knights are away...
You've got some nerve, don't you?
Cut it out, Tillfur.
I told you...
Wait. Headmaster? Third-year knights?
Does that mean this is...
Academia Cavalerilor Regali (Academia)
Bun-venit la Academie!
In other words, it was an unfortunate accident.
Right, Lux Arcadia, prince of
the former Empire of Arcadia?
I'm sorry for causing a ruckus on my way here.
A former prince?
But Headmaster!
Now, now... We were the ones
who called you here for the job,
and I'll vouch for your innocent character
as a longtime acquaintance.
This boy isn't nearly gutsy
enough for such a stunt.
Um...
Ah, yes, yes, the main matter.
You know about this academy, don't you, Lux?
Yes. It's the Drag-Knight academy run by the new kingdom, isn't it?
That's right. Since the coup d'état five years ago,
the new kingdom has invested significant resources into training its Drag-Knights
to be on par with the military
forces of other countries.
As girls are said to have higher aptitude
in general for being Drag-Knights,
this academy is actually an all-girls school
intended to train them.
However, I thought I'd ask
you to work here, Lux.
What?!
B-But I'm a man!
Why would you ask me?
There are only a few male Drag-Knights
left after the coup d'état,
so boys like you are valuable.
And those two swords hanging from your waist
aren't just for decoration, right?
Headmaster!
Wait! Wait! Wait!
Wait a second!
I haven't deemed this man acceptable!
Allowing this perverted groper
to work at this school is...
unthinkable!
You're the one from...
Hey, Miss Lisha, if you get that close
he's gonna mount you again!
You girls better be careful, too!
This talk is becoming pretty serious.
Fair enough.
Okay, then. I'll leave his punishment to you,
Lisesharte, as the victim of this incident.
What?!
Then fight me!
I'll determine whether or not you are worthy of becoming a Drag-Knight of this academy.
This'll be interesting to watch!
You can beat a man for sure.
Will it really be that simple?
Beat him!
He won the prize money in the royal capital tournament, and he's still undefeated.
He's also known as "The Undefeated Weakest."
A pervert like him is still undefeated?
That doesn't sit right with me.
Listen well, Lux Arcadia.
This match will be a one-on-one duel
with our Machine Dragons.
If you lose, you will be jailed as a criminal.
If you win, you will be acquitted
and may work here!
Are we clear?
Tell the whole academy:
There will be an exhibition of the new kingdom's princess crushing the former empire's prince!
The new kingdom's princess?
Lisesharte Atismata. That's my name.
Seriously?!
First princess of the new Kingdom of Atismata.
A princess of the new kingdom that
destroyed your empire five years ago.
Nice to meet you, Former Prince.
What?!
Jeez...
What are you doing, Brother?
I'm appalled.
Sorry about everything.
I'm sorry I caused such a
commotion at your school, Airi.
Um, you're gonna stay standing?
Yes.
I heard that if you get too close,
with just a breath, you can lift my skirt.
What do you think I am?!
She's my roommate in the girls' dorm.
Her name is—
Yes. I am Noct Leaflet, a first-year.
It's disappointing that Airi's big brother
is an unbelievable pervert.
But it was a misunderstanding!
If you get incarcerated,
how am I going to pay your debt?
Since the coup d'état,
as surviving members of the former imperial family, we've been considered criminals.
The debt we'd taken on in exchange for amnesty is not something I can ever pay for by myself!
I need you to work diligently as a handyman
for the people of this kingdom.
And that's what I've been trying my best to do.
I see. And as a result of those efforts, you jumped into the girl's bath and groped people, right?
If you go to jail for that,
it'll also cause me trouble.
S-Sorry.
Anyway, no matter what you do,
you must beat Miss Lisesharte.
Is she strong?
Yes.
Miss Lisesharte is presently
undefeated in this school.
But even if she hasn't lost to anyone,
that goes for you as well, right, Lux?
Right.
All machines, deploy the barrier.
Now, let the Machine Dragon match between the first princess of the new kingdom, Miss Lisesharte,
and the former seventh prince
of the former empire, Lux, begin.
Come on, don't these people
have better things to do?
Lux Arcadia!
Why do you think I
challenged you to this fight?
Because I'm a prince of the former empire?
If you win, I'll tell you.
Both parties, prepare!
Come, symbol of power,
winged dragon of the crest!
Obey my sword and soar!
Wyvern!
What? Just a Wyvern, Lux Arcadia?
Huh?
My Divine Raiment Machine Dragon, Tiamat,
is on a completely different level to that generic machine you're using.
Divine Raiment... Machine Dragon...
Divine Raiment Machine Dragon...
It's a rare, ancient weapon that holds an ability that
generic Machine Dragons can't hold a candle to.
None but the most skilled can even use one.
Yes. There's too great a power gap compared
to Lux's generic Wyvern Machine Dragon.
Battle, start!
How do you fare at dancing, Lux Arcadia?
I'm a little on the rough side, personally.
Show me a good time, my prince!
Dodging my attacks with only swordplay?
I have one favor to ask of you.
What is it?
If we keep going like this and the match
ends with a draw, can't we work things out?
I-I'm sorry about what happened
at the bath. Really, I apologize.
Oh...
It seems you're not just some ordinary fool.
You're the king of fools!
Reveal your true nature, Tiamat!
Seven Heads!
She added more special armaments?!
Not good.
By the way, isn't it dangerous
for us all to be here?
A word of advice.
You should get rid of that broken-down Wyvern
and use that other Sword Device of yours.
Sorry, but I mustn't use that one.
Then meet your end here...
together with the pride of the former empire!
Got you!
Y-You'll kill me at this rate!
Redeploy the barrier!
Well, at least she's thinking about
avoiding the spectators. I think.
Yes. As things are,
Airi's big brother is sure to lose.
He asked for it.
But even though he is that way,
there is one good point to him.
What's that?
Once he's decided on something,
he'll absolutely follow through with it.
Why can't I defeat him?
At this rate, time will run out and it'll be a draw.
Is this the reason he's called
the Undefeated Weakest?
Very well. Out of respect for your skill,
I'll let you witness my Tiamat's Divine Raiment!
Grovel before the name of God.
Thresher!
Divine Raiment...
Secret, special abilities exclusive to
Divine Raiment Machine Dragons.
Tiamat's Divine Raiment controls gravity.
But to use a Divine Raiment on top of
all the other weapons she's deployed...
It's over, Fallen Prince!
What happened?
She's losing control!
This looks bad.
Hurry and get out of your Machine Dragon!
I'm not going to lose like this!
The barrier disappeared?
Why is there an Abyss?!
Looks like a Gargoyle!
An Abyss...
Those monsters should
only come from the ruins.
Why is it here?
Threat detected! Triad, evacuate
all students to the school buildings!
Everyone, remain calm! Don't panic!
Everyone, take shelter in the school buildings!
All Wyverns, deploy a barrier
around the Gargoyle.
Protect the students at any cost!
What's going on?!
Howling Roar!
Lux Arcadia?!
Miss Lisesharte, may I ask one favor of you?
You two!
Why haven't you evacuated yet?
And what are you doing, Noct?
You're part of the Triad!
Airi's big brother...
He's crazy to face an Abyss
with a generic Machine Dragon!
You shouldn't interfere until
the instructors come to help.
No.
There is only one enemy here.
That means he won't lose.
I managed to regain control
over Tiamat, but at this rate...
You...
Miss Lisesharte, may I ask one favor of you?
I can't destroy that Abyss with my Wyvern.
So please land and take aim at the enemy.
You think you can order me around?!
I'll give the signal to fire the cannon.
That signal will be...
right after I raise my sword over my head.
I don't know what you're planning to do with that broken sword,
but with the remaining power, Seven Heads
can manage another more shot.
Make sure I can hit, Fallen Prince.
Lux Arcadia! Reinforcements are coming! Hold out!
You're finished!
If a strong defender acts
as a diversion for an attack,
their ally can put all their power
into one powerful finishing shot.
You know your tactics, you monster.
I'm the same as you.
Intentionally taking the enemy's attack
to create an opening...
This is the first time a man
has tried to help or protect me.
Lux Arcadia, huh?
So what do you intend to do now?
Are you going to support my
Bahamut with your Wyvern?
Or perhaps...
D-Do your injuries hurt?
Um, did you come here to take care of me?
O-Only because you saved me.
No, that's not...
Honestly, I can't figure out whether
you're being modest or arrogant.
Are all men of the former empire like that?
I don't know. When I was young,
I was forced out of the imperial court.
And why did you do that anyway?
A normal person wouldn't face an Abyss
in a generic Machine Dragon, you know?
I don't really remember.
I just felt that's what I had to do.
I see.
Well, that's fine.
You protected me—
You protected us.
That's plenty enough.
You're an openhearted person,
aren't you, Princess?
Yes, that's right.
To people of ability, I'm quite
the lenient and generous princess.
Okay, I believe you completely, Lux.
I'm glad.
I have to tell you the real reason
I challenged you to a duel.
Huh?
I-I couldn't let you get away
with... seeing that, s-so...
Oh! S-Sorry about that. I saw everything.
But... it was pretty.
You idiot! Filthy pervert! Drop dead!
What I was talking about... i-is this.
Because you saw this at the bath back then.
Isn't that... the crest of the former empire?
Why in the world do you have it?
I still can't tell you that. But...
Don't tell anyone about this crest. Please.
It's okay. I won't tell anyone.
Do you swear?
Yes. I swear on my Sword Devices.
Okay. That settles that, then.
But why did you stubbornly refuse to use that black Sword Device?
Um... That's because...
Well, it looks like we both have secrets.
Starting tomorrow, you will formally be a member of this academy.
Okay.
By the way, I had your job
from the headmaster canceled.
You'll attend this school as a Royal Knight Cadet.
Am înțeles
Stai, ce?!
Domnișoară Lisesharte?
Also...
Please call me Lisha,
as you would a classmate.
C-Ce?
Lux Arcadia, nu?