Cazul 1: În derivă
Chiar... am supraviețuit, nu-i așa?
Hei... Cu tine vorbesc.
Eu nu sunt "tine".
Atunci, spune-mi numele tău.
Before asking someone's name,
you should first introduce your—
Oh, for crying out loud!
Then let's do introductions.
Ce?
I'll go first.
Eu sunt Suzumori Asuka.
I'm in Class C, and I'm on both the
basketball team and the track team.
Încântată de cunoștință.
I'll go next.
I'm Kujou Shion from Class 2-B.
I like to play piano, and I have
a dog named Arnold.
Pleased to meet you.
Um...
I'm from Class A. My name is Amatani Mutsu.
My hobbies are reading and cooking... Oh!
And I've held on to the number one spot
in my class since I was a freshman!
Also, I've never been late once!
And I'm confident in my ability
to memorize things!
I also know a lot about astronomy!
Really... Okay. Next.
Onishima Homare.
Class F.
Huh? That's it?
You don't have anything else?
Something to make people like you?
Something to make people like me?
I don't know if this counts, but...
Being stranded like this...
This isn't my first time.
We're stranded?
Are You Lost?
daremo jibun no ibasho wakannakunattari shite
samayoutte aruku no
Așa este, m-am pierdut!
sounan desu
michitarita hibi yori mo taritenai kurai ga ii
ikiru tame ikiru no
mayoi naku tondemo tondemo na toraburu deatatte
Fetelor, distrați-vă!
Girls have fun!
Cu 20 de ore în urmă
Listen closely, Homare.
When you face your opponent, make sure
to stand ready with your blade hidden.
Homare, you should never eat slugs raw.
Moose testicles are a rare and valuable
cut of meat that can be eaten raw.
But don't expect much in regard to flavor.
Papa...
B*lls stink!
Huh?
Papa?
B*lls?
Huh?
Oh! She's awake.
I-I'm fine...
How is this fine? We got washed away!
It's a miracle we survived,
but how long do we have to wait to be rescued?
I'm already dying of thirst.
Well, we have lots of water, right?
You can't drink seawater.
Huh? Why?
Because there's salt in it.
You'll lose more moisture than you take in.
Let's say that a person
needs two liters of water a day.
If you lose two percent of that, you get thirsty.
At three percent, signs of dehydration start.
At five percent, you get
headaches and dizziness.
At ten percent, organ function decreases...
leading to death.
You really know a lot about this.
What's all this?
H-Hey!
You shouldn't be moving yet...
A... A fish?
It's a flying fish.
Huh?
You're not... Are you going to eat it?
What we need right now is moisture.
Digesting food uses a lot
of moisture too, so...
It's better not to eat for now.
Wrap it in fabric and crush it well...
then when you squeeze it like this...
You can drink the bodily fluids, like the
moisture from the organs and the blood.
Here. You should have some, too.
Are You Lost?
Really...?
If there are flying fish...
that means there's land nearby.
I can't see anything besides the horizon.
When you're on the water,
the horizon you see isn't very far away.
It's probably about four
or five kilometers ahead.
I'm amazed you can still wear that shirt.
The circumference of the Earth
is about 40,000 kilometers, so...
The radius would be about 6,400 kilometers.
If you put our view point
at just over one meter, then...
According to the Pythagorean theorem...
It's true. What we're seeing is only
about four or five kilometers away.
Wow! You're super smart!
I guess I shouldn't have expected
any less from someone wearing glasses!
G-Glasses have nothing to do with it.
Forget that, we need water! Water!
Unlike that fish juice girl,
the rest of us are delicate!
How thirsty are you?
I'm dying of thirst!
I see. All right, then.
Huh?
Close your eyes, open your mouth,
and lie down facing up.
Why?
To help remove resistance to the idea.
Don't worry.
When it's fresh, it's sterile.
What are you guys doing?
Oh, I missed.
Wait, please! Not that!
It's better than dying, isn't it?
She's still fine! Probably!
But...
Do I have to keep waiting? Hurry up!
Are You Lost?
I see.
A rescue team... never came for us.
Our one and only class trip is...
Why did it turn out like this?
If nothing had gone wrong,
we'd be in bed at the hotel right now.
Does anyone have any fun stories?
I guess not, right?
Hey. Hey!
Is it morning?
You're finally awake.
Hey, I can see land.
What?
Over there.
But with these currents,
we're going to miss it.
Dying would be better than
having to stay here forever.
We have no choice but to swim.
That is the most reasonable choice.
A tiger shark?
It couldn't be worse.
What's wrong?
It's nothing. Just get swimming.
It's pretty far, isn't it?
It's just a little further! Keep—
Sh...
Shark!
Damn.
I kept using an old-style phone
in case of disasters, but...
Well, there's no helping it now.
Is everyone all right?
I was so scared...
I can't take any more.
Where's the shark?
It swam off.
Sharks have special receptors
in their noses, the ampullae of Lorenzini,
that can sense electricity.
You can deliver a pretty severe
shock using a cell phone battery.
It's amazing you know that.
I learned from my father.
Hey, is this place really safer... for us?
Are You Lost?
Yes!
Acum
Hey! We're not done with introductions!
What do you mean, this isn't
the first time you've been stranded?
Oh.
Before, in the Pacific Ocean,
the Atlantic Ocean, the Indian Ocean...
While I was traveling with my father
we ran into a few problems.
Right.
So... I guess you're sort of a pro
at getting stranded, Onishima-san.
What do we do now?
What is essential in a survival situation is—
Amatani-san! Are you all right?
We need to carry her to the shade, gently.
I'm sorry...
Don't worry about it.
Her pulse is normal.
It's most likely dehydration.
You should rest here
in the shade without moving.
First, we need to find drinking water.
Please gather up any empty bottles
you find washed up on the beach.
I'll go, too.
I probably have the most
endurance of anyone here.
Wh-What's that about?
You two are going to look for water,
and we have to pick up trash?
To secure large amounts of water,
we will need receptacles.
And it would be best
if someone stayed with her.
About finding water. Allow me
to give a simple explanation.
Hey. Did you eat something just now?
There are five ways to obtain drinking water.
First, to take it from plants or animals.
You can get water from
coconuts and cut banana trunks.
Though it doesn't seem like
this island would have either.
You can get water by cutting
the bamboo and vines
that are more likely to be here, but...
it takes a really long time.
The second way is to purify undrinkable water.
The third way is to distill seawater.
But we don't have the tools for either.
The fourth way is rain water, but...
We can't wait around for rain to fall.
The fifth way is to find a water source.
Given the size of this island,
there should be a spring somewhere.
Just wait a little longer.
I-I've been feeling lightheaded for a while.
Collect your spit in your mouth
and breathe through your nose.
Nu mai am nici salivă în gură!
Nu-ți face griji.
Ți-am dat puțină de la mine.
Hei! Rezistă!
H-Homare...
C-Ce... este asta?
Oh.
Este un picior.
De la lăcusta pe care am mâncat-o mai devreme.
Primul meu sărut... a avut gust de lăcustă.
Data viitoare, cazul 2:
"Prima noastră masă."
Cazul 2: Prima noastră masă