Nu credeam că mă voi mai întoarce într-una din astea.
Nu-ți face griji. De data asta nu va mai dura cinci ani!
Is it okay to shorten the
amount of time I'm young?
Tehnologia anti-îmbătrânire a evoluat mult.
You'll be able to maintain
your youth for 30 years!
Bine.
Începe.
Switch... on!
Ești la pubertate, deci te-ai înălțat ceva!
Ți-am făcut și o operație pe retină, deci nu vei mai avea nevoie de ochelari.
Asta e motivul?
Chiar mă întrebam de ce văd mai bine.
Acum, să mergem acolo și să ne pregătim!
Exact cum credeam! Arăți grozav!
Mă simt ca o persoană diferită.
Tocmai a luat naștere Neo Shouta!
Deci acesta e Numărul 3...
Doi Shouta...
E-E împotriva regulilor să intri în camera altui Număr fără permisiune!
Scuze! Era un terorist la TV spunând chestii înfricoșătoare,
deci noi căutam un loc unde să fim în siguranță!
Doi, unde ai fost în tot acest timp?
Într-un loc numit orașul Keimon.
A avut loc un atac terorist acolo, deci am fost evacuați aici.
Dar se pare că nici acest loc nu e cu mult mai sigur.
Aș vrea să te întreb ceva.
P-Pe mine?
Ce fel de persoană e această Mans nu știu cum?
Chloe?
E greu de spus ce gândește.
Ea și restul OF au spus că
the ones behind that airwaves hijack,
Izanami, are evil. Terrorists.
Chloe mi-a salvat viața, dar nu știu care dintre ei are dreptate încă.
Înțeleg.
Mersi!
Oh, tu ești Kuroda Maria, nu?
D-Da!
Cine-i acolo?
Soră mai mare!
C-Chifuyu!
S-Sunt așa de fericită că ești în s-siguranță...
Deci aceea e sora lui Chifuyun, nu?
Mi-am făcut atât de multe griji pentru tine...
Chifuyu, mă bucur că ați reușit să vă întâlniți aici!
Sunt mereu bine!
Dar de ce e îmbrăcată cu acele haine?
Mi-am făcut griji pentru tine!
Mai întâi atacul terorist
și apoi aflăm că mai există încă patru bărbați rezistenți la virus, pe lângă Shouta.
Au fost niște zile nebune.
Creierul meu nu reușește să țină pasul!
O, așa e. Vă mulțumesc că ați a-avut grijă de sora mea mai mică!
Nu, ei bine...
Eu sunt cea care are grijă de ele!
Nu trebuie să te pleci în fața lor!
Ți-am tot spus să nu te mai porți așa!
Vai, Doamne...
O, așa e! Soră mai mare!
Am auzit că ești însoțitoarea Numărului 2, nu-i așa?
Da, dar...
Te-ai împerecheat cu el?
C-C-Ce naiba mă întrebi?!
Nu ai făcut-o încă?
N-Nici măcar nu am vorbit depsre asta...
Doi Shouta
Ce părere ai despre Mizuhara?
Hm... Un softy, exact cum am auzit.
Părea inteligent.
În comparație cu Numărul 1, Hino.
Doar era student la medicină.
Înțeleg.
Dna profesoară e aici?
Dna profesoară Yuzu a fost trimisă într-un loc sigur după atacurile teroriste.
Nu le-am spus nici măcar liderilor OF unde e.
Și acum, ne vom întâlni mâine cu Mans nu știu cum!
Să te culci devreme, bine?
Dna profesoară...
Mizuhara Reito
Scuze că te-am deranjat la ora asta.
Nu, eu ți-am cerut să vii...
Deci? Despre ce voiai să vorbim?
U-Um... would you come with
me to the shower room?
Well...
No, I didn't mean that!
Akane-san and I always do
this so nobody will hear us.
I forgot to explain that to you.
So this is something you don't
want the leaders of UW hearing?
The terrorist attacks, the arrest
of Kihara and the other directors...
The airwaves hijacking...
Too much is happening.
Come with us! Let's escape!
The one who was talking during the airwaves
hijacking was Erisa, the girl I'm looking for.
It didn't occur to you that I might tell UW?
Well...
No, it didn't.
You've always been there for me
since I woke up from cold sleep.
Come with me, and let's find out
what's true and what's a lie!
UW say they're terrorists, but I trust Erisa!
So...
I...
can't go.
Because the UW is important to you?
Wh-What's wrong? What are you—
If you want me to come, then...
Suou-san!
Mate with me right here.
Here? With you?
Wh-What's gotten into you?
If you want me to leave UW
and put myself in danger,
shouldn't it be easy for you?
Do you really not want
to go with me that much?
Why?
You know I'm going to refuse.
I want to go!
But I can't...
Who is this?
A man named Mizuhara Reito.
He's a very important person to everyone.
Mizuhara...
Mizuhara Reito
Suou-san! I'm sorry.
I... didn't mean to make you cry!
Wh-Who are you people?
Reito Mizuhara. You're coming with me.
The girl, too.
I'm Pope. Director Mansfield's aide.
Episodul 11
Evadarea
Chloe-san's aide?
Akane Ryuuzouji and Sui Yamada
have been captured, as well.
Akane-san and Sui-chan? Why?
They, as well as Mira Suou, seem to
have taken quite a liking to you.
We can't have you forgetting your position
and running around doing whatever you like.
You're coming to America with us.
America?
The Izanami terrorists in Japan make
it too dangerous for you to be here.
You're the most valuable person in the world.
We need to keep you safe, of course.
Don't worry. The Director's told me
to ensure you're treated properly.
Get in. We're heading to the airport.
Hi!
How did you—
This won't kill you!
Akane-san! Sui-chan!
Don't move.
This gun is loaded.
I'm not bluffing.
Suou-san!
What happened?
She saved us, too.
Katagiri-san! Kuroda-san!
What are you doing? Hurry.
The GPS has been off since yesterday!
Intercept their communications and find them!
We can't have them getting
on the highway! Hurry!
UW Japan Branch
National Affairs Director Office
The staff are in a big hurry over something.
Did something happen?
One of my girls made a mistake, is all.
It's not an issue.
Now, you didn't come all the way from
Keimon City to say hello, did you?
Did you, Doi-san?
As Shouta-sama's attendant,
I'd like to be the one to speak.
I want to make a deal!
How about it? It's a good deal, right?
I understand your proposal.
It does make sense.
I'll give it full consideration.
So, I have a request...
Go ahead. Anything.
I want you to introduce me to the Three Magi.
I've heard about them.
The three geniuses who run UW.
All of different ages,
and born in different places!
All they have in common is
their brilliant intellects,
and hatred of men, I suppose.
Oh, am I right?
That was a joke!
If Doi-san's willing to show
us a cooperative attitude,
you'll get a chance.
Well, you can set that up for us later.
There is one more thing, though!
What is it?
Are you going to be occupying Japan?
"Occupying"? If I know my Japanese,
that's not the right word.
We've been sent from World HQ
to protect the Japanese people.
You can use whatever words you like.
But I think a Japanese
person should rule Japan.
You're wasting my time.
Just come out and say it.
Would you give that position to me?
The position of National Affairs Director.
This is the place.
Rei-nii!
Mahiru!
I'm glad you made it here!
Everybody helped.
Thank you, everyone.
I wondered what Katagiri-san would want
after she contacted me out of the blue.
She wanted help getting Mahiru out!
You knew Katagiri-san, huh?
I was a Citizen Relations Officer,
so I know a lot of the locals.
Katagiri-san's successor
doesn't care about us all.
Everybody hates UW, but we like her!
What?
Nothing...
But still... I can't believe
Mizuhara Reito is actually your brother!
Sorry for not telling you.
These days everybody's got their secrets.
You're cuter than on TV!
Thanks.
Hey, get your hands off humanity's treasure!
It's not like I'm hurting him.
It's ready?
Yeah. It's a little old, but it works.
Thanks.
Onee-sama... what will you do now?
Listen, everyone.
We'll stay here until sunset.
And then?
I have a plan.
We'll get moving when night falls.
Rest up until then.
Thank you, Katagiri-san.
It's not for your sake.
May we join in?
After you grew up, it felt like
you were going to leave us.
But you can still make that face, huh?
Did you like the old me better?
I'm not sure.
I liked how cute you were!
Even if I do this to you?
Shouta-san... that was amazing.
You all rest up.
How was it?
I'm feeling good.
It's been a few days since you mated.
You had a pretty good time, I bet.
Yeah, it felt great.
What's wrong?
No, it just feels like you've
really grown up! I'm happy!
Did Miss Mansfield get back to us?
"I'll think about it!" was all she said.
I guess it won't be that easy to get the
position of National Affairs Director.
And Number 2 ran, it looks like.
He's braver than I thought.
Things are going to get busy!
We'll have to have the others help!
That's it.
We'll use this ship?
This is as far as Mira and I go.
I have someone who'll get
it out of Japanese waters.
Ask them for the rest.
Katagiri-san, thank you.
Mizuhara Ryuu, your brother...
I'll do everything I can to keep him safe.
Thank you for taking care of my brother.
Thank you!
Reito.
We'll go on ahead.
Me, too!
Um, Suou-san...
Yes?
Thank you for everything.
No, I didn't do anything.
I should thank you.
It was an honor to be by your side.
I'll come back, I promise!
Stay safe until then.
I will.
Reito, this is the person who'll
be getting us out of Japan.
You're...?
Yes. I'm with Izanami.
The mysterious organization?
We'll be heading south.
South? To where?
Taiwan.
You'll meet Erisa there.
Taiwan? Not Niigata?
It's too risky to stay entirely within Japan.
Erisa is on her way.
Erisa...
She said she wanted to see you.
So much has happened since
I woke up from cold sleep.
Suou-san...
are you sure you can't
betray the Japanese branch?
You were thinking about
Suou-san, weren't you?
Mahiru, I didn't...
I'll tell Erisa-chan!
Why?
This is for you.
A tablet?
Who's it from?
No idea.
Why is she mad?
Oh, it's on.
Hino-san!
You're braver than you look!
Sorry for worrying you.
But I think you made the right call.
The blonde chick told me no more
mating and won't even let me leave.
She's basically got me locked up!
I wish you could've come with us...
But we had to act fast.
Well, this tablet's special. My lovely and
talented assistant prepared it for me.
If it uses an underground net
connection, UW can't detect it.
And...
Let me know what you're
up to once in a while!
Yeah, stay safe, Hino-chan.
Say hi to Mahiru-chan for me!
I'm worried about Mizuhara-kun,
but also everybody else who isn't here.
Kitayama-chan, too.
I'll do everything I can
to keep the girls safe.
Yeah, thanks for everything.
Hino-sama, did you want to
leave with Mizuhara-sama?
No...
I can't leave all of you behind.
Hino-sama...
Oh, that girl's Number 1's mating partner.
She's pretty.
Ow!
F-Forgive me!
Was it that hard to get
a single man back home?
Give me another chance.
You know what'll happen if you fail, right?
Yes, ma'am.
UW Japan Branch
National Affairs Director Office
Now then, it's your turn.
I should've kept my eyes on
Miss Suou, as well as Miss Katagiri.
All of this was my plan.
Former attendant Suou had
nothing to do with this.
What beautiful friendship.
Or... is "friendship" not the
right Japanese word for you?
Take them to the cells.
Come.
Now then, it's time for our next step...
In the plan to exterminate all men...
This is the place!
What is this place?
This window's a one-way mirror!
What's this?
I'm giving you a new girl as a
present to celebrate your rebirth!
Choose your favorite from in there.
From in there?
I saw her yesterday...
She was an actress when
you went into cold sleep.
I thought I'd seen her somewhere.
But she's Hino-san's partner, right?
When World HQ came, they told all
the Numbers to stop mating, right?
Except for you.
I want you to let Shouta-sama mate,
with certain conditions.
I see. So that's what you meant.
This world is amazing!
Now, who do you want?
We'll head to the meeting place.
It's beautiful!
It's unbelievable!
Wow.
This is the place.
Erisa...
Vor reuși în sfârșit să te văd?
Reito...
Reito, mă bucur că te-ai vindecat...
Sunt... Sunt așa de fericit că ești bine!
Te-am așteptat...
atât de mult...
Erisa, I'm going to develop
a cure for the MK Virus.
If nobody else will do it,
we'll have to do it ourselves.
And if there's two of us, it'll be more
likely to work than if it was just one!
Right?
Yeah.