Nu se poate face un vaccin
pe baza unui virus inactiv.
Și nu ajung nicăieri cu o
variantă mai slabă a virusului.
La naiba!
Dă-mi o lună.
Trebuie să-mi țin acea promisiune?
Experimentele pe creaturi vii sunt dificile, deci...
Au...
S-Scuze! Eram pierdută în gânduri!
Sunt bine, dar...
U-U-U-Un bărbat!
Ce a fost asta?
Autograful meu?
Da.
Poftim.
Mersi.
El e un pervers care atacă orice femeie vede.
S-Scuză-ne!
Pervers?
Asta e cam nepoliticos.
Ai pus o fată la pământ
când erai pe hol, nu-i așa?
Nu! Ea...
Ești dezgustător.
Nu vei mai primi toată această atenție pentru mult timp doar pentru că ești bărbat.
Ce vrea să însemne asta?
Mizuhara, putem vorbi?
Suou!
Ce vrei să spui prin faptul că nu vei mai fi însoțitoarea mea?
Mizuhara...
Voi sunteți...
Bun, ai venit.
Ți le voi prezenta.
Ele sunt Katagiri Rea și Kuroda Maria.
Vor fi noile tale însoțitoare.
Ce se petrece aici?
Mizuhara Reito, you are
now famous worldwide,
and in a unique position compared
to the rest of the Numbers.
Deci îți vom da mai mult de o însoțitoare.
There's no rule saying you can only have one.
Kuroda Maria is a researcher.
Our technology director
trusts her quite a bit.
She'll be useful in your research.
N-Nice to meet you.
Katagiri will relieve Suou
and see to your needs.
She was a Citizen Relations Officer.
Citizen Relations Officer?
Her job was to interact with the people
on behalf of UW, and keep them pacified.
She knows the outside world well.
If you want to know something, ask her.
I'll be going, then.
Suou-san!
Why did you make her leave?
If you like her that much,
just mate with her.
I will not!
Don't get so mad!
As soon as the paperwork is finished,
Suou Mira will no longer be your attendant.
But she may still stay with
you as a mating candidate.
It's your fault she was forced to leave.
Her most important mission was to get you
to mate with as many girls as possible.
She failed, so of course she lost the job.
If you don't like it, then why
not go mate with someone?
And while I'll permit you to
continue your research into a cure,
if you're not going to mate with anyone,
your other freedoms will be restricted.
That's not fair!
Mira!
It's been a long time.
Yes.
You've lost weight.
Take care of Mizuhara-sama.
You don't need to worry about that man.
He's just a loser who only
thinks of women as tools.
That's not who he is.
Goodbye.
Wait! Listen, Mira!
If you let your guard down around a man...
You're as beautiful as ever, aren't you?
Like time's stopped.
Um, Kuroda-san?
Y-Y-Yes?
What is there where we're going?
It's called Keimon City.
There is a hot spring.
A hot spring? Is that all?
Um... somebody important in
the MK Virus research field.
Somebody important?
What are you doing?
Sorry!
I'll go change.
You should just go over there.
I'm not Mizuhara-san's attendant right now.
You've got a difficult
personality, too, don't you?
I'm sorry, Kuroda-san.
No, I'm sorry.
I'm not used to men.
Is it okay if we try to
be a little more casual?
We're close, age-wise.
Okay...
Kuroda-san, you said you
study virology, right?
Yes.
I know a decent amount about
the MK Virus, I think.
The MK Virus was artificially created!
How do you think it was born?
There are three theories
on the origin of viruses.
The regressive hypothesis,
The escape hypothesis,
and the virus-first hypothesis.
But we don't know yet.
And since we don't know, "how it was born"
may not even be the right phrase to use.
It's possible that something that's existed for
eons only just now came in contact with humanity.
In fact, in biology, viruses aren't
even treated as living creatures...
She's suddenly much more talkative...
Is it possible that a human made it?
You've got an interesting theory.
Put on your clothes.
We might find some clues where we're going.
Wh-What do you mean?
Keimon City is where the first victim
of the MK Virus in Japan appeared.
It's huge!
The lake's so big!
There's a group of students on a trip here.
But beyond that, we have
the place to ourselves.
I heard we're having
spiny lobster for dinner!
Let's go play ping-pong! Ping-pong!
Forget that. Let's hit the hot springs!
We're not here to play!
This place is pretty...
I wish Mahiru-chan could've come.
We can't let an outsider tag along.
Creating an environment that relaxes
Reito is part of your job, right?
My job is to manage his daily life
and help him focus on viral research.
We disagree there, then.
Um...
That looks fun! Let me join in!
Knock it off!
I wish I could've gone into
the open-air bath, too...
A holographic open-air bath!
This isn't bad either.
Why...?
It's fine. It's more fun
if we all go in together.
There's no "Men's Bath" and
"Women's Bath" these days.
I'll leave...
Hold on.
I'll wash your back as thanks
for all the help you give me.
No, you're the one who's
helping me all the time!
It's the other way around!
Then maybe I'll ask you for help, then.
Wash our backs.
It's so nice, having Reito-sama wash my back!
Okay, all clean.
Thank you!
G-Go ahead.
O-Okay...
She's like a different person.
Does her personality change when
she's talking about the virus?
Sorry! Was it too hot?
I'll do the rest myself.
Go ahead.
Sit down.
She has such a pretty back.
Why not have him wash yours, too?
Not a chance.
Okay, I'm last, then.
It's finally over...
Not that.
My skin is sensitive.
Will you wash me with your hands?
That feels so good. You're good at this.
I-I'll wash it off.
Not yet. Here, too.
You can do the legs, too, can't you?
Run your hands over every little bit.
And lastly this.
I'm leaving!
Do the rest yourself!
And I was so close, too.
It's been so long since
I've seen Ms. Taniguchi.
I'm Katagiri Rea with UW's Japan branch.
This is...
I know.
We're here to talk about your husband...
I told you everything I could.
I saw your press conference.
Thank you.
But it's not my problem.
My husband's not coming back,
even if you do make a cure.
Taniguchi-san, can you
tell us what your husband
was doing just before
he contracted the virus?
No.
Please! This is for all humanity's sake!
You took his body and sliced it into pieces!
Ma'am, that's called an autopsy. We have
to do it to find out what happened...
I don't care.
He hated doctors.
Taniguchi-san!
Don't touch me.
What do I have to do to get you to help me?
You can screw me.
I'm joking, of course.
Leave.
The MK Virus appeared in multiple
spots all around the world at once.
There's a theory that it was bioterrorism
by a nation-state or terrorist group.
A theory it arose naturally.
And even a theory that the Earth
itself created it to purge humanity.
But we don't know where it came from.
Ms. Taniguchi's husband was
the first victim in Japan.
Episodul 5
Prima victimă
He hated technology and had no GPS on him.
If we knew what he was doing and where he was
before he got sick,
it might give us a clue, but...
She greatly distrusts UW.
The government at the time was really rough.
The person you care about was here.
Why not meet him, Erisa?
Spitalul Central al orașului Keimon
You never learn.
It doesn't matter how many times
you come. It won't change a thing.
Please!
If we know what your husband was doing,
we might know where the virus came from!
You should just stop making
vaccines and start making kids.
Your biggest job right now is making kids.
I'm sure you're having some fun with
the crowd of girls behind you, though.
I'm...
Mizuhara hasn't mated, that is, had any
sexual relations with women after waking up.
The rest of you, leave.
I don't get it.
Most people in your situation would be going
at it like a rabbit with any girl he could find.
You'd have enough time left
over to research the medicine.
I don't have the kind of
personality you'd need
to be having fun with girls
while doing research.
You gay?
No.
There are a lot of girls who are very pretty.
And honestly, I'd love to
do what they want me to.
So why?
That's what would benefit the world the most.
There's a girl I'm in love with.
I know it's selfish,
but I figured if I put my efforts into
finding a cure for the MK Virus,
it would make up for it.
We're done talking.
It feels so good to be outside!
If Rea-san finds out I brought you to the
open-air bath, she'll get mad at me!
It's fine! Nobody's here.
Don't blame me if something happens.
Taniguchi-san managed to
avoid telling me anything.
Come on, hurry!
Reito-sama, hide!
Um, this bath is in use...
She's so cute!
The students?
I'll just have to hide in here for a little.
Oh!
U-Um...
I'll be going—
Leave, and I'll scream.
If you don't want to
cause a ruckus, sit down.
Why are you wearing a yukata in the sauna?
Because I'm an exchange
student that loves Japan!
The rich depths of the Japanese heart!
I don't think that's how it works.
Now, let's play a game.
If I leave the sauna first,
I won't tell anybody you're here.
And if I leave first...
You'll have to do one thing I tell
you to do, Mizuhara Reito-san.
She knows me. Of course she would.
Let's see who can last longer.
It's so hot.
I should introduce myself.
I'm Chloe. I'm an exchange
student from America.
Y-Your Japanese is very good.
A little weird, but good.
I love Japan.
Would you like to have sex with me?
Oh, you call it "mating," right?
You shouldn't try to endure
things for too long.
That goes for the sauna,
and for a woman's temptation.
I'm good at self-control.
What about you? You should
probably give up and leave soon.
Your samurai soul is impressive...
Have some water.
I should call Akane-san.
Wait a second.
Feed me with your mouth.
No, no.
I'll go get the nurse!
If you don't... I'll scream.
Reito-sama, I brought help!
Reito-sama is mating with a
strange woman before any of us!
No, this is...
Reito-sama, you traitor!
Sorry for bothering you.
You're such an animal.
You've got it wrong.
That was fun.
It was an act?
American girls are strong.
It'd take more than that to knock me out.
Now let's have a nice long
chat, Mizuhara Reito-san.
Harder!
Sorry.
Please.
Thank you.
There's a bakery on the corner
just outside this building, kid.
I want a white bean jam pastry from there.
I can send someone from UW...
I'm not eating it unless he gets it for me.
All right. I'll go.
Mizuhara-san!
You.
I want to talk with you privately.
Come in.
You know about Tachibana Erisa, right?
She's Mizuhara-sama's childhood friend.
That's not what I meant.
I'll ask a different question, then.
Tell me what that kid's like.
Why do you want to know?
Just answer me.
Don't you want to help him?
Mizuhara-sama is very selfish.
It's wonderful that he's working on a cure.
But I think he could mate at least once or
twice a week even while doing his research.
With the world on the brink of destruction,
having someone he's in love with is not
a good enough reason to refuse mating.
He really is selfish.
But not many people could do that.
He has the same desires as any normal man.
But he's always fighting them.
And he can keep being selfish
in the face of the entire world.
He may really be able to save the world.
You know him well.
Well, I'm always watching him.
I got it.
You're late.
I don't want it now.
Are you never going to have kids, then?
If it really will help humanity,
I might, some day.
You'll give up on the girl you love.
No. Even if I did mate, I'd only
do it because they wanted me to.
My heart wouldn't change.
I only love one girl.
I'm tired today.
Come back tomorrow.
I'll make you listen to
me talk about old times.
Okay.
I would like to talk about
my husband once in a while.
I'll come! I promise!
No one would fault you for giving up on saving
the world and being with the man you love.
You're so stubborn!
If you don't hurry, you'll lose him!
He had a whole bunch of pretty
ladies with him today—
Even if Reito falls in
love with someone else,
I'll only ever love him.
You're both very similar.
Spitalul Central al orașului Keimon
Her condition suddenly worsened!
She was doing just fine until today.
V-Va fi bine, nu?
E în comă. It could go either way.
Um, this is from her.
Ce este?
Dnă Taniguchi, ce ați pățit?
Dacă se va întâmpla ceva,
dăi asta acelui băiat.
Taniguchi-san.
I'll take it.
I'll come give it back when she's better.
Aveți grijă de ea până atunci.
Bine...
Episodul 6
Comploturi conectate