Bună dimineața.
Bună dimineața...
Acea cămașă...
Scuze.
Ți-am împrumutat-o.
Nu avem școală azi.
Haideți să ne petrecem timpul împreună relaxându-ne.
Asta dacă nu te deranjează...
Desigur că nu!
Bine.
A trecut o săptămână de când am făcut-o prima oară cu dna profesoară.
Și acum, o facem în fiecare zi.
Corpul doamnei profesoare devine din ce în ce mai bun.
Dacă am putea rămâne așa pentru totdeuna...
Da.
Vrei s-o facem din nou?
M-am simțit atât de împlinit în acel moment.
Nu aveam nicio idee ce urma să se întâmple...
Doar voi primi...
Renunță odată.
Toată lumea!
Shouta-sama's going to be
participating in gym class today.
Do I really have to?
It's been over a week since
you woke up from cold sleep.
You need to get some exercise in.
Um, I don't really exercise...
You don't need it because you're
getting plenty with Yuzu-sensei?
Of course you'd know.
Since you're the one who set us up together.
Well... Yuzu-sensei is a little shy,
so I did give her a little push.
I am grateful for that.
Then do what I want you to today.
Swimming's fun.
One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight...
Two, two, three, four,
Other side!
It feels like they're all staring at me.
One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight...
Two, two, three, four,
Next!
One, two, three...
Am I being too self-conscious?
You can do it, Shunka!
Akira, hang in there!
Toudou, 25.72 seconds.
Hiiragi, 26.03 seconds.
I guess I couldn't beat
you after all, Aki-chin.
You almost had me.
Shunka, you've gotten faster.
Shunka-chan, Toudou-san,
they both have such amazing bodies.
Those commoners are wasting their time.
No matter how hard they work, I'll be #1.
Um, are you competing or
something, Chifuyu-chan?
What? You hadn't heard?
Well, you've got something
to look forward to, then.
They used to call me the Flying Fish
of the Rhine River. I'm sure to win.
Flying fish don't live in rivers.
Doi-san, I'm so sorry about yesterday.
Were you okay where that ball hit you?
Yeah, I'm just fine.
Don't worry.
I'm glad.
Um...
If I get first place... um...
If you didn't have that massive rack,
your time would probably be even better.
Why you...
Wait! Wait! Wait! Wait! Wait!
My legs... My legs aren't
touching the bottom!
Chifuyu! It's shallow
enough that you can stand.
Ichijou! 24.88 seconds!
Ichijou Natsu gets first place!
It's Ichijou-san.
Natsu, wow!
Wow...
Sorry. I have some work I have to do today.
I see.
Tomorrow, then.
Yeah.
See you tomorrow.
Come in.
Hello!
I-Ichijou-san?
I'll be staying starting today.
Um...
Shouta-sama! I forgot to tell you!
Karen-chan, what's going on?
The air conditioner broke
in one of the rooms.
So we're changing the rooms!
But there's just one room fewer than we need.
So she'll be staying in your room!
But...
I'm sure she'll repay the favor somehow!
But for now, she'll be staying with you!
Was that what everyone was competing
for at the pool today?!
Ding-ding!
The right to spend a week in your room.
It's more fun if you make it a game, right?
A week from now it'll be a different girl,
so get along with her.
Hey, Karen-chan!
So... we'll be staying
together for a week, okay?
Yeah.
Good morning.
Good morning...
I couldn't really sleep.
And what's all this stuff about
changing my roommate every week?
Maybe I shouldn't have been going
to Yuzu-sensei's room every night.
Is she mad?
Sorry. Can you look away while I change?
Sorry!
Ichijou-san, you're not changing?
We'll be late.
Um... Uh...
Can I ask you for something?
If there's something I can do...
Can...
Can you help me change?
My maids would always change me at home.
I've been trying to do it on my own
since I came to this school, but...
It takes so long, though,
so I had my roommate do it.
She really is rich.
I'm sorry... I'm such a failure.
Th-That's not true.
If that's how your family is,
it's not your fault.
I'll help you.
Raise your hands.
I-I've got Yuzu-sensei!
I can't look at this!
This scar...
That was a big surprise this morning!
The Ichijou clan's an old one.
They're not like most families.
I can't believe she can't
even get dressed on her own.
It's going to be a long week.
To her, letting other people
see her naked is normal.
It didn't bother her, did it?
It bothered me more than her.
We haven't talked at school.
Why not help her change in the bath?
S-Sorry!
Don't worry! I'll go wash my face, okay?
Oh, Doi-chin!
Shunka-chan!
Oh, I've been meaning to ask...
What is it, Doi-chin?
When Ichijou-san takes a bath,
how does she change?
You want to take a bath with Natssun?
No!
I'm kidding!
She always went with her roommate,
who would dress her.
I see.
Doi-chin, I'm heading to class.
Did you see what was on TV yesterday?
Come to think of it...
It's hard to believe I'm talking
to girls so naturally like this.
That sounds like Ichijou-san.
It's not funny!
Sorry, sorry.
Her family has some issues.
Try to help if you can.
Sure, but...
Can I come to your room tonight?
Sorry, not today, either.
Sensei, are you avoiding me?
Of course not!
If you're upset about me having a girl
in my room, I'll tell Karen-chan.
Um... it's a biological thing? For girls?
You know what I mean, right?
Of course! Sorry!
I wasn't thinking about your side of things.
No, sorry for making you worry.
Anyway, you need to make sure you're getting
along with her, and the other girls.
But all I need is you...
It makes me happy to hear that.
But if you only give me attention,
the others will get angry with me.
I'll call you later.
I don't think any of the others except
Karen-chan know about Sensei and me.
But do they really like me?
I can't sleep...
Maybe Ichijou-san likes me...?
Doi-san?
Can I sleep in your bed?
I was able to handle it last night,
but to tell the truth, I can't sleep
unless someone else is in my bed.
I-If that's the case, then...
You're a really nice person, huh?
A-Am I?
You saw the scar on my butt today, right?
It's from when I was little,
but it hasn't gone away.
It bothers me, but you didn't bring it up.
I was supposed to get
married after high school.
To a man 20 years older than me,
for my father's business.
But both my future husband and my
father died five years ago to the MK Virus.
I'm a bad woman...
I'm glad the virus came.
Because now, I can be with you.
I loved you from the
moment I set eyes on you!
You're not a bad woman.
I'm glad the world turned out like this, too!
I'm so happy.
Take off my clothes.
I'm used to having the servants do it,
but when you look at me
my heart beats faster.
Forget it. Let's just see where this goes!
Time for our next segment.
Ever since he woke up,
Ever since he woke up, Mizuhara-san
Mizuhara-san has been
spending his days working
has been spending his days working
to develop a cure for the virus.
He had curry for dinner.
I'd like to have him as a grandson.
I'd like to have him as a grandson.
If I were just 10 years younger...
He's kind of like,
the type you want to protect!
-
He's kind of like, the type you want to protect!
He has such cute eyes!
Reito-kun, work hard at your research!
I read books.
Huh?!
Huh!?
Um...
I like girls who are
serious and hard-working.
Is there any demand for this program?
Ninety-four percent of the country watches it.
I can't believe I said
that to the whole world...
Let me see Reito-sama!
He's not here.
There's another big crowd today.
Many want to mate.
Will you look at the list?
I'll pass.
Oh, did you see Mahiru?
About that...
Mahiru-san is spending a lot
of time in the refugee area.
Refugee area?
I've been ignoring it until now,
but if they find out she's your sister,
there's no telling what would happen,
so I'll ask her to stop.
I see.
I apologize for the trouble.
Good morning.
Morning.
Want some?
Thank you!
What's wrong?
Would you help me drink it?
What should I do?
Thinking about leaving
your room makes me sad.
Mahiru is headed to the refugee camp?
Mizuhara-kun!
Hino-san, hey there.
Look at this!
What is this?
This is...
I'm gonna be a dad soon!
Congratulations!
If it's a boy, it's good
news for the whole world!
We don't know which it'll be yet.
Sorry.
Don't worry about it.
A kid, huh?
I can't even imagine it.
You're starting to get a
little frustrated, aren't you?
What are you doing?
It's not healthy to have
blue balls, you know.
Shouta-kun, have you been doing okay?
Yes. I was sad I couldn't see you.
Me, too.
Are things going well with Ichijou-san?
Yes.
Um, Sensei, I—
It's okay.
Shouta-kun, you belong to everyone.
You can't help it.
Everyone? What do you mean?
Do you know something?
Just what I said.
Ask Kamiya-san!
Sensei!
It's rare for you to want to talk to me.
I've been thinking...
About what?
So many strange things have happened
since I woke up from cold sleep.
Yup.
The world's changed a lot
over the past five years.
I thought, at first, you were lying to
me about there not being any other men.
But nobody would benefit from
lying to me on this level.
I don't know what the
girls are thinking, but...
It didn't feel like Sensei or
Ichijou-san were putting on an act.
So... almost all the men in the world
have died except for a few in cold sleep.
That's true, I think.
Of course!
I wouldn't lie to you.
Are there other men besides me who
have resistance to the MK Virus?
Hmm...
It's a wide world.
There might be at least one.
This school is a way to experiment
on me somehow, right?
Why do you think that?
Resistance to the MK Virus makes
me incredibly rare and valuable.
I'm sure you did a lot of tests
on me while I was asleep.
But you don't know how the virus
works or why I'm resistant.
Go on.
You aren't locking me up and
experimenting on me for two reasons:
one, out of respect for
my human rights, and two,
if I killed myself out of stress,
the loss would be incalculable.
So this school...
The point of this school is to bring
together girls that you think I'd like,
to keep me in a good mood while you get data
to help you to fight the MK Virus, right?
If that's the case, that's not fair
to Yuzu-sensei and Ichijou-san!
You're using them!
I'll help you any way I can,
so leave them out—
This might be the right time.
Let's go to the classroom.
Episodul 4
Secretul școlii
Okay, everybody!
Class is temporarily canceled!
Your guess back there was
close, but not right.
I'm impressed with how close you got to the
truth with the limited information you have!
Then...
As you guessed, this whole school
was put together for you.
For you to mate with as
many girls as you can!
M-Mate?
Impregnate? Sex?
Artificial insemination doesn't work.
The MK Virus may be to blame.
We don't know if your immunity
will be inherited by your child,
but if we don't have you
mate and spread your genes,
humanity probably won't survive!
We did a lot of prep work before
bringing these girls here.
None of them dislike you.
Actually, they're all very interested in you!
So none of them are being coerced.
If you manage to impregnate one of them,
we'll take good care of both the
mom and kid, so don't worry!
In other words, you and we
both want the same thing!
That's...
I'm getting dizzy.
A picture's worth a thousand words!
I'll show you how much they all want you!
Stand up!
Everybody, take off your clothes!
I'll help you as much as I can,
so make lots of babies and save humanity!
Now, which girl will you choose?
The school with Number 3 is going well.
Forget that!
This is the one we have to talk about!
True. If we're not going
to force Number 2 to mate,
there's no need for her to be his attendant.
It's settled, then.
We'll remove Suou Mira from her position
as Mizuhara Reito's personal attendant.
Episodul 5
Prima victimă