We'll arrive in Japan by tomorrow night.
Great. I'm all set here, as well.
Mizuhara Reito's worldwide broadcast
UW Simultaneous World Broadcast
showed the world that at least one man
with resistance to the MK Virus exists.
World HQ wants him in America immediately.
Yes. That's the order the leadership gave.
But the Japan branch is
hiding other men, as well.
Our investigation revealed that.
And that's why I was brought here?
Yes. Stay sharp upon your arrival.
Yes, ma'am.
So this is the messenger from UW World HQ?
Yes. All we know is her title
and her name, Mansfield.
The Peacekeeping Activities Bureau.
Officially, it's an organization that
monitors potential threats to UW's leadership.
But the rumors say they shut down terrorists
in Australia and Canada by force.
Are they coming to search for Izanami,
that terrorist organization?
HQ wouldn't send a messenger just for that.
What are they planning?
Look at this.
We've seen a lot of strange things happening
around Number 2, Mizuhara Reito.
What we found from Mansfield's background
is that she is former military,
and was promoted at incredible speed.
The one thing I hear about Miss Mansfield
is that you don't want to mess with her.
But with all the Numbers in our
possession, we have the initiative.
Just follow the plan.
You don't need to tell me.
Good morning, Doi-kun.
Morning.
Good morning.
She's today's girl, huh?
Good mor—
Come to my room today.
What's wrong?
I'm sorry. I'm on my period...
Okay.
Some other time.
Yes, that's right.
Sorry! I've got another call!
Were you talking with someone?
Just a personal thing.
I see.
Anything going on?
The World HQ messenger I told you
about before is coming tomorrow.
They're finally here, huh?
I don't really need to do
anything special, right?
Correct.
Anything to report?
Nope! Everything's going great!
All right. I'll end the call, then.
Now then, who will help
me more if I join them?
There, there.
Jeez...
How many times have you
washed your mouth out today?
It just bothers me.
Sorry for making you do the unpleasant stuff.
Did he force himself on you?
Nope.
I just waved him off.
So? How are things on your end?
Going well. UW World HQ's
messenger is almost here.
We'll put the plan into effect soon.
I'm so happy...
It's been so long since
you took my clothes off!
Now, let me do it.
Girls' Dorm Bath
Doing it in the girls' dorm
bath is pretty exciting.
This way.
Wow, it's really big.
Welcome.
Shou-chin, I'll wash you clean.
Thanks.
Hey, Shou-chin, I was the only one who didn't
get to join in at the pool last time.
Give me a reward.
Of course.
Shou-chin!
Shunka-san, why don't you and
Shouta-san have fun together?
O-Okay. It's so slick...
I feel like I'm going to slip!
Girls' Dorm Bath
This is so great.
Let me join in, too!
Yanagi-san!
Hey, you're with Koyu-chin's
faction, aren't you?
There aren't any "factions"!
And if there were,
I'd be with my own faction!
Anyway, during the swimming race, you were
using me as a way to have fun, weren't you?
I noticed!
Doi-chan, come on.
Remember the taste of my body.
Let's all do it together, then.
After that, I indulged myself
in every lustful urge.
In the library.
Nurse's Office
In the nurse's office.
In the middle of class.
Anything I wanted to do to a girl, I did.
The things holding me back
gradually begin to break...
Please no ghosts! Please no ghosts!
Please no ghosts!
It's okay, Sui-chan!
Boo!
This is an old hospital! There's ghosts!
If you scare me again I'll get really mad!
So we ostensibly came to
Keimon City to visit Taniguchi-san.
But the Directors have
to be watching us, right?
I submitted the paperwork to have
you come here, Mizuhara-kun.
We got permission easily, too.
It'll be fine. Probably.
There's no time to waste worrying about it.
The secrets to humanity's
survival may be here.
So anyway, what are your
feelings towards Mira?
You know she's into you, right?
W-Well...
I think she's a wonderful person.
You know, I've been thinking...
Are you a virgin?
It would explain a lot, I think.
So, what's the deal?
I'll leave it to your imagination.
Oh, I thought you had an iron will,
but you're actually just a virgin!
Got it, let's go.
Don't just decide that...
Akane-san, don't tease Reito-sama!
A moving corpse!
Don't hurt me!
Go away, ghosts! Go away, ghosts!
Go away, ghosts!
I'm kidding.
Go away, ghosts! Go away,
ghosts! Go away, ghosts!
Are you okay, Sui-chan!
Reito-sama! I'm scared!
You scare me more than the ghosts.
This air duct is big enough
for a person to fit through!
Welcome to Japan.
Thank you for coming to
greet me, Director Kihara.
Your Japanese is very good, Ms. Mansfield.
No, I'm not Ms. Mansfield.
I'm her aide. She's elsewhere.
In a very important place to this country.
You know what I mean, right?
It really is cramped...
Yeah.
What? What's wrong?
Did you see that?
No, I didn't see anything!
This way!
Look at that...
What's a place like this
doing beneath a hospital?
Huh? Is that...?
Let me see!
What?
Akane-san! If you climb
on top of me like that...
Reito-sama!
Oh, my. Fancy seeing you here.
You're...
So you did find this place.
Kuroda, what the hell do
you think you're doing?
Th-The Technical Director...
Wh-What is this place?
Who could even say?
I bet you already know, don't you?
Are Reona and Hatsumi and
the other girls here?
Is this where you made the MK Virus?
I always wanted to say this line...
"Now that you've seen this place,
you won't leave alive!"
Soldiers?
I'm glad I made it in time.
Chloe-san!
We meet again, Mizuhara Reito-san.
I'm Chloe Mansfield,
from UW World Headquarters.
You're with UW World Headquarters?
Yes. I had a lot of fun at
the hot springs, though.
I'm in charge of the UW Department
of Peacekeeping Operations.
In charge? At her age?
Ever since your big announcement,
I pretended to be an exchange student
and investigated what's going on Japan.
That included what you,
and the five directors were up to.
Oh, right! We need to treat her!
She attempted to delete you.
We didn't have a choice!
Reito-sama!
I see.
This factory has a bomb inside.
There's no time to disarm it.
Let's go!
Who set the bomb?
Reito-sama! We need to get out!
This way! This way!
Get in!
The car? The helicopter? Which?
We were so close to finding
something on the MK Virus, too!
It's Hakuro's turn today!
No, it's mine!
And it's got nothing to do
with you, anyway, Koyuki-san!
Where is Kamiya-chin when we need her?!
Everyone, I have a suggestion!
All set. Now...
Okay, Shou-chin. Go ahead.
Let's all do it. The four of us.
Okay, everyone... now turn
your butts toward me.
The view is amazing!
Who could've imagined this, five years ago?
They called me Dojii. They made fun of me.
And now... I've got one
hot girl after another.
None of this felt real after
I woke up from cold sleep.
But now there's no doubting it.
This world is my paradise!
And I'm going to enjoy
every last second of it!
Orgy! Orgy! Or-Or-Orgy!
Episodul 9
Petrecerea desfrâului
This whole school exists for
Shouta-sama to indulge himself.
Every girl here is just
someone for him to snack on!
So we can't have the food running away.
When will you let me go back to Tokyo?
Soon. Shouta-sama is breaking
out of his shell.
When he does, you and
the rest of the girls...
What are your intentions
for making this insane place?!
If you just want babies, there are other ways!
Well, of course...
Mizuhara-san,
there's something I've always wondered
since you showed yourself to the world.
Are you really the only male
who can survive right now?
Does she already know about
Hino-san and the other men?
Why did the Japanese directors decide to
show you to the world without telling us?
And what was that strange facility?
Why did it explode?
There's a simple answer.
And someone as smart as you
has already figured it out.
As you're aware, Ms. Hope,
the Technical Director is a bit of an oddball.
She seemed to be doing some kind of
mysterious research in Keimon City.
But we have nothing to do with it.
Director Kihara.
I believe you knew all about it.
In fact, you were the one giving
the orders, weren't you?
Let me ask another question, then.
There are people other than Mizuhara Reito
who possess resistance to
the MK Virus, aren't there?
Ms. Hope, we're placing you under arrest.
So you've shown yourselves
for who you really are, then.
Do you know who you're pointing guns at?
Director, we're not your personal army.
We work for UW.
That's right!
Don't tell me...
Director-General Shutou has been telling
us all about what you've been up to.
That's right!
You... traitor!
How scary! Don't get mad at me!
On behalf of Chloe Mansfield,
the head of UW Peacekeeping Operations,
I'm placing you three under arrest.
You're under arrest for manufacturing
and spreading the MK Virus,
for ignoring orders from UW World HQ,
and violating your duty
to report your activities,
illegally exploiting the Japanese people...
The list could go on forever.
It's very likely that facility
was where the MK Virus was made.
D-Did they destroy it to cover their tracks?
It's the obvious assumption.
What they did is blasphemous!
Inhuman! Truly frightening.
If we knew how their MK Virus
production process worked,
maybe we could've made a cure!
It was quite likely.
But the Japanese directors were
lying to you this whole time.
They were supposed to be helping
you make a cure, right?
The MK Virus was artificially created!
Erisa was put in danger when
she investigated the MK Virus!
And there are other unpleasant occurrences
as a result of the Japanese director's plan.
Are you aware of the worldwide
incidents of terrorism?
No.
The huge decrease in population has
drastically reduced human productivity,
creating gaps in economic wealth
and widespread discontent.
And then everyone finds out that the only
surviving man is completely under UW's control.
When Ms. Kihara of the Japanese
branch revealed you to the world,
it caused more terrorist
acts all over the globe.
You know about Erisa Tachibana, right?
Look at this.
She's currently with a terrorist
group opposing UW rule.
N-No...
I guess there'll always
be festivals like these.
Hey, Reito! I want to try that!
Look! I got a big one! It's so cute!
You're right...
This takoyaki's so great!
Want another?
Erisa? What's wrong?
I feel sad for some reason...
I saw something about the state of
the world on the news the other day.
When I think of the fact that
there are kids in regions without good
medicine, who can't eat like this...
That's why you're becoming a doctor, right?
You can join an NGO or work on
a vaccine for a fatal illness.
That's why you're studying
so hard all the time.
So nobody will blame you
for having some fun today.
And there's seaweed in your teeth.
You always do this!
What happened, Erisa?
Is she a little better now?
She has a cute face when
she's like this, at least...
U-Um...
Another explosion?
That's my sister's school!
I just got a report from
one of my women in Tokyo.
One of the men who are
resistant to the MK Virus,
the ones the Japanese
branch calls the Numbers,
was just kidnapped by terrorists.
Episodul 10
Cele două numere