senseishon wo makiokoshichau
I'll create a sensation
In a vector way of love
renai kan no bekutoru e
I'm heading forward in a straight line
icchokusen ni mukattekun da
Maidens Are Falling for Me: The Two Elders
Can you follow me?
tsuite koreru kana
I know that we'll see eye to eye
tatoeba me to me
attari shita shunkan
hyotto shite nante kitai
The classroom is like a new highway
kyoushitsu wa marude
Acchi to kocchi tobikau
shisen no haiwei
For some reason those invisible eyes have reflections in them
mienai hazu no
kakushou teki sougo rikai
hitomi ni nazeka utsutte
Don't stumble once you find a junction
jankunshon no naka de
kakushin teki nabigeeshon
mayowanaide iku yo
Let's go!
tsurechigaenai
We can't pass each other,
konna ni chikaku ja butsukachau yo
we'll bump into each other if we're that close
ippotsuuko ja yada
I don't want a one way street
kurosu oobaa sore de ii yo
We can just do a crossover
senseishionaru na impakuto ni notte
I took a ride on a sensational impact
renai kibun kasanareba
And our loves crossed ways
ichokusen de mukattekun da
I'm heading forward in a straight line
supiido agete
Increasing speed
kurosu oobaa shita kokoro butsukatte
We did a crossover, and hit our hearts out
koi mo makiokosu
And love sprouted
Who is she?
Is she a transfer student?
She looks so elegant and mature.
I believe some of you are forgetting how impolite it is to stare.
The Knight Princess!
My apologies!
How do you do, our knight?
Sorry to surprise you like that.
Are you okay?
Oh, yes.
Really?
Glad to hear that.
Have you explored the school grounds yet, Kisakinomiya Chihaya-san?
No, I haven't.
Huh, how do you know my name?
Kajiura-sensei told me.
I'm Nanahara Kaoruko from 3-C.
We're in the same class.
The same dormitory building as well.
Nanahara-san?
Just Kaoruko is fine.
Come on, I'll show you around!
We're—
Well, none of the students actually call it "Seio Girls' Academy."
We just say "the school" or "Seio."
We're a bit different from other schools, don't you think?
To be honest, it's too early for me to say.
What's the word for something that doesn't follow social norms?
Otherworldly?
Yeah, that's what I meant.
Some people call it a greenhouse too.
Really?
Perhaps, in both good and bad ways.
Students must be in class before the bell rings and be ready to start class once it does.
Have you forgotten that rule already,
Nanahara Kaoruko-san, Kisakinomiya Chihaya-san?
My deepest apologies, Kajiura-sensei.
Kisakinomiya-san!
How is it?
Do you think you could get used to it?
I don't know yet.
I see.
Your mother put you in my care.
Don't be afraid to ask for help.
Correct!
Everyone, please be quiet!
In this case, you have to pay attention to the process, and...
You're amazing.
Everyone, please translate the second chapter and turn it in the day after tomorrow.
Class dismissed.
All rise.
Are your parents foreigners?
No.
My grandmother is a westerner.
I see.
Sorry for prying.
It's just that you're so fluent in English.
I'm not particularly fluent in English.
It's just that all I've ever done is studying.
I envy you.
You can translate the whole second chapter easily.
If you'd like, I could tutor you.
Are you serious?
Yes.
How about tomorrow after school?
Oh my, are you already asking her out on a date?
Kaori-san!
S-Stop that!
I was just...
You can't do that, Kaoruko.
You shouldn't cheat on homework.
Geez, Kaori-san!
You were eavesdropping, weren't you?
But you were speaking so loud.
Stop it already!
This is Kamichika Kaori-san.
She also lives in our dormitory.
And this is—
I already know.
She's Kisakinomiya Chihaya-san, right?
Today is only her first day,
but she's already the talk of the town.
I suppose it is unusual to have
someone transfer in their senior year.
On top of that, my hair is silver.
Kaori-san, don't bully her!
I was only jealous because you
didn't take long to get close to her.
Ugh, stop teasing!
Let's head back to the dormitory now.
I'm starving!
Okay.
Wait, it's raining!
You're right.
It's a drizzle.
Fine, mist-like drops.
The dormitory isn't far. We can run there.
It is, isn't it?
Chihaya-san?
Are you okay?
Yuu, open your eyes!
You're drenched! You'll catch a cold!
Are you an angel?
No.
Wake up. If you stay out here, you'll get hypothermia.
I like the rain.
Let me sleep.
Should I call Hatsune from the dormitory?
No, we should get her inside first.
Chihaya-san?
You're pretty strong.
She—I mean Yuu-san, is quite light.
Yuu-chan, what have you done?
You know very well about your own condition, right?
You have to keep your body warm.
Do you want soup?
No thanks.
Okay.
For now, let's move to your room.
Oh my, she should know that
Hatsune-oneesama would be worried about her.
Yuu-san didn't eat her breakfast today either.
She didn't? Umm...
Sorry for not introducing myself!
I'm Kudo Hinata.
Kisakinomiya Chihaya.
Hinata-san, whom should I ask for
permission to use the kitchen?
Uh, you don't need to ask to use the kitchen.
Yuu-chan, you won't get better if you don't eat.
I'm fine.
Come in.
How do you feel now?
If it's not too much to ask, would you like to eat dessert together?
What is this?
It's called Eaton Mess.
It's a traditional dessert from Eaton College, England.
It's a mixture of strawberry, cream, and pieces of baked meringue.
Wow!
They look like cherry blossom...
petals!
Bon appétit!
Go ahead!
It's delicious.
It's sweet.
Would you like tea?
Yes, thank you!
I'm really grateful, Chihaya-san.
It's been a while since I've been able to talk so much with Yuu.
You're exaggerating.
All I did was bring her a dessert.
It's the first time I've seen her ask for seconds.
Kaoruko, you're doing it again.
What?
Oh, no.
Kaoruko-san, did you catch a cold too?
N-No, I'm fine.
It's nothing.
She just has a habit of staring at people.
S-Stop it, Kaori-san!
I just thought that you were amazing.
I mean, you even knew how to make sweets.
You're the embodiment of what a lady should be.
Oh my, it looks like she's sunk her fangs into you already.
Kaori-san!
I guess it's a fever after all.
Not you too, Hatsune!
Thank you very much!
What?!
It's my honor to be praised by someone like yourself.
Um, ah...
At Seio, underclassmen are to assist their seniors as a little sister would assist her elders,
and it is an upperclassman's job is to guide her juniors like an older sister.
Therefore, I'm your "little sister" here.
"Little sister"?
I served you as your maid back home.
I will continue to serve you here.
Come, I've prepared everything.
It's time for your bath.
The other girls have finished bathing already.
You need not worry about them seeing you.
An ideal lady, huh?
Chihaya-chan.
Mom.
How long will you shut yourself in this room?
Say, why don't you just transfer to Seio?
What?
Some fine ladies go there.
I think it'd be perfect for you.
No, Mom, that's not the issue here.
I'll ask Kajiura Hisako-san to push through the transfer for you, since she's the acting principal at the moment.
No, like I said—
You're charming, no one will notice.
Mom, that's not the problem!
Seio is an all-girls school, and...
I'm a boy, for Pete's sake.
This isn't going to work out after all.
F-Fumi?!
I will wash your back.
W-Wait a minute!
Leave it to me.
Eh.
It is my job to do my best to ensure
that you have a good time here.
B-But, you're a girl!
You can't—
If the mere sight of my tiny figure excites you so,
then it will be impossible for you to spend your time safely here.
Therefore, you must get used to a girl's body.
Fumi, some—
I think that it's also important for you to learn this sensation.
Y-Your breasts... Your breasts, they're touching my back!
You don't have to go that far, I'm fine!
The days and crisis as a maiden
The aroma of cape jasmine?
Kaoru-oneesama, I'm...
Don't cry. It wasn't your fault.
Now, wipe your tears. Don't let anyone see you crying.
Did we dazzle you?
Won't you greet me, Chihaya-san?
Ah, sorry.
Now you can tell the others that
the rumors about me were true.
No, I wouldn't do such a thing!
Thank you and sorry!
It seems that you're a bit
different from the other students.
Well, I'm a bit different myself.
Are you?
No matter what, I will live true to myself.
Huh, Kaori-san?
What kind of person is she?
Well, I like her.
She's a bit unique and the way she like to tease others is a problem.
But, she's a good person on the inside.
I think so too.
I think she'd be delighted.
About how you want to learn more about her true self.
Rumors about her spread around often.
I still can't believe it.
You're beautiful, good at just about everything, and you even show concern for others.
No, I'm not that perfect.
I'm envious of you too, for how
straightforward and easygoing you are.
Now, let's continue studying!
Sure.
I'm kind, huh?
I want to see her again.
Did you get homesick already?
Oh, Kaori—
I knew it, you're a boy.
I knew it wouldn't be so easy.
Oh my, giving up already?
I won't protest, even if I am expelled...
If that is your wish.
I'm surprised that you could be so honorable.
I'll listen to what you have to say.
I'm surprised that you'd follow such
an absurd order from your parents.
Well...
Well, my family...
My tea isn't as good as Fumi's,
so I made you a simple herb tea.
It's a Maroon Blue, correct?
Not only is the color beautiful,
but it will also warm up your body.
Why?
Are you asking how I figured it out?
Remember how cautious you were about touching when we first met?
Furthermore, you lifted Yuu easily.
No matter how light Yuu is, it's no simple task for a girl to lift another girl.
Through the eyes of a girl, you were too perfect,
if only because that's the role you were playing.
That's how I figured it out.
Well, there were a few other things that
I don't think anybody besides me noticed.
I...
Rest assured.
You also told me that you wouldn't expose me.
I'll do the same for you.
You're not going to expose me?
Personally, I think it's okay for you to stay here.
Huh, why?
Because I think it'll be fun.
Since you've discovered me on my secret
rendezvous with her, I think you'll understand.
I also stand to gain something from this.
Sorry to interrupt your conversation!
Kaoruko-san, could I have a moment with you?
Chihaya-san.
Kaoruko, who is she?
She's Kisakinomiya Chihaya-san.
She's a new tenant in our dormitory.
Nice to meet you!
I'm Kelly Grandselius.
I am the night itself, the princess who wields the stars.
Princess?
Venus and Pluto have made a spectrum, huh?
I believe that you were born under unfortunate stars.
Um...
Kelly, come here!
Kaoruko?
Come on, let's go!
Kaoruko-san!
We're closing soon...
Okay.
Are you wondering whether Kaoruko has figured out that you're a boy?
Yes.
I say this as a matter of fact, not to flatter you,
but you're a perfect girl on the outside.
I don't think anyone except me has figured out that you're a boy.
If you're so worried, then maybe you could act less perfect in front of her.
So, why are you worried?
It's nothing. I was just a little uneasy, that's all.
Hey, Fumi...
Yes, Chihaya-sama?
I think I don't belong here.
Chihaya-sama?
Kaoruko-san?
Chihaya, would you come with me?
I want to talk...
If I win, you'll tell me the truth.
The first one to land a clean hit is the victor.
I'll end this match in an instant.
And if I win?
You can do as you please.
Understood.
En garde!
Faire!
Let me confirm something first.
Are really you a boy?
Yes, I am.
You must think that I'm acting odd now.
Kaoruko-san.
I don't know what you're thinking or what you're planning.
What are you here for?
I don't know either.
You might not believe me, but
this is something that I must do.
However, since you've discovered my identity, I'll have to leave Seio.
You're going to leave?
Do you think that'll solve everything?
Did you fool us with such halfhearted feelings?
I'm...
I don't understand you.
So I'll test you using my reference.
Commence!
Does lying come naturally to you?
Did you fool us with such halfhearted feelings?
I'm...
You even involved Kaori-san!
What were you trying to achieve?
I'm...
Chihaya!
Alto!
That's enough, you two.
Kaori-san!
Geez, what were you trying to do anyway?
So, what do you think, Kaoruko?
You still can't forgive him?
I don't care anymore.
I've calmed down now.
Why didn't you do anything?
It's all about camouflage and imaging tactics.
He'll become my ally, in return I'll protect his secret.
I don't understand.
Why?
Why are you accepting me?
N-No reason.
Well, Yuu-chan would be sad if you suddenly left.
Also, I kind of admire you.
Moreover, you look like my older sister.
Although I must say that it makes me a bit furious.
So, I don't think it'd be a bad idea if you stayed.
That's all.
Chihaya-sama, wipe your tears!
W-Why are you crying?
What's wrong?
No, it's nothing.
It's nothing.
Really, it's nothing.
Sorry!
Those are tears of happiness, right?
You're happy that you can watch
girls undress for the next year, correct?
What?!
T-That's right, changing clothes.
I'm surprised that you can keep going to this school
despite being found out by two girls in the first few days.
Fumi believes this to be a miracle.
I agree.
Chihaya!
Last time in PE, you...
Y-Y-You saw me in my underwear, didn't you?!
The Maidens Are Falling in Love with Me
-The Two Elders-
The days and crisis as a maiden
shurebu goku kokoro no iro wa
A heart tainted in slate blue,
kimi ni wa dou utsutteiru no
how is it reflected in your eyes?
kazari no nai koto made gomen
Sorry that I can't say something beautiful
todoketai to omou
But still I want you to know
sabitsuita kioku namida te wo fureta
I touched the sad memory with my hand
yobisou you ni utau you ni
As if I'm calling for you, singing for you
kono hibi no naka ima wo kanade yukou
We are playing a symphony of those days now
itoshiisha ni furete
Touching the gentleness
hashita wa ochitteku
The fractions are falling
mujaki no hitomi mamorita hito
The person who protected those innocent eyes
mebaeta himitsu nijimu hikari kakushi kirenai
This letter, which can't keep the secret of a name
kono tegami
when it touches a light
kimi wo mitsumete itai
I don't want to take my eyes off of you
Kaoruko, you already have
everything, don't you?
I don't know how to
answer the girl who
asked for help
and cried.
I am sure
Chihaya
will also hate me.
The Distress and Melody of being a Maiden
Next