Good day, Silver-Haired Princess.
Hello, Knight Princess.
A good day to you, too.
I'll be voting for you, Silver-Haired Princess.
Huh?
I'm voting for the Knight Princess.
Uh...
It's only appropriate that one of you be elected as this year's Elder Sister.
"Elder Sister"?
senseishion wo makiokoshichau
I'll create a sensation
renai kan no vector way
In a vector way of love
ichokusen ni mukattekun da
I'm heading forward in a straight line
tsuitekoreru kana
Can you follow me?
Maidens Are Falling for Me: The Two Elders
tatoeba me to me chotto shite nante kitai
I know that we'll see eye to eye
kyoushitsu wa marude shinshen no haiwei
The classroom is like a new highway
mienai hazu no hitomi ni naze ka utsutte
For some reason those invisible eyes have reflections in them
jankushion no naka de mayowanaide
Don't stumble once you find a junction
iku yo
Let's go!
tsurechigaenai
We can't pass each other,
konna ni chikaku ja butsukachau yo
we'll bump into each other if we're that close
ippotsuuko ja yada
I don't want a one way street
kurosu oobaa sore de ii yo
We can just do a crossover
senseishionaru na impakuto ni notte
I took a ride on a sensational impact
renai kibun kasanareba
And our loves crossed ways
ichokusen de mukattekun da
I'm heading forward in a straight line
supiido agete
Increasing speed
kurosu oobaa shita kokoro butsukatte
We did a crossover, and hit our hearts out
koi mo makiokosu
And love sprouted
I apologize.
I didn't feel it was necessary to tell you at this point.
It's one of this school's annual
traditions to choose an Elder Sister.
Elder Sister?
As in, a sibling?
It's an election where students pick a senior to
serve as a role model for the entire student body.
It might not sound that convincing coming from me,
but being the Elder Sister commands much more
respect than even President of the Student Council,
owing to the fact that you need
seventy-five percent of the vote to win.
Seventy-five sounds quite high for an election.
Does that mean nobody wins if someone doesn't get seventy-five percent?
No,
when that happens, the candidates are allowed
to give their votes to other candidates.
I see.
But being the Elder Sister doesn't give you any sort of authority, right?
The Elder Sister might not have any official authority,
but she does have a lot of influence.
The more I hear about this, the stranger it sounds.
I don't believe I'm good enough to win, though.
Sorry I'm late.
Kaoruko-chan, could you please act more like a lady?
You're a student of Seio, you know.
Why are you in such a hurry?
I came to ask Chihaya to tutor me in English and math.
She's coming with me to the library.
By the way, how did you score on the midterm?
I think the fact that she needs tutoring gives it away.
Kaori-san, that's mean.
I think all you need to improve your grades is
to get into the habit of studying every day.
Every day?
I don't even want to think about that.
Then, we'll just have to work even harder.
What?
Aww.
Well, just try your best.
If it isn't Utano-chan and Awayuki-chan.
Good to see you.
Likewise.
Chihaya-oneesama, please visit the Flower Arranging Club next week, if you can.
We just received some summer flowers and
we'd love you to teach us how to arrange them.
Can't we just ask Uta-chan?
Don't you like Onee-sama's work?
I do, but...
Okay.
I'll come by.
Thank you very much.
Now, if you'll excuse us.
Of course.
See you later, then.
So the two legendary birds have arrived together.
"Legendary birds"?
What are you saying?
It means that you two are especially close.
A meeting of two souls is always
accompanied by light and pain.
Pain?
You mean like, a fight?
I wonder...
Farewell, then.
Bye.
The most important thing is that you can use the formula.
Your fingers are long, Chihaya.
And yours...
Hm?
Nothing.
What is it? That just makes me more curious.
I just thought that your hand looked small.
Huh?
No they're not.
No one has ever said that to me.
But it's the truth.
Look!
Kiyora, they're here.
Ah, Chihaya-san.
Hatsune-san asked me to find you?
What is it?
It seems that you have a visitor.
I have a visitor?
Of all things, the pearl necklace's wire snapped,
and the pearls were scattered all over the stairs.
Thank God some people who were passing by helped me pick them up.
Why are you here, Mother?
I decided to drop by.
I was worried about how you were doing here.
But that doesn't mean you can just barge in...
Sorry, Chitose-chan.
I almost thought you were someone else.
Really, Mama?
Fumi, could you bring me a cup of tea too?
Y-Yes.
Hatsune-chan told me that you're getting a lot of votes.
You might even become the new Elder.
I don't know if I'll win, though.
There are so many others who are much more suited to it than I.
Aw, Chitose-san, now that you've transferred here,
you've suddenly transformed into a fine young lady.
Right?
Huh?
Oh, yes.
She even tutors me.
Tutoring, too?
Really?
Yes.
I'm surprised.
My daughter used to be so fragile that
she'd be bedridden from a simple cold.
She would've never had the stamina to tutor.
Look at how reliable she is now!
I guess putting you in this school was the right choice.
I barely recognize you now.
You're so much more feminine.
It seems you've made lots of friends too.
I'm happy for you, Chihaya-chan.
I'm back.
Would you like to eat, Chihaya-sama?
I'm too tired today, I'll pass.
I just want to rest.
Understood.
It's lavender.
It can help you relax.
Thank you, Kaori-san.
Let me start off by saying
that I don't know all the details.
I haven't met Chihaya's mother in person.
Did something happen?
I might be overthinking this,
but she called Chihaya "Chitose-chan" earlier.
Chihaya didn't correct her and
started calling her "Mama" instead.
For some reason, it made me...
Uncomfortable?
Exactly!
Why didn't Chihaya correct her?
He always calls her "Mother."
Why would he change that?
Good morning, Kaoruko-san.
G-Good morning, Chihaya.
You're up quite early, Sleeping Beauty.
You think so?
Well, you're up pretty early too.
You're right.
Why are they looking at us?
Because the top four candidates for the
Elder election are walking to class together.
Top four?
Yes.
Rumors say that one of you four will win.
Makio-san, you've gotten some votes too?
Nope, not one.
Huh? Why?
Because she's also known as
"Her Royal Highness" by most.
They're afraid to vote.
Must be nice.
Yes.
Chihaya.
Yes?
How does being one of the candidates make you feel?
Personally, I'm overjoyed that
everybody approves of me as a lady.
Today, we will be making an
arrangement using lilies as the base.
It's a delicate flower, so please watch carefully.
Yes.
Here's a get-well present, Chitose-san.
Thank you, Chi-chan.
They smell good.
Get well soon, okay?
Okay.
Chitose-chan.
Chitose-chan!
Chitose-chan!!
Onee-sama.
Onee-sama!
Maiden, Love and Light
Kaoruko-sama.
Fumi-chan, how is he?
The doctor just examined him.
He's sleeping now.
The doctor said that he was exhausted
from lack of rest and stress.
I see.
Say, Fumi-chan,
who is Chitose?
She was...
She was Chihaya-sama's twin sister.
He had a twin sister, huh?
Yes.
However, Chitose-sama died when she was 10 years old.
I see.
That must be the reason why Chihaya is so protective of Yuu-chan.
Chihaya!
...sorry.
Huh?
I'm so sorry!
I have to be strong.
If I can't be strong for Mother, then who will?
I have to endure.
I know that it's wrong.
But she's my mother!
It's what she told me to do!
I don't matter anymore.
It doesn't matter whether I'm around or not.
Chihaya, are you okay?
Kaoruko-san.
I...
You cut yourself handling a flower.
It's unusual for you to be that careless.
Cut?
The doctor said it wasn't serious.
You can relax, Chihaya.
Kaoruko-san.
Can I really become an ideal woman?
Huh?
Is your wound okay now?
I only cut my hand a little.
I'm rather embarrassed that I fainted over a little blood.
I'm glad you're okay.
I'm lucky that I fainted in the training room on a mat,
and I wasn't hurt even more.
You have to take care of yourself now
that the Elder election is coming up.
Chihaya, be more careful.
I will.
Thank you for your concern.
Are you really okay with that?
It's my duty to serve Chihaya-sama.
If he chooses to live as Chitose-sama,
then I will abide by that.
But, Chihaya's—
Sorry.
I believe you have the dignity of a true lady, Onee-sama.
I hope you become the Elder Sister.
Thank you very much.
I'm honored by your compliments.
Farewell.
Kaoruko-san?
What's wrong?
Is there something wrong?
Are you seriously aiming to become the Elder Sister?
Well, it's decided by a vote,
so I don't think it'd be correct to say "aiming."
That's not what I meant.
Eh?
Chihaya, is that what you really want?
Yes, it is.
Come on, let's go!
Kaoruko-san, what are you doing?
Your fingers are long, yet...
Why are you so...
You're an amazing person, Chihaya!
You can speak English fluently,
and you're good at math.
You even tutored me!
You're even better than me at fencing!
You struck me while I just hesitated.
Isn't that the real Chihaya?
You were the one who told me I should be myself.
So, you be yourself.
I don't want you to be someone else.
I want you to stay with me.
I want to be with you.
Kaoruko-san.
I...
Why?
Are you doing it for your mother?
Or...
Chihaya!
Wait!
Hey, Chihaya!
Chihaya.
Chihaya, I love you.
Please stay with me.
Kaoruko-san, I...
Can I be myself?
Yeah.
But, I...
Thank you, Chi-chan.
They smell good.
Chihaya.
Kaoruko-san.
I will now announce the results of the Elder Sister election.
When I call your names, please come up to the stage.
Shingyoji Makio-san.
Why did she call on me?
Minase Hatsune-san.
Nanahara Kaoruko-san.
Kisakinomiya Chihaya-san.
Yes.
If one of you wishes to resign and give your votes to another candidate, please step forward.
Speak now or forever hold your peace.
I hereby give all of the votes that I received,
to my friend, Nanahara Kaoruko.
Makio.
We've been through the same things.
I, Minase Hatsune, hereby give all of the votes
that I received, to Kisakinomiya Chihaya.
Hatsune-san.
I'm grateful to you for mending my relationship with Yuu.
Nanahara Kaoruko-san and Kisakinomiya Chihaya-san,
should I take your silence as
unwillingness to give up your votes?
Both are tied at 368 votes.
Everyone, I say this as your student council president,
but I propose that both Nanahara-san and
Kisakinomiya-san become the new Elders.
All who agree, please clap.
But, the Elder is supposed to be...
Isn't it wonderful that you both get to be Elders?
What?
And with that, this year's Elder Sisters are Nanahara
Kaoruko-san and Kisakinomiya Chihaya-san.
Once again, please take care of me, Chihaya.
Sure.
The Maidens Are Falling in Love with Me
-The Two Elders-
Maiden, Love and Light
shurebu goku kokoro no iro wa
A heart tainted in slate blue,
kimi ni wa dou utsutteiru no
how is it reflected in your eyes?
kazari no nai koto made gomen
Sorry that I can't say something beautiful
todoketai to omou
But still I want you to know
sabitsuita kioku namida te wo fureta
I touched the sad memory with my hand
yobisou you ni utau you ni
As if I'm calling for you, singing for you
kono hibi no naka ima wo kanade yukou
We are playing a symphony of those days now
itoshiisha ni furete
Touching the gentleness
hashita wa ochitteku
The fractions are falling
mujaki no hitomi mamorita hito
The person who protected those innocent eyes
mebaeta himitsu nijimu hikari kakushi kirenai
This letter, which can't keep the secret of a name
kono tegami
when it touches a light
kimi wo mitsumete itai
I don't want to take my eyes off of you