U-Um!
Stand still, Chihaya.
I can't do it otherwise.
But, Kaori-san, this is a bit...
Just let me handle it.
So, why are you getting dressed in my room?
Because if the two of us are alone in a room together, people will get suspicious.
W-Well, that's true...
Looks great.
Remember, when they get to the stethoscope, only undo the first button.
Okay.
Do you think I can get through my physical?
Just tell them that you're too embarrassed to undress.
If a popular "girl" like you acts too suspicious, it'll only attract more attention.
I understand.
Knight Princess.
How does Chihaya look?
Does he look like the Silver-Haired Princess of Seo now?
Or is he still an uncultured man to you?
It's mortifying... He's so angelic that it depresses me.
Huh?
Girls, would you like some sweets?
What is this?
Fumi's favorite...
They're ice cream sandwiches.
Yay!
I'm delighted, but...
Who's going to eat all these?
Huh?
Well...
You must really love these, Fumi-chan.
Here, eat with us, Fumi-chan!
No, I'm...
C'mon, sit! Sit down!
Don't be shy!
But, uh...
Um, okay. I'll take that one.
senseishion wo makiokoshichau
I'll create a sensation
renai kan no vector way
In a vector way of love
ichokusen ni mukattekun da
I'm heading forward in a straight line
tsuitekoreru kana
Can you follow me?
Maidens Are Falling for Me: The Two Elders
tatoeba me to me chotto shite nante kitai
I know that we'll see eye to eye
kyoushitsu wa marude shinshen no haiwei
The classroom is like a new highway
mienai hazu no hitomi ni naze ka utsutte
For some reason those invisible eyes have reflections in them
jankushion no naka de mayowanaide
Don't stumble once you find a junction
iku yo
Let's go!
tsurechigaenai
We can't pass each other,
konna ni chikaku ja butsukachau yo
we'll bump into each other if we're that close
ippotsuuko ja yada
I don't want a one way street
kurosu oobaa sore de ii yo
We can just do a crossover
senseishionaru na impakuto ni notte
I took a ride on a sensational impact
renai kibun kasanareba
And our loves crossed ways
ichokusen de mukattekun da
I'm heading forward in a straight line
supiido agete
Increasing speed
kurosu oobaa shita kokoro butsukatte
We did a crossover, and hit our hearts out
koi mo makiokosu
And love sprouted
Somehow I managed to come out unscathed.
Now you can relax for a while.
How do you do, Silver-Haired Princess?
Knight Princess, it's good to see you!
Likewise!
True to your reputation,
you've earned a nickname in no time.
Don't forget about yours. Your nickname sounds gallant and fits you perfectly.
Chihaya, are you trying to make fun of me?
You're too cute, Kaoruko.
Stop teasing me!
A concert?
Oh, I forgot that you didn't know.
Chihaya-oneesama!
Utano-san!
I'm Sasou Utano. I wish to support you with my body and soul, as a member of the ensemble.
I look forward to your guidance.
Huh? Um...
I am Nishina Eri of the same ensemble.
Pleased to meet you.
Likewise.
Actually, I'm the one who's going to need guidance.
I'm sorry, Yuki-chan!
Sorry to interrupt your study session,
but I wanted to explain some things about the concert to Chihaya-oneesama.
Do pardon our rudeness, Aoyuki-san.
Why is the president of the floral design club here too?
I just want to be helpful to my seniors.
So, about the concert...
Yes?
The founders believed that all students need to be able to play musical instruments.
Thus, anybody who performs well in music must join an ensemble.
And each year, they perform in a concert.
Speaking of, the rush for this year's concert tickets has already begun.
Tickets for a student concert?
Isn't it natural that one would be attracted to beauty?
Oh gosh, what should I do?
Kaoruko-chan, don't forget your etiquette.
But like...
It seems that the concert is stressing out Kaoruko-sama.
The concert?
By the way, what instrument will you play, Kaoruko-san?
I played the cello last year.
How wonderful.
Cello requires nimble fingers and a free spirit. It fits you perfectly.
Her performance last year was astounding.
Hatsune-san! Are you being sarcastic?
Huh?
But such sounds aren't easy to make, correct?
Didn't your performance stop everyone in their tracks?
I knew it. You are being sarcastic.
I'm just bad in front of crowds.
I'd like to hear you perform.
Not you too, Yuu!
I'm looking forward to hearing your cello.
Fine, I'll try my best.
By the way, Chihaya-sama, are you
good at playing any instruments?
I can play a little piano.
Really?
Show us!
I'd love to hear you play.
I'm not that good.
Hm?
You're amazing!
Chihaya, that was impeccable.
Chihaya, is there anything you can't do?
Of course.
I have my share of faults, like everyone else.
But you're amazing.
Thank you very much.
Kaley!
Hi, Kaoruko.
Are you signing up for the concert?
No way.
This is Kimihara Harumi-san, a 2nd-year.
She's been playing violin since she was three years old.
I thought I'd let her play instead.
I see.
Nice to meet you, I'm—
I already know who you are, Knight Princess.
Ah, okay. Excuse me, then.
Sure, see you.
Have a nice day.
Just like that, keep playing smoothly.
That's very good.
You two make the perfect duet.
I'm so happy to be a member of
Chihaya-oneesama's fan club right now.
Thanks to you, I feel like I can get through it now.
Not at all.
You're the one who's been working hard and concentrating.
Huh, me? Really?
Yes, you.
Yup, yup.
For some reason that makes me want to work even harder.
Okay, everybody, all together now!
Okay!
I understand where you're coming from,
but...
I booked it too.
No, but...
What's wrong, Eri-chan?
Oh, hi girls.
There's a bit of a problem regarding the use of the music room.
Sorry, this is the committee's fault.
It's been double-booked.
We can't both use it at the same time.
Who will use the music room first?
We're a string ensemble, but you use a piano. We can take a smaller room.
That's very generous of you.
Okay...
Let's...
I don't believe that instruments should factor into this.
I believe that both parties have the same needs.
Ah, well, you're right.
She has a point.
What should we do then?
Fortunately, we have an upright piano at our dormitory.
It's enough for my personal practice.
How about we use the dormitory for today's practice?
Are you sure about that?
Yes.
Do you agree, Kaoruko-san?
What about you, Eri-san?
I don't mind.
Well then, that settles it.
Any objections?
No.
Mm-hmm.
Is that so?
I knew it...
Yeah, I'm still fine.
Okay, okay, I got it.
Don't worry about me!
See you!
They'd come this far after me...
Once more, I'll have to...
The Distress and Melody of Being a Maiden
Let's take a short break!
By the way, remember Kimihara-san from yesterday?
I heard from a classmate that she's transferring after the concert.
The timing's a bit strange...
Yeah, students normally transfer at the end of the semester.
Maybe something happened to her family.
Kaoruko-san!
Sorry, I'll be back soon!
Debt?
A loan?
The rumors say that the lenders aren't afraid to rough you up.
No wonder she looks scary right now.
Shh! She'll hear you!
We don't know what she'll do if she hears us.
Kimihara Harumi-san!
I'm going to look for Kaoruko-san.
The weather is beginning to look ominous as well.
Family circumstances?
Yes, just as you thought.
My father's company has gone bankrupt.
We've caused trouble for you and your father as well.
Hey, is there anything I can do for you?
Just say it! Whatever it might be!
I made the mistake of believing we were on the same level.
It seems that I've made a grave mistake.
You, the Knight Princess, are indeed a lady to the core.
Um, this is for you...
Sorry!
You'd do anything for me? If you're serious, then I want to be you.
Change places with me!
You have everything, don't you?
Give me everything you have!
Give me your friends, your popularity and your future at Seo!
That's, uh...
Kaoruko-san!
That was Kimihara-san, wasn't it?
What happened?
Kaoruko-san?
Huh? Uh...
Sorry.
Let's head back.
Finally, the rain started falling.
According to the weather forecast, it's going to be a downpour.
Chihaya-sama?
Kaoruko-sama just left.
In this weather?
Where to?
I'm sorry.
I greeted her but it seems she didn't notice.
Is something the matter?
No.
I'm going to look for her nearby.
Debt?
A loan?
The rumors say that the lenders aren't afraid to rough you up.
Shh! She'll hear you!
We don't know what she'll do if she hears us.
You have everything, don't you?
Give me everything you have!
Kimihara-san!
Kaoruko-san!
Chihaya?
You're hurting yourself.
Please use this.
Mm-hmm.
Thank you.
What happened exactly?
I felt like I had to practice.
Who is Kimihara-san to you?
N-Nobody.
Do you really think that I can't help?
Is it because I'm a man?
Is it because I've lied to you once?
That's not it!
I can't speak about it to you.
Please go back!
Look me in the eyes, Kaouruko-san!
I know you'll hate me.
I know you'll come to hate me too.
I don't know how to answer the girl who's crying out for help.
I'm always like this. I just sit and watch.
Every time it happens, I tell myself that I'll do something next time,
but in the end, I can't.
I'm... I'm so mad at myself!
You are a kind person.
You're loyal, hardworking and honest.
Me?
It's okay.
Just this once, please...
Sure.
I've always hated being the daughter of a loan shark.
I've hated myself for thinking like that too,
but I don't have the courage to face it.
I can't be of any help to anyone.
I'm sure Kimihara-san understands that you're not at fault.
But...
While that was a form of your kindness,
it may be that there's no correct answer.
We can only pray that she tries her best
to stand on her own two feet again.
Yes, I want her to try.
Thank you, Chihaya.
No, that kindness of yours,
is why I admire you, Kaoruko-san.
Huh?
Thank you.
I have butterflies in my stomach.
It seems Kaoruko-sama isn't nervous anymore.
I guess so.
I'm sorry!
I used to think that we could switch places and fix everything, but not anymore.
I will always be me and you will be you. We have to accept that.
I know that.
I've always wanted to stay here, but now I can't.
I know that I should hate you, but I can't
stop admiring you no matter how hard I try.
You can hate me. You can also admire me.
You can do both.
But, I will always remember you.
You're every bit the Knight Princess I knew you to be.
The Maidens Are Falling in Love with Me
-The Two Elders-
The Distress and Melody of Being a Maiden
shurebu goku kokoro no iro wa
A heart tainted in slate blue,
kimi ni wa dou utsutteiru no
how is it reflected in your eyes?
kazari no nai koto made gomen
Sorry that I can't say something beautiful
todoketai to omou
But still I want you to know
sabitsuita kioku namida te wo fureta
I touched the sad memory with my hand
yobisou you ni utau you ni
As if I'm calling for you, singing for you
kono hibi no naka ima wo kanade yukou
We are playing a symphony of those days now
itoshiisha ni furete
Touching the gentleness
hashita wa ochitteku
The fractions are falling
mujaki no hitomi mamorita hito
The person who protected those innocent eyes
mebaeta himitsu nijimu hikari kakushi kirenai
This letter, which can't keep the secret of a name
kono tegami
when it touches a light
kimi wo mitsumete itai
I don't want to take my eyes off of you
Have you two heard the news?
Huh?
After the concert, Harumi-san transferred to a music school and won a national competition right away.
Really?
Yes, she received a scholarship. She might even study abroad.
That's wonderful!
That handkerchief is cute.
Yeah, thank you.
This is a present from my friend.
She's Chihaya-sama's
twin sister
Chihaya...
Is that your wish?
The Two Elders
Next
A Maiden's Love and Light