Până aici mi-a fost.
Vă rog să... continuați fără...
Rem!
Nu în căruță! Nu în căruță!
Oare va fi în regulă?
Păi, nu e ceva nou.
Totuși, are un teribil rău de mișcare.
Nu mai rezist!
Oh, domnule!
O putem vedea acum!
Aceea e capitala regală,
Seven Wall.
Ce treburi aveți aici?!
Un bărbat dubios cu coarne?
Nu ești o creatură demonică, nu?!
Oh, haide, ne-au înconjurat deja?
Lumachina e cu noi,
deci nu vreau să provoc zarvă.
Hei, tu, femeia de acolo!
Dă-ți jos gluga ca să-ți putea vedea fața!
Se pare că nu am de ales.
Îi voi intimida puțin.
Presupun că sunteți pregătiți de consecințe din moment ce îndreptați sulițele spre mine.
N-Nemernicule...
Diablo...
Nu mai există cale de întoarcere.
Se pare că trebuie să continui cu...
Vă rog să așteptați.
Ați putea lăsa aceste persoane să treacă?
Tu ești...
Nu ne-am văzut de mult.
Am primit scrisoarea lui Rem și te așteptam, Diablo.
Alicia?
Episodul 8: Vizită în capitala regală
Incredibil!
Poți vedea întreaga capitală de aici!
E uimitor!
Vă rog să folosiți acest han după cum doriți,
pe timpul șederii voastre în capitală.
Ei bine, Alicia, îți apreciem amabilitatea...
Dar dacă vom sta într-un asemenea loc, vom rămâne fără bani cât ai zice pește.
Nu trebuie să vă faceți griji de asta.
Doar lăsați totul în seama mea.
Ce? În acest caz...
Da.
Dacă Diablo îmi cere, voi cumpăra acest han cât ai bate din palme.
C-Ce... tocmai... a spus?
Rem!
Hm... Bine spus.
La naiba! Cât de bogată e Alicia?!
I apologize for the delayed
introduction, Head Priest.
Eu sunt Alicia Cristela, un cavaler regal.
E o onoare să te întâlnesc.
Îți mulțumim pentru că ne-ai ajutat să intrăm.
Mă bucur că am putut fi de ajutor.
Scuză-mă, dar...
Ce relație ai cu stăpânul meu?
And you are?
My entire being exists to serve my master.
Sh-Shoot!
Alicia is a Demon Lord worshiper
who put our lives in danger
to resurrect the Demon Lord.
Even though she's sworn loyalty to
me now, if Rose learns about that...
Rose, you don't need to pry.
If he asked me to die...
If he asked me to die, then I would die.
Does that explanation suffice?
Then it would be correct to recognize
you as one of my master's possessions?
Unless he has forsaken me.
Understood.
Then I shall I recognize you
as one of Master's possessions.
Thank you.
And you must be Horn-san, then.
I heard you recently joined his companions.
She got past Rose so easily...
That's right! I'm Horn!
Her communication skills are scary!
I can't go on any longer.
Farewell!
Thank you... for everything...
It hurts.
I can't eat any more.
Me neither.
Good grief.
Even my healing can't help with this.
I wanted to eat a lot so I can become big and
strong like you, Mister, and help out more.
Grasswalkers will always look like children,
even after reaching adulthood.
I know that's true, but...
Well, just take your time
and serve me faithfully.
If my master desires it,
then as much as I wouldn't like it,
there is a way to empower her.
Empower me?
If you place this treasure around your neck,
it will form a Master-Servant Pact
with my master,
and the Servant's abilities
will be empowered, too.
A Master-Servant Pact?
Sounds nice.
A pact with him, huh?
Hold on a minute.
Doesn't the servant who forges that
pact die when the master does?
Please let me go to heaven!
I-I'll die?!
What's the problem with that?
My master possesses unparalleled power,
so becoming his servant would grant
more benefits than words can explain.
I'd become that powerful?
But I'd die...
Listen carefully, Horn.
Once you forge that pact,
there's no way to go back.
Also, how will you go about finding work
or someone to marry you in the future
if you have a collar around your neck?
What are you going to do?
Marriage?
I...
What?
I take it back.
The idea of letting riffraff get close
to my master is outrageous!
I've arranged sleeping
chambers for each of you.
It might be a little cramped
for you, Diablo-sama.
Please forgive me.
No, it won't be a problem.
This is practically a king's bedroom.
So it seems you've already
surmised the general situation.
Yes.
Diablo-sama, might I draw closer to you?
Yes, I'll allow it.
Pardon me.
Uh...
She's getting this close?
You've come to the royal capital
because of Lumachina-sama, yes?
Y-Yes.
The king hasn't learned that
I plotted to resurrect the Demon Lord,
but I was held responsible for
my absence during the emergency,
so I'm currently under confinement.
But I believe I can prove
useful to you, Diablo-sama.
Please tell me the details.
She's a virgin killer!
She manages to look innocent
instead of slutty
while making such a strong appeal
with her feminine features!
She's a true virgin killer!
Alicia is to be feared!
What's the matter, you two?
Uh, the room was too big.
Yeah, I couldn't relax in there.
Want to sleep together?
Shall we?
So the Head Cardinal, Vishos...
He sought Lumachina-sama's life, too.
The mortal races truly are disgusting.
Even the Church that believes in God...
Naturally, we'll need to make
them pay for their crimes.
Yes.
I can gather evidence of their wrongdoing,
as you've requested.
But...
It's unlikely we can make
them answer for their crimes.
What do you mean?
The kingdom is unable to interfere
in the Church's internal affairs.
So it won't be able to sentence
Vishos and the other Cardinals.
This is why we need your power, Diablo-sama.
Huh?
Enact a bloody purge!
Use your power to bring the
iron hammer of justice down
upon those fiends in human skin,
and restore this world to its proper state!
Bring their demise!
Bring about the great demise!
Please, Diablo-sama!
This woman is crazy!
Please forgive my rudeness.
I will do everything I can
to investigate the Church.
Good.
I'm kind of beat now.
Time to sleep.
Diablo...
R-Rose?!
Are you awake, my master?
Replenishing your magic power?
Yes.
I can recover my magic power
by staying in the dungeon or
staying by your side, Master.
<<Charging>>
Up until now, I've received magic power
a bit at a time by staying near you,
<<Charging>>
but I finally...
Beep, beep!
Charge is currently at 30%.
We recommend switching to low-power mode.
...reached that point.
Why didn't you say something sooner?
I didn't want to burden you,
so every night, I waited
until after you went to bed
and quietly rested at your side,
but apparently I don't
recharge when you're asleep.
You've been there this entire time?!
So I...
I...
propose high-speed charging!
"High-speed"? What do you mean?
Well, in just 30 minutes of action, I can
recover a week's worth of Master's energy—
I mean, magic power.
Okay, what do we need to do?
I-I...
I'll receive magic power through contact!
Contact? All right.
So where do we do this?
Does the bed work?
No, the bed is...
Shit!
I can't believe I just invited
a woman to join me in bed!
And she shot me down, too!
I'm heavy, so if I climbed into bed, it would...
R-Right, her body is mechanical.
All right. Tell me what
you would like me to do.
Th-Then if you'll pardon me...
H-Hey, Rose?!
What are you...
Master, please charge me like this.
Please bless me with your magic power.
Rose, do you really need that?!
I don't have any experience either,
so I'm not sure...
B-But if I could have a part of your
body make contact with my own, then...
A p-part? Which part?
All right! Prepare yourself!
S-So soft!
Where?
Where do I...
Here? Is it here?
Just do it the same way as when
I poured magic power into Rem!
Okay, here I go, Rose!
Okay!
My master!
H-Hey, Rose, what's wrong?!
Beep, beep.
Charge is currently at 120%.
Good grief...
All filled up now, Rose?
Good for you.
Diablo-sama,
these are records of the Church's
financial dealings for these past few years,
and evidence of their various wrongdoings.
You gathered this much? How?
Well, I bought off the White Masks.
The White Masks?
What are those?
They're the believers of great faith
who are permitted to enter the sanctuary.
You really bought off those people?
Unfortunately.
When I told them I would buy evidence
of bribery, many of the White Masks...
According to these documents,
Vishos and those serving under him
have been using a majority of the donations
from believers as their personal funds.
That's awful.
That's not all, either.
Just as Vishos has tried
to kill Lumachina-sama,
he has killed many who
got in their way already.
Th-That's terrible!
Unforgivable, even!
God's...
God's own servants have
taken the lives of others?
And yet I...
I never knew about any of it.
Lumachina...
I'm mad!
I'm mad, I'm mad, I'm mad...
Now do you understand?
The mortal races are disgusting things.
Ruin is the only path to their salvation!
This world needs a purge brought
about by a Demon Lord!
Now bring the bloody purge—
Stop it.
P-Pardon me.
But Diablo-sama,
even though we have all this evidence,
the law cannot punish him.
We need your power to...
Good grief... I guess it's come to this.
Things might get a bit rough.
Our turn's finally up!
Facing the church, huh?
Yeah! We can't let them do this!
Please wait, Diablo-sama.
Would you please grant
me just one more chance?
What do you intend to do?
I'm going to march to the Cathedral
with this evidence in hand,
confront Vishos and his subordinates,
and pronounce their excommunication.
She still insists on punishing
them through proper means, huh?
That's just the kind of woman she is.
Diablo-sama...
Very well. You can give it a shot.
Head Priest,
this is as far as I can go with you.
Please allow me to ask one last question.
Do you believe the mortal
races are worth saving?
That is for God to decide.
But it makes me happy when people are
able to live with a sense of salvation.
I see.
The church is six blocks away from the inn.
These are the outfits worn by believers.
If you wear them, you should be able to
get close to the sanctuary without trouble.
Once we cross this bridge,
we'll be in the church's district.
While there's no roof,
it's as holy a place as the
inside of the cathedral.
Those who live here, and those who work here,
are all ardent believers.
That's the cathedral?
It's more lackluster than I expected.
Mister?
No, look up.
Huh?!
Th-That's the sanctuary?!
I-It's floating! It's floating!
Vishos and his subordinates are
up there in the sky, too.
How do we get there?
We'll use the floating passage.
Pardon me, but are you pilgrims?
Please, allow me to offer you some prayers.
Sorry, but we're in a hurry.
Huh?
You're turning down prayers?
Sh-Shit!
I responded like he was one of those
marketers outside a train station!
Please forgive our rudeness.
We've just traveled here from
the old Demon Lord's Domain.
We're just so eager, you see.
That's quite the long journey!
Everyone!
Let us offer prayers to
these faithful believers
who have visited from the
old Demon Lord's Domain,
and build our faith together!
H-Hey!
Diablo-sama...
To the faithful, prayers are
as important as breathing.
Please...
God, grant these people your blessings.
Let your love and mercy be with them.
Well, now I'm stuck...
Vishos...
Vishos-sama?!
It's Vishos-sama!
Vishos-sama?
Welcome home.
We've been waiting for you,
Head Priest Lumachina.
Th-This woman's the Head Priest?
The Head Priest!
Oh!
What a miracle!
The Head Priest!
Vishos, someone tried to kill me
when I went to Zircon Tower.
That's terrible!
That man was the Paladin, Gewalt,
and Vishos, that assassin was sent by you!
And now, in the carriage behind me,
I've gathered evidence
that all of you have killed many others,
along with financial records of your bribery.
So I hereby pronounce:
Head Cardinal Vishos and those
Cardinals serving under him
are hereby excommunicated.
E-Excommunicated?!
Vishos-sama is?!
What?!
Well said.
How deplorable.
It would seem the duties of
Head Priest were too much
for a young, growing woman who wants to play.
After abandoning your duties,
engaging in all manner of debauchery,
and returning with such
shady individuals in tow,
you've created such fake evidence
to attempt to cast us out?
What?!
You would call my claims lies and falsehoods?
Your wrongdoing—
There's no way such things could happen!
If those things were to happen,
the church would lose all significance,
and the faith built up by our believers
would lose all meaning, would it not?!
No matter how great the cost, you must
repent for the sins you've committed!
Absolutely right, Head Priest—
no, former Head Priest!
You've abandoned your duties
and hidden your whereabouts!
Now you seek to destroy the very church
itself to cover your sloth and debauchery!
H-How could you...
R-Rem...
Yeah, I don't like where this is going.
Diablo...
Lumachina...
If you get emotional now, you'll lose.
Bear with it.
Don't.
Don't cry...
Lumachina Weselia!
You should resign from your
position as Head Priest
and repent for your sin
of abandoning your duty!
B-But...
Now!
Seize this sinner and her companions!
Th-Th-There are so many Paladins!
Wh-Wh-What do we do?!
My believers, this is a great act of faith.
Now, seize those people!
L-Let go of me!
Diablo!
I-I can't!
I can't take this!
I don't want to, but I guess
I'll mow them down.
You mustn't.
You lost the debate!
That only leaves fighting!
Even so, we can't allow blood
to be spilled at the cathedral!
Are you sure about this?
If it will save everyone else...
You would say that.
Then at least go on your own two feet!
Lightning Strike!
If you don't want to die,
then make way for her!
Thank you for the prayers
you offered earlier.
May God's blessings be upon all of you, as well.
Soon even God will be within my grasp!
Next Episode    "Storm the Church"
I'll dole out punishment to those
of you who have lost faith in God!
All of you can face the same death!
Diablo-sama, grant us judgment for our sins.
Don't Miss the Next Episode!
Illustration: Shimahara