Raportez!
Nava 13 a fost distrusă de inamic!
Nava 22 nu mai poate naviga!
Când au devenit creaturile
demonice atât de puternice?
Când li s-a oferit puterea unui Lord Demon?
Fanis!
Varakness.
Oh, draga mea Fanis,
Fanis Laminitus!
Am venit ca să te fac a mea,
așa cum am promis.
Ți-ai ales rochia de mireasă?
Episodul 6: Armata Lordului Demon
La naiba cu tine!
Ți-ai adus femeile pe câmpul de luptă?!
Acestea sunt iubitele mele soții și comandante ale armatei Lordului Demon.
Când vei intra și tu în haremul meu, Fanis,
ele vor deveni surorile tale.
Sunteți cu toții niște proști!
Chiar crezi că m-aș căsători cu o creatură demonică?
Nu mă face să râd!
Ți-am pregătit deja inelul.
Vreau să încep să-l porti cât mai repede cu putință.
Iar apoi vom face dragoste împreună cu aceste femei.
Idiotule.
Și eu ți-am pregătit ceva.
Vai, Fanis, chiar mă bucur să aud asta!
Îți voi oferi un sfârșit potrivit aroganței tale!
Glontul Fulger!
Mi...nunat!
Oh, Laminitus i-a venit de hac!
Am reușit!
L-a eliminat pe comandantul inamicilor!
Trăiască lordul nostru!
Inform all our forces that the
enemy's commander is dead!
Apoi atacați cu toții simul...
C-Ce?
Acesta era asul tau din mânecă?
Sunt surprins.
Nu am mai fost rănit așa de rău niciodată.
I-Imposibil!
Sunt sigură că i-am străpuns inima!
Draga mea Fanis,
acum a venit momentul să-ți ofer cadoul meu.
They even have magic like this?
Stand strong! All units maintain—
Când ai...
Cucu-bau!
Varakness a spus că vrea să te facă soția lui,
dar eu urăsc femeile cu sâni mai mari decât ai mei.
Deci nu vreau ca tu să te alături haremului.
Deci ce ai spune dacă ai muri acum?
Laminitus!
Și acum, cine urmează?
Ce este asta?
Chiar poate fi asta numită o luptă?
Parcă ar fi...
Așa este.
Presupun că ăsta pare mai mult un măcel al raselor muritoare săvârșit de creaturile demonice.
C-Cineva...
În acest ritm, soldații mei... și poporul meu...
Cineva...
Cineva să ne salveze!
Ești așa o proastă.
Nimeni nu vă va salva.
Acum e timpul să mori!
Ce se petrece aici?
Ce?!
Ce se petrece?!
Ascultați, gunoaielor!
Eu sunt Lordul Demon dintr-o altă lume,
Diablo!
Nu-mi pasă de un oraș al raselor muritoare,
dar nu voi tolera ca ei să se autointituleze armata Lordului Demon fără permisiunea mea.
Diablo?
Stăpâne, cumva...
Voi anihila această așa-zisă armată a Lordului Demon!
Să mergem, Diablo!
Da!
Trebuie să ne ajutăm reciproc la greu!
Da, te voi urma oriunde, Diablo!
V-Voi veni și eu!
Dar chiar dacă ne vom grăbi,
ne va lua trei zile să ajungem la oraș...
Vom folosi asta.
Teleportarea!
Îți permite să te întorci la un loc în care ai fost anterior cât ai clipi.
Stăpâne...
Nu am părăsit niciodată acestă temniță.
Deci nu voi putea să...
Voi visa la ziua când te vei întoarce aici în timp ce îți aștept venirea.
Oricât de mult timp va trece.
Nimănui nu-i place să fie lăsat singur.
Rose, vei veni și tu cu noi!
Ce? Dar eu...
Dacă consider că ești unul din obiectele mele,
ar trebui să fii și tu teleportată cu noi.
Obiect?
Fir-ar! Chiar nu ar trebui să tratez o fată ca pe un obiect!
Un obiect...
Obiectul stăpânului...
Vai, cât de minunat sună asta!
Ce?
Chiar sunt binecuvântată.
Te rog să mă tratezi ca obiectul tău și să mă folosești cum dorești!
Sunteți gata?
Vom merge la Turnul de Zircon!
Locul va fi câmpul de luptă,
deci trebuie să fiți pregătite!
Da!
Da.
Teleportare!
Fulgerul Meteorit!
Acest bărbat...
C-Ce este asta?!
Cine este acel bărbat?!
Toți care încă sunteți în viață!
Ridicați-vă armele și săbiile!
Apari, Asulau!
Finish them all at once!
I can't believe my Summon's
become this strong.
This ring is incredible.
Now, on to the next one!
Have a Triangle Shot with Tempest Arrows!
There!
I'm glad everyone's safe.
Now, let's keep pushing on!
You got the foul smell of Fallen on
the clothes I received from my master.
I won't be killing you in an instant.
I'll teach you brainless
Fallen what true fear is.
Now die. Asterismos!
Didymoi!
Karkinos!
Parthenos!
Oh, look what I've done.
I killed them in an instant again.
Well, time to resume cleaning.
God, grant this man your
mercy and heal his wounds.
Save him.
Heal him.
Horn-san, who's next?
R-Right!
Maybe you should rest a bit, though...
I'm fine.
Diablo-sama is...
No... God is on my side.
Tornado Impact!
Oh?
That Sorcerer...
Now he looks worth killing.
Don't let those monsters into the city!
You're alive, then,
Lord of Zircon Tower?
Diablo...
That was you?
This woman really is scary!
I'm genuinely grateful for your party's aid.
Don't misunderstand.
I simply couldn't overlook those
daring to call themselves
the Demon Lord's Army without my permission.
But unless he...
Unless Varakness is defeated,
we can't win this battle.
Varakness?
That's right.
He's the army's commander-in-chief,
with powers granted by a Demon Lord.
His own might goes without saying,
but he also commands a powerful
sorcerer and a powerful healer,
and he has a Fallen that can
appear out of others' shadows,
so even getting close to him isn't easy.
No matter what kind of foe he is,
once I hit him with Grand Magic...
Huh?
Sh-She's kissing him?!
Huh?!
Are you kidding me?!
Now he's g-g-groping her damn breasts?!
Who on earth...
Rings?!
Wedding Rings?!
Boobs
Rings
Matching Looks
Dating
Hug
Shacked Up
In Love
Kiss
Happy Marriage
Couple
Boobs
Nightly Endeavors
Romance
Holding Hands
Honeymoon
Harem
Lap Pillow
Boobs
They're...
What is this?
A harem?
He's flirting and getting it on
with tits on the battlefield?!
Wh-What?
What's going on?
I'm off to murder them!
H-Hey, Diablo?
Oh? How reckless.
Challenging me to battle head-on, are you?
Varakne—
Impossible!
Wh-Why, you...
That was a stupid trick. Totally worthless.
Now try showing me your next trick.
Hold it. Don't move, now.
You dared to kill my little sister!
Now, how shall I slice you u—
Wh-What?!
Begone to a world where all has stopped.
Absolute Zero!
N-No way!
My body is freezing!
N-No!
I don't want to die!
Too late now.
Next one!
Wh-Who on earth is this mortal?
Stop that.
That man has the power of Magic Reflection.
If you use magic recklessly, you'll die.
Oh? Well done figuring it out.
I never imagined two of my
wives would be defeated.
Awfully complacent, aren't you, womanizer?
Try protecting your third wife!
Flare Burst!
Wh-What power...
Why?!
Why did you go after them?!
You're not making any sense.
What's so strange about attacking
the enemy that opposes you?
Besides, targeting the healer
first is just basic tactics.
Why, you...
I'll rip you apart myself!
Oh?
You'll make this a little entertaining, then?
Die!
So this is your trick?
H-How can a mortal evade me?!
I was granted power by a Demon Lord,
and in terms of level,
I'm surely at least 160!
Blame your equipment.
I don't know which Demon Lord
granted you power,
but raising your level
to the cap is standard.
After that, it's the equipment you
use that determines superiority.
Beyond that, it comes down to personal skill,
reaction speed, and situational awareness.
Wh-What are you talking about?
You can't understand that?
But I come from another
world where that's true.
There's not a single reason
I'd lose to a mere Fallen!
You're all bark.
If I can just hit you,
I'll end you with this single blow!
It's futile.
Your attacks won't reach me thanks to the
effect of the Mystic Gem of Illusion.
What?!
I think it's about time we end this!
O White, with your purifying heat
and light, return all to white!
White Nova!
I-Impossible!
Everything is fading...
Oh? I'm surprised you're still breathing.
Why, you...
Why, you! I'll never forgive you!
I've got you now!
Energy Drain!
A blood sucking spell?
That's your trump card?
That's so disappointing for a hidden trick!
Wh-What strength...
But the Demon Lord is still—
Hmph!
No matter which Demon Lord tries
to revive, I'll pulverize them!
Because I am the true Demon Lord, Diablo!
The true Demon Lord,
you say?
We did it!
Diablo!
Mister!
Diablo-sama!
You handled that easily.
That was incredible!
That was really great!
Diablo, you provided the greatest
service in this battle.
Thank you for saving our city.
I already told you.
I wasn't thinking about protecting
a city of the mortal races.
I simply taught them the
power of the true Demon Lord.
So you did.
So good!
That's bad manners, you gluttonous elf.
Water! Water!
You see?
Where's Horn?
Oh, she said was going to use the
bathroom before she sat down.
Oh, yeah, she was looking a little down.
I wonder if her stomach's upset.
Hey there, Horn!
I was shocked to learn you're a woman,
and one of those being
honored for the battle, at that!
I bet you earned a huge reward, right?
Hand it over!
We took you with us on all of
those adventures before, right?
I didn't receive any reward!
I left before I did.
But even if I had, I wouldn't hand it over.
I'm not listening to you jerks anymore!
What was that?!
Even the same adventuring
was completely different!
I had fun adventuring with all of them!
I...
I sucked and couldn't do anything, but...
By "all of them," you mean the
hangers-on with the Head Priest?
"Honored," my ass! You make me laugh!
Speaking of them, there's that black
panther woman and that elf with huge tits.
The women were hot!
That damn Demon's living it up!
I bet he spent most of the battle
hiding and quivering in the shadows!
Take that back!
What?
D-Don't make fun of my friends!
They're all really incredible!
And every one of them worked their
hardest to protect this city!
Risking their lives!
They're nothing like you trash,
extorting money from the weak!
Oh?
So those are your final words, huh?
If I stayed quiet and let
you insult my friends,
I'd never forgive myself!
Then die!
It reeks.
It reeks of monsters out here.
Wh-Who are you?!
Horn...
I didn't know monsters showed up
in the middle of the city here.
Though they're all low-level trash mobs.
M-Mister!
You bastard!
Get him!
This is an exception, got it?
I know.
I...
wasn't of any use at all.
So I thought I didn't belong there.
No use, huh?
So what?
Huh?
Did someone tell you to leave?
No...
Then did you want to leave yourself?
A-Absolutely not!
I wanted...
No one's told you to leave.
And you don't want to leave, either.
So there's no need for you to leave.
Is there anything wrong with that?
Th-There isn't.
I want to stay with everyone!
Then you should stay with
us as long as you like.
O-Okay.
I can't hear you!
O-Okay!
What? Are you crying?
I-I'm not crying!
You're crying.
I'm not crying!
These are good!
Data viitoare: Micuțul Lord Demon
Owner, bring out more biscuits!
Oh! The Demon Lord is finally motivated!
I can't turn a blind eye to a Demon Lord
and a Fallen within the city.
Nu ratați episodul urmatorul!
Ilustrație: Kantoku