Diablo!
N-Nu se poate...
D-Diablo!
Diablo...
Cine ar fi crezut că Mersul Subacvatic îmi va fi de folos într-un moment ca acesta?
Deși nu mă pot mișca la
fel de liber pe cât credeam.
Horn!
Episodul 5: Lupta cu Dragonul Negru
Această mantie de rang EX arde foarte bine.
Și îmi plăcea așa de mult.
Dar a fost cât pe ce.
Am ajuns și să-mi pierd Sceptrul lui Tenma din cauza a ce s-a întâmplat.
Nu îi va face bine să stea cu hainele alea ude pe el.
Și nu mai am altceva ce aș putea arde...
Presupun că-l voi dezbrăca.
Bun...
Are un corp așa delicat.
Ar trebui să-și mărească puțin pectoralii.
Și acum pantalonii...
Bănuiesc că nu am de ales.
Doar suntem amândoi băieți.
Vai, sunt așa de uzi
încât nu reușesc să-i scot...
Ce?
Nu o are.
Chestia aia...
Nu o are. Chiar nu o are.
Chestia care trebuia să fie aici, nu este!
Unde este?!
Ce? Domnule?
De ce ești dezbrăcat?
D-D-D-Domnule?!
L-La naiba! Asta e de rău!
C-C-C-Ce încerci să-mi faci?!
Te-ai trezit în sfârșit, femeie firavă ce ești!
Acest Lord Demon tocmai ți-a salvat viața!
Ce?
A-Am auzit că voi rasele muritoare puteți pieri dacă stați cu hainele ude pe voi, deci ți le-am dat jos!
Fii recunoscătoare!
Chiar am fost luată prin surprindere.
Și eu!
Îți mulțumesc că m-ai salvat, dom...
Hmpf. Dacă-ți este frig, doar apropie-te.
Mă întreb dacă Diablo este teafăr.
Cunoscându-l pe Diablo, sunt sigură că se va întoarce la noi alături de Horn.
Iar tot ce putem face noi este să avansăm.
Și eu cred în Diablo.
Aveți dreptate.
Doar este Diablo, la urma urmei!
Când i-am spus să se apropie,
mă refeream de foc!
Cum naiba s-a ajuns la asta?!
Aha! D-De ce erai deghizată în bărbat?
Când eram mică, am fost separată de părinții mei.
Poate că m-au abandonat,
dar când trăiești pe cont propriu,
este mult mai bine să arăți ca un bărbat.
Sunt sigur că i-a fost greu să trăiască pe cont propriu.
Este așa de curajoasă.
Acum mult timp, stăteam astfel cu familia mea în zilele reci.
Serios?
Tăticule...
D-De unde a mai scos-o și p'asta?!
E-Ei bine...
Domnule, am spus asta...
Așa este, din respect!
Vreau să spun că te respect ca aventurier!
Înțeleg...
Oricum, pe unde suntem acum?
Dar, domnule...
Crezi că fetele sunt bine?
Shera poate învinge cu ușurință cu arcul ei
toți monștri de la nivelul
unde ne-am separat.
Nivelul zece are o podea
mișcătoare drept mecanism,
dar este foarte precaută, deci vor fi bine.
Cimitirul de la nivelul unsprezece
are cadavre care atacă, dar cu puterea rugăciunilor lui Lumachina...
Atunci, asta înseamnă că se vor descurca!
Dar dacă vor da peste gardianul final
de la nivelul doisprezece,
chiar dacă-și vor lucra împreună...
Ce? Gardian?
Trebuie să ajungem la ele cât mai repede.
D-Domnule!
Bucură-te! Mulțumită acestor chestii,
știu exact unde ne aflăm!
Bun, acesta este nivelul doisprezece.
Da, haideți să dăm tot ce...
Rem, este cineva aici.
Așa se pare.
Acela este un dansator al morții de nivel 80.
O, vai, nu.
Asta înseamnă că am ajuns aici înainte voastră deși eu încercam să vă prind din urmă?
Gewalt!
Deci ai supraviețuit.
Ce este asta?
Nu-l văd pe Demon prin preajmă.
Oare ce s-o fi întâmplat cu el?
Asta este perfect, Lumachina!
Te rog să mori odată!
Apăreți, Albine de Foc!
Shera și arcul ei nu ne pot scoate din această...
Shera!
Da!
Apăreți, Asulau, Câine de Piatră, Libelulă!
Shera, acum!
Da!
Închisoarea de Trandafiri!
Mare păcat! Știam deja că veți face asta.
Nu-mi vine să cred că folosește
creaturile invocate astfel...
The desperate looks of weak women
are just to die for!
Și acum, oare cum ar trebui să vă ucid?
Ce este asta?!
Ce se petrece?!
Asta este magie de vânt.
Diablo!
Puny beings who dare invade my land,
I will grant you all the same death.
It can't be!
Why is one of those here?
Puny beings, if you wish to resist,
then unleash your power.
A... A Large Black Dragon...
H-Hold on!
I have no intention of
conquering this dungeon!
If you will not resist,
then I'll simply slaughter
you with a single blow.
Don't get cocky,
you damn lizard!
Appear before me, Ifrit!
The ultimate fire summon!
Yes, this is my super trump card!
Get him, Ifrit!
That's it, Ifrit!
Ruin him!
This really burns through MP...
Hurry up and defeat him!
You did it! That lizard bastard's—
Are you finished, puny being?
Filled with enough despair now? Then...
You shall die!
Ifrit!
No... No way...
My trump card!
The ultimate summon!
That is the most you mortal races can achieve.
L-Let's run.
Yeah.
Huh?
Lumachina?
Lumachina-chan?
Please hang in there. I'll heal you now.
God...
Please save this man.
Please grant him your generous mercy.
Are you crazy?
Do you have any idea what I've done?
It's all right.
God grants us all the opportunity
to repent so long as we live.
God...
Please heal the wounds
this man suffers from,
and permit him to live...
Oh?
God... must be a wonderful man.
Would you please hear us out?
Hmm...
A Human blessed with one wing by God,
an Elf with a Demon Lord's bow,
and you are the vessel of...
This is quite interesting.
But...
The lives of you puny
beings last but a moment.
Even if they were to end now,
it would make but a scant difference.
N-No way...
Now, begone!
Looks like I made it in time.
Sorry to make you wait!
I'm in a bit of a hurry.
I don't feel like letting you
put on your show right now,
you petty Dragon!
Oh?
You would insult me?
Then I'll grant you the death you desire!
Gather, light,
against those who crawled forth
from darkness and defy providence!
Learn just how arrogant
you are!
Without Tenma's Staff,
this takes more time, but...
Make it...
Make it in time...
It should make it in time!
Yes!
Hercules Lance!
Wh-Why, you...
Thunder Axe!
Incredible!
Incredible, Mister!
Impossible!
I can't die at the hands of...
a puny being!
I cannot die yet!
I have yet to leave behind
one to inherit my memories.
You...
I see. So you're a virgin, too.
I guess Dragons wouldn't have many
chances to meet other Dragons.
Who gave you permission to flee?
You are the guardian of the twelfth floor.
Disobeying the Master's orders
warrants a thousand deaths.
Wait, is that...
Shall I clean up your mess?
What?! Why, you...
Get out of my way!
You're a mere puppet!
Don't call me a puppet!
Now pay the price for your sins...
with your death!
Krios!
It's not my duty to be the
guardian of the twelfth floor.
I'll have to clean up here.
It's really true.
If I recall,
I found her appearance cute when
I was creating the dungeon,
so I placed that Magimatic
Maid on the thirteenth floor.
I believe her name was...
Now to clean up.
Do you have your memories from those days,
Rose?
My name is Diablo.
No, perhaps I should I say... it's @Diablo-13?
Master?!
I've just returned, Rose.
Welcome home,
my master.
Th-This is the treasure vault?
I-Incredible!
T-T-Treasure!
It's full of treasure!
What?!
You made this entire dungeon, Diablo?!
That's incredible!
So that's why you knew
so much about the tricks.
Thank goodness.
They're not wondering if I set them up.
By the way, Diablo, who is that?
My entire being exists to serve my Master.
And what kind of base-born mare are you?
Mare?
I was asking Diablo.
I wasn't asking you!
Master, may I mince this woman?
What do you mean by that?
Would you like a taste of Asterismos?
Cut it out already!
Master, here is the White Ox Statue you seek.
You sure made us go through a lot of trouble.
So with this, we can save
Lumachina-chan, right?
But how do you go about using this?
You don't even know that much?
That said, though, it's not
like I can just click "Use."
I can feel it.
The warmth of God is coming from this statue.
Hey, Lumachina, are you all right?
Yes.
I can feel God so close to me...
Is she... getting off on this?
It's so hot!
I can't... stay on my feet...
Lumachina-chan?
Lumachina...
The marks...
The marks are a little fainter!
It's incredible...
The power of God...
Yeah.
Look, they've already grown so faint.
Sorry, did that hurt?
Right now, it's... tingling...
and numb right there...
You should be okay now.
This is actually treatment, right?
The power of God...
Yeah, I can tell.
The light is steadily going
inside you, Lumachina-chan.
It's almost there, Lumachina-chan.
God is...
God is entering me!
You look so good, my master.
Yeah, you look cool, Diablo!
Of course. I'm the Demon Lord
from another world, after all.
Mister!
A skirt?! A mini-skirt at that?!
That armor not only improves your speed,
but grants magic resistance, too.
You should accept it gratefully.
Yeah, but...
It's really cute!
I didn't know you were a girl, though, Horn-chan.
Um...
How's it look? It shows...
a little too much skin, doesn't it?
That clothing grants physical defense,
magic resistance, and speed buffs,
while the ring has the power
to strengthen Summons.
R-Right...
They're all rare items.
Yes...
Thank you very much.
Not fair!
Everyone's getting new outfits,
while I'm just getting Tempest Arrows!
That's just how it is.
At your current level,
that's all you can use.
Boo...
Wow, pretty!
Hey, can I have this?
Yeah, do as you please.
What's the matter, Horn?
Oh, uh... It's nothing!
So cute!
All right, it's about time to...
Rose, is something wrong?
No.
Granting Master's wishes is my true joy.
But watching you share such
treasures with those people...
makes me... makes me...
crazy with envy!
Before, you only adored me, Master.
Rose...
Back then, she was the only one I spoke to.
This is the first item I ever obtained.
Would you like me to place this in the vault?
No, I'm not asking you to manage it.
That's... a p-pre...
The Demon Lord is bestowing it upon you!
You're... giving this... to me?
Y-Yes.
Thank you so much,
my master.
Now even you should be able
to carry that around with you.
Yes!
Now we can save all those afflicted
by the Death Knell Disease!
To the city, then!
I think it's pointless to take it there now.
What do you mean by that?
It appears the Demon Lord's Army
is advancing on Zircon Tower City.
Reporting!
Half of the people have finished evacuating!
Too slow! Speed it up!
Reporting!
The Demon Lord's Army is 5,000 melds away,
and roughly 300 large monsters
have been spotted!
I shall come to collect you on
the night of the next full moon.
So much for the next full moon.
Mincinosule.
Sunt 300 de creaturi demonice împotriva celor 4000 de soldați ai noștri.
Nu avem destui oameni!
Armata Lordului Demon?!
Sunt atât de multe creaturi demonice!
Ce naiba se petrece...
În acest ritm, orașul va fi...
Foarte mulți oameni vor...
Nu am nicio idee ce se petrece,
dar salvarea unui oraș de la un atac e o caracteristică de bază a jocurilor!
Trebuie s-o facem!
Soldații mei! Poporul meu!
Data viitoare: Armata Lordului Demon
Cineva să-i salveze!
Nemernicule! Te voi ucide cu orice preț!
Return all to white, White Nova!
Nu ratați următorul episod!
Ilustrație: kekocha