Cât de sinistru!
Ce caută chestia asta la această biserică?
Te autointitulezi Lord Demon,
dar acum că m-am contopit
cu Dumnezeu, te voi îngropa!
Acea voce!
Vishos?!
Acea voce e a lui Vishos!
Nu se poate!
Ce caută Vishos acolo?!
Vishos?
O chestie atât de respingătoare nu ar putea fi Dumnezeu.
Gura, fetițo!
Și tu vei simți judecata acestui Dumnezeu!
Numești chestia aia Dumnezeu?!
Zeul Distrugerii, Europa,
e doar o armă magică invocată cu ajutorul unui ritual magic!
Cum de știi asta?!
Nu-i pot spune că știu datorită faptului că era monstrul de clasă șef de la un eveniment ocazional din Cross Reverie.
Hmpf! Doarece sunt un Lord Demon dintr-o altă lume!
Nemernic misterios...
Dar!
Nu contează cine ești, tot nu-l vei învinge pe Europa!
Atacurile lui Europa nu sunt magice, deci Inelul Lordului Demon nu le poate reflecta.
Poate că nu e la fel ca în joc,
dar dacă testez și o dau în bară, s-ar putea să ies destul de șifonat.
Asta e de rău!
Asta e chiar foarte rău!
Ce se întâmplă?!
În acest ritm...
Wow, that's a raid boss, isn't it?
Ce?
Încep colectarea de informații.
Zeul Distrugerii, Europa.
Nivelul lui depășește 200.
Ce?!
That appeared from the lowest
floor of the sanctuary.
Ceea ce înseamnă că
trebuie să existe ceva acolo!
Rem!
Will you just keep running,
self-proclaimed Demon Lord?!
La naiba!
Explozie!
Știam eu.
Those are enchantments.
It has its damn barrier up.
Acum că am devenit Dumnezeu, sunt invincibil!
Vishos!
Lumachina...
Câte acțiuni corupte mai
ai de gând să săvârsești?
Oricâte este nevoie ca să subjug
Dumnezeul acestei lumi!
Voi începe cu tine!
Mori!
Au dispărut?
Unde s-au dus?!
Episodul 10: Dumnezeul fals
D-Diablo?
Asta nu-i a bună.
I've been playing solo for so long, I never
picked up any spells to protect someone else.
La naiba!
Am primit ceva daune de la chestia aia.
Stop moving around!
Lumachina, aș vrea să faci ceva pentru mine.
B-Bine!
Vraja Anulare!
Poți folosi această vrajă, nu?
Miracolul care elimină magia...
Da! Desigur!
Trebuie să-i eliminăm bariera
defensivă ca să-l putem învinge.
Îl va învinge pe Lordul Demon, nu-i așa?
Cred că am putea fi salvați.
Vishos a spus adevărul!
Așa este!
Vishos!
Te rugăm, salvează-ne!
Vă înșelați!
Dacă acela e Dumnezeu, atunci, de ce distruge sanctuarul?
De ce încearcă s-o omoare pe Head Priest?
No! They're both Demon Lords!
Lumachina-sama is the only one who constantly
tried to share the word of God with us!
Eu cred în Lumachina.
U-Unde s-a dus domnul și ceilalți?
Sunt în regulă. Sunt în regulă, nu-i așa?
I-am găsit.
Acolo.
O God that art in Heaven, please use
your power to ward off the wicked
who would bring calamity to your children,
the mortal races.
Purify them.
Exorcise disaster, and grant
them your blessings.
Ward them.
Purify them.
A priest's miracles are powerful,
but they take a long time to activate.
Can I keep her safe through it?
Plănuiți să folosiți Anulare?
Cât de stupid!
There's no way that'll make it in time!
Nu te voi lăsa!
I won't let you interfere with Master!
Rose!
Out of my way! Move!
Păpușă inutilă!
Nu mă numi păpușă!
Magimatic Sol!
Proasto!
Rose!
Rose...
De ce ai făcut asta?!
S-Stăpâne...
Mă bucur că ești bine.
Eu...
Te-ai descurcat bine.
Acum, lasă restul în seama mea.
R-Rose...
Lumachina, continuă-ți rugăciunea.
B-Bine!
Săgeata Fulger!
Toți cei care-mi stau în cale vor fi eliminați!
Zidul Vulcanic!
E inutil!
Ei bine, Lordule Demon, înțelegi acum puterea lui Dumnezeu?!
Acum, dispari împreună cu acest sanctuar antic!
Îmi voi construi aici castelul!
Un castel demn de un nou Dumnezeu!
Oare chiar nu vom reuși?
Diablo.
Totul e pregătit.
Lumachina, eliberează vraja!
Bine!
O God...
O sacred purification!
Cât de naivi!
I've invested far more years into this!
Nu voi pierde în fața unei fetițe!
P-Puterea lui Dumnezeu este...
The light's being pushed back?
Mori, Lumachina!
Asta e de rău! Foarte rău!
Fugim? Vrei să fugim din nou?
Hei, rugăciunile tuturor...
Privește, sunt atât de multe!
Ce?
Eu nu văd nimic...
You do seem like the type who
wouldn't believe in God, Horn-chan.
Ce? Ce?!
Incredibil. Sunt atât de multe.
Cu atât de multe rugăciuni,
Dumnezeu nu are de ales decât să le audă.
It kind of feels warm...
That's elven royalty for you!
She's looking good!
C-Ce e această lumină?!
Asta e lumina rugăciunilor celor credincioși.
E puterea credinței.
Imposibil!
Rugăciunile credincioșilor
sunt complet inutile!
Greșești.
Dumnezeu ascultă rugăciunile tuturor oamenilor.
O God, grant us your purifying light!
Imposibil!
Diablo...
La naiba cu voi!
Bună treabă, Lumachina!
Vishos!
Protecția ta tocmai a dispărut!
Shining Lance in my right hand,
and Darkness Lance in my left hand.
Mai mult... Mai mult!
Te voi străpunge cu toată puterea mea magică!
Even with its enchantments gone,
the God of Destruction, Europa,
won't lose to a mere Elemental Sorcerer!
You don't know, do you?
Once it's lost its enchantments,
Europa is the weakest of all raid bosses.
Raid?
Light and Dark Composite Magic:
Annihilation Sphere!
Dispari din această lume!
T-Tu ești...
Vai, vai, nu ne-am văzut de mult.
Tu ai făcut asta?
Did you, a Paladin, betray the Cardinal?
Oh, nu.
Nu mai sunt un paladin...
Din nefericire.
You mean this is what your
new employer desired?
Silencing people?
Ești deșteaptă, dar, în același timp, proastă.
Vrei să mori?
Well, whatever.
Îți sunt dator, sau, mai exact, lui Lumachina.
Ce e asta?
Ai auzit vreodată numele Tria?
Diablo...
Please grant us God's judgment.
Oh, right. I was talking about
passing God's judgment on them.
I'll have to talk my way out of this!
Looks like you've all come to your senses!
This time, you didn't lose sight of the
God you should truly be praying to!
Now, remember that feeling swirling
in your hearts right now!
That is true faith!
How was that?
Too big a stretch?
Yes, I can feel God's love
so much, I'm shuddering.
Oh, God!
Thank you so much!
Our faith will never waver!
Lumachina!
They bought it!
Remember, should you make
the same mistake again,
I will burn you to ash with crimson hellfire.
Da, Diablo.
Oh, fir-ar...
Am rămas fără mana.
Voi pica.
Voi pica...
Deci domnul era Dumnezeu?
Nu prea cred.
Oh, a picat.
Lumachina!
Deci ești bine!
Tria!
Îți mulțumesc pentru noaptea trecută, Diablo.
Știu că nu e mult, dar voiam măcar să-ți mulțumesc.
T-Toate astea?!
Please use it for your traveling expenses.
Bine.
Cum este Rose?
Nu ai de ce să-ți faci griji.
Doarme în acest moment.
Oh, asta e bine.
Dar ești sigură că ar trebui să rămâi aici?
Da.
Biserica trebuie să-și redobândească încrederea pierdută.
Iar cardinalii și paladinii trebuie să-și ispășească păcatele săvârșite.
She's having them atone for their
wrongdoings within the church?
Pare mult de muncă.
Încă îmi continui investigațiile.
Vishos and the others must have
had vast financial backing
to misappropriate the church as they did.
Mai e și problema acelui monstru respingător.
De unde au făcut rost de el?
Și eu sunt curioasă în legătură cu asta.
Potrivit lui Rem,
Gewalt i-a redus la tăcere pe oamenii lui Vishos.
Ceea ce înseamnă că...
organizația care l-a angajat...
Sunt surprinsă.
I expected you to be less
sharp about that stuff.
Oh, I'm still not very good at it.
Dar trebuie să-mi deschid mintea.
Ai devenit mai puternică, Lumachina.
Plenty of hardships await the church.
I need faithful...
No, I need people I can rely on.
Diablo,
could I possibly ask you
to remain with the church?
As Head Paladin?
Huh?
You want Diablo?
Mister?
As a Paladin?
What do you say, Diablo-sama?
I'm sure Tria and the other
Paladins would accept it.
Please lend us your might.
Not good.
A Demon Lord can't be a Paladin.
More importantly, I suck at group activities!
Ahem!
Lumachina, I'm not the one you need now.
You're right.
Your power is far too great.
If I relied on you, I would
be the same as Vishos,
using force to make our believers follow me.
That's what your trying to say, isn't it?
Indeed.
No, it's because I can't always talk in front
of huge crowds like I did yesterday!
Thank you so much.
I'll work hard.
G-Good.
Lumachina, do you believe in me?
Of course.
Then what if I told you that I'm not God?
If you said so, then it must be true.
But belief isn't aimed
toward titles or positions.
The feelings that I hold
toward you now are...
That's what they should be called.
I see.
Nothing beats a bath after clearing a quest.
This would be even better if
I got a level up or an item drop.
Diablo?
Hmm? Shera?
I knew you'd be in the bath.
Hey, Shera!
What's the matter?
Oh, sorry.
We were, um... worried that you disappeared.
The baths in this inn are great.
You all should take one, too.
Huh? You don't mind?
A-Are you sure?
No need to hold back.
B-But...
Yay!
If you ask the maids, they'll bring
hot water to your rooms, too.
Come on, Rem!
O-Okay.
Bath, bath!
A bath with Diablo!
Th-This is embarrassing.
This feels great, Diablo!
Th-There's something hard
pressing against me.
Oh, sorry.
That might be my foot.
No, I think it's me.
Diablo...
I'm sorry, but could you please
move a little further away?
Rem, don't push!
You'll knock him against them.
You're pushing, too.
And, um, he's pressing against mine.
Diablo...
won't mind if we press against
him a little bit, you know.
Are you sure?
Diablo, it's not a bother, is it?
Other worlds rule!
Rem, I thought you didn't
handle carriages well.
Well, I figured it out.
If I'm holding the reins, I can handle it.
You mean it?
Your arm will be restored to normal?
I'm equipped with self-repair functions.
As long as you allow me to stay by your side...
I see!
I'll allow it, of course!
You can accompany me forever.
Your words are more than I deserve!
I'll engrave them into my memory device
and play them back on an infinite loop!
Uh, please, not an infinite loop...
Still, a lot of things happened, huh?
Even though the quest was supposed
to be just escorting Lumachina-chan.
That's true.
Battuta deceived us and put us in danger.
That curry was delicious, wasn't it?
We joined the battle against
the Demon Lord's Army.
The feast we had in celebration
was delicious, wasn't it?
We got captured by believers
and fought Vishos.
The meals at the inn were delicious, weren't they?
Though I think my breasts
might have gotten bigger.
Why does it always go there?!
I could ask you why yours
aren't getting bigger.
Pantherians as a species all
have big breasts, right?
You're going there, you fatty elf?!
Hey! It's not fat!
By the way, Master,
are you sure it was right to let
the servant you just obtained go?
Yeah. It's how it has to be.
M-Mister, I want to stay in the royal
capital and attend school to learn magic!
I want to become a Sorcerer like you!
Maybe I can never be that great, but still...
Do as you please.
Th-Thank you so much!
I'm a little surprised.
Horn-sama is currently a high-level Thief.
Her learning magic from scratch
would be inefficient,
so I thought you'd be against it.
Of course it's inefficient,
but that struggle is what she desires,
so she should struggle for it.
M-Mister! You're so generous!
Yeah! Diablo's so open-minded!
That's one thing I always hated...
Discouraging those who wanted
to take a roundabout path.
Look! It's Faltra City!
În sfârșit, ne-am întors acasă!
Wow! It's a special, extravagant lunch!
It's a nice change of pace, isn't it?
The mortal races' food...
Expensive, expensive...
Can't afford to pay...
I'm footing the bill today. Okay?
Oh! Onee-sama!
In that case,
bring out all the biscuits!
Look, Emile!
Here and here.
The income and expenses aren't right.
How could I do this?!
This is all to defend all women!
I, Emile Bichelberger,
will change the Guild's finances!
Good grief.
Quit slacking off and work harder!
You three, too!
Oh? So he pulled it off?
As expected of Diablo.
So where is he now?
Right!
We've received word that he's
already returned to Faltra.
To this city, you say?
Perhaps I'll visit him
with some liquor tonight.
I just hope he doesn't run
away like he did that night.
Ta-da!
Well?! Does it look good?!
Yes, it's lovely, Horn-san.
Now, I'll tenderly teach you the
proper elegance and refinement
worthy of a duke's recommendation.
Huh?!
The repairs are coming along steadily
thanks to the cooperation of
our faithful, Lumachina-sama.
I'm grateful to hear that.
I'm sure God is delighted, as well.
I wonder if you've arrived yet, Diablo-sama.
Welco—
Welcome back!
Huh? What did you say?
I said I got this ring from you, Diablo!
I gave you that ring?
I'm telling you, it's true!
In the dungeon's treasure vault!
That item's name, without
a doubt, is "Marriage Ring."
Diablo!
Let's share eternal happiness together!
U-Um...
I believe you should be
fair about such things.
Favoritism isn't good.
Huh?!
Do you not have one for me?
Nope!
But I can't say that!
I obtained that one through a quest, so...
No problem!
I already asked Sylvie about
a quest to get a ring!
So you're not trying to monopolize him?
I like it better with both
you and Diablo together!
Right?
Indeed. I was just hoping to
conduct some magic experiments.
Haideți să acceptăm această misiune!
Da!
Să mergem!
Dacă asta e dorința ta, stăpâne.
Urmați-mă, fetelor!
Bine!