Suzuki?
National Newcomer Audition 2019 in Kamifurano
Let's aim for Budoukan!
Performance Postponed
Notice of Performance Postponement
To slow down the spread of the new virus...
I'll wait for it to resume - It's over
Congrats for the suspension
Suzuki!
How did you come here?
How didja come 'ere?!
Huh? Who's that?!
You're the granddaughter of that grandma, huh?
That gramma's grandkid, huh?
(He's mine now)
This lad's mine now.
I've granted his wish
It ain't me if I hadn't granted his wish.
The aquarium, the giant Chinese banyan, the flow of time...
The aquarium, the giant Chinese banyan...
Is this what Gramma was talkin' about?!
Hey, Suzuki!
Just a bit more
A lil bit more.
You wished for a world without suffering, right?
You were wishin' for a world with no sufferin', ain't you?
What's she talkin' about? Mr. Super Weird!
Hey! Hey!
You're in trouble!
Hey, be quiet!
You shut yo' mouth!
I won't shut up! Serves you right! Go away!
Suzuki... I don't really know you,
so I don't understand anything, but...
Ichirou Suzuki,
you're really super weird!